kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
At the hellish Tea Party,
Big Mom finally started shrieking.
Big Mom finally shrieked.
After failing to assassinate Big Mom,
Luffy and the others were cornered.
Luffy and the others executed a mission
in which they planned to make Big Mom shriek.
During that confusion,
Sanji saved the members of the Vinsmoke Family
To take down Big Mom, Luffy and the others allied with Bege
and broke the portrait of Mother Carmel,
But then,
And her past has been revealed.
Bege transformed himself into a huge castle.
Their plan was...
and Bege fired the deadly poison KX Launcher
at Big Mom. However...
Oh, cool!
successfully making Big Mom shriek.
Semla!!
...to break her most-treasured portrait of
Mother Carmel, the mysterious nun,
Meanwhile, as the Big Mom Pirates
came attacking,
How dare you...
And memories of the past came back to Big Mom.
and show it to her.
Linlin!
Germa 66 fought back
using their scientific technology.
Linlin destroyed the village of Elbaph!!
We should retreat too-rero!
The mission failed!
Charlotte Linlin, also known as Big Mom,
has been...
Mother Carmel saved Linlin who was on a rampage...
At last, Big Mom has started shrieking.
And the whole team took shelter in the castle.
...feared for her brute strength since she was a child
and was abandoned in Elbaph, country of the Giants.
Please forgive her!
However, their attacks were blocked
and on top of that, the castle is stuck.
But Carmel had a different, secret side.
Oh, no! We're on the rooftop!
We have nowhere else to go!
There, she met Mother Carmel,
a nun who was admired by everyone,
"Mom's Secret!
The Giant's Island Elbaph and a Little Monster!"
I've been trafficking kids for 50 years.
and lived happily with other orphans...
We have no chance of winning, either!!
She's the greatest product we've ever had!
"Cutting the Father-Son Relationship!
Sanji and Judge!"
Semla!!
And on Linlin's birthday, it happened.
What a voice!
"The Evil Army!
Transform! Germa 66!"
How dare you...
Happy Birthday, Linlin!
Linlin!
Mother...
Bring me Semla...
Please listen to me, Mother...
Full-Scale Rook!
Carmel... I'm sorry...
No one listens to what I say.
She may look like a child...
Thank you, everyone!
We piled up your favorite sweet, Semla,
and made this Croquembouche!
Don't do it! Jorul-sama!
We'll start killing anyone who steps out...
But she's a god of Disaster!
Hey, Mother... Where did you go?
I hope it's good!
Just come out already!
Eat as much as you want!
Big Mom's tears...
Uh-huh! Thank you!
How could you have been
used by them so much...
"The Birth of Mom!
The Day That Carmel Vanished!"
What's behind them goes back 63 years ago
to Elbaph in the New World.
I-I'm a victim, Big Brother!
It's so delicious!
Just kick all of their asses already!
What?
That is where the world-famous Giants,
the Warriors of Elbaph, lived.
Linlin! Let me give you a coup de grace
with my own hands!
Everyone?
Mother?
Poison?
That woman is troublesome...
Where did you go?
Semla...
Hmm? Huh?
"The Launcher Blasts!
The Moment of Big Mom's Assassination!"
What?!
Now, come on.
There you are!
You're something, Bege!
You turned into such a big castle!
No, Linlin!
CHARLOTTE LINLIN
(A HUMAN, FIVE YEARS OLD)
The Castle-Castle Fruit is cool!
What's the name of this place?
This is no time for that!
Think about the situation we're in!
I'll tell you about it later.
Come on down now, Linlin.
Dammit...
The assassination plot that we worked on for over a year
ended in failure!
Se...
Uh-huh!
Jorul!
Hup!
...m...
...la!
This is the first time we've failed to kill someone.
Hey, hey.
Where am I?
Are you going to go somewhere?
In the end, the Emperor of the Sea proved
out of our league...
Now, what should we do?
Daddy has work to do near here.
We don't have that much time.
I'll tell you why.
Linlin, can you be a good girl
and wait for us?
What?! I'm coming with you...
If you're a good girl, you can eat as
many sweets from the bag as you like.
That's right!
Beardfall-sama!
What?!
Jorul-sama!
The Big Father!
All of them?!
Then, I'll wait, I'll wait!
Mama!
I'll be waiting for you!
63 years ago, Mother Carmel and the other children
went missing.
Oh, cool!
Se... m... la!
Goodbye!
What the hell is that?!
There were two people who witnessed the whole thing
which even Big Mom herself didn't know.
See you again!
Open the gate!
What has she done...
Come back soon!
She stopped crying?
Linlin...
Allies!
Let's take shelter in the castle for now!
Don't cry yet.
But still...
Where did you go?
After having caused that much damage,
we're lucky she's only being deported.
Mama...
All right, hurry up!
One of them was a warrior from Elbaph,
who came down to see if the House of Lambs was okay.
That fool, Bege, has betrayed us.
Yeah, I wanna go in!
She is... more than we can handle...
...she's a good girl.
Firetank Pirates! Cover them!
M-Monster!
--Rero!
--Yes, sir!
Betrayal?
They say the Holy Mother lives here.
She'll save Linlin.
Semla!
He turned pale and started running,
Damn!
Listen carefully, you guys!
and never came back to this island again.
Hold Linlin!
Let's set off! This area is dangerous!
Put out the fire in the village!
This castle is me.
It's strong but not unbreakable.
--Catch her already!
--Okay!
Eventually, all the Giants in Elbaph
and the other places got to know the story
If they destroy the castle, I'll die.
Then the castle will be gone...
Don't rough her up!
Bege! I saw it with my own eyes!
Could you get Semla?
and Charlotte Linlin has been even more hated
by the Giants...
And once you guys get thrown out,
the monsters will prey on you, too!
There's some for the Festival
in the village storehouse!
I can't believe you were
plotting to kill Mama!
See you!
Bring them now!
Is that what he's been
up to from the beginning?
Prey?!
O-Okay!
...to the extent that
no one wants to utter her name.
Wow! Those are big fish.
Get inside the castle-rero!
Rook! Cannon preparation!
Where did you go?! Mother! Everyone!
--Mother, what are you doing?!
--It's dangerous!
And the other witness...
Cannon firing!
Stay back!
I won't forgive them...
...was a cook who used to be a pirate
and was living on the island she was left on, named Streusen.
So cool!
Oh?
It's a robot! A castle robot!
Mama!
How can you be excited at a time like this?!
I can feel her anger...
All gone...
How long can we hold out?
It's all gone.
He was amused by it.
Gebur...
GROWL
I'm hungry...
You're damned if you stay and damned if you leave.
It's snowing!
Mother!
Aren't they back yet?
You're in dire straits!
My eardrums are gonna be busted-nen!
Don't blame it on me, Bege!
That launcher was the world's most advanced...
He had an ability...
...to turn any object into food,
which was the Cook-Cook Fruit power.
GROWL
Mochi?
...tstag!
It's strange.
They've been gone for a long time.
--Wh-What was that?
--Father!
I'm starving...
Hey, Bege! What's the matter?!
Momma, Papa... Where did you go?
Honey, are you okay?!
I've never seen a monster like that.
Why aren't you coming back?
Don't leave me alone...
Could it be...
I no longer hear the shriek-nen!
It's from outside!
Mother!
I'm okay now-nen!
What?
If I let her be alone, she'd die.
That's a waste.
Outside?
I'll give you a voice.
Regarding Elbaph,
a century ago, it was home to Giant warriors
that were feared by the world.
Is that...
What's that?
You bastards!
Where did you go, Mother?
The Tamate Box!
Come out!
They were the Giant Pirates!
The treasure that's been passed down
for generations on the Fish-Man Island!
Hey, what's the matter, little girl?
They raised havoc on the seas everywhere
and burned down countless cities.
Bege!
Straw Hat!
If you just keep crying,
you'll only get hungrier.
That famous Tamate Box!
I'm scared!
Say, little girl,
do you wanna talk about your dreams or something?
However,
She's looking at us!
Move, move, move!
one day, all of a sudden,
the Giant Pirates lost their two captains
Come out!
Who are you, old man?
Let me escape first!
Obey me!
Hey, don't come too close.
and passed into legend.
Hey, old man, have you seen Mother?
Don't you know where everyone's gone?
--There's a face in the fire!
--What?!
Shortly thereafter, several of its stragglers
Bege!
I'm scared...
Straw Hat!
who weren't careful after
the loss of their leaders,
What?!
It's like a demon!
I don't know...
But I bet they'll come back soon.
were caught by the Navy
and were about to be executed.
All right!
I name you "Pandora"!
Big Mom came to her senses!
Kill them!
You think so?
Wh-What the hell is this?
Yeah, I'll stay with you until then.
I'm good at cooking.
If it's just you, I can provide enough food.
I brought them!
Big Mom!
Feed her now!
Semla!
Who's messing with Gastino-sama?!
It's delicious! It's delicious!
Please wait!
I'm hungry...
Halt the execution!
Simmer down!
Heaven is asking for reconciliation!
Count on me!
A beautiful wandering nun appeared!
Honey!
Big Brother!
SISTER CARMEL
Her name was Sister Carmel.
He's gonna kill me!
That damn beast!
Heaven is asking for reconciliation?
What are you talking about?!
All of you, come out of the castle!
All those badasses came together!
Do you know how much terror
they caused...
Show yourselves, you fools!
An even greater reason for penance!
Why can't you see that?
Run! They're definitely gonna kill me!
Honey!
See?
Father!
These two who met at the time
will be the co-founders of the Big Mom Pirates.
So you betrayed me?
Big Brother! Thank you!
Bege!
If you kill them,
Honey! Stay with me!
The fire...
the warriors of Elbaph will form an army
to seek revenge against humans!
Let's go!
...is gone...
Hey, look!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Forgive their sins!
Come out, Bege! Straw Hat!
How cute!
Hi, Mother!
Mother...
Worked a miracle...
They're gonna come attacking!
Shut the gate now!
No, it wasn't me.
Bege!
Linlin!
I'll lead them!
Take Pez!
Come to your senses! They'll shoot you!
No! Nami and the others aren't here yet!
The god of the sun brought everything under control.
So, at the tea party today,
if we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?!
To a world where all races join hands
Come out!
I'm so happy!
Wait!
--Hey! Get up here!
--Hurry up!
Mama! It's me!
Bege's my husband and we have a child!
and share laughter!
Mama would be devastated!
Punish her... Don't think her as a child...
And no one there would be able to move
for more than five seconds!
Guys!
Please forgive him! Let it go!
They eventually called Carmel "Mother"
and opened an orphanage...
I won't let you go!
Chiffon!
If you don't do anything...
she'll bring more disaster in the future...
Then the KX Launcher will show
its real strength...
...called "House of Lambs"
where she took in children
You look exactly like Lola as always...
Cover them-rero! Hurry-rero!
of any race or birth, who had no place to go.
and the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom -
will die!
The attack is coming!
--Jorul-sama!
--Get him treatment now!
Watch out!
Get back, Chiffon!
On Elbaph where the Giants live...
Madame!
Mama! Please!
Beardhill-sama!
At the same time, she worked as a bridge
between the Giants and humans...
I told you not to show your face!
Nami!
You're doomed, Big Mom!
Linlin...
I'll squeeze you to death!
Mama!
Nami-san!
And then, 37 years later...
Nami!
Please forgive her!
We're gonna fight you!
That was close...
Are you okay?
Mother Carmel met Linlin.
Madame!
Were you conspiring with them to kill me, too,
Chiffon?!
Won't you let me do it, Carmel?
You're in good hands now, Linlin.
Achoo-uch.
You're not gonna live to eat
tomorrow's sweets!
Until your mom and dad come back,
let's be friends and live together!
--Ouch, ouch! It's hot!
--You can't get away now!
Jorul is my friend who I fought with for 300 years.
Mama!
Chobro!
They won't come back!
You've been abandoned!
Mother.
When the castle is destroyed and Bege dies,
they'll all be thrown out of there.
Everyone gets in my way.
All children here are very unique.
Geniiie!
He's too old... I don't think he can make it!
So unique that our parents dumped us!
Don't let anyone get away!
Being a warrior isn't about living long...
It's about how you die!
You'll become friends with them
in no time.
The Firetank Pirates. The Straw Hats...
True happiness for people is to be equal.
Uh-huh! Thank you!
Plus, Jimbei! Germa 66!
I'm starving!
We have to bring it to an end...
But to find a country like that in the world today
is nearly impossible.
You're huge! Are you a Giant?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
They messed up the wedding
and the Tea Party!
Anyone who defies Elbaph's laws
can't be forgiven!
Chopper!
Let's eat then!
I can't believe we've been taken so lightly.
There was a prince who got expelled
from his country in the aftermath of a coup...
Carrot!
So let's make this place our country!
I understand!
But even if she can't be forgiven,
Let's hang them up
to set an example for others!
Nami-san!
And a child who was almost enslaved
because of poverty...
since the poor Linlin was abandoned by the whole world
and ended up in the House of Lambs,
A country where everyone will look at things
in the same way!
Come out!
All these troubled children
who couldn't be controlled even by their parents...
Country?!
Yes, a country without racism or
anything of that sort
Bege!
...were living in the village of the Giants
regardless of their birth or race.
Honey!
I can't give her up!
and everyone will look at things
in the same way!
Are you okay?
What'll you do?
In the same way! That's nice!
Hey, Mother!
Damn, that old bag!
Is she new?
I'll leave here along with her!
Everyone should get bigger!
More than anything, to Linlin
who had always been bigger than the others,
Even with a cannon,
the Big Father won't get a scratch,
Wow! How cool!
Carmel!
That's a beautiful dream, Mother!
but its defenses aren't a match for her!
Elbaph was the first place she'd seen
I've got to get out and kick her ass!
where people, houses, and
everything else fit her size,
Beardhill-sama! Please kill Linlin!
No, Luffy!
Chopper, stop him!
Why should we pardon her
after she's done such a horrible thing?!
Linlin!
and she was very comfortable.
Okay!
Linlin!
This is great!
What happened to your Elbaph pride?!
Everyone, let's work hard together!
What the?! Hey! Let go of me!
I'll do it!
Hey, Chopper! Let go of me!
--Me too!
Luffy! Don't get carried away!
Yeah!
Let's make this place a dreamland!
We came to take back Sanji-kun,
didn't we?!
I'll do my best too, Mother!
We got a copy of the Ponegliff
You're a good girl, Linlin.
and achieved Sanji-kun's wish
to save his family!
I am!
If there are a lot of countries like that,
the world will be more peaceful.
We accomplished our goals!
If you have enough time to fight back,
think about how we can escape instead!
Let's go! Germa 66!
Alright then, why don't you get out of my sight now?!
Everyone can become happy.
If we wanted to fight, we would've brought
Zoro and everyone else too, right?
Mother's dream was my dream!
Why?!
Luffy-san, Nami-san is right.
Hajrudin!
Let go of me! Let go!
No! No!
Peace? Is that your dream, Linlin?
We made it this far
because there are only a small number of us.
It's not good to fight!
It is! I'll build a country
that Mother would like!
Let's all go to the Land of Wano safely
where Zoro-san's waiting!
Come on! It's not good to fight!
Mother always says "Be nice to each other"!
What happened to Beardfall-sama?
Bege!
He died.
Father!
Bege!
What? Why did he die?
No!
THE NEXT DAY
Look! Bege is...
Why did it happen? Why did it happen?
I feel sorry for him.
What should we do then?!
Doesn't she remember?
Why don't you stop crying already?
Bege is getting attacked on our account!
Jorul, the hero of the Giants, died...
Oh, no. What's the matter, Linlin?
Hey, hey, hey! I wanna see Mother's magic!
Mother, listen...
Magic?
A god of Disaster named Linlin...
Carmel's miracle...
Yeah, she was good at doing magic tricks.
Good boy, good boy. Don't cry!
A bear and a wolf were
fighting in the forest.
I think she put out her hands like this...
It's not good to fight and I thought
I had to help them become friends
The details of that day...
Dammit...
Our results are catastrophic...
...spread across a small number of
the Giant nations all over the world.
Then...
so I put them in the same cage yesterday.
I'm not willing to sit by
and watch your relish in your success!
But the bear ate the wolf.
Together with the orphans of the House of Lambs
who refused to be separated from their Mother,
Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Wait a minute, Bege-san!
You can't drag us down with you!
So I hit the bear.
What?! The magic trick that Mother used to do!
Why?!
and Charlotte Linlin
who became the enemy of all the Giants,
The bear seems sorry.
How many times did you hit him?
I did what I had to do too!
I could do it too!
Give me back my heart now!
Mother Carmel left Elbaph.
Flower, flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Just once...
Drag you down...
She killed the bear with a single blow?
And they all started a new life
at the new House of Lambs.
That's not a bad idea.
Earth!
--Earth!
--Flower, flower!
I didn't care about you guys at all
from the beginning.
Shoot! Shoot!
It's done! Is this good enough?
More than enough.
I'm sorry for asking these favors.
What the...
Is that a Devil Fruit power?
Oh, I understand!
You just wanted them to become friends!
Without your help,
I couldn't build a house deep in the mountains like this.
--Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
--Tree! Tree!
Linlin, you're so sweet!
Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
But...
Don't mention it. To be honest,
I don't wanna see Linlin's face,
ELECTRIC BLUE
...my precious subordinates...
Uh-huh!
Then, let's go play with everyone else!
Flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
but you're the Holy Mother even for the Giants, Carmel.
You can ask anything of us.
...and my beloved wife and child are here.
Uh-huh!
Wow! I could do it too, Mother!
To Linlin, Carmel was the first person ever
to really understand her.
Thank you!
When she returns,
I'm gonna show it to her!
To relieve the children's growing concerns,
Carmel tried to smile even more.
I saw it! Linlin killed a
bear with a single blow!
I can't let them die!
--Tree!
--Flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Honey!
She's dangerous!
Wait, wait!
Father!
Did you hear Eyri-kun, the Giant,
got injured?
What an amazing power!
She's the real deal.
A few days after leaving Elbaph,
they were the same as they'd always been...
She tried to hit a mosquito on him!
Thank you, Linlin!
Let's sing together
Bege!
She broke several of his bones!
No, Linlin's gonna kill me!
How interesting! Alright, I decided!
I'm gonna set out to sea with her!
Wait, wait!
Ouch! Ouch!
There's only one way...
What are you doing, Linlin?
The House of Lambs was filled with
the children's laughter.
--Nice! Nice!
--A country where...
What?
...for everyone to survive!
Mother! Help!
Look after the house while I'm away.
...everyone grows big
and looks at things in the same way and is equal.
Well, he's got one too many elbow joints
so I thought it'd be nice to tear it apart for him.
Only one?!
I'll clean the bathroom!
What is it?!
I'll do the laundry!
No, he's from the Longarm Tribe!
That's normal for him!
Alright, Linlin. Let's build the dreamland!
What time will you be back?
I'll return as soon as I finish buying groceries.
Oh... I see...
Count me in!
Do you need anything?
Ouch!
Uh-huh!
Shortcake!
Linlin, what are you doing?!
--A set of cards!
--Toy swords for samurai fighting!
He's got fins so I thought it'd help by
tearing them off for him.
You annoying bastards!
Okay.
Stop that. The Fish-Men often have
characteristics of fish!
Come out!
See you, Mother! Take care!
I'm gonna destroy it!
All of you, burn to death!
Oh... I see...
It's not gonna last long...
A legend grew about the House of Lambs.
I was terrified!
Get ready to attack anytime.
Any troubled child will be born again
with Mother's help and meet good foster parents...
I can crush them with this!
Let's get rid of...
Everyone, forgive her!
The appointed time is long past.
...every one of them!
Linlin is a kind girl!
I hope she didn't run away with the kids!
That damn Carmel!
I-Is that...?!
Just come out already!
Then, I'll keep you all in the mirror dimension!
You're right on time...
If she did such a thing,
she'll be in trouble with Cipher Pol.
Carmel pardoned everything.
Of course. Have I ever stood you up?
The only way to survive... That is...
Wait, wait!
Stop, you guys!
Let's get to business.
What's wrong?
This room in the Big Father...
is actually inside of my body...
I just heard a voice from somewhere...
Linlin will kill me!
Wait, wait! Wait, wait!
What?
KASHII
10 months later in Elbaph, the
New World's strongest country,
There is a good girl.
Hey!
Don't panic!
tough ones had accepted
Linlin open-heartedly.
OIMO
I see nobody.
But I'm sure I heard...
Wait, wait.
No matter how strongly we're attacked...
--Flower, flower!
--What?
It's almost been 40 years...
Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
Whether the Big Father leans or falls over...
Flower, flower!
Have you ever seen a duel last that long?
What... What is that?
Flower, flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
I'm the only one who'll get hurt.
No, never! Let's go and pick them up
after another decade or so.
I didn't expect you to leave Elbaph...
As long as you guys stay here,
you're not gonna get affected!
Flower, flower! Flower, flower! Flower, flower!
These Giants - Kashii and Oimo -
are talking about...
That's how much I didn't wanna let go of her.
--Come to think of it...
--It's only Bege-san who is suffering.
What?!
The flowers are singing?!
Dorry the Blue Ogre.
Tree, tree, tree!
And...
We can hear Big Mom's voice...
Let's play, let's play!
Brogy the Red Ogre.
They met Luffy and the others
and bonded tightly.
But it remains calm inside.
Let's play!
Let's play, let's play!
Think about it. She's only five now but she's already so
exceptional that she could destroy half of the Elbaph village.
We will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!
That's right...
And it won't change
even if I turn back to my human form.
Have faith in us, and
continue straight ahead!
Wh-What's going on with this forest?!
But the price is...
Hakoku Sovereignty!
I know it's not too high.
Let's play, let's play!
So you mean,
we'll be safe as long as we stay here...
In the Navy,
she'd become a vice admiral or a fleet admiral.
Stay away!
Listen... I'll change back to my human form
keeping you guys inside.
Now go!
In Cipher Pol,
she'd be the toughest shield for the Celestial Dragons.
Oimo and Kashii went out to pick up
Dorry and Brogy as they said.
Then, Caesar will carry me and fly away
to escape.
Germa 66! They're the best-rero!
I've been trafficking kids for 50 years.
If it goes well, we can get out of trouble.
The Germa that I saw on the comic strip!
Stop!
But they got caught and fooled
by the Navy on their way
She's the greatest product we've ever had!
The real ones are here now!
How could you do that?!
Hey! How could you put my life in danger
without even asking me, you fool!
and were forced to guard the gate at Enies Lobby
for half a century.
37 years ago, I put on a good show with the Navy
and snuck into Elbaph.
What?
Y-Y-You're Charlotte Linlin, aren't you?
Germa's scientific technology.
That's like digging our own grave!
Then, it was none other than Sniper King
who taught them the truth and freed them.
Those are the shape-memory armors!
They're even resistant to fire!
John Giant became
the Navy's first Giant soldier
We'll get riddled with bullets in an instant!
There's no chance of success!
We're here to pick you up.
Pick me up?
I'll bind them with my candy again!
There are many users of the Color of Arms too!
because of my connections!
That's right. Now, come over here.
After learning the truth,
Kashii and Oimo became allies of Luffy and the others
I can turn into gas but it doesn't matter!
I've been fooling the kids
at the House of Lambs
--No!
--What?
Candy Wave!
You don't know if there's any chance of success!
and created havoc in Enies Lobby.
You're all bad people!
You can't tell unless you try.
and selling fresh orphans once every two years
to the Government.
Wh-What... What?!
You're only agile when you're escaping!
What did you say, you fools?!
They're perfect for intelligence agents, right?
Let me ask you a question.
Hey, Linlin! Did you guys finish preparing?
Orphans can't be traced.
It hurts! So sad! It really hurts!
All right! All right!
I'll try to come up with the money.
Sanji...
Kneel before Germa's scientific might!
Kashii, preparing for what?
See? The flowers say, "It hurts"!
Of course, you will!
Why did you save us?
Oh, Linlin-chan, I guess
it's your first time.
It takes a lot of work to act as the Holy Mother!
Say sorry!
We're hateful enemies to you
and we totally fell into the trap!
Be careful!
Don't think she's just a kid!
MOTHER CARMEL - AN ORPHAN SELLER
(UNDERWORLD NAME: MOUNTAIN HAG)
In Elbaph, we undergo fasting for 12 days
before the Winter Solstice Festival!
I was thinking to take this occasion to retire from the job...
Fasting?
So this'll be my last deal. I need you to pay me in full!
We won't eat anything.
You're only allowed to drink water.
Because my father would be sad...
For 12 days starting tomorrow.
What?!
You obnoxious fleas!
If I had stuck to my resentment
from my old days...
Eventually, the two took to sea
and showed what they were capable of,
What do you all wanna sing today?
I'm gonna be hungry!
But if you can endure it,
we'll have a festival!
"Binks's Brew"!
and became infamous.
What? That's a pirates' song.
Please let me out!
Hey, look at this wanted poster!
Dad! I'm sorry!
That's right!
We'll become pirates some day!
Fight against yourself, Hajrudin!
A 50 million berry bounty for a kid?!
Oh, that's very cool!
I'm sorry to be born weak!
How is that possible?
Stand up, Hajrudin!
Help me, Dad!
You've got a huge body
but you're not so formidable.
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Help me! Dad!
A castle fell at the hands of a girl?!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
The mastermind is Charlotte Linlin!
This Giant boy, Hajrudin...
HAJRUDIN
O'er across the ocean's tide, the sunset is goin' wild
He'd be disappointed in me
for becoming such a small-minded rat...
Cipher Pol reported that she's a security risk!
She'll become a powerful villain one day!
...will eventually meet Luffy in Dressrosa
and be impressed by his determination.
See the sky! Birds singing in circles passing by!
...who'd laugh at your blood family's death.
Catch her at any cost!
But I'll sell you brats to the Government
rather than pirates!
Yeah!
Along with Bartolomeo and the others,
Don't catch cold.
he exchanged cups of sake as
parent and son with Luffy.
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
Tarte tropezienne!
Kouglof au chocolat!
Sing a song, it won't be long before we're casting off!
I don't wanna live a life in which I'm too ashamed...
He is now a member of the Straw Hat Fleet.
Madeleine! Brioche!
...to face him!
Cross the gold and silver waves, changin' into water sprays!
And the colorful tower of macarons!
So delicious!
The tough boy!
Sailing out on our journey to the ends of the sea!
Dorry or Brogy, either
of the chiefs will return
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
There she is!
and the Giant Pirates
will roam again for sure!
Watch out, Linlin.
If I hand over the rest of the kids along with Linlin
to the Navy tomorrow, it's all over.
...in front of other people!
You're a warrior!
Don't stop training yourself, Hajrudin!
I'm eating sweets!
Yeah!
Before that,
I'll celebrate your special day so much, Linlin...
I like the spirit! Rydin!
Don't interrupt!
It's a shame that I don't want anyone to know!
Nami-san!
Uh-huh!
Are you guys okay?!
You realize that, don't you?
--Come, this way!
--Huh? What is it?
I am!
Sanji-kun!
I'm glad that you're okay, Nami-san!
Sit down, Linlin!
13 years ago,
Okay! But what is this?
Chief Beardfall-sama! Chief Beardhill-sama!
CHIEF BEARDHILL JARUL (345 YEARS OLD)
CHIEF BEARDFALL JORUL (344 YEARS OLD)
Vinsmoke Sanji who escaped from Germa
died once at sea...
Gum-Gum...
Carmel preaches "trade rather than
robbery" and that's good too.
One, two, three!
...Jet Whip!
Happy Birthday, Linlin!
And that's what you wished for.
Luffy!
But we shall not forget that we are warriors!
--Hurry up!
--This way!
Charlotte Linlin continued wreaking havoc
Yes!
and became a threat to the world overnight.
Jarul-sama and Jorul-sama are so cool!
We should retreat too-rero!
Thank you, everyone!
FORMER CO-CAPTAINS OF THE GIANT PIRATES
(TWO OF THE WORLD'S OLDEST WARRIORS)
HEROES OF THE GIANTS
No wonder all Giants
respect them as warriors!
We piled up your favorite sweet, Semla,
and made this Croquembouche!
She's a pirate!
I wanna be like them some day!
So admit this!
Run!
I hope it's good!
You're not my father, Vinsmoke Judge!
It's called Croquembouche? Looks delicious!
What brought both of you here today?
We'll eat Semla in the village so we came here
to pick up the children at the House of Lambs.
Don't ever show yourself in front of us again!
Let's have a tea party!
We're just in time, Linlin.
A tea party?
Nice, Linlin.
Well, well, the legendary hidden treasure,
the Tamate Box!
We'll spend time gracefully sitting around tables,
drinking tea and eating sweets!
Why don't you become
the king of the sea like this?
What's Semla?
It's a very delicious sweet!
I came far enough that they won't find me!
I like how it's chaotic-nen!
That'll be more fun!
What?! A sweet?
That sounds great!
I wanna have that! A tea party!
Before the fast, we'll get a lot of nutrition
by eating Semla!
Bring me sweets!
Let's take this opportunity to
replace what's inside...
--Let's make tea.
--Join us, Mother!
Your Majesty!
Are we gonna eat it now? The sweet?!
Oh, no!
Okay, okay.
If you do, I'll guarantee you a peaceful dreamland!
Thank you!
Sweet cream dolloped in
sweet bread with marzipan,
Yay!
Alright, let's start!
If you all just listen to me,
I know you'll be happy!
topped with a dusting of sugar!
--Eat as much as you want!
--Eat, eat!
It's the fun before the fast!
Very well.
Uh-huh! Thank you!
Those who don't listen are selfish
so I've got to kill them!
I promise...
Sounds delicious!
...I won't approach you...
It's so delicious!
...or the East Blue!
Mother, I miss you...
She eats so fast!
I miss you!
All right, everyone!
The tea party's fun!
The recent birth of Prince
Loki at the castle!
Mother!
I'm so happy! It's so delicious!
And Rodo and Goldberg who
were born in the village!
I'll make everyone big one day!
I already did my part!
One day, Mother Carmel vanished.
Then, let's sit around the table together again!
Doing more isn't part of our deal!
Thank the Sun for our children's growth!
That was the day Linlin had the happiest birthday
ever in her life.
But there are still people
who don't listen to me!
Thank the Sun!
Thank you for the food!
She's still vulnerable!
We can still kill her!
Come out!
Yeah! Semla!
We have a lot so eat as much as you want!
Bege! Straw Hat!
I'm so sad and I can't stop crying!
This is our last chance!
This is...
This is... Semla...
The special friends at the House of Lambs,
who had similar backgrounds.
Come out!
Linlin, eat, eat!
Because the one-and-only portrait of Mother...
Cannon firing!
--Honey!
--Father!
Uh-huh!
The open-minded and generous Mother
that she loved.
I don't wanna be here anymore!
You're a good girl.
S... S...
Being surrounded by everyone's smiles
and eating her favorite sweet, sweet birthday cake,
So sweet!
Damn!
If nothing is done, you'll die too, Caesar!
Candy Wall!
It's delicious!
The one-and-only portrait of Mother
that was precious to me...
Linlin couldn't hold back her tears.
Perospero!
I'm happy!
Oh, that hurts...
...got broken by them!
Eat as much as you like, Linlin.
Open the gate!
Germa's on your side too?
I'll eat... I'll eat it all!
Gang Bege!
Until you and Caesar Clown fly away into the sky,
Delicious! Delicious! Sweet! Sweet!
Delicious! Delicious!
What a lovely day...
Tears blurred her eyes.
Get ready for this, you rats!
I won't forgive...
Delicious! Delicious!
we Germa will escort you!
You won't be laughing for long!
I won't forgive...
W-Wait a minute!
Why do you decide what I'm gonna do?!
Your high-handed attitude hasn't changed, Judge!
The Straw Hats!
Whoa-whoa, don't rush, Linlin!
We made it for you!
--Delicious! Delicious!
--Whoa-whoa! Hey, Linlin!
It's all yours!
Don't eat so fast!
There won't be enough to go around!
Thank you!
Rook! Movement!
Oh, yeah... You Germa people can fly too...
Don't forget to thank the Sun!
I won't forgive them!!
Eat more!
Then, we'll leave you behind, okay?
Semla!!
Let's stay friends!
No problem.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Alright, if we need to buy time, I'll...
Let's stay together and have fun!
It's delicious! It's so delicious! Semla!
Yeah! We'll stay together forever!
--That's okay, Luffy.
--But...
I'll shoot her in the back
until we run out of bullets!
FASTING - DAY 3
Mother... I'm starved to death...
Go to hell, Big Mom!
The Winter Solstice Festival celebrates
the death and the resurrection of the Sun.
Cannon...
Fighting through the severe winter,
the Sun will shine down on us again.
...firing!
You're a good girl, Linlin...
What happened?!
Mother!
FASTING - DAY 4
Father, the cannons on the left
have been destroyed!
The more you suffer,
the more you appreciate the Sun.
The mission failed!
I don't wanna be indebted to this "failure"!
We are family.
All the cannons in the castle are
stuffed with mochi,
So... let's keep going!
and we can't fire them!
That's how they wanna settle it...
What?!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
If Mother says so, I'll... keep trying...
Wait, wait! Whoa-whoa!
It's so delicious!
K-Katakuri!
They failed!
I didn't say I was gonna do this, you fools!
Listen, since I can fly,
I'll plunge into the site with a mirror to escape!
In that case,
the Big Father will run her over to a pulp!
What a lovely birthday.
Caesar!
FASTING - DAY 5
Shut up and do it!
Lick!
Ouch!
Oh, I'm so happy!
I was carried away so I even bit the table!
I'm losing weight...
You haven't changed.
Once you finish,
dive into Caesar's mirror quickly!
You'll regret this!
Yeah? That's strange...
Linlin!
Thank you, everyone!
I'll never forget about today...
Unfortunately, it's time to do my job!
Dammit!
Come on out already!
You're doing great! A little more to go!
Bege!
I can't believe the launchers that I made were destroyed!
That monster old bag! After all, she's the Emperor of the Sea!
Uh-huh!
Straw Hat!
Linlin started liking Mother so much.
What?
FASTING - DAY 6
Are you ready?
How did it go?!
Everyone?
Caesar Clown...
Semla was so delicious...
Mother?
I wasn't ready at all from the beginning!
You guys should protect me!
One day, Mother Carmel...
Where did you go?
I...
Alright! Let's go crazy!
...disappeared all of a sudden.
Retreat, everyone!
Dive into the mirror!
...wanna eat it... again...
I have an announcement for
everyone in the castle!
You have the wrong idea.
Hmm? Huh?
Our mission is to let Caesar and Bege escape
quickly and safely.
Where are you?! Everyone! In the house?
FASTING - DAY 7
This is a battle for evacuation.
Defense is harder than offense.
The assassination of Big Mom...
I know.
Oh, no!
I understand the mission.
Mother, help!
Hey!
What's the matter, Gerd?!
...ended in failure.
What unbelievable wind pressure!
Everyone!
Linlin-chan is...!
Linlin!
This is...
Oh, there you are!
The Big Father's limbs are bound with candy.
Get ready to step out!
Semla!!
Getting ready to step out!
What?
We're ready!
We can't even move now!
How dare you...
Linlin!
Bege!
Bring me Semla...
We'll be surrounded by the
"Emperor of the Sea" Big Mom Pirates
Don't leave me alone...
All right!
Semla!
and forced to fight a hopeless battle
under siege.
Where are you, everyone?
Linlin destroyed the village of Elbaph!!
I'm gonna deactivate the castle!
No...
It's a nightmare!
She finally did it! Linlin!
She has no right to thank the Sun!
Hey, Mother...
Even if she's a child,
we can't forgive everything!
Why did you disappear all of a sudden?
Jorul-sama!
Semla... Semla...
Let's go!
Carmel... I'm sorry...
Oh, no! We're on the rooftop!
We have nowhere else to go!
She may look like a child...
Don't do it! Jorul-sama!
We have no chance of winning, either!!
But she's a god of Disaster!
Motha! Where're ya?!
What is she saying?!
Where did you go?!
Germa! Start attacking!
Semla...
Mother!
Luffy and Germa 66 join forces
and a deadly escape plan begins!
Big Mom finally comes to her senses!
A huge event occurs that will change the fate of
the innocent monster Charlotte Linlin!
The moment to assassinate
the Emperor of the Sea finally comes!
Luffy and the others get caught by
the formidable Big Mom Pirates.
Like a raging beast, she attacks the Big
Father to bring down Luffy and the others!
The enraged Big Mom's shriek rings out,
and when Bege's deadly poison gas weapon fires,
That's when those five finally
unite their strength and stand up!
Her long standing feud with the Giants and a
Big Mom's furious attacks raise Luffy's fighting spirit!
Meanwhile, Sanji and his father, Judge, face each other.
What words will they exchange?
stunning secret of the miracle-making
Holy Mother Carmel,
Germa 66, the group of modified humans that terrorized the world,
shows their true power!
To prove himself as the future King of the Pirates,
his special Gear Four techniques blast!
Luffy's allied force's mission finally comes to a climax!
and even the origin of the hellish Tea Party...
All of those mysteries are now revealed!
The long-standing conflict between
father and son comes to an end!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Launcher Blasts! The Moment of Big Mom's Assassination!"
"Escape From the Tea Party! Luffy vs. Big Mom!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Evil Army! Transform! Germa 66!"
"The Birth of Mom! The Day That Carmel Vanished!"
"Cutting the Father-Son
Relationship! Sanji and Judge!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!