kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
Luffy and the others executed a mission
in which they planned to make Big Mom shriek.
Their plan was...
...to break her most-treasured portrait of
Mother Carmel, the mysterious nun,
and show it to her.
At last, Big Mom has started shrieking.
"Mom's Secret!
The Giant's Island Elbaph and a Little Monster!"
What a voice!
Mother...
Please listen to me, Mother...
No one listens to what I say.
Hey, Mother... Where did you go?
Big Mom's tears...
What's behind them goes back 63 years ago
to Elbaph in the New World.
That is where the world-famous Giants,
the Warriors of Elbaph, lived.
Now, come on.
CHARLOTTE LINLIN
(A HUMAN, FIVE YEARS OLD)
What's the name of this place?
I'll tell you about it later.
Come on down now, Linlin.
Uh-huh!
Hup!
Hey, hey.
Where am I?
Are you going to go somewhere?
Daddy has work to do near here.
Linlin, can you be a good girl
and wait for us?
What?! I'm coming with you...
If you're a good girl, you can eat as
many sweets from the bag as you like.
That's right!
What?!
All of them?!
Then, I'll wait, I'll wait!
I'll be waiting for you!
Goodbye!
See you again!
Come back soon!
Linlin...
Don't cry yet.
After having caused that much damage,
we're lucky she's only being deported.
She is... more than we can handle...
They say the Holy Mother lives here.
She'll save Linlin.
Let's set off! This area is dangerous!
See you!
Wow! Those are big fish.
Oh?
All gone...
It's all gone.
GROWL
I'm hungry...
It's snowing!
Aren't they back yet?
GROWL
It's strange.
They've been gone for a long time.
I'm starving...
Momma, Papa... Where did you go?
Why aren't you coming back?
Regarding Elbaph,
a century ago, it was home to Giant warriors
that were feared by the world.
They were the Giant Pirates!
They raised havoc on the seas everywhere
and burned down countless cities.
However,
one day, all of a sudden,
the Giant Pirates lost their two captains
and passed into legend.
Shortly thereafter, several of its stragglers
who weren't careful after
the loss of their leaders,
were caught by the Navy
and were about to be executed.
Kill them!
Please wait!
Halt the execution!
Heaven is asking for reconciliation!
A beautiful wandering nun appeared!
SISTER CARMEL
Her name was Sister Carmel.
Heaven is asking for reconciliation?
What are you talking about?!
Do you know how much terror
they caused...
An even greater reason for penance!
Why can't you see that?
If you kill them,
the warriors of Elbaph will form an army
to seek revenge against humans!
Forgive their sins!
I'll lead them!
To a world where all races join hands
and share laughter!
They eventually called Carmel "Mother"
and opened an orphanage...
...called "House of Lambs"
where she took in children
of any race or birth, who had no place to go.
On Elbaph where the Giants live...
At the same time, she worked as a bridge
between the Giants and humans...
And then, 37 years later...
Mother Carmel met Linlin.
You're in good hands now, Linlin.
Until your mom and dad come back,
let's be friends and live together!
They won't come back!
You've been abandoned!
All children here are very unique.
So unique that our parents dumped us!
You'll become friends with them
in no time.
Uh-huh! Thank you!
I'm starving!
You're huge! Are you a Giant?
Let's eat then!
There was a prince who got expelled
from his country in the aftermath of a coup...
And a child who was almost enslaved
because of poverty...
All these troubled children
who couldn't be controlled even by their parents...
...were living in the village of the Giants
regardless of their birth or race.
Hey, Mother!
Is she new?
More than anything, to Linlin
who had always been bigger than the others,
Elbaph was the first place she'd seen
where people, houses, and
everything else fit her size,
and she was very comfortable.
This is great!
No! No!
It's not good to fight!
Come on! It's not good to fight!
Mother always says "Be nice to each other"!
No!
THE NEXT DAY
Why did it happen? Why did it happen?
Oh, no. What's the matter, Linlin?
Mother, listen...
A bear and a wolf were
fighting in the forest.
It's not good to fight and I thought
I had to help them become friends
so I put them in the same cage yesterday.
But the bear ate the wolf.
So I hit the bear.
The bear seems sorry.
How many times did you hit him?
Just once...
She killed the bear with a single blow?
Oh, I understand!
You just wanted them to become friends!
Linlin, you're so sweet!
Uh-huh!
Then, let's go play with everyone else!
To Linlin, Carmel was the first person ever
to really understand her.
I saw it! Linlin killed a
bear with a single blow!
She's dangerous!
Did you hear Eyri-kun, the Giant,
got injured?
She tried to hit a mosquito on him!
She broke several of his bones!
Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing, Linlin?
What?
Mother! Help!
Well, he's got one too many elbow joints
so I thought it'd be nice to tear it apart for him.
No, he's from the Longarm Tribe!
That's normal for him!
Oh... I see...
Ouch!
Linlin, what are you doing?!
He's got fins so I thought it'd help by
tearing them off for him.
Stop that. The Fish-Men often have
characteristics of fish!
Oh... I see...
I was terrified!
Everyone, forgive her!
Linlin is a kind girl!
Carmel pardoned everything.
Wait, wait!
Linlin will kill me!
Wait, wait! Wait, wait!
KASHII
10 months later in Elbaph, the
New World's strongest country,
tough ones had accepted
Linlin open-heartedly.
OIMO
Wait, wait.
It's almost been 40 years...
Have you ever seen a duel last that long?
No, never! Let's go and pick them up
after another decade or so.
These Giants - Kashii and Oimo -
are talking about...
Dorry the Blue Ogre.
And...
Brogy the Red Ogre.
They met Luffy and the others
and bonded tightly.
We will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!
Have faith in us, and
continue straight ahead!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
Now go!
Oimo and Kashii went out to pick up
Dorry and Brogy as they said.
But they got caught and fooled
by the Navy on their way
and were forced to guard the gate at Enies Lobby
for half a century.
Then, it was none other than Sniper King
who taught them the truth and freed them.
After learning the truth,
Kashii and Oimo became allies of Luffy and the others
and created havoc in Enies Lobby.
Hey, Linlin! Did you guys finish preparing?
Kashii, preparing for what?
Oh, Linlin-chan, I guess
it's your first time.
In Elbaph, we undergo fasting for 12 days
before the Winter Solstice Festival!
Fasting?
We won't eat anything.
You're only allowed to drink water.
For 12 days starting tomorrow.
What?!
I'm gonna be hungry!
But if you can endure it,
we'll have a festival!
Fight against yourself, Hajrudin!
Stand up, Hajrudin!
This Giant boy, Hajrudin...
HAJRUDIN
...will eventually meet Luffy in Dressrosa
and be impressed by his determination.
Along with Bartolomeo and the others,
he exchanged cups of sake as
parent and son with Luffy.
He is now a member of the Straw Hat Fleet.
The tough boy!
Dorry or Brogy, either
of the chiefs will return
and the Giant Pirates
will roam again for sure!
You're a warrior!
Don't stop training yourself, Hajrudin!
Yeah!
I like the spirit! Rydin!
Uh-huh!
Chief Beardfall-sama! Chief Beardhill-sama!
CHIEF BEARDHILL JARUL (345 YEARS OLD)
CHIEF BEARDFALL JORUL (344 YEARS OLD)
Carmel preaches "trade rather than
robbery" and that's good too.
But we shall not forget that we are warriors!
Yes!
Jarul-sama and Jorul-sama are so cool!
FORMER CO-CAPTAINS OF THE GIANT PIRATES
(TWO OF THE WORLD'S OLDEST WARRIORS)
HEROES OF THE GIANTS
No wonder all Giants
respect them as warriors!
I wanna be like them some day!
What brought both of you here today?
We'll eat Semla in the village so we came here
to pick up the children at the House of Lambs.
We're just in time, Linlin.
What's Semla?
It's a very delicious sweet!
What?! A sweet?
Before the fast, we'll get a lot of nutrition
by eating Semla!
Are we gonna eat it now? The sweet?!
Sweet cream dolloped in
sweet bread with marzipan,
topped with a dusting of sugar!
It's the fun before the fast!
Sounds delicious!
All right, everyone!
The recent birth of Prince
Loki at the castle!
And Rodo and Goldberg who
were born in the village!
Thank the Sun for our children's growth!
Thank the Sun!
Thank you for the food!
Yeah! Semla!
We have a lot so eat as much as you want!
This is...
This is... Semla...
Linlin, eat, eat!
Uh-huh!
S... S...
So sweet!
It's delicious!
I'm happy!
Delicious! Delicious! Sweet! Sweet!
Delicious! Delicious!
--Delicious! Delicious!
--Whoa-whoa! Hey, Linlin!
Don't eat so fast!
There won't be enough to go around!
Don't forget to thank the Sun!
Semla!!
It's delicious! It's so delicious! Semla!
FASTING - DAY 3
Mother... I'm starved to death...
The Winter Solstice Festival celebrates
the death and the resurrection of the Sun.
Fighting through the severe winter,
the Sun will shine down on us again.
FASTING - DAY 4
The more you suffer,
the more you appreciate the Sun.
So... let's keep going!
If Mother says so, I'll... keep trying...
FASTING - DAY 5
I'm losing weight...
You haven't changed.
Yeah? That's strange...
Linlin!
You're doing great! A little more to go!
Uh-huh!
Linlin started liking Mother so much.
FASTING - DAY 6
Semla was so delicious...
I...
...wanna eat it... again...
FASTING - DAY 7
Oh, no!
Mother, help!
What's the matter, Gerd?!
Linlin-chan is...!
This is...
Semla!!
How dare you...
Linlin!
Bring me Semla...
Semla!
Linlin destroyed the village of Elbaph!!
It's a nightmare!
She finally did it! Linlin!
She has no right to thank the Sun!
Even if she's a child,
we can't forgive everything!
Jorul-sama!
Semla... Semla...
Carmel... I'm sorry...
She may look like a child...
Don't do it! Jorul-sama!
But she's a god of Disaster!
Semla...
A huge event occurs that will change the fate of
the innocent monster Charlotte Linlin!
Her long standing feud with the Giants and a
stunning secret of the miracle-making
Holy Mother Carmel,
and even the origin of the hellish Tea Party...
All of those mysteries are now revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Birth of Mom! The Day That Carmel Vanished!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!