My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Sanji and Pudding's bloodbath wedding
finally began.
To take down Big Mom, Luffy and the others allied with Bege
and broke the portrait of Mother Carmel,
successfully making Big Mom shriek.
And memories of the past came back to Big Mom.
Charlotte Linlin, also known as Big Mom,
has been...
...feared for her brute strength since she was a child
and was abandoned in Elbaph, country of the Giants.
There, she met Mother Carmel,
a nun who was admired by everyone,
and lived happily with other orphans...
Semla!!
How dare you...
Linlin!
Bring me Semla...
Carmel... I'm sorry...
She may look like a child...
Don't do it! Jorul-sama!
But she's a god of Disaster!
"The Birth of Mom!
The Day That Carmel Vanished!"
Linlin! Let me give you a coup de grace
with my own hands!
Semla...
No, Linlin!
Se...
Jorul!
...m...
...la!
Beardfall-sama!
Jorul-sama!
Se... m... la!
What has she done...
But still...
...she's a good girl.
Semla!
Hold Linlin!
Put out the fire in the village!
--Catch her already!
--Okay!
Don't rough her up!
Could you get Semla?
There's some for the Festival
in the village storehouse!
Bring them now!
O-Okay!
--Mother, what are you doing?!
--It's dangerous!
Stay back!
Gebur...
Mother!
...tstag!
I'll give you a voice.
What's that?
Obey me!
--There's a face in the fire!
--What?!
I'm scared...
It's like a demon!
I name you "Pandora"!
I brought them!
Feed her now!
Semla!
It's delicious! It's delicious!
Simmer down!
The fire...
...is gone...
Hey, look!
How cute!
Hi, Mother!
Mother...
Worked a miracle...
No, it wasn't me.
The god of the sun brought everything under control.
I'm so happy!
Punish her... Don't think her as a child...
If you don't do anything...
she'll bring more disaster in the future...
--Jorul-sama!
--Get him treatment now!
Beardhill-sama!
Linlin...
Please forgive her!
Won't you let me do it, Carmel?
Jorul is my friend who I fought with for 300 years.
He's too old... I don't think he can make it!
Being a warrior isn't about living long...
It's about how you die!
We have to bring it to an end...
Anyone who defies Elbaph's laws
can't be forgiven!
I understand!
But even if she can't be forgiven,
since the poor Linlin was abandoned by the whole world
and ended up in the House of Lambs,
I can't give her up!
What'll you do?
I'll leave here along with her!
Carmel!
Beardhill-sama! Please kill Linlin!
Why should we pardon her
after she's done such a horrible thing?!
What happened to your Elbaph pride?!
Alright then, why don't you get out of my sight now?!
Why?!
Hajrudin!
Let go of me! Let go!
What happened to Beardfall-sama?
He died.
What? Why did he die?
I feel sorry for him.
Doesn't she remember?
Jorul, the hero of the Giants, died...
A god of Disaster named Linlin...
Carmel's miracle...
The details of that day...
...spread across a small number of
the Giant nations all over the world.
Together with the orphans of the House of Lambs
who refused to be separated from their Mother,
and Charlotte Linlin
who became the enemy of all the Giants,
Mother Carmel left Elbaph.
And they all started a new life
at the new House of Lambs.
It's done! Is this good enough?
More than enough.
I'm sorry for asking these favors.
Without your help,
I couldn't build a house deep in the mountains like this.
Don't mention it. To be honest,
I don't wanna see Linlin's face,
but you're the Holy Mother even for the Giants, Carmel.
You can ask anything of us.
Thank you!
To relieve the children's growing concerns,
Carmel tried to smile even more.
Wait, wait!
A few days after leaving Elbaph,
they were the same as they'd always been...
No, Linlin's gonna kill me!
Wait, wait!
The House of Lambs was filled with
the children's laughter.
Look after the house while I'm away.
I'll clean the bathroom!
I'll do the laundry!
What time will you be back?
I'll return as soon as I finish buying groceries.
Do you need anything?
Shortcake!
--A set of cards!
--Toy swords for samurai fighting!
Okay.
See you, Mother! Take care!
A legend grew about the House of Lambs.
Any troubled child will be born again
with Mother's help and meet good foster parents...
You're right on time...
Of course. Have I ever stood you up?
Let's get to business.
There is a good girl.
I didn't expect you to leave Elbaph...
That's how much I didn't wanna let go of her.
Think about it. She's only five now but she's already so
exceptional that she could destroy half of the Elbaph village.
But the price is...
I know it's not too high.
In the Navy,
she'd become a vice admiral or a fleet admiral.
In Cipher Pol,
she'd be the toughest shield for the Celestial Dragons.
I've been trafficking kids for 50 years.
She's the greatest product we've ever had!
37 years ago, I put on a good show with the Navy
and snuck into Elbaph.
John Giant became
the Navy's first Giant soldier
because of my connections!
I've been fooling the kids
at the House of Lambs
and selling fresh orphans once every two years
to the Government.
They're perfect for intelligence agents, right?
Orphans can't be traced.
All right! All right!
I'll try to come up with the money.
Of course, you will!
It takes a lot of work to act as the Holy Mother!
MOTHER CARMEL - AN ORPHAN SELLER
(UNDERWORLD NAME: MOUNTAIN HAG)
I was thinking to take this occasion to retire from the job...
So this'll be my last deal. I need you to pay me in full!
What do you all wanna sing today?
"Binks's Brew"!
What? That's a pirates' song.
That's right!
We'll become pirates some day!
Oh, that's very cool!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
O'er across the ocean's tide, the sunset is goin' wild
See the sky! Birds singing in circles passing by!
But I'll sell you brats to the Government
rather than pirates!
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
Sing a song, it won't be long before we're casting off!
Cross the gold and silver waves, changin' into water sprays!
Sailing out on our journey to the ends of the sea!
If I hand over the rest of the kids along with Linlin
to the Navy tomorrow, it's all over.
Before that,
I'll celebrate your special day so much, Linlin...
--Come, this way!
--Huh? What is it?
Sit down, Linlin!
Okay! But what is this?
One, two, three!
Happy Birthday, Linlin!
Thank you, everyone!
We piled up your favorite sweet, Semla,
and made this Croquembouche!
I hope it's good!
It's called Croquembouche? Looks delicious!
Let's have a tea party!
A tea party?
We'll spend time gracefully sitting around tables,
drinking tea and eating sweets!
That sounds great!
I wanna have that! A tea party!
--Let's make tea.
--Join us, Mother!
Okay, okay.
Thank you!
Yay!
Alright, let's start!
--Eat as much as you want!
--Eat, eat!
Uh-huh! Thank you!
It's so delicious!
She eats so fast!
The tea party's fun!
I'm so happy! It's so delicious!
One day, Mother Carmel vanished.
That was the day Linlin had the happiest birthday
ever in her life.
The special friends at the House of Lambs,
who had similar backgrounds.
The open-minded and generous Mother
that she loved.
Being surrounded by everyone's smiles
and eating her favorite sweet, sweet birthday cake,
Linlin couldn't hold back her tears.
Eat as much as you like, Linlin.
I'll eat... I'll eat it all!
What a lovely day...
Tears blurred her eyes.
Whoa-whoa, don't rush, Linlin!
We made it for you!
It's all yours!
Thank you!
Eat more!
Let's stay friends!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Let's stay together and have fun!
Yeah! We'll stay together forever!
You're a good girl, Linlin...
Mother!
We are family.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
It's so delicious!
What a lovely birthday.
Lick!
Oh, I'm so happy!
I was carried away so I even bit the table!
Thank you, everyone!
I'll never forget about today...
What?
Everyone?
Mother?
One day, Mother Carmel...
Where did you go?
...disappeared all of a sudden.
Hmm? Huh?
Where are you?! Everyone! In the house?
Hey!
Everyone!
Linlin!
Oh, there you are!
What?
Don't leave me alone...
Where are you, everyone?
Hey, Mother...
Why did you disappear all of a sudden?
Motha! Where're ya?!
What is she saying?!
Where did you go?!
Mother!
The moment to assassinate
the Emperor of the Sea finally comes!
The enraged Big Mom's shriek rings out,
and when Bege's deadly poison gas weapon fires,
Luffy's allied force's mission finally comes to a climax!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Launcher Blasts! The Moment of Big Mom's Assassination!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!