Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Who are you?
"Blue-nosed Reindeer!
Chopper's Secret"
Isn't that... backwards?
You're too slow... and you're
not completely hiding, either...
Just what are you?
Sh... Shut up, human!
And, how's your fever?
It talked!!
Be quiet, Chopper!
Your fever seems to have
come down a little, girl.
Are you happy?
Who are you?
38.2 degrees... Hmm...
You're doing more or less all right.
I'm a doctor. Dr. Kureha.
Call me Doctorine.
Doctor... Then I'm in the...
My secret to staying young?
No, I didn't ask that.
You're right. You're in the
castle on top of the mountain.
Then there were two others
besides me, right?
Yeah, they're sleeping in the next room...
very deeply. What tough guys...
This was the cause.
What... is this?
You were bitten by a bug called Kestia.
It's a poisonous tick that lives in jungles
with high temperature and humidity.
Once you're bitten by it,
bacteria come in and
keep you in pain by lying dormant
inside your body for 5 days.
It causes high fever of above 40 degrees,
coinfection, myocarditis,
arteritis, cerebritis!
Given the infection's progression
from the bitten area,
I'd say you've been
infected for three days.
The suffering must've
been unusually harsh,
but it would've eased up in 2 more
days even without any treatment.
In 2 more days...?
Yeah, because you
would've died in 2 days.
What?!
It's called the "5-day disease."
I heard that Kestia died
out 100 years ago,
but it was useful that I kept
the antibiotic just in case.
Where did you guys come from?
Were you out walking around
with your belly exposed
in a jungle on an ancient
island or something?
Well, that's just silly...
Ah...
That ring a bell? What a crazy girl...
Now...
Stay in bed. Your treatment
hasn't completely finished yet.
Thank you so much. So long as my
fever comes down, I'll be fine.
My body will take care of
itself after that, right?
You're too optimistic.
This disease normally takes at
least 10 days to fully treat.
Of course, if you want to
suffer some more and die...
Even with my medicine,
you'll have to rest at least 3 days.
What? I can't stay here for 3 days!
We have to take Vivi to Alabasta soon!
When a patient of mine leaves me,
she's either cured or dead.
I won't let you get away.
He climbed this mountain
with his bare hands?!
This 5000m high Drum Rock?!
His entire body is nearly frostbitten.
What was he thinking dressing like this?
Heat water immediately
and throw him into it.
This guy's bleeding badly.
6 broken ribs and a spinal fissure.
Can I operate on him?
Apparently, the most critical
one is this girl. She's dying.
Chopper! Have phenicol,
cardiotonic and tialcillin ready!
Does she have an infection?
Yeah. The pathogen
isn't from this island.
Hm?
Don't worry. I'll make both that
bleeding kid and this girl all better.
So rest assured.
They're my friends...!
I get the picture. I'll save them.
Chopper! Let's begin treatment!
They're my friends...!
I'm... I'm hungry...
Meat...
Venison stew needs to be
cooked in a pot for 3 hours...
Then the meat becomes properly tender...
Meat...
Venison...
Ahhhh! Help!
Wait, meat!
Wait, Luffy! I'll cook this guy!
Hm?
Nami...
Nami-san!
You got better?
Yeah, thanks.
Okay, then! I'll make a nutritious
venison dish for Nami-san!
Wait!
I'm surprised!
They can already move around?
What's that talking stuffed
deer with a blue nose?
You asking me what he is?
Don't run away, meat!
Wait, Luffy! I'm telling you
not to eat it yet!
Stop it, humans!
His name is Chopper.
He's just a reindeer with a blue nose.
Reindeers don't speak.
S-stop it, you jerks!
If he's different from
ordinary reindeers in some way,
If he's different...?
I'm not food!
it's just because he ate a
Human Human Fruit. That's all.
A Human Human Fruit...
One of the devil fruits...
Yeah... He's a reindeer who
gained the humans' abilities.
Rats! Rats!
And I taught him everything
I know about medicine.
Wapol-sama.
That Straw Hat is up there...
I'm starting to get a bit hungry.
I'll eat the rubber man for a snack.
We're going up.
Dalton-san!
Did you find him?!
Dalton-san! Don't die!
We'll find him in time, for sure!
Be alive, Dalton-san!
Who's that?
Don't just stand there! Help...
Gotta bow.
Like I said, don't just
stand there and help us!
What the heck is that thing?!
We found him! We found Dalton-san!
What?! They found him?!
Great!
Dalton-san!
So, who is that?!
This is terrible...
There's no heartbeat.
Become one of my crew!
Please, old lady!
We need a doctor on our ship!
Luffy... You said that's your name, right?
Yeah.
Did you just say "old lady"?
Yeah, I did, old la...
Watch... what you say!
I'm still in the youthful 130s.
Whoa... What an incredible old hag...
Are you asking me to be a pirate?
Don't be ridiculous!
It'll be a waste of my glorious time.
I'm not interested in the sea.
Who cares? Let's go on
an adventure, old lady!
Hey hey. I just told you to
watch what you say, didn't I?
So they're pirates...
Hm?
Ah!
--Wait, meat!
--Wait!
Hold it, brats!
Wait!
Hold on, Nami-san!
I'll cook a nutritious reindeer dish!
Before that, I'll eat you guys!
Old hag!
Where the heck did she come from?
She's coming! She's coming!
I don't care about the food.
I just want some peace and quiet.
Snow...? Even though
this is inside the castle...?
Cold...!
--I should close the door.
--Stay in bed!
You still have a fever!
I don't. It seems like
it's pretty much gone.
Looks like I lost them...
Even so, no!
Since Doctorine's medicine works well,
the fever goes away quickly.
But Kestia's bacteria
still remain in your body.
Have the antibiotic shot
and stay in bed, or you'll...
Thank you...
Hm?
You've been attending me, right?
Sh...
Shut up!
I don't wanna be thanked by a human!
Don't mock me! You jerk!
Don't be silly, you dummy!
Seriously, don't be so...
He's the type that
can't hide their emotions...
This castle is strange.
It's cold and there's snow inside.
Oh...?
Ahhh! It's cold!
Like I told you before, you're slow!
Look at this...
There's snow everywhere in the castle.
The doors for the unused
rooms are all frozen, too.
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Hey hey, Luffy! Give up on
asking that old hag to join us!
She's not a doctor!
She's trying to kill us!
Are you guys pirates?
Yes...
R-real ones?
Real ones.
You have a flag with a skull?
It's attached to our ship.
Are you interested in pirates?
No! You idiot! No!
You idiot!
Okay, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But... Then... wanna come, too?
What?!
To the sea! Why don't you
come with us...? Hm?
If you do, that'll help me a lot!
If we have a doctor on our ship,
I won't have to stay here for 3 days, right?
On top of that, on our ship, we...
D... Don't be ridiculous!
I'm a reindeer!
There's no way I can stay with humans!
To start with, don't you
get scared when you see me?
I'm a reindeer, but I stand on
two legs and I even speak...
What? Are you trying to scare me?
My nose is blue, too...
There you are!
Reindeer!
Wait!
Those brats sure are quick.
I don't like it... girl...
What?
Are you tempting the reindeer without
my permission while I'm not here?
Oh? Do I need permission
to make a move on a man?
No, you don't. If you wanna
take him, go right ahead.
But it won't be easy.
He has a scar in his heart...
It's a big scar that
even I can't cure...
The moment he was born into this world,
his group and even his
parents abandoned him...
What?
because he had a blue nose.
He always walked at the very back
of the group all by himself...
even though he was a new-born child...
And one day, he ate a devil
fruit and was treated
as a monster even more.
The reindeers fiercely
pressured him to leave.
He was no longer an ordinary
reindeer in any way.
Still, he wanted friends...
So he went down to a village,
as a human this time.
Hey... what's that creature?
But his figure wasn't
exactly human, either.
For some reason,
his nose stayed blue, too.
It must be a yeti!
It's dangerous!
Get the children inside quickly!
A gun! Bring me a gun!
Shoot him to death!
You damn monster!
Go away!
He didn't know what was wrong.
Nor did he know what to blame...
You damn monster!
He just wanted friends,
yet he was called a monster...
He was no longer a reindeer...
He wasn't a human, either...
He's lived all alone like that...
Can you guys heal the scar in his heart?
Hey, Luffy. Look at that door at
the front entrance. It's wide open.
Hm?
No wonder it's cold.
In any case, let's close this door.
With it open like this, there's no difference
between outside and inside the castle.
Hey! Stop it! Don't touch that door!
Huh?
Never mind what he says.
Let's close it, or we'll freeze to death.
True.
Hey! Didn't I tell you to... stop it?!
What's with him? Why is he angry?
Hey Luffy. Come over here.
Hm?
Look up there.
Hm...?
Ah!
They're baby snowbirds.
Well, if we close the door, they'll fall...
That's why they can't close it...
It's cold!
Hold on a sec...
What is it?
Ah! Wasn't he speaking earlier?!
Well, come to think of it, I sort of
remember him standing on two legs.
He's a monster!
Wh... What the heck is that?
He's walking on two legs...
He's a reindeer...
He's fluffy...
He's short...
He becomes big...
And he's a monster!
What a cool guy! He's interesting!
Sanji! Let's have him join us!
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Nami! Did you see the reindeer?
Geez, you guys! Cut it out already!
Well, it's not that we're
not trying to eat him.
Chopper has had lots of
hardships in his life.
I see...
But I heard that there was
one person who accepted him.
Really? What kind of person was that?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Outcast's Dream!
Hiriluk the Quack!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!