My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom
and getting a fierce attack from her family,
After failing to kill Big
Mom, Luffy and the others
After failing to kill Big Mom, Luffy and his allies
escaped from the Whole Cake Chateau
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and his allies were backed into a corner
executed a plan to escape from the
Tea Party at the risk of their lives.
Luffy and the others were trying to escape
from the Tea Party at the risk of their lives.
Luffy and the others narrowly
escaped into Bege's body.
but the Whole Cake Chateau's collapse
let them make an escape.
and saw Kingbaum again
on their way to the Sunny.
Caesar is trying to get out of the site carrying Bege
You were so close.
Listen carefully, you guys!
I don't know who did it
but I gotta thank them!
who has the whole team inside of his body,
Sparking...
Being driven by her Hunger Pang attack,
Big Mom chases Luffy and the others.
This castle is me.
It's strong but not unbreakable.
...Figure!
with Germa 66 escorting them.
We didn't have to kill her!
Just go!
To save Reiju who was cornered,
Luffy and Sanji went outside.
However, while facing the overwhelming
forces of the Big Mom Pirates,
If they destroy the castle, I'll die.
Then the castle will be gone...
Now,
Wedding cake!
the "Emperor of the Sea" Big
Mom Pirates have been...
they got caught.
And once you guys get thrown out,
the monsters will prey on you, too!
...annihilated!
The one that becomes
the King of the Pirates in the end...
However, Big Mom and her family members
were saved by Streusen's ability.
You're damned if you stay
and damned if you leave.
Everyone got defeated?
And only a wedding cake will stop her attack.
...is me!
All right, let's start...
You're in dire straits!
The wedding cake was a chocolate chiffon cake!
Meanwhile, Stussy of Cipher Pol-"AIGIS" 0
Then, Bege told Luffy and the others
the only way to survive.
...the executions.
who was undercover and
infiltrating the Tea Party,
Mama...
Then, the Tamate Box that Big Mom got
from the Fish-Man Island caused a huge explosion
I can make as good a chocolate flavor as the head chef,
if not better!
Mama!
Listen... I'll change back to my human form
keeping you guys inside.
let the Tamate Box she was trying to get ahold of
fall off a cliff.
And Big Sis Chiffon is an expert of
chiffon cakes!
Luffy and his clan who got away from
the Whole Cake Chateau...
and the Whole Cake Chateau started crumbling.
--What?!
--No!
Then, Caesar will carry
me and fly away to escape.
...parted ways with Bege's group
and headed for the Sunny.
Together, we can make that cake!
If it goes well, we can get out of trouble.
You can drop dead without worrying!
All right. Let's run then.
I'll use your scientific technology and...
We'll part with you guys here, Straw Hat.
Take the Spear of Elbaph!
And the one who volunteered to
escort them in the plan was...
...I'll make the world peaceful!
Elbaph?!
Open the gate!
Meanwhile, Katakuri and the others
formed pursuit units.
Gang Bege!
Until you and Caesar Clown fly away into the sky,
Terrific!
I don't know who did it
but I gotta thank them!
We'll split up into two groups
and chase them!
Look out for her attack!
we Germa will escort you!
We didn't have to kill her!
One group, bring back Straw Hat's head!
And the other, bring back Bege's!
Thunder Bolt!
I don't wanna be indebted to this "failure"!
Now,
Come on out already!
the "Emperor of the Sea" Big
Mom Pirates have been...
Bege!
...annihilated!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Straw Hat!
A detached force is already invading Germa.
"The Execution Begins!
Luffy's Allied Forces Are Annihilated?!"
Okay... Brulee, come with me!
Get ready to step out!
"The Chateau Collapses!
The Straw Hat's Great Escape Begins!"
Getting ready to step out!
However, in the midst of that...
We're ready!
Bege!
Father-sama!
I'm gonna deactivate the castle!
Everyone! Get out of the city!
Smoothie!
Help!
Let's go!
Run as far as you can!
At a time like this?!
"Pudding's Determination!
Ablaze! The Seducing Woods!"
Germa! Start attacking!
Where's Reiju? Are they okay?
"The Spear of Elbaph!
Onslaught! The Flying Big Mom!"
Did he die?!
Damn!
Father!
Sky Walk!
Hey, wait, guards!
"Escape From the Tea Party!
Luffy vs. Big Mom!"
Are you guys leaving us...
He deactivated the castle!
Where is the wedding cake?!
Oh, no...
Mama...
Mama!
Katakuri!
Run!
See? We're totally targeted!
You were so close.
It's impossible!
Just a little more to go.
There you are, you fleas!
We're dead!
The Queen's Hunger Pangs!
Sparking...
The castle is bigger than the city!
We can't get away!
She's having another attack
in such a short period of time!
Wedding...
...Figure!
No one can make it even if they run!
...cake!!
Don't worry. We'll do our part! Just go!
That resembled the Giants' technique!
She remembered the wedding cake
that was destroyed, which she couldn't eat!
You don't have to tell me!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
You think you caught me cold?
Big Brother!
Why is it?
What's in Mama's hand?!
Seems like you don't value your life.
Kingbaum!
It's no use to threaten me.
Calm down.
Unfortunately... I don't feel fear.
Mama! Forgive me-ju!
I've been forced to do this-ju!
Big news! This is big news!
It's too late.
You're still alive... I'll put you at ease.
Don't you care about your own life?
Oh, yeah! I can't fly!
Oh, no! The next attack will come!
Let's get off and fight!
Germa!
Goodbye... Vinsmoke Judge!
Oh, no!
Kingbaum! Who was the girl you were with?
Your girlfriend?
Hurry up!
D-Damn...
Why do I have to...
Oh, all right already!
But...
...if this is the end of the Big Mom Pirates,
No, stop, Kin-chan!
Big Bro Opera!
Are you okay, Kin-chan?
We won't let you do it!
Hey! Wake up!
--Kin-chan!
--Lady Tree!
it surely is big news.
Don't tell me she took your lifespan!
Brother!
You came to save your father?!
S-She's my fiancee-ju.
Big Bro Opera stood in Mama's way
to stop her!
They're gonna fly over the wall!
Wow! Fiancee?!
What beautiful family love! I like it!
That's right-ju!
We promised to stay together forever-ju!
Nobody get close to Mama!
Hey!
Don't mistake us. It's part of a Germa
member's duties to save our leader!
Sanji-kun!
Don't let them get away!
This way! Hurry!
Then...
you must live on!
And that's all.
What cold-hearted children.
Stop!
Survive for her sake!
On behalf of your cowardly father,
We have to do something...
To see her again!
Heavenly...
Where is it?!
I'll...
Go! Fast!
The wedding cake!
...Fire!
...rediscipline you if you want!
This way!
Please hurry up!
Sanji! Luffy!
I see... Then, die.
You're right-ju!
I can't just drop dead now!
You're alive!
If you think you can do it...
Run, Kingbaum!
Go ahead!
What lies ahead is a new life with her!
--Sorry to keep you waiting!
--You're so reckless!
Honestly!
All of you, hurry up!
They'll come chase us soon!
A future filled with love is waiting for you!
I'm so relieved.
Reiju!
Forget it, Niji! Yonji!
Go, Caesar! Let's run far away!
Nami!
That's what happens to the weak!
Do your job!
Lady Tree!
You're riding on Jimbei's shoulders!
Quit bossing us around!
You don't have to tell me that!
Don't let them get away!
Shoot, shoot!
Run away! Run away! Run away!
My brother's so unlovely.
Yes!
That's okay!
--She's like a devil...
--That's our Nami!
That's okay! I'm not gonna get beaten!
Because Nami-san is so cute!
Don't turn back, Caesar!
You gotta give it your best, too!
They're gone.
Give me the cake!
So cute and delicate...
It's impossible!
Mission complete!
What are you doing?!
Okay, it's my turn!
Withdraw!
Shoot them down!
I said, "You can't go"!
Roger.
Wait, Luffy! I have a plan!
Pursuers from the Big Mom Pirates
will surely come! We must hurry!
But Sanji's sister is...
Is everything okay?!
Wedding...
Don't go, Luffy.
--Come on, Caesar!
--What happened to Luffy and the others?!
What are you gonna do?!
Count on me!
Cutting through this area and
the Seducing Woods is the shortest way to the Sunny!
...cake!
Black Ball!
--You're dead!
--Just surrender without a fight!
Soft and fluffy...
Moist and fluffy...
Thunder likes thunder!
...life
There's no such thing
You know what to do!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
The only way to stop Mama's Hunger Pang attack
is to give her the food she craves!
That Germa woman...
--What is this?
--M-My neck...
Don't push your luck.
Are you okay?
None of you can get away.
Be prepared!
That's it!
Big Sis Smoothie!
He ate them!
What we need is... the wedding cake!
It's delicious! It's delicious! So delicious!!
Hey, are you okay?
Where is the head chef?!
He's the only person who can rebake the cake!
You guys, go ahead and run!
That poison woman!
It's not gonna be that easy.
Oh! Mama!
Outta my way!
Oh, no...
W-Well... Streusen-sama...
Lie there for a while.
This is it!
Oh, wait!
I won't let anyone get away!
Gour-Metamorphosis!
What are you doing, Zeus?!
...saved everyone's life but...
First...
Oh no, he's totally into it.
...he himself missed a landing big time...
They're running towards the Seducing Woods!
I'm gonna start with you!
Little Germa girl!
Wedding cake!
He needs several days to recover!
Once we get in the forest,
we'll have the upper hand!
Gum-Gum...
Diable Jambe, Crosse...
Because Kingbaum is...
If it goes on like this,
Sweet City will be destroyed. Grr!
...the master of the forest!
...Elephant Gun!
What can we do to stop Mama?!
It's Kingbaum-sama!
Extra...
...Strike!
Kingbaum-sama is coming!
...Hachis Hash!
We can't let her rampage here in the capital!
Get out of my way!
What the?!
You told me not to go out!
Yeah, you're not supposed to!
But I am!
Not fair!
Awesome!
--Oh, my...
--You're something, Big Tree.
Luffy!
Sanji-san!
Where is it?!
They got out...
Move! Move! Move!
What are you gonna do, you fools?!
--Let's go, Reiju!
--Yeah!
Mama!
You too!
Oh, look! There's the Sunny!
Why are you guys trying to get away from me?!
That was close.
--What?
--It's a straight line to the coast.
How annoying!
Does he...
I guess he's got an idea!
Your plan is amazing!
That's our Perospero-sama! Grr!
That's my Nami-san!
Remember what you said to me, Straw Hat?
When you were at the Fish-Man Island?
Mama! The wedding cake...
GERMA KINGDOM
Heavy cream?
We're gonna get swept away!
...isn't gone!
You said "I'll kick your ass."
We kept a spare cake on standby, Mama!
--Is this...
--A sponge cake?
That brat who stood up to me
has piqued my interest.
You poison-woman...
Big Bro Peros!
I'm impressed, Germa...
No! What are you talking about?!
Have it your way, instead
of the Fish-Man Island,
Did you think I'd say that?
I-It's made from carefully
selected ingredients...
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
And it's meltingly delicious...
Monkey D. Luffy.
I know your name now.
It's the best wedding cake ever!
Hidden darts?!
It's no use...
What happened?
I really want you to have it but, believe or not,
the Straw Hats stole it and ran!
Come to the New World!
You can't beat me if you can't hit me.
The Whole Cake Chateau turned into
a real whole cake...
What's with him?!
Sure, wait for me there.
I don't have to beat you...
Our job is to let them escape.
They're now heading to the southwest coast
trying to get away!
That saved us...
It must be the head chef who did it.
I'm gonna show all I've got
for the first time in a long time.
There's some business
I want to settle with you, too.
You're a pain
so I just wanna stall you...
People who say such a thing
are often weak.
I can't leave it in your hands -
that's too dangerous!
I thought I was gonna die!
"And buy some time," huh?
Wedding...
...cake...
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
Besides, even if I can't hit you,
I can blow you up with me!
That's right! They got it! Lick!
Are you okay, Mama?
What's the matter?
Show me what you've got already.
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
Cake...
Okay.
My castle turned into a cake...
I assume she's listening
to me to some extent.
Sparking Figure!
Remember what you said to me
after you came to this island?
If she goes after Straw Hat,
it's like killing two birds with one stone!
Double!
The sweets that are created
by Streusen's ability...
You said,
"We're the ones who'll have the last laugh."
Big Bro Katakuri!
Take this!
...will fill your stomach
but don't taste good.
You haven't become the King of the Pirates.
Can he talk her into it?
Bring it on!
Mama!
That's all.
I'm glad that you're okay.
I'm gonna pick a fight with you again!
Just because you're the Emperor of the Sea,
don't be cocky!
Dammit... My wedding cake...
I'll win Sanji back!
You're too slow!
We're the ones who'll have the last laugh!
If you're lying,
Cake...
Niji!
Okay!
And now you're trying to run?
You coward!
you'll pay with your lifespan!
I'll burn you to a crisp!
Are you okay?
I need your help!
C... C...
Alright! You're okay now.
Mama!
Co...ward...?
How thrilling!
I thought I was gonna die.
I'm gonna be crushed by the cake!
Zeus!
--Look at them!
--They look kind of cool!
--Don't fall for it, Luffy! She's provoking you!
--Just one punch!
Yes, Mama!
Of course-rero! They're Germa-rero!
I hear a voice from there!
Hey! Luffy!
Hurry and help that person!
Yeah, I said those things!
To fulfill their job,
they don't care about their own safety...
Th-That's...
Big Mom!
Sparking!
They're ruthless to others and themselves.
No wonder they're strong.
Montd'Or-sama! What happened?!
Wedding cake!
Why did the Whole Cake Chateau collapse?
But the Big Mom Pirates are not
easy opponents to beat.
What happened to Pudding-sama's wedding?
Not just Germa,
you do your best too, Caesar!
How... fast... he can move...
The city got smashed
and we thought we were finished!
I can go faster if you want.
--Shut up!
--What?!
Don't say such an irresponsible thing!
It's not finished yet!
Cut the crap!
Mama!
The people who plotted to kill Mama got away!
What's the matter?
I'm in trouble!
Now, Caesar!
Even if Mama gets the Straw Hats,
they don't have the cake!
I'm sure they haven't gone that far yet!
The one that becomes
the King of the Pirates in the end...
--What should I do?!
--I thought that was pretty smart but...
Contact the Tartes of all Totto Land islands!
Go! You can make it-rero!
That's it! Go!
As long as Big Mom doesn't ride on Zeus,
we can shake her off!
You can do it, Caesar!
The Straw Hats and the Firetank Pirates!
...is me!
You're still a loser, though!
His name is Zeus?
When Mama comes back,
I'll be dead!
Huh? What did you just...
Yes, that cloud was created by
part of Mama's soul...
Not a single one of them will get away!
But you bought some time!
Watch out, you...
Yeah, I'm Zeus.
We've got to make the cake now
or this island will be over, too!
NORTHWESTERN PART OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Zeus-sama!
What?
--Zeus!
--He's here!
Be careful! He's strong!
Well, it's impossible...
Think about it, Smoothie.
--Hey! Get out of my way!
Hey, hey, those small thunderclouds!
I want more of them!
I guess this is far enough.
--Huh? Who are you?!
Get out!
How many days do you think even the head chef, Streusen,
needed to make that cake?
What?
--You're me!
Black Ball? Were they good?
--No, he can't be me!
The rare ingredients that we collected
by robbing other countries are gone!
I've never had such rich-tasting thunderclouds
that went down so smooth!
It's me, Caesar Clown!
Thank you, Bege!
I really thought we were dead...
Don't thank me!
Brulee?!
And the person who can bake it is in a coma!
He can't make the cake!
Hey, are there more?
I feel like I did something
good and that makes me sick.
Oh, those taste good?
I won't let you escape!
I'm the one who carried you! You jerks!
I have grudges against you guys
piled up like a mountain.
What's more troubling is that
Mama hasn't even tasted the cake!
Shut up, loser!
I finally get to settle
the score a little bit!
Do you remember what you did to
those kids at Punk Hazard?
It's fluffy!
Give me, give me, more, more!
So this time, we have to provide...
We don't need you anymore so...
Go drop dead.
Hey, Cloud!
Forget it and give us a lift!
The never-before-eaten delicious cake
which has been built up in Mama's head.
Boost the voltage!
I'm doing it!
What are you doing, Luffy?!
No, I can't. Only Mama who gave me
part of her soul can ride on me.
Hey! How could you speak to
a genius like that?!
Just come back already!
I can turn this place into a
poison gas trap if you want!
Who can make such a thing?!
You seem to be preoccupied with
Mama and the others...
Is this all you've got? It feels kinda nice.
Oh, so you're just an ordinary cloud.
So ordinary...
But we'll take care of you in her place!
This is bad.
Zeus... In that case...
Here. It's your heart.
A real electric shock....
At the very least this
island will be destroyed!
Can we really fly over the wall?!
Will you become my servant?
What lies ahead of that is... unknown.
Huh?
...should work like this!
Gladly!
It's my... my... my...
Don't worry-rero!
She's not asking you.
Germa 66 will protect us-rero!
Then you can eat the Black Ball every day!
What? Really?!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
They're our evil heroes
who are absolutely invincible!
You're free, too.
Is he dead?
You should've crushed it.
You're doomed!
You have no loyalty to your boss?
Do you want me to help you?!
No!
Oh, please!
I know you can become a huge thundercloud
that covers up the whole sky!
Nice try.
Damn Germa...
You should've crushed it.
I'll knock them down directly then!
That was so cool!
Oh, really?
Leave them to me.
I can handle them single-handedly.
I've never been complimented like that!
Pudding!
--Oh, Pudding-sama!
--Pudding-sama!
Don't take me lightly!
I'll start with you!
Other people might have succumbed...
Stealth.
The wedding cake was a
chocolate chiffon cake!
My heart...
But I can neutralize your poison.
M-Mama...
My heart is back!
Here she comes!
I can make as good a chocolate flavor as the head chef,
if not better!
I'll never see you guys again!
Wedding cake...
And Big Sis Chiffon is an expert of
chiffon cakes!
Goodbye, idiots and stupid girl!
--Why did it collapse?
--Hey!
Together, we can make that cake!
Big Mom!
--Yeah, it was sudden.
--Hey!
--What happened?
--Bye!
That's my man-rero!
Are you sure, Pudding?!
--I have no idea.
--Hey!
But Chiffon is married to Bege
who is our enemy now!
It's not over yet!
Hey, guys!
Father!
Just as expected, it seems like
Big Mom and her family members have all survived-rero!
Whoa, you guys gotta fight with me.
Reiju?!
I'll make her do it!
There's the evil Pudding!
What?! Pudding-sama is acting like a thug!
You'd better focus.
The whole fallen castle turned into a cake...
The truth is the ingredients for the cake...
That's Streusen's ability.
...were gathered together at
Chocolat Town, Cacao Island,
Everyone!
He was a mystery to me all along...
the gateway to our territory.
So there are actually extra supplies of
the rare ingredients!
We're in trouble, Caesar!
I'm so excited-rero-rero!
I don't think he's just a head chef.
Big Bro Peros!
He must be quite a fighter, too.
Once Mama eliminates the Straw Hats,
lead her to Chocolat Town!
I guess it's my turn. Alright!
I'll end the matter!
I thought that was it for
the Big Mom Pirates...
M-Mama...
You sure?! That's so helpful, Pudding!
Mama!
How lucky they are.
Everyone got defeated?
Seducing Woods!
But that's okay. The castle collapsed.
Stop buzzing around like a fly!
I got insulted by Sanji!
Are you even trying?
Stop them!
I feel a little better.
Oh, no...
What a beautiful eye!
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
Now, all there's left to do is run, right?
If Mama can wipe them out...
That's all we've been doing...
There were too many obstacles at the beginning.
I have to give her a reward.
All right. Let's run then.
We're finished...
I... I can't ask for more-rero!
We'll part with you guys here, Straw Hat.
Just you wait!
What? Really?
Sanji!
No...
Good, Germa!
We failed to kill Big Mom...
Germa!
Keep protecting me like that!
What's wrong?
My heart just thumped...
We have no reason to stay together anymore.
Oh, no! Mama's angry!
You fools!
If nothing is done,
we'll all get killed for sure!
I guess some cutie is talking about me
as always...
That's right.
You guys had better hurry, too.
Everyone who rebels against Mama...
I don't want that!
I see the Seducing Woods!
...will be burned to death by me!
Then...
It turned back to the annoying forest.
Even when you get to your ship,
it'll take a day to sail out of Big Mom's territory.
Are we gonna go into that forest again?!
I hope we'll be okay.
Here comes a terrible one!
Can't we just kick them out of our way
and go straight?
The damn Oven, huh?
We have only one option.
That's true!
Hey, what's that?
We can't!
You two will be the first!
Good luck!
While you're rampaging like that,
you'll lose all sense of direction in this forest!
No, stop, Kin-chan!
Castle Tank!
Rather than sit and wait for death to come...
Are you okay, Kin-chan?
That's right.
This forest disorients people.
Ow, ow, ow!
The seam hurts-ju, Lady Tree...
We'll fight, right?
I'll leave the rest to you!
--I'm going too!
--Me too!
Burn to death?
I'm sorry... But they'll stick together soon.
Just like us!
"The Straw Hats went that way"?
THE STRAW HATS WENT THAT WAY
We're going too, of course!
I'll beat you up before you get a chance!
Don't do such a pathetic thing!
I have no choice...
My command is
nothing compared to the queen's-ju!
Shut up! We have to survive!
How arrogant!
Ow, ow, ow! Take it easy.
Father!
Why don't you let us say goodbye-rero?!
Yeah, I became friends with Nami!
Not yet! This is just a
taste of what's to come!
Don't get too cozy!
This is the beginning of the real escape!
But...!
What? No! How?!
Hey!
Lady Tree!
Wait!
Hey!
You got too hot!
Form two military units, Daifuku.
Run as hard as you can
for the sake of love and the future!
You're alive, Kingbaum!
That insolent mouth again!
Okay.
We'll split up into two groups
and chase them!
Seems like we got away from Oven safely.
Good to see you again!
It's Mama's order! Stop them!
Tree!
One group, bring back Straw Hat's head!
And the other, bring back Bege's!
Get out of my way!
I'm not gonna die here-ju!
Oh, no! Someone's chasing us again!
All right, let's start...
Why are you doing this, Kingbaum-sama?!
G... G...
Is it Daifuku!
Go away!
...the executions.
You can't get away from here!
You can do it, Kingbaum!
Mama.
I'll make you pay, you bastards!
We're really dead this time!
--Kin-chan!
--Lady Tree!
Don't worry.
We won't let anyone escape...
--Hang on tight!
--Okay.
Tree! Don't stop!
Cake...
Don't look back! Go straight!
Gum-Gum...
I thought I was gonna die!
Its ingredients were carefully selected...
Dammit!
...Gatling!
Oh? Nami, I thought Lola's Vivre Card
was taken away from you.
Am I finally facing someone with a backbone?
It was going to be the
best wedding cake ever...
All right, let's start...
Enjoy that relaxed attitude while you can.
Yes, they took it.
But I cut in half just in case.
I was looking forward to it...
...the executions.
Genie-uine...
That's smart!
This is fast!
Since he's the master of the Seducing Woods,
he can travel a straight line!
...Rage Split!
All right!
Keep going to the Sunny at full speed!
Wedding cake...
I'll fight you again sometime!
Go!
You guys are like the plague-ju!
Get out of this country already-ju!
You're a bad loser!
Mama!
Mama?
You can't escape!
The Tamate Box!
Did you say something?
Give me a break!
Do as Nami-san says!
Where's my wedding cake?!
I'll squeeze you guys to the last drop!
Oh, that's convenient.
Not now...
Bring it to me now!
They keep coming.
Our targets are right there!
Take them down!
All right!
Make sure to hold her up here!
Wedding cake!
Kingbaum! Go faster!
Don't get in my way! Germa 66!
Yeah!
That's our job.
Look behind us! Enemies!
Ouch, it's hot. What is that?
It's...
Charge!
Yeah!
Ugh.
Go faster, Kingbaum!
I'm going as fast as I can-ju!
What is it?
If you get caught, I'll rip that seam!
You're terrible!
That's Prometheus-sama!
My wedding cake!
He's angry!
Damn Germa!
I guess I bought some
time for them to escape.
Something passed over our heads!
Hey, Kingbaum.
Anyway, just get us over the wall!
Where is it?!
--That voice...
--No way!
That's the only thing on my mind!
You betrayed Mama...
Run!
There are still more of them!
What?!
P-Prometheus-sama!
Wedding cake!
It's hot!
We're in trouble-fa!
My...
Here he comes!
If I can make it over the wall,
I can survive!
A little back in time...
--Is he trying to crush us?
--Kingbaum, get away!
Big Bro Opera!
Big Mom!
Smoothie! We gotta run-fa!
O-Over the wall...
RYUGU KINGDOM, FISH-MAN ISLAND
Wait!
You're responsible for all this!
I'm gonna be free soon!
Give it to me!
Luffy and the others saved the Ryugu Kingdom
from the New Fish-Man Pirates
Why did you lie and say
you killed Straw Hat?!
Kingbaum, run!
Your fiancee's waiting for you, isn't she?!
Lick.
I'm not gonna let them get away.
and received the Tamate Box
from King Neptune as thanks.
It's inexcusable to deceive your family!
Candy Wall!
But...
Even if you run now,
you have nowhere to go!
Your Majesty!
About giving all the stolen treasure
to Luffy-kun and the others if they can find it...
Oh, no!
Take responsibility for it!
GERMA KINGDOM
What?!
I need to ask them to return
just the Tamate Box.
Wh-What the hell is that?!
You'd better run-fa!
What are you saying?
Take them down!
He can't move! Let's get off!
Perospero must've done it...
I'd never tell anyone to return
what I already gave them!
Wedding cake!
That was our last hope...
Even if what's in it is not treasure...
Mama!
...but a bomb?
It's over... Oh, my freedom...
What?
What? Are you...
There's going to be a huge
explosion if they open it?!
Shoot! We'll be engulfed in it!
Go back!
The Clone Soldiers are created to be
fighters who don't fear death.
...trying to get in my way?!
I must ask them to return it immediately.
Run!
No, just go straight!
Nami! This way!
Nami-san!
You-gara will get hurt, too!
We, the Big Mom Pirates, will
take that military power over!
You gave all the treasures to Big Mom?!
Nami!
GERMA KINGDOM
Maybe it won't explode,
Minister of the Right.
Your Majesty, you are so positive!
Black...
I can't reach Judge-sama or Ichiji-sama!
...Bug!
What happened?
Now, back to the current action...
What's that?!
Go!
What?! But...
From the ceiling of the East
Baum Cake second floor,
a giant crack is running through
the Red-bean Baum Cake Meeting Room!
Tree!
The Big Mom Pirates?!
Not just a crack! It broke up!
We'll take over the Germa Kingdom!
Kingbaum...
This is the Red-bean Baum Cake third floor!
What's happening?!
Oops...
Nami-san!
The room is starting to slant!
You saved us! Germa 66!
Okay, we'll pick up the Shark Submerge
It's not an earthquake!
I clearly heard a big explosion earlier!
A room where they manufacture Clone Soldiers!
I found it!
Yay! He got through the wall of candy!
Only Germa could've done it!
and go straight to the Sunny!
--Is it an enemy attack?!
--It keeps leaning!
Yeah. Be careful!
We gotta hurry up, too,
and get back to the coast where we landed!
Go! Caesar!
What's going on?
He's a loser though!
No way...
Uh-huh! Let's get out of the territory
before they come for us!
It's falling over-bon...
Dammit! I got this far now!
I don't wanna die!
--Hey! I'm leaving, okay?!
--Okay, let's hurry up!
Humph! A throne without a king...
The Whole Cake Chateau!
--Straw Hat!
--Let's go!
Once I get over the wall, I...
I can be...
Hey! Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
It's falling over-bon!
It's so sad...
Wedding cake!
Straw Hat!
...free!!
Break it down immediately!
Cock-a-doodle-do!
There is a king.
SWEET CITY, THE CAPITAL
You're...
Where's Bege?
Th-The hidden undersea treasure,
Tamate Box, is right there...
We'll catch up to him soon!
There's a fire in the Seducing Woods...
I'm going to do this,
that and the other thing!
Was it our enemy's cannon?!
SWEET CITY, THE CAPITAL
This is the Emperor of the Sea's stronghold!
How can anyone invade this island?!
I think Mama is fighting.
I'm gonna enjoy my freedom to the fullest!
This is the Mirroworld. Montd'Or!
So it really was an explosion?!
We have 10,000 soldiers
who are waiting to be sent anytime anywhere!
Wh-What the hell?!
I can't believe it got stuck
in such a place-nen...
Goodbye!
What caused the blast?!
Stealth!
What?! Wait a minute!
Stop falling!
I have no choice. I gotta jump off...
The Tea Party turned out to be
like that-chocolat?!
Everyone's gonna die!
Got it. We'll be in touch.
What will you do with the Tamate Box,
Du Feld?
Does it have something to do with
the wedding on the rooftop?!
Th-The Straw Hats?!
Candy. Biscuit. Nuts.
Y-You are...
Yeah, it was a disaster!
The wedding and the wedding cake were all ruined!
Battleships from those islands, keep an eye on
the southwest coast where the Straw Hats' ship is moored
...Stussy! Were you watching?!
You guys aren't allowed beyond this point!
You bushy-haired freak!
The execution of the Vinsmokes was foiled!
and don't let them raise anchor!
On top of all that, Bege was betraying us
and plotting to kill Mama!
Yes, sir!
Burn! Burn! Burn!
Your encirclement will be
the first hurdle for them.
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn Bege... I completely respected
him for his great abilities-noir!
But now I can see what's in it...
Burn to ashes!
Tart ships from Flavor Island
and Liqueur Island will follow that.
This has to be a joke!
But we still don't know anything
about the explosion.
COMPOTE - ELDEST DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
The hidden undersea treasure...
Let's see how valuable it is!
Get ready and stand by at the port.
But this is big news!
Wait for the Warning Signals
from the Territory Slugs.
Those fools were on the rooftops, too,
so if they did it, they must've been suicidal.
Don't push your luck!
Roger.
Was that what I think it was?
I think so!
Thank you for doing whatever you like
in our kingdom!
They can't get away from the security network of
the Territory Slugs.
It's not very likely.
Flying Finger Pistol...
But one mystery has been solved-mour.
The timing was dead-on!
What else could have caused it?
We, the World Government,
will have the Tamate Box...
FORMERLY: "QUEEN OF THE PLEASURE DISTRICT"
Oh, no...
The thing is during the Tea Party,
SOUTHWEST COAST - THE SUNNY
But... why the Tamate Box?!
all lines of communication
to the venue were jammed-bon!
STUSSY, AN INTELLIGENCE AGENT OF CP-"AIGIS" 0
It's noisy in the forest.
How silly.
No wonder...
It was probably Bege and his allies.
Of course, I'll lay the blame on you.
Guys, hold onto something!
Was there anything that you wanted to report?
Mama is going after them herself
so there is zero chance for them to make it here.
You'll write a story like that,
won't you? Morgans.
Where are Straw Hat and the others?
Well, during the Tea Party, the Sun Pirates
who were staying on the east coast...
She knew I was here!
What is all this?
Sure but can I at least get a scoop on
what's in it?!
I don't know...
I bet so.
How dare you make a fool of us!
Well, then, why are we setting up an ambush?
But it saved us anyway!
Otherwise, all of us would've been killed.
That's right! They fled! Grr!
Yes, you can take pictures.
You're quick to understand.
The Big Mom Pirates!
You bastards are totally unforgivable!
Pekoms?!
Just in case.
That's maybe because you're
a manipulator of information.
All members of the Fish-Man Pirates
packed up and fled!
No, I run a newspaper! I'll sue you!
We'll pay you back with interest.
What's going on?! What's happening?!
I see... That's why Jimbei did that.
They're coming after us with the Tart Tanks!
--What?!
--No!
Fire!
Jimbei...
...quit the Big Mom Pirates
and joined the Straw Hats.
We'll get to the coast soon!
They can't catch us!
Big Mom!
Once I take down Kaido...
What?! Jimbei quit?!
Brother Bege!
Luffy, control yourself!
Something saved us...
Wow! You scared me!
Yeah...
And now I know the reason for his action.
You're next!
--Shut up!
--No!
We don't know if we've been...
Pudding-sa... I mean, Pudding!
Even if you're a young girl, I'm not gonna show mercy!
Big Mom!
Let go of me, Jimbei!
He knew Mama'd take out her anger
on his friends.
Going back to the Sunny is our objective!
Don't forget!
...saved or not, yet!
So to tell his friends about
that and give them time to flee,
I've got to talk to Big Sis Chiffon!
Let me see her now!
We're in big trouble, Mama!
Jimbei once reneged on his request to quit.
The Whole Cake Chateau is crumbling now
due to an unknown explosion!
This is like nothing...
It's a clever strategy and very Jimbei.
Big Sis Chiffon! Where are you?
Big Mom is nearing!
Katakuri!
Luffy...
Our troops are already chasing
Straw Hat and Bege!
Pudding! What brings you here?!
What brings Mama to the front line?!
You said, "Just one punch"!
Big Sis!
And look at her...
She doesn't seem like herself!
I need your help!
Got it.
And a detached force is
already invading Germa.
Kaido?
Don't tell me it's her Hunger Pangs!
Mama's having another Hunger Pang attack!
Wedding cake!
Okay... Brulee, come with me!
He can't be taken down by you guys...
She's craving a wedding cake!
Something's going on outside!
Of course, I will, my brother!
Can you take out Straw Hat and the others?
Shake her off, Kingbaum!
We don't feel anything in Bege's body though!
Hunger Pang attack?!
It's impossible-ju!
Yes, and the wedding cake she wants
is a chocolate chiffon cake!
--No, it's not!
--How can I do that?!
And, you bastards...
What is happening?
I wanna make them pay!
--Run for yourself!
--Hey, Tree!
They drove me like a horse
I don't know. But...
I guess that's enough information for you.
How can you even dream of
getting out of my territory?!
Rush to the Sunny!
and made me help them try to kill Mama!
...the place is in chaos now.
So you need my chiffon cake.
I'm planning to do so...
Could it be...
If we combine my chocolate
and your chiffon cake,
I'm gonna cut off Straw Hat's head!
...that the Whole Cake Chateau is shaking?!
I realized it's necessary to get rid of him
before he really becomes...
Big Mom!
What kind of joke is this?!
we can make a wedding cake
that will satisfy Mama!
Am I dreaming?
Our dream has now been crushed...
...a threat to Mama down the line.
If we let her eat it,
we can stop her attack!
Look, Caesar!
There are ghosts who were left behind
after a mere 66 dream-like days
It's a big mess....
and who can't even set foot
on the soil of their homeland...
Straw Hat!
How did it happen?!
Give me the cake!
I'm sorry, Pudding...
And I can't face them!
I'm leaving this country just like Lola.
Who did it and what did they do?!
Shut up!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I no longer care what happens to Mama
or to this country!
Big Brothers...
Everyone! Get out of the city!
My...
Big Sisters...
...cake!!
Yeah! So just go away, Pudding!
Smoothie!
Judge!
Oh my brothers and sisters!
Run as far as you can!
It's not that...
I can't stop!
Hang on, Kingbaum!
I shouldn't have entrusted a person
Mama!
At a time like this?!
like you with 300-years' worth of
our kingdom's wish for vengeance...
What's the matter, Smoothie?!
My real purpose is...
Everybody! Run!
I hate myself!
Take the Spear of Elbaph!
...not to save Mama or this country, either!
Elbaph?!
It's not working!
Look out for her attack!
Don't tell me it's happening now!
You can drop dead without worrying!
I'll use your scientific technology and...
Mama!!
...I'll make the world peaceful!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Oh, good boy, good boy.
Wedding...
...cake!
It's her Hunger Pangs!
Terrific!
I don't know who did it
but I gotta thank them!
Thunder Bolt!
We didn't have to kill her!
Now,
I need to stop Mama as soon as possible...
Wedding cake!!
the "Emperor of the Sea" Big
Mom Pirates have been...
...annihilated!
Otherwise, he...
...and his friends will get killed!
Luffy and the others are confused by
the shifting ways of the Seducing Woods!
The giant chateau that is bigger
than a mountain crumbles!
Luffy and his clan run straight to the Sunny!
Big Mom flying at their back!
The Seducing Woods before them!
The five Vinsmoke siblings get
into a truly deadly battle
against Big Mom and her clan!
But that's when the real hell begins!
The members of the Big Mom
Pirates fall one after another.
However, in the midst of the scramble,
the untamed warrior Pedro's lightning speed,
With the pressure on in
this no-win situation,
The Emperor of the Sea, Big
Mom, who lost her mind due
Nami hatches a scheme to find a way out!
Meanwhile, an unexpected disaster
has occurred and the fight
In that desperate situation,
Streusen exercises his true ability!
to anger finally shifts
into serious attack mode!
Meanwhile, a single tear
glistens in Pudding's eye.
and Nami's magic cast from her new weapon,
the Sorcerer's Climate Baton, will clear their way!
to escape from the hellish Tea
Party comes to a shocking climax!
With three special Homies at her side,
she closes in on Luffy like the wind!
Luffy and his allies' deadly escape plan enters
another stage!
But is it real or fake?
Her true thoughts are revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Lightning Counterattack! Nami and Zeus the Thundercloud!"
"The Chateau Collapses! The Straw
Hat's Great Escape Begins!"
"The Execution Begins! Luffy's
Allied Forces Are Annihilated?!"
"Pudding's Determination!
Ablaze! The Seducing Woods!"
"The Spear of Elbaph! Onslaught!
The Flying Big Mom!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!