My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom
and getting a fierce attack from her family,
Luffy and the others narrowly
escaped into Bege's body.
Listen carefully, you guys!
This castle is me.
It's strong but not unbreakable.
If they destroy the castle, I'll die.
Then the castle will be gone...
And once you guys get thrown out,
the monsters will prey on you, too!
You're damned if you stay
and damned if you leave.
You're in dire straits!
Then, Bege told Luffy and the others
the only way to survive.
Listen... I'll change back to my human form
keeping you guys inside.
Then, Caesar will carry
me and fly away to escape.
If it goes well, we can get out of trouble.
And the one who volunteered to
escort them in the plan was...
Open the gate!
Gang Bege!
Until you and Caesar Clown fly away into the sky,
we Germa will escort you!
I don't wanna be indebted to this "failure"!
Come on out already!
Bege!
Straw Hat!
Get ready to step out!
Getting ready to step out!
We're ready!
Bege!
I'm gonna deactivate the castle!
Let's go!
Germa! Start attacking!
"Escape From the Tea Party!
Luffy vs. Big Mom!"
He deactivated the castle!
See? We're totally targeted!
There you are, you fleas!
We're dead!
Germa!
Hurry up!
D-Damn...
Why do I have to...
Oh, all right already!
They're gonna fly over the wall!
Don't let them get away!
Stop!
Heavenly...
...Fire!
Reiju!
Forget it, Niji! Yonji!
That's what happens to the weak!
Do your job!
My brother's so unlovely.
That's okay! I'm not gonna get beaten!
What are you doing?!
I said, "You can't go"!
But Sanji's sister is...
Don't go, Luffy.
--You're dead!
--Just surrender without a fight!
That Germa woman...
--What is this?
--M-My neck...
Are you okay?
Big Sis Smoothie!
That poison woman!
Outta my way!
I won't let anyone get away!
First...
I'm gonna start with you!
Little Germa girl!
Gum-Gum...
Diable Jambe, Crosse...
...Elephant Gun!
...Strike!
You told me not to go out!
Yeah, you're not supposed to!
But I am!
Not fair!
Luffy!
Sanji-san!
They got out...
What are you gonna do, you fools?!
--Let's go, Reiju!
--Yeah!
You too!
Why are you guys trying to get away from me?!
Remember what you said to me, Straw Hat?
When you were at the Fish-Man Island?
You said "I'll kick your ass."
That brat who stood up to me
has piqued my interest.
Have it your way, instead
of the Fish-Man Island,
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
Monkey D. Luffy.
I know your name now.
Come to the New World!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business
I want to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your hands -
that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
Remember what you said to me
after you came to this island?
You said,
"We're the ones who'll have the last laugh."
You haven't become the King of the Pirates.
That's all.
I'm gonna pick a fight with you again!
Just because you're the Emperor of the Sea,
don't be cocky!
I'll win Sanji back!
We're the ones who'll have the last laugh!
And now you're trying to run?
You coward!
C... C...
Co...ward...?
--Don't fall for it, Luffy! She's provoking you!
--Just one punch!
Hey! Luffy!
Yeah, I said those things!
Big Mom!
The one that becomes
the King of the Pirates in the end...
...is me!
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Just come back already!
You seem to be preoccupied with
Mama and the others...
But we'll take care of you in her place!
Can we really fly over the wall?!
Don't worry-rero!
Germa 66 will protect us-rero!
They're our evil heroes
who are absolutely invincible!
You're doomed!
Damn Germa...
I'll knock them down directly then!
Leave them to me.
I can handle them single-handedly.
Don't take me lightly!
I'll start with you!
Stealth.
That's my man-rero!
It's not over yet!
Whoa, you guys gotta fight with me.
I'm so excited-rero-rero!
I guess it's my turn. Alright!
Stop buzzing around like a fly!
Are you even trying?
I... I can't ask for more-rero!
Good, Germa!
Keep protecting me like that!
You fools!
Everyone who rebels against Mama...
...will be burned to death by me!
Here comes a terrible one!
The damn Oven, huh?
You two will be the first!
I'll leave the rest to you!
Burn to death?
I'll beat you up before you get a chance!
How arrogant!
Not yet! This is just a
taste of what's to come!
You got too hot!
That insolent mouth again!
Seems like we got away from Oven safely.
Oh, no! Someone's chasing us again!
Is it Daifuku!
You can't get away from here!
We're really dead this time!
I thought I was gonna die!
Am I finally facing someone with a backbone?
Enjoy that relaxed attitude while you can.
Genie-uine...
...Rage Split!
I'll fight you again sometime!
You're a bad loser!
You can't escape!
Give me a break!
I'll squeeze you guys to the last drop!
Make sure to hold her up here!
Don't get in my way! Germa 66!
That's our job.
Damn Germa!
I guess I bought some
time for them to escape.
Anyway, just get us over the wall!
That's the only thing on my mind!
There are still more of them!
If I can make it over the wall,
I can survive!
O-Over the wall...
I'm gonna be free soon!
Lick.
I'm not gonna let them get away.
Candy Wall!
Oh, no!
What?!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Perospero must've done it...
That was our last hope...
It's over... Oh, my freedom...
Shoot! We'll be engulfed in it!
Go back!
No, just go straight!
Black...
...Bug!
Go!
What?! But...
Oops...
You saved us! Germa 66!
Yay! He got through the wall of candy!
Only Germa could've done it!
Go! Caesar!
He's a loser though!
Dammit! I got this far now!
I don't wanna die!
Once I get over the wall, I...
I can be...
...free!!
Th-The hidden undersea treasure,
Tamate Box, is right there...
I can't believe it got stuck
in such a place-nen...
I have no choice. I gotta jump off...
What will you do with the Tamate Box,
Du Feld?
Y-You are...
...Stussy! Were you watching?!
Ow, ow, ow...
But now I can see what's in it...
The hidden undersea treasure...
Let's see how valuable it is!
Flying Finger Pistol...
We, the World Government,
will have the Tamate Box...
FORMERLY: "QUEEN OF THE PLEASURE DISTRICT"
STUSSY, AN INTELLIGENCE AGENT OF CP-"AIGIS" 0
How silly.
Of course, I'll lay the blame on you.
You'll write a story like that,
won't you? Morgans.
She knew I was here!
Sure but can I at least get a scoop on
what's in it?!
Yes, you can take pictures.
You're quick to understand.
That's maybe because you're
a manipulator of information.
No, I run a newspaper! I'll sue you!
--What?!
--No!
Once I take down Kaido...
You're next!
Big Mom!
This is like nothing...
Luffy...
You said, "Just one punch"!
Kaido?
He can't be taken down by you guys...
And, you bastards...
How can you even dream of
getting out of my territory?!
Big Mom!
Our dream has now been crushed...
There are ghosts who were left behind
after a mere 66 dream-like days
and who can't even set foot
on the soil of their homeland...
And I can't face them!
Judge!
I shouldn't have entrusted a person
like you with 300-years' worth of
our kingdom's wish for vengeance...
I hate myself!
It's not working!
You can drop dead without worrying!
I'll use your scientific technology and...
...I'll make the world peaceful!
Thunder Bolt!
The five Vinsmoke siblings get
into a truly deadly battle
against Big Mom and her clan!
Meanwhile, an unexpected disaster
has occurred and the fight
to escape from the hellish Tea
Party comes to a shocking climax!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Execution Begins! Luffy's
Allied Forces Are Annihilated?!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!