My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and the others were trying to escape
from the Tea Party at the risk of their lives.
You were so close.
Sparking...
...Figure!
Just go!
However, while facing the overwhelming
forces of the Big Mom Pirates,
they got caught.
Everyone got defeated?
All right, let's start...
...the executions.
Then, the Tamate Box that Big Mom got
from the Fish-Man Island caused a huge explosion
and the Whole Cake Chateau started crumbling.
Terrific!
I don't know who did it
but I gotta thank them!
We didn't have to kill her!
Now,
the "Emperor of the Sea" Big
Mom Pirates have been...
...annihilated!
"The Chateau Collapses!
The Straw Hat's Great Escape Begins!"
Help!
Where's Reiju? Are they okay?
Damn!
Sky Walk!
Oh, no...
Mama...
Mama!
Run!
It's impossible!
The castle is bigger than the city!
We can't get away!
No one can make it even if they run!
Big Brother!
Calm down.
Big news! This is big news!
Don't you care about your own life?
Oh, yeah! I can't fly!
But...
...if this is the end of the Big Mom Pirates,
it surely is big news.
Hey!
Sanji-kun!
This way! Hurry!
Go! Fast!
This way!
Please hurry up!
Sanji! Luffy!
You're alive!
--Sorry to keep you waiting!
--You're so reckless!
Honestly!
I'm so relieved.
Go, Caesar! Let's run far away!
You don't have to tell me that!
Run away! Run away! Run away!
They're gone.
Mission complete!
Withdraw!
Roger.
Soft and fluffy...
Moist and fluffy...
...life
There's no such thing
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, no...
This is it!
Gour-Metamorphosis!
What the?!
Mama!
That was close.
Heavy cream?
We're gonna get swept away!
--Is this...
--A sponge cake?
What happened?
The Whole Cake Chateau turned into
a real whole cake...
That saved us...
It must be the head chef who did it.
I thought I was gonna die!
Are you okay, Mama?
Cake...
My castle turned into a cake...
The sweets that are created
by Streusen's ability...
...will fill your stomach
but don't taste good.
Mama!
I'm glad that you're okay.
Dammit... My wedding cake...
Cake...
Are you okay?
I need your help!
Alright! You're okay now.
I thought I was gonna die.
I'm gonna be crushed by the cake!
I hear a voice from there!
Hurry and help that person!
Th-That's...
Montd'Or-sama! What happened?!
Why did the Whole Cake Chateau collapse?
What happened to Pudding-sama's wedding?
The city got smashed
and we thought we were finished!
--Shut up!
--What?!
It's not finished yet!
The people who plotted to kill Mama got away!
I'm sure they haven't gone that far yet!
Contact the Tartes of all Totto Land islands!
The Straw Hats and the Firetank Pirates!
Not a single one of them will get away!
NORTHWESTERN PART OF THE WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
I guess this is far enough.
Get out!
Thank you, Bege!
I really thought we were dead...
Don't thank me!
I feel like I did something
good and that makes me sick.
I'm the one who carried you! You jerks!
Shut up, loser!
Do you remember what you did to
those kids at Punk Hazard?
We don't need you anymore so...
Go drop dead.
Hey! How could you speak to
a genius like that?!
I can turn this place into a
poison gas trap if you want!
Here. It's your heart.
It's my... my... my...
You're free, too.
You should've crushed it.
No!
Oh, please!
You should've crushed it.
My heart...
My heart is back!
I'll never see you guys again!
Goodbye, idiots and stupid girl!
--Why did it collapse?
--Hey!
--Yeah, it was sudden.
--What happened?
--Bye!
--I have no idea.
--Hey!
Hey, guys!
Father!
Just as expected, it seems like
Big Mom and her family members have all survived-rero!
The whole fallen castle turned into a cake...
That's Streusen's ability.
He was a mystery to me all along...
I don't think he's just a head chef.
He must be quite a fighter, too.
I thought that was it for
the Big Mom Pirates...
How lucky they are.
But that's okay. The castle collapsed.
I feel a little better.
Goodbye, Straw Hat!
Now, all there's left to do is run, right?
That's all we've been doing...
There were too many obstacles at the beginning.
All right. Let's run then.
We'll part with you guys here, Straw Hat.
What? Really?
We failed to kill Big Mom...
We have no reason to stay together anymore.
That's right.
You guys had better hurry, too.
Even when you get to your ship,
it'll take a day to sail out of Big Mom's territory.
That's true!
Good luck!
Castle Tank!
"The Straw Hats went that way"?
THE STRAW HATS WENT THAT WAY
Don't do such a pathetic thing!
Shut up! We have to survive!
Father!
Why don't you let us say goodbye-rero?!
Yeah, I became friends with Nami!
Don't get too cozy!
This is the beginning of the real escape!
Form two military units, Daifuku.
Okay.
We'll split up into two groups
and chase them!
One group, bring back Straw Hat's head!
And the other, bring back Bege's!
Mama.
Don't worry.
We won't let anyone escape...
Cake...
Its ingredients were carefully selected...
It was going to be the
best wedding cake ever...
I was looking forward to it...
Wedding cake...
Mama?
Where's my wedding cake?!
Not now...
Bring it to me now!
Wedding cake!
My wedding cake!
Where is it?!
Run!
We're in trouble-fa!
My...
Big Bro Opera!
Smoothie! We gotta run-fa!
Wait!
You're responsible for all this!
Why did you lie and say
you killed Straw Hat?!
It's inexcusable to deceive your family!
Even if you run now,
you have nowhere to go!
Take responsibility for it!
You'd better run-fa!
Wedding cake!
Mama!
What? Are you...
...trying to get in my way?!
GERMA KINGDOM
I can't reach Judge-sama or Ichiji-sama!
What happened?
What's that?!
The Big Mom Pirates?!
We'll take over the Germa Kingdom!
Okay, we'll pick up the Shark Submerge
and go straight to the Sunny!
Yeah. Be careful!
We gotta hurry up, too,
and get back to the coast where we landed!
Uh-huh! Let's get out of the territory
before they come for us!
--Hey! I'm leaving, okay?!
--Okay, let's hurry up!
--Straw Hat!
--Let's go!
Hey! Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
I'm going to do this,
that and the other thing!
I'm gonna enjoy my freedom to the fullest!
Goodbye!
What?! Wait a minute!
The Tea Party turned out to be
like that-chocolat?!
Th-The Straw Hats?!
Yeah, it was a disaster!
The wedding and the wedding cake were all ruined!
The execution of the Vinsmokes was foiled!
On top of all that, Bege was betraying us
and plotting to kill Mama!
Damn Bege... I completely respected
him for his great abilities-noir!
But we still don't know anything
about the explosion.
COMPOTE - ELDEST DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Those fools were on the rooftops, too,
so if they did it, they must've been suicidal.
It's not very likely.
But one mystery has been solved-mour.
The thing is during the Tea Party,
all lines of communication
to the venue were jammed-bon!
It was probably Bege and his allies.
Was there anything that you wanted to report?
Well, during the Tea Party, the Sun Pirates
who were staying on the east coast...
That's right! They fled! Grr!
Pekoms?!
All members of the Fish-Man Pirates
packed up and fled!
I see... That's why Jimbei did that.
Jimbei...
...quit the Big Mom Pirates
and joined the Straw Hats.
What?! Jimbei quit?!
Yeah...
And now I know the reason for his action.
He knew Mama'd take out her anger
on his friends.
So to tell his friends about
that and give them time to flee,
Jimbei once reneged on his request to quit.
It's a clever strategy and very Jimbei.
Katakuri!
Our troops are already chasing
Straw Hat and Bege!
Got it.
And a detached force is
already invading Germa.
Okay... Brulee, come with me!
Of course, I will, my brother!
Can you take out Straw Hat and the others?
I wanna make them pay!
They drove me like a horse
and made me help them try to kill Mama!
I'm planning to do so...
I'm gonna cut off Straw Hat's head!
I realized it's necessary to get rid of him
before he really becomes...
...a threat to Mama down the line.
Everyone! Get out of the city!
Smoothie!
Run as far as you can!
At a time like this?!
What's the matter, Smoothie?!
Everybody! Run!
Don't tell me it's happening now!
Wedding...
...cake!
It's her Hunger Pangs!
Wedding cake!!
Luffy and his clan run straight to the Sunny!
But that's when the real hell begins!
The Emperor of the Sea, Big
Mom, who lost her mind due
to anger finally shifts
into serious attack mode!
With three special Homies at her side,
she closes in on Luffy like the wind!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Spear of Elbaph! Onslaught!
The Flying Big Mom!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!