My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and his allies were backed into a corner
but the Whole Cake Chateau's collapse
let them make an escape.
I don't know who did it
but I gotta thank them!
We didn't have to kill her!
Now,
the "Emperor of the Sea" Big
Mom Pirates have been...
...annihilated!
However, Big Mom and her family members
were saved by Streusen's ability.
Mama...
Mama!
Luffy and his clan who got away from
the Whole Cake Chateau...
...parted ways with Bege's group
and headed for the Sunny.
All right. Let's run then.
We'll part with you guys here, Straw Hat.
Meanwhile, Katakuri and the others
formed pursuit units.
We'll split up into two groups
and chase them!
One group, bring back Straw Hat's head!
And the other, bring back Bege's!
A detached force is already invading Germa.
Okay... Brulee, come with me!
However, in the midst of that...
Everyone! Get out of the city!
Smoothie!
Run as far as you can!
At a time like this?!
"The Spear of Elbaph!
Onslaught! The Flying Big Mom!"
Where is the wedding cake?!
The Queen's Hunger Pangs!
She's having another attack
in such a short period of time!
She remembered the wedding cake
that was destroyed, which she couldn't eat!
What's in Mama's hand?!
It's too late.
Oh, no!
Big Bro Opera!
Hey! Wake up!
Don't tell me she took your lifespan!
Brother!
Big Bro Opera stood in Mama's way
to stop her!
Nobody get close to Mama!
We have to do something...
Where is it?!
The wedding cake!
All of you, hurry up!
They'll come chase us soon!
Nami!
You're riding on Jimbei's shoulders!
Quit bossing us around!
That's okay!
Because Nami-san is so cute!
So cute and delicate...
Pursuers from the Big Mom Pirates
will surely come! We must hurry!
Count on me!
Cutting through this area and
the Seducing Woods is the shortest way to the Sunny!
You know what to do!
The only way to stop Mama's Hunger Pang attack
is to give her the food she craves!
What we need is... the wedding cake!
Where is the head chef?!
He's the only person who can rebake the cake!
W-Well... Streusen-sama...
...saved everyone's life but...
...he himself missed a landing big time...
He needs several days to recover!
If it goes on like this,
Sweet City will be destroyed. Grr!
What can we do to stop Mama?!
We can't let her rampage here in the capital!
Where is it?!
Does he...
I guess he's got an idea!
That's our Perospero-sama! Grr!
Mama! The wedding cake...
...isn't gone!
We kept a spare cake on standby, Mama!
Big Bro Peros!
No! What are you talking about?!
I-It's made from carefully
selected ingredients...
And it's meltingly delicious...
It's the best wedding cake ever!
I really want you to have it but, believe or not,
the Straw Hats stole it and ran!
They're now heading to the southwest coast
trying to get away!
Wedding...
...cake...
That's right! They got it! Lick!
I assume she's listening
to me to some extent.
If she goes after Straw Hat,
it's like killing two birds with one stone!
Can he talk her into it?
If you're lying,
you'll pay with your lifespan!
Zeus!
Yes, Mama!
Wedding cake!
I'm in trouble!
Even if Mama gets the Straw Hats,
they don't have the cake!
--What should I do?!
--I thought that was pretty smart but...
When Mama comes back,
I'll be dead!
But you bought some time!
We've got to make the cake now
or this island will be over, too!
Well, it's impossible...
Think about it, Smoothie.
How many days do you think even the head chef, Streusen,
needed to make that cake?
The rare ingredients that we collected
by robbing other countries are gone!
And the person who can bake it is in a coma!
He can't make the cake!
What's more troubling is that
Mama hasn't even tasted the cake!
So this time, we have to provide...
The never-before-eaten delicious cake
which has been built up in Mama's head.
Who can make such a thing?!
This is bad.
At the very least this
island will be destroyed!
What lies ahead of that is... unknown.
Do you want me to help you?!
Pudding!
--Oh, Pudding-sama!
--Pudding-sama!
The wedding cake was a
chocolate chiffon cake!
I can make as good a chocolate flavor as the head chef,
if not better!
And Big Sis Chiffon is an expert of
chiffon cakes!
Together, we can make that cake!
Are you sure, Pudding?!
But Chiffon is married to Bege
who is our enemy now!
I'll make her do it!
There's the evil Pudding!
What?! Pudding-sama is acting like a thug!
The truth is the ingredients for the cake...
...were gathered together at
Chocolat Town, Cacao Island,
the gateway to our territory.
So there are actually extra supplies of
the rare ingredients!
Big Bro Peros!
Once Mama eliminates the Straw Hats,
lead her to Chocolat Town!
I'll end the matter!
You sure?! That's so helpful, Pudding!
I got insulted by Sanji!
What a beautiful eye!
If Mama can wipe them out...
I have to give her a reward.
Just you wait!
Sanji!
What's wrong?
My heart just thumped...
I guess some cutie is talking about me
as always...
I see the Seducing Woods!
Are we gonna go into that forest again?!
I hope we'll be okay.
Hey, what's that?
No, stop, Kin-chan!
Are you okay, Kin-chan?
Ow, ow, ow!
The seam hurts-ju, Lady Tree...
I'm sorry... But they'll stick together soon.
Just like us!
Ow, ow, ow! Take it easy.
What? No! How?!
Hey!
You're alive, Kingbaum!
Good to see you again!
Tree!
G... G...
Go away!
I'll make you pay, you bastards!
--Kin-chan!
--Lady Tree!
Don't look back! Go straight!
Dammit!
Oh? Nami, I thought Lola's Vivre Card
was taken away from you.
Yes, they took it.
But I cut in half just in case.
That's smart!
This is fast!
Since he's the master of the Seducing Woods,
he can travel a straight line!
All right!
Keep going to the Sunny at full speed!
Go!
You guys are like the plague-ju!
Get out of this country already-ju!
Did you say something?
Do as Nami-san says!
Our targets are right there!
Take them down!
Yeah!
Look behind us! Enemies!
Charge!
Yeah!
Go faster, Kingbaum!
I'm going as fast as I can-ju!
If you get caught, I'll rip that seam!
You're terrible!
Something passed over our heads!
--That voice...
--No way!
What?!
Wedding cake!
Big Mom!
Give it to me!
GERMA KINGDOM
Take them down!
The Clone Soldiers are created to be
fighters who don't fear death.
We, the Big Mom Pirates, will
take that military power over!
A room where they manufacture Clone Soldiers!
I found it!
Humph! A throne without a king...
It's so sad...
Break it down immediately!
There is a king.
You're...
Wh-What the hell?!
Stealth!
You guys aren't allowed beyond this point!
You bushy-haired freak!
Burn! Burn! Burn!
Burn to ashes!
Don't push your luck!
Thank you for doing whatever you like
in our kingdom!
Oh, no...
How dare you make a fool of us!
The Big Mom Pirates!
You bastards are totally unforgivable!
We'll pay you back with interest.
Big Mom!
Luffy, control yourself!
--Shut up!
--No!
Let go of me, Jimbei!
Going back to the Sunny is our objective!
Don't forget!
Big Mom is nearing!
What brings Mama to the front line?!
And look at her...
She doesn't seem like herself!
Don't tell me it's her Hunger Pangs!
Wedding cake!
Shake her off, Kingbaum!
It's impossible-ju!
--No, it's not!
--How can I do that?!
--Run for yourself!
--Hey, Tree!
Rush to the Sunny!
Straw Hat!
Give me the cake!
Shut up!
I don't know what you're talking about!
My...
...cake!!
Hang on, Kingbaum!
Take the Spear of Elbaph!
Elbaph?!
Look out for her attack!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Big Mom flying at their back!
The Seducing Woods before them!
With the pressure on in
this no-win situation,
Nami hatches a scheme to find a way out!
Meanwhile, a single tear
glistens in Pudding's eye.
But is it real or fake?
Her true thoughts are revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pudding's Determination!
Ablaze! The Seducing Woods!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!