My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
After failing to kill Big Mom,
In order to escape from the Whole Cake Island,
Luffy and his allies finally reached the Sunny.
After failing to kill Big Mom,
After failing to kill Big
Mom, Luffy and his allies
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and his allies escaped
from the Whole Cake Chateau
Luffy and his allies
escaped from the Whole Cake Chateau
Luffy and his allies escaped
from the Whole Cake Chateau
and continue heading towards the Sunny.
However, Sweet General Katakuri and the others
who were there waiting blocked their way!
Big Mom chases after them
in the middle of her Hunger Pangs attack.
Wedding...
Ikoku Sovereignty!
It's the coast! Get to the Sunny!
...cake!!
While Big Mom closes in
Meanwhile, in order to take back the Sunny
Bring...
and the grand fleet of Tarte ships led by Amande
narrows its encirclement,
Maybe because she didn't get to eat
the cake at the wedding!
that has been captured
by the Big Mom Pirates,
...the cake!
Brook and Chopper continue a perilous fight.
Perospero covered the Sunny with candy
and restrained its movement.
Luffy and the others were running desperately
while shaking off attacks from the family...
Meanwhile, Brook and Chopper
arrived at the Sunny first,
However, due to Perospero's ability,
they have been coated with candy.
They fended off the onslaught of Big Mom
who is experiencing a Hunger Pangs attack,
but it was the Big Mom Pirates
who were waiting for them.
Did you see the power of Candy Wave?!
Gum-Gum...
Finally, just as Luffy and the
others who got through the
and entered the Seducing Woods
where Kingbaum rules...
I'm a perfectionist!
Seducing Woods come close to the Sunny...
Do you want to fight?
Of course!
Seducing Woods!
...Eagle Bazooka!
To let the Sunny flee, Pedro...
Candy Maiden...
We'll save the Sunny!
Stop them!
Roger said, "Everyone has their own turn"!
Diable Jambe!
...Decoration!
Pudding asked Sanji to make a
Big Mom has Luffy and the others
cornered even more by using the Homies.
wedding cake since it's the only
thing that can stop Big Mom.
What are you talking about?
"Before the Dawn!
Pedro, the Captain of the Guardians!"
Flambage Shot!
This is my turn!
That way, we can distract her attention from you!
So hang in there until that time!
It turned back to the annoying forest.
But they suffered even more onslaughts
from Big Mom.
This will break all of your-gara magic spells, right?
No one can get through here!
Sanji was about to part ways with
Luffy and the others for the time being but...
Go around and get to the ship!
Duck!
Tree!
No, run straight!
Bombs?!
Kingbaum...
Stop, you fool!
What are you thinking?!
What are you doing right there?!
Nami-san!
Goodbye.
Gum-Gum...
Get away!
Wedding cake!
"A Coincidental Reunion!
Sanji and the Lovestruck Evil Pudding!"
"Save the Sunny!
Fighting Bravely! Chopper and Brook!"
...Red Hawk!
So you need my chiffon cake.
That's right.
Ikoku Sovereignty!
If we combine my chocolate
and your chiffon cake,
Is it a flame?!
We're almost there.
we can make a wedding cake
that will satisfy Mama!
I know!
If we let her eat it,
we can stop her attack!
Pedro!!
I need to stop Mama as soon as possible...
There it is!
Enough already...
Listen!
It's the Sunny!
You-gara guys must go forward!
That was close.
I'm glad that it's safe!
Everyone's okay, right?
Otherwise, he...
...and his friends will get killed!
Let's go! The Sunny is waiting for us
at the coast!
"I'll Be Back!
Luffy, Deadly Departure!"
Luffy and the others are already there,
it seems!
Wait! Their course is off.
Let's hurry up!
"A Lightning Counterattack!
Nami and Zeus the Thundercloud!"
Rabian, descend again!
Fly straight from the previous spot to the sea coast!
Roger!
Luffy-kun and everyone!
Pedro!
Hey, guys!
Wait! It's not that way!
There's a wall ahead of you!
Don't tell me Big Bro Peros is...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What? Pudding? She's the nice Pudding!
Pedro!
I thought we were going straight.
SOUTHWEST COAST - SEDUCING WOODS
Oh, no! Mama and Perospero-sama...
The dawn of the world will come before long!
Of course, we've been fooled.
Everyone! The sea coast is this way!
...Got involved in the explosion!
Okay, let's go!
As long as Big Mom is having a Hunger Pangs attack,
all you can do is run!
We won't let you go!
Hunger Pangs? What is that?
Why are they...
Leave them to me!
...On board our Sunny?
It's a tantrum!
Memory Filament!
I'm sorry. Your friends aren't here. Lick!
The candy of his special ability
is starting to melt!
Until she gets to eat what she craves...
she keeps rampaging without discretion!
Flashback!
I can't believe he sacrificed himself...
Wedding...
How dare you, Pedro!
Zeus Breeze...
Oh, I've got to go grocery shopping...
...cake!!
His-teia ability is just like Luffy's!
Big Brother hit me!
...Tempo!
She's almost unconscious...
It's time to walk my dog.
My son is missing.
Has anyone seen him?
What she craves this time
seems to be a wedding cake!
What's going on?
I thought I was gonna die!
Anyway, let's go before it's too late!
Are you guys okay?!
What's going on?
Maybe because she didn't get to eat
the cake at the wedding!
Memories of the former owners
of those souls that've been
infused into the Homies...
Luffy! You shouldn't have ruined the cake!
...are flashing back temporarily.
No, Carrot!
While they're confused,
they're not under Mama's control!
Let go of me! Let me get back to where Pedro was!
Maybe he's still alive!
Wedding...
So Luffy-kun and the others can
get out of the forest now!
But the plan succeeded!
...cake!
No! You saw that explosion...
He saved us!
And you don't often get to eat
a delicious cake like that!
I see. Thank you, Pudding-chan!
We've had no chance to survive
up until now!
Here she comes!
Why?! Since when were you there, Sanji...
Don't tell me Luffy and the others are...
You have to understand Pedro's reasoning!
Please!
Were you eating during the mission?!
...san!
Well, since a short while ago.
What should we do, Luffy?!
We're surrounded!
--What?!
--Didn't you notice?!
Is that...
Ready to fly, Nami?!
I ate it, too! That was so good!
Seems like Mama finished them off with Zeus.
Mama'll be here.
Now, Pudding-chan,
let's rush to Chocolat Town.
Yes, it's all set!
Anyway, hurry up!
I'm sure the Sunny isn't that far from here!
Chopper! Brook! Are you with us?
Luffy! Kick Katakuri off of the ship!
G-Get off and swim, idiot!
Lick!
We'll try to set sail somehow!
Your eye is beautiful even when you're mad...
Oh?
The Straw Hat and his allies are dead.
But in this forest,
you can't be sure if you're going straight!
I got it!
Jimbei!
Yes, they're with us!
--This way!
--Okay!
Now if we can lead Mama to Pudding
and let her eat the cake, everything'll be okay.
Set sail, you guys!
Are you okay, Pudding?
That bastard!
He must've come through the mirror dimension!
I-I'm fine... D-D-Don't mess with me!
Things are going smoothly.
O-Or I'll kill you, Sanji...
If we waste this moment...
...san!
Listen! Everyone has their own turn.
Oh! It's the end of the forest!
we'd make Pedro ashamed of us!
All right! Let's go straight to Cacao Island!
We'll get out of here no matter what!
He's saying such a thing but
they'll be fine, right?
Is this really the right way?!
Yeah, I'm sure they will!
Oh! Look!
Wedding cake!
That river looks familiar!
Lick! I guess your friends are dead...
Brook! Chopper!
At any price!
Is that your ship?
The Sunny must be right across the river!
That's never the case
for Luffy-san and the others!
Why is everyone...
Yeah, it's getting attacked.
I don't wanna get involved with
Mama's Hunger Pangs.
I guess they were ambushed...
Wait a minute!
...so heated up?!
That's right! They'll be back!
Lick.
Oh, no! Our big brothers are there!
And what are you two gonna do?
Armament Hardening!
Go away, Big Mom Pirates!
Even if you can take back the ship at the risk of your lives,
no one'll return.
If I remember right,
that bridge was broken!
Our brothers are attacking
Sanji-san's friends...
Carrot!
Gum-Gum...
You're right...
Hmph! Your friends are dead!
If the forest is our enemy,
we can't trust anything!
...Hawk Gatling!
That will teach ya!
They're no match for my brothers!
If you wanna get out of here on that submarine,
I don't mind letting you go, if it's just the two of you.
They're trying to fool us...
Your friends will be swallowed by the sea!
So I'm sure they're shifting the landscape
to confuse us...
What are you saying, Pudding?!
Oh, no! That's not what I meant to say!
Come on! Is that all you've got?!
In other words,
Oh, we appreciate your concern.
Ow, ow, ow...
this isn't the place we think it is!
Why?! I'm using Haki but I can't hit him...
Don't hold back! Try to strike harder!
What do you wanna do?
Go back to the ship?
You can master swordsmanship
after you dedicate all of yourself!
No, I'll come along with Pudding-chan.
But...
What?
Meanwhile, around the Juice River
in Sweet City...
...no thanks.
Are you sure?
We'll keep on going then!
Kung Fu Point!
Yeah, we don't need to worry about them.
Oops...
Oh, there it is! The Juice River!
Get up! Get on your feet, Carrot!
And take the sword!
Get off of the ship, you bastards!
It's our Sunny!
Instead, let's get started...
The Shark Submerge is moored there!
Until you-gara become a full-fledged swordswoman,
I'll teach you with all my might!
So that's the river...
...on the cake that can make Big Mom unconscious
as soon as possible!
Do you want to fight?
Of course!
What?!
She-gara have no aptitude for swords.
The river is filled with heavy cream!
We'll save the Sunny!
Pedro! It's none of your business.
I guess you want to die. Lick!
Oh, it smells good!
Chopper! Brook! Are you all right?!
Carrot will become a strong swordswoman
under my guidance.
Stay with us!
It looks delicious! I'm gonna eat!
There is more than one way to get stronger.
There must be a way that's better suited for her.
You're quite tough...
It's so sweet!
How could you hold out this long
against these many people?
I can't believe the debris from
the crumbled Whole Cake Chateau flew this far...
Where is it?
No, no! You're too soft, Pedro!
Lick.
Training should push you to your limits
and break you!
The cake!
Let's get started! A fully-standing show!
Yeah!
That's so annoying.
Mmm! Mmm! It's so good!
If you think everyone's like you-gara,
you're totally wrong.
Go to hell!
Now, what should we do...
Carrot.
This is it!
What?!
Kung Fu Point!
Don't get shocked by the unexpected.
I mean, Chopper-san!
Can I take her-gara under my care?
What?
That was so powerful!
Of course, only if she's interested.
I think...
My Climate Baton can't generate
such strong lightning!
Die!
...Luffy and his crew are...
Yum-yum!
With that much power...
...the ones who our tribe
and the Kozuki Family
have been awaiting for centuries....
How's that?!
--Where's Big Mom?
--She must've been hit directly!
The ones who'll lead the
world to the new dawn!
What an interesting exotic animal...
We have to escape from Big Mom
of course...
She's probably in that giant hole!
What is this?
For centuries?!
Did we happen to take down Big Mom?!
But we gotta do something about the situation
or we won't reach the Sunny!
Get off the ship!
Take a fighting pose.
Oh, yeah!
Isn't there any way?
That's more suited for you-gara.
Lola's Vivre Card won't help us anymore...
Yeah, since Mama herself is right behind us!
Hey, Montd'Or, can you hear me?
That gives you all the more reason
to keep feeding him, Nami.
You-gara can float in the air for quite a while.
Yes, I can hear you.
What is it?
If you take advantage of that and your Electro,
you-gara can acquire your own strength and way of fighting.
Surround the southwest coast of the
Whole Cake Island with battleships.
Yeah... Zeus!
You have to keep your
eyes on the prize, baby.
Where's this sound coming from?
Roger, Big Bro Peros.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Clank.
Attack me. I'll be your training partner.
Surround the coastline-soir?
Not that I have eyes myself.
It's...
It's delicious! So delicious!
All right!
I guess Straw Hat and the
others are still alive.
If we let Zeus go back to Mama,
we'll have no chance to escape from her.
What?!
Mama was pursuing on land
and Katakuri-sama was waiting at the ship,
Wedding...!
You're right.
You fight quite well against
the Chess Peacekeepers, skeleton...
Hey! Give me more!
Big Mom's voice?!
I thought so...
but are they still alive-bon?
Cake!
Yeah, they're so persistent.
Because I am...
Is she alive?!
Come back, Zeus!
I thought I couldn't become strong.
...Soul King!
Tarte of Nuts Island, respond!
I can't believe there's a suited skill for me.
Enemies keep coming out of the mirror...
This is Amande on Nuts Island.
She's not someone who'll get beaten
that easily...
Surround the southwest coast.
Thanks to you, Pedro.
Don't let Straw Hat and his clan get away
at any cost!
If we're too slow, she'll catch up!
It's the mirror in Nami and Robin's room.
Will they get mad if we break it?
It doesn't matter how you fight.
She's climbing up!
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Oh, no! I'm gonna get scolded!
Roger.
If we can break it, let's break it
and apologize later.
Hey!
Prometheus!
Is the hole too deep for her to climb out?
Why do you disobey Mama's orders, Zeus?!
Everyone has their own turn.
Coup de...
Who are you gonna apologize to? Lick.
Let's run while she's at it!
What?
Yeah. While Big Mom can't move!
Coup de Burst!
This ship can leap 1 km ahead!
Zeus! Look at me!
You saw the lightning earlier, right?
Carrot...
You'll have your turn, too.
That was pretty intense.
If we try to set sail normally,
the ship will be sunk by Big Mom!
The exquisite Weather Egg
filled with juicy thunderclouds!
No, she's already on her way...
It shows how mad Mama is.
I don't quite understand
but we can escape that way, right?
I bet there aren't even bones left of
Straw Hat and the others.
Wow! That looks great!
--The ground is...
--No way!
Yeah!
Whoa, wait, Zeus!
Okay! Let's bet on it!
No one will return to this ship.
Big Mom is coming!
Hey, Sun!
I'm saying I'm going to
show some mercy on you.
How dare you...
Don't worry...
There you are!
There's no stopping for Big Mom
when she has a Hunger Pangs attack!
I know you can do it...
No matter how much you try,
our soldiers will emerge endlessly.
...burn up the tree guy!
Carrot! You-gara go help them
get ready to sail!
Wedding...
Gum-Gum...
--What?
--Hurry up!
...Hawk Gatling!
And you guys will use up all of your energy
eventually.
...cake!
Okay!
I'm sure you can...
If you submit right here, right now,
I'll at least spare your life...
Oh no! Run!
Wedding...
Is it there?
The wedding cake?!
Just let it go already.
That's our Luffy!
No... The ground's gonna crack open!
Electrical...
What a useless conversation.
Here she comes!
We got sick and tired of answering to
that line of yours...
Hey, Brook, Chopper!
Stay with me!
As long as I'm here, I won't let you set sail!
Run!
Even if we can make it out of here,
it's meaningless if you guys end up dead...
I just need you to get off of the ship.
What the?!
B-Bring...
Don't think...
The Sunny is ours!
...the cake!
...that you can beat me with just that!
We spotted the Straw Hats
at the southwest coast!
Do you really wanna fight me?
Oh! Ow, ow, ow!
This is Minister Amande from
the Tarte of Nuts Island...
If the Color of Arms doesn't work,
it'll prove more troubling than Logia!
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
We'll corner Straw Hat and the others.
I'm gonna burn you all to death!
Everyone has their own turn.
Ow, ow! It's hot! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I know you can do it...
I'm sure you can...
I see...
It's terrible.
Wait, Pedro!
Battleships are coming from the sea,
and Big Mom from the land.
Here I go!
Come back, Zeus!
Seems like you really
don't value your life...
I will! I will, but...
Don't go!
We're totally stuck in the middle!
All right.
I wanna eat just one more juicy thundercloud!
I'll kill you with my own hands.
You...
Lick.
Nami! We have to get going!
Jimbei!
Cross the bridge now, you all!
I know! But I have to load
two more barrels of cola!
Okay!
Spear Wave!
Okay, baby?
I'm sorry, Pedro...
I'll do the rest so you go prepare
for the Coup-de-something!
Cake...
Murasame!
You took the trouble to teach me...
Where is it?
All right, I'll leave it to you then!
Did it work?!
I can't believe I'm completely helpless...
Of course!
My...
...wedding cake!
He's merely a mass of compressed flames!
I have to live up to the expectations you had...
that made you sacrifice yourself for our escape...
He could just be considered
a big talking fire!
You bastard...
Pedro... I'm sorry...
Brook!
I see the sea coast ahead!
For now, I want you to call me...
Hurry up!
Oh, the Shark Submerge!
...Soul King!
We made it!
But, is Pudding really on our side now?!
Candy Wave!
Get your foot off of Carrot!
I don't know! We shouldn't lower our guard
until we get out of their territory!
I'm so happy!
Chopper-san, well done!
I think we can make it!
Carrot! Leave him to me!
This is the real scream of my soul!
We're almost there!
It's filled with cream in there, too!
Luffy...
What was that?!
I'm gonna eat it all!
Soul King!
Candy?!
Oh, no! We can't use Coup de Burst like this!
Cake!
I hope you're strong enough to kick me out...
A skeleton with a strange skill, huh?
I won't let you get away!
Don't stop!
Hey, Zeus!
--It's strange...
--What's wrong?
How could you do that?!
We'll set sail! I'm the captain of this ship!
What's wrong?!
I haven't seen Mama's children
who were with her a while ago...
This is serious!
The Sunny has been caught by candy!
Gum-Gum Elephant Gun!
How long are you gonna keep fighting?
Your friends have already died.
What?!
Why did you get us involved?!
Don't tell me...!
I'm sorry... It wasn't my intention!
Of course, I'll keep fighting
until I get the ship back...
Did you see the power of Candy Wave?!
I don't care about your intention!
Don't ever be inattentive again!
Are they...?!
MOBILE
I'm a perfectionist!
KATO
Otherwise, I'll have no words of apology
to my friends when they get here!
COMPO
Be prepared, Straw Hats!
Oh, there he is!
Yes, I know...
--Nami!
--I know!
LAURIN
This Seducing Woods will be...
But those were so delicious...
Those thundercloud eggs.
Okay! While they're at it...
TABLET
Your graveyard!
What a waste of energy!
What should we do?
HIGH-FAT
The sails can stay like that.
Drop dead!
Turn Brook and Chopper back,
as well as the ship, candy jerk!
What?! I can't believe they got ahead of us!
Huh?!
Soul...
Towards the northwest, Coup de Burst!
Hey, do you really understand?!
Mama's orders are absolute!
The Homies must've shifted the landscape!
...Parade!
Azimuth: 45 degrees to northwest!
Pitch: 35 degrees!
If nothing is done...
Cake!
I know...
I've been frozen?!
Three cola barrels are loaded.
Agitate the energy!
It's either being destroyed by Mama...
Give it to me!
...or being sunk by the cannons!
My wedding cake!
Ice Burn!
We're closed in from both sides...
What is this vibration?!
Oh, no!
Then, there's only one thing to do!
By shaking the cola barrels up and down,
we're tapping the energy of the carbonation!
Yeah, let's kick their asses!
Dodge!
I see...
Either way, you have no chance to survive!
I certainly can't attack others
If you do that.
Damn...
That was close!
This way, you can't stop it
even if you know what'll happen!
Thank you, Jimbei!
Everyone, be careful!
Another one's coming!
Those fools... I won't let them get away...
I'll avenge Big Bro Peros!
We managed to make it to the sea.
All ships, prepare to fire towards the enemy ship!
Cake!
How can you keep standing on ice?!
Adjust the angle of elevation!
All we have to do now is get to the Sunny.
Duck!
Shark-chan, come back!
I'm a...
Mama!
Chopper-san, could you grab it over there?
Let's pull it close to the Sunny before they start attacking!
...reindeer!
I thought you were a raccoon dog!
It's so sweet - I'm very happy!
No, I'm not!
What? I don't like it.
It's sticky all over...
All right!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
You can't get away from me...
See? The helm is slippery...
Straw Hat!
Watch out! Move out of my way, Fish-san!
Good job!
Thanks to you!
Brook! Isn't that a mermaid?!
Oh, please! We're almost to the Sunny!
What?! Mermaid-san?!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Let's pull it close before Big Mom comes!
I mean, a merman!
The forest is... What happened?!
Beast Sword - Karajishi!
Oh...
Wedding cake!
Is everyone okay?!
Jimbei-san, thank you!
Rabian, go faster!
What is he doing? Fishing, maybe?
Tie the rope to the bar!
Okay!
Damn!
Run! If we get caught,
we're all going to die!
Give us a hand, Nami!
I don't care anymore...
Sorry! I'm not done here yet!
I'm sorry, Big Sis, for asking this...
Let's get closer!
Give me the cake!
Hey, do you know how much my bounty is?
I'm not interested...
That's okay! It's been a long time
since we made a cake together!
What? Brook!
Forget it.
It's 700 million.
Brook!
Boy! What do you want?!
You can't get away, Straw Hat!
On top of that...
I'm not someone who a weakling
like you can defeat!
--She's coming...
--...This way!
Come on, Prometheus!
Lick!
Yes, Mama!
You're going?! Are you kidding?!
This will be the last time we talk...
Bege! Didn't I tell you?!
The Straw Hats saved my young sister, Lola's life!
Nami! Not yet?!
Get away!
Luffy!
I know! A little more to go!
Heavenly...
Be careful with my brother and Mama!
Aim at its bow!
Run, guys!
But, Chiffon, it's dangerous! I'm worried!
Go away! No, my hands are slipping!
...Fire!
He's right-rero!
You must escape with us-rero!
Okay! Fire!
Oh, I'm sorry. That was too loud...
We can't leave without you, Ma'am!
You escaped death. Lick.
Come back, Chiffon!
Dangerous?! Yes, I'm fully aware of it!
It's pointless to die here!
The dawn of the new world is coming!
You're Pedro, aren't you?
I saw you five years ago, too...
I have to go back!
"Thank you for saving Lola."
It's so easy to just say the words!
You're so handsome.
Whether you really mean it or not will be proven
when the person you're indebted to is in trouble!
I'll reduce it to 50 years.
Go on with your life.
You're right, but...
Oopsy!
--She's coming...
--...This way!
At that time,
That's how you do your duty,
right, darling?
if you hadn't sacrificed your left eye,
you would've been killed for sure...
Nami! Not yet?!
I know! A little more to go!
If something happens to me,
Okay! Fire!
Was that how bad you wanted to survive?
please take care of...
You silly rabbit!
All right...
Are you tired now, Soul King?
...Pez for me!
How old are you now?
Garchu!
I'm 27...
Gavotte...
They're firing at us one after another!
You've had 50 years of your lifespan drained
so it's like you've lived 77 years already.
...Bond en Avant!
Stop!
--We're in trouble!
--Nami!
Chiffon!
It's not working...
Ma'am!
The cola energy has reached its maximum!
Yes!
Now, I wonder how many years
you can expect to live...
Now! Go!
Big Bro Tablet!
Brook!
You'd better pay attention!
Coup de...
I at least wanna choose where to die myself.
I have to save Nami and the others
and return to my family!
Are you okay, Brook?!
Wait!
Don't worry... I can still fight...
By the way,
Big Sis! There he is!
Diable Jambe!
you were the captain of the Nox Pirates...
Pudding? Were you listening?
What's wrong?!
You've cut down quite a lot of our troops...
"Nox" means "night," doesn't it?
S... Sanji-san is...
We'll bring you guys down
and take back the Sunny!
Flambage Shot!
Wait!
That sounds rather negative.
S... S...
Big Mom!
They say, "Every night comes to an end."
You're so naive...
I'll make you face reality.
Sanji...
Oh, no! We gotta get going!
And...
Huh? What?
..."nox" means the same as...
S...
I can't use the Coup de Burst!
Gum-Gum...
..."before the dawn"...
S...
--Nami!
--What's the matter? I thought it'd fly!
Sanji's there! That fool!
If I can serve as a foundation for the
Huh? What the...
I think cola has leaked due to the impact!
Say what?!
My leg...
new dawn of the world
that the Master and the others are hoping for,
...Eagle Bazooka!
What?!
Damn! I can't move!
that's what I want the most.
I know you guys have it!
Chopper-san!
I think I have enough time for that...
--They're coming!
--Let's bring them down!
Straw Hat!
No problem!
Brook!
You once said that "before the dawn"
and "nox" meant the same thing...
She's coming up!
You fools...
Those candies will slowly
seep into your bodies.
Shark Brick Fist!
Can't we do something?!
Good job, you guys! Let me have a go, too!
But the only thing that's waiting for you
is the eternal darkness called death.
It's no use! Just run!
Jimbei, wait!
Thanks, Jimbei!
I'll go load cola so could you take my place?
Please!
No...
Don't mention it! Keep luring Zeus!
Give it to me!
It's no use.
You won't be able to move from there...
What?!
Okay!
Don't worry. We have a Tone Dial
with an audio recording of Franky for these occasions.
It's you again...
So persistent...
Chopper-san!
Straw Hats!
Th-This?!
--What?
--Pudding! Chiffon!
Don't panic, don't panic.
It's not over yet!
Oh, Pudding! What's wrong with you?!
You fooled us!
Man...
Franky's navigation system, activate.
What kind of positive thinking did you have
to believe you could take the ship back?
To stop Mama's Hunger Pangs attack...
O... Okay...
There it comes! Gather up!
See? We should've tied her up
in the first place!
In order to catch you guys,
Second round, prepare to fire!
Maintain your aim.
To stop Mama's...
But why's Chiffon with her?!
I thought she ran away with Bege's group!
we're mobilizing all of our soldiers
across the island
--To stop...
--Wanna fight?!
Oh, good... Seems like it's not broken.
to set up surrounding nets at various places.
No, I don't! Listen to me!
It's just one of the barrels fell on the floor...
You have nowhere to run.
Pudding-chan, you're okay!
All ships are prepared to fire for a second round!
That idiot who lost his life
by the deadly roulette that day...
I'm glad that your pretty self isn't hurt!
The difference in power is obvious!
Fire!
So lovely! So lovely!
They fired again!
Pudding, get it together!
Chopper-san, let's bring them down no matter what
until the cola energy is filled up!
Damn!
Was his name Zepo?
I... I can't even transform!
I'll let you see him in hell now!
Yeah!
Free Chopper-san!
Die!
Oh, no! Mama's coming!
Idiot! It's too late!
Mama!
So that's the Roger Pirates' ship...
The Oro Jackson!
We have no time!
Pudding, get right to the point!
When the barrel of cola is loaded,
push the lever forward!
It's punishment for standing against me!
Okay!
I'll turn you into a Candyman and lick you!
All right!
Sanji-san...
Lick!
Pudding-chan...
The candy will coat your whole body,
I'll save you at any price...
It's starting to move! I gotta hurry!
fill you up inside and stop your breathing.
You-gara...
And with that agony,
Price...
...have no right to call
my partner an "idiot"!
Where is it...? The wedding cake!
it only takes three minutes
to kill the target!
P...
What are you doing?!
Don't bite our Sunny!
Roger! Oden-sama! Take me along!
No way...
Pathetic! You fools!
You're not gonna make it!
And then, it's complete!
A sweet corpse - Candyman!
Damn! If it goes on like this...
Even if you escape by ship,
Hey, everyone! Don't get separated!
Mama will chase you to the farthest sea
and sink you to the ocean floor!
Idiot! Go away!
Or we'll never see each other again!
I'll do anything! Take me with you!
Big Bro, I'm here to save you!
Okay!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Carrot! Hang on. Can you get up?
Chopper-san!
Luffy, stop Carrot!
What did you say, you bastard?!
Kid, you still have to wait.
Stop!
All right!
Yes... Nami, thank you.
That is not it, Pudding!
What are you talking about?!
I'm not a kid, I'm Pedro!
You're right! You're right!
What am I saying?!
It's too late to cry over your choices!
Where is it?!
Listen!
I certainly gave you a chance!
Mama believes that you guys stole the wedding cake
she really wanted to eat!
Big Mom!
My time is limited.
We're really in trouble!
We have to get out of here before the ship is destroyed!
I said I'd let just the two of you go.
Is everyone okay?
Listen! Everyone has their own turn.
Seems like it!
Cake!
You guys really don't know anything!
What?! We don't have a cake!
I know! But right now, Mama would chase you
even across the water until she gets the cake!
This island...
You rats!
Be patient and wait!
...isn't sweet at all!
It'll come naturally. Your turn, I mean...
Is that... Pedro?! Is he alive?!
The Sun guy is back!
Go deep into the forest!
Chopper-san!
That's right! So, Sanji! Come here!
But if we just run without a plan,
they might get ahead of us again!
Why don't you count the sound of
the second hand?
Goodbye, Pedro.
Watch as your friends get killed by Mama
and go through hell!
You're right...
Okay, Roger!
Oh, I have an idea!
Listen! I'll jump up and tell you
the direction of the ship!
That's just what sweet fools
like you guys deserve...
Damn! Pedro, that bastard!
That is not it!
What are you talking about?!
That way, even if they change the landscape,
we'll be fine, right?
Oh, stop! I don't wanna get sweetened!
--That's not Pedro!
--No...
You're right! I wanna disappear!
Yeah, you're right!
If that's what you came to say,
go away, you fools!
Oh, man... I felt my blood freeze...
Pedro!
Oh, stop!
Okay, I'm going!
Roger...
My Candy Armor is destroyed completely...
Wait a minute! That wasn't it!
What about him?
I'll turn you into a Candyman and lick you!
Black-Leg Sanji!
What?
Pudding told me you're good at
making sweets, too!
I won't let you do it!
No way... Why is he-teia alive?!
They say he died!
Yeah, I'm excellent at any kind of cooking!
You've got to be kidding!
Are you okay, Carrot-chan?
He's not gonna die!
He's the King of the Pirates!
Uh-huh, I'm okay.
Okay! Then, help us bake the cake!
Seems like all the shots of the second round
were intercepted!
I'm not kidding!
We'll make the cake which is the only thing
that can stop Mama!
Third round! Hurry up and load!
Seems like...
He got caught by the Navy
and at an execution ground in the East Blue...
...it's not gonna be that easy.
Hey, Big Brother Peros!
And we'll help you guys escape!
L-Let go of me!
That's Mama...
Chiffon! Why?!
Leave it to me!
Wedding...
Nami! Carrot!
I wanna pay my debt to you for saving Lola!
And I'll risk my life to do it!
--Pedro, will you be okay?
--Who do you think I am?
Jimbei!
Brook!
Her Hunger Pangs attack won't stop...
Chopper!
Thank you, Chiffon!
Cake!
Uh-huh!
Hmph! Maybe that's how we end up!
But unlike my sister, I'm not doing it for you!
We have to lead her to
Pudding on Cacao Island...
Awesome!
Beast Sword!
If she finds out there's no cake
on this ship, she'll kill me.
Karajishi!
The cake that I was gonna bake for myself
happened by chance to be the one Mama craves now!
A-A-And I just passed by here by coincidence!
I didn't know you guys were here!
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Listen to me!
I don't think we have gotten that far yet...
I'll be back! I'll leave the rest to you!
Find it!
S-So it's not like I came all the way to stop her
because I didn't want you to die, Sanji...
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
There it is!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
Let me eat!
It's that way!
Okay!
...san!
That's our Pedro!
I'll guide you from above!
When the lever returns to its original position,
the filling is complete!
--Okay, let's go!
--Yeah!
Her personality is like a roller coaster!
I won't let you get away!
All right, everyone! Hang onto something!
This is the beginning.
A new era has finally dawned.
I see! That's good!
Where can we bake the cake?!
I got it!
Duck!
Cake!
We're ready anytime!
What?
It's the coast! Get to the Sunny!
We're ready, too!
Cho... Choco... Cho...
We have extra supplies of the ingredients
at Chocolat Town!
Okay, here we go!
He was alive? Straw Hat...
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
First, we'll go to Chocolat Town
and bake the cake as fast as we can!
Don't let them get away! Fire!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
It must be our soldiers who got struck
by the lightning...
Then, we'll carry it on a ship
and deliver it to you!
Now!
Everybody! Don't forget to shout it!
Who are they?!
Take this!
The ship has been hijacked!
And we'll let Mama who comes after you
eat the cake.
Watch out!
Coup de...
What? Brook?! Chopper?!
Wishes will be carried over.
The tide of time, people's dreams...
What's that?!
You...!
That way, we can distract her attention from you!
So hang in there until that time!
...Burst!
Get back to the Mirroworld.
Those things can't be stopped.
All of you will end up...
Is she coming?!
Wedding...
As long as people search for
the meaning of freedom,
...lying at his feet in a few seconds.
Super!
Once you sail out to sea,
you'll have enemies in front of you, too!
those things will see no end.
Cake!
Jump into the mirror!
But I believe you guys can endure it!
Perospero and Katakuri...
Those two of all others...
We will!
Guys! Did it go well?!
Then, I'll come with you!
Is this it?
--What?!
--Yeah, hop on quickly!
I'll have it!
Fly away at max speed!
The disaster continues!
Roger...
Zeus!
W-W-Wait!
Who said you can ride it, idiot?!
It's a delicious cloud!
Okay!
It's amazing that you got this far...
I'm impressed.
I decided.
Th-There's no space!
What?
Don't take my place!
Is that...
But your destination is a graveyard!
I'll take... to sea, too!
Cake!
What is it?!
This is Amande.
The enemy ship fled
to the sky.
You must die here!
So delicious!
Even if you deny it,
the dawn didn't come to you...
The sky?!
Lick.
Hey, where's Luffy?!
She surfaced!
You think... so?
My Weather Egg is inside of Zeus...!
Candy Maiden!
Roger said, "Everyone has their own turn"!
The cake you guys will bake
is the only hope to stop Big Mom!
What is he doing?!
A wall of candy!
It's obvious that it's not just a wall!
--That's Straw Hat!
--Run!
Hey, Zeus!
What are you talking about?
Uh-huh!
This is my turn!
Guys!
Sanji-kun! Carry me and run!
I'm gonna leave you for now
but I promise I'll return!
MIRROWORLD
Okay, Nami-san!
Fish-Man Karate...
This will break all of your-gara
magic spells, right?
Uh-huh!
Everyone, run as far as you can, too!
Gum-Gum...
Okay!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Bombs?!
Stop, you fool!
What are you thinking?!
Shark Brick Fist!
Do you have a plan?
Yeah, I know you will!
Jet Bazooka!
Uh-huh!
Let go of me!
Stop!
I'm counting on you, Zeus!
Yes!
You succeeded...
I...
Not yet, not yet...
Here, I can pummel you as much as I want!
Hey!
Don't underestimate me!
Pudding!
...had a feeling that this
would be my last journey.
Chiffon!
What do you mean, Pedro?
Huh? What is it?!
--The path to the ship!
--He cut it off himself!
Oh no! She's gonna do it again!
Candy Maiden...
Pedro?!
Get away!
...Decoration!
Goodbye.
It's gigantic...
What are you doing right there?!
This is it!
Luffy! See you at sea!
Zeus Breeze...
I'm counting on you, Sanji!
No one can get through here!
So that's a captain's determination...
Ikoku Sovereignty!
What the?!
Go around and get to the ship!
But you're no match for me.
No, run straight!
This place will be your graveyard.
...Tempo!
I'll go back to the Sunny!
After I take you down!
Gum-Gum...
What do you mean, Pedro?
One day, you'll see how important it was...
...Red Hawk!
...to save Luffy and the others here
and let them set sail!
Pedro!!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
Pedro cleared the path for
a slight chance of escape!
Unbelievable power and speed, as well as
Haki of the Color of Observation that allows him to see the future!
Katakuri and Perospero!
Big Mom's strongest lackeys attack the Sunny!
The man who once attained everything
this world has to offer...
Big Mom's attacks stop!
However, from deep in the dark
underground, a creepy voice echoes!
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
However, to crush that ray of hope,
The Big Mom's Pirates' most formidable agent,
Katakuri's extraordinary fighting strength!
There is a Mink who carries
Big Mom and Katakuri
mercilessly attack the Sunny!
The sweet and horrific Candyman seeps into
the King's last wishes on his shoulders
and fights at the risk of his life!
Meanwhile, Pudding shows a new side!
Chopper and Brook's bodies to take their
lives, leaving them in a desperate situation.
There is only one way to survive!
To clear the way for Luffy
and the others who are in
To save his friends,
Luffy faces his biggest-ever challenge!
She lets her girly mind go crazy
and shares with Sanji a plan to work miracles!
With Pedro's wishes in mind,
Luffy takes a big bet with determination!
Will Luffy be able to make it in time?!
a desperate situation, Pedro, that
man, takes the bet of a lifetime!
On the next episode of One Piece!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Man with a
Bounty of Billion! The Strongest Sweet General, Katakuri!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I'll Be Back! Luffy, Deadly Departure!"
"Save the Sunny! Fighting
Bravely! Chopper and Brook!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Coincidental Reunion! Sanji
and the Lovestruck Evil Pudding!"
"Before the Dawn! Pedro, the
Captain of the Guardians!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!