My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
After failing to kill Big
Mom, Luffy and his allies
escaped from the Whole Cake Chateau
and continue heading towards the Sunny.
Ikoku Sovereignty!
They fended off the onslaught of Big Mom
who is experiencing a Hunger Pangs attack,
and entered the Seducing Woods
where Kingbaum rules...
Seducing Woods!
Stop them!
Big Mom has Luffy and the others
cornered even more by using the Homies.
It turned back to the annoying forest.
Tree!
Kingbaum...
Nami-san!
Wedding cake!
So you need my chiffon cake.
That's right.
If we combine my chocolate
and your chiffon cake,
we can make a wedding cake
that will satisfy Mama!
If we let her eat it,
we can stop her attack!
I need to stop Mama as soon as possible...
Otherwise, he...
...and his friends will get killed!
"A Lightning Counterattack!
Nami and Zeus the Thundercloud!"
SOUTHWEST COAST - SEDUCING WOODS
As long as Big Mom is having a Hunger Pangs attack,
all you can do is run!
Hunger Pangs? What is that?
It's a tantrum!
Until she gets to eat what she craves...
she keeps rampaging without discretion!
Wedding...
...cake!!
She's almost unconscious...
What she craves this time
seems to be a wedding cake!
Maybe because she didn't get to eat
the cake at the wedding!
Luffy! You shouldn't have ruined the cake!
But the plan succeeded!
And you don't often get to eat
a delicious cake like that!
Were you eating during the mission?!
I ate it, too! That was so good!
Anyway, hurry up!
I'm sure the Sunny isn't that far from here!
But in this forest,
you can't be sure if you're going straight!
Is this really the right way?!
Oh! Look!
That river looks familiar!
The Sunny must be right across the river!
Wait a minute!
If I remember right,
that bridge was broken!
You're right...
If the forest is our enemy,
we can't trust anything!
They're trying to fool us...
So I'm sure they're shifting the landscape
to confuse us...
In other words,
this isn't the place we think it is!
Meanwhile, around the Juice River
in Sweet City...
Oh, there it is! The Juice River!
The Shark Submerge is moored there!
So that's the river...
What?!
The river is filled with heavy cream!
Oh, it smells good!
It looks delicious! I'm gonna eat!
It's so sweet!
I can't believe the debris from
the crumbled Whole Cake Chateau flew this far...
Mmm! Mmm! It's so good!
Now, what should we do...
I mean, Chopper-san!
Yum-yum!
We have to escape from Big Mom
of course...
But we gotta do something about the situation
or we won't reach the Sunny!
Isn't there any way?
Lola's Vivre Card won't help us anymore...
Yeah, since Mama herself is right behind us!
That gives you all the more reason
to keep feeding him, Nami.
Yeah... Zeus!
It's...
It's delicious! So delicious!
If we let Zeus go back to Mama,
we'll have no chance to escape from her.
You're right.
Hey! Give me more!
Come back, Zeus!
If we're too slow, she'll catch up!
Oh, no! I'm gonna get scolded!
Hey!
Prometheus!
Why do you disobey Mama's orders, Zeus?!
Zeus! Look at me!
The exquisite Weather Egg
filled with juicy thunderclouds!
Wow! That looks great!
Whoa, wait, Zeus!
Hey, Sun!
How dare you...
...burn up the tree guy!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
That's our Luffy!
What the?!
Don't think...
...that you can beat me with just that!
Oh! Ow, ow, ow!
If the Color of Arms doesn't work,
it'll prove more troubling than Logia!
I'm gonna burn you all to death!
Ow, ow! It's hot! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Come back, Zeus!
I will! I will, but...
I wanna eat just one more juicy thundercloud!
You...
Jimbei!
Cross the bridge now, you all!
Okay!
Spear Wave!
Murasame!
Did it work?!
Of course!
He's merely a mass of compressed flames!
He could just be considered
a big talking fire!
You bastard...
Oh, the Shark Submerge!
I'm so happy!
Chopper-san, well done!
It's filled with cream in there, too!
I'm gonna eat it all!
Cake!
Don't stop!
--It's strange...
--What's wrong?
I haven't seen Mama's children
who were with her a while ago...
Don't tell me...!
Are they...?!
MOBILE
KATO
COMPO
Be prepared, Straw Hats!
LAURIN
This Seducing Woods will be...
TABLET
Your graveyard!
HIGH-FAT
Drop dead!
What?! I can't believe they got ahead of us!
The Homies must've shifted the landscape!
We're closed in from both sides...
Then, there's only one thing to do!
Yeah, let's kick their asses!
We managed to make it to the sea.
All we have to do now is get to the Sunny.
It's so sweet - I'm very happy!
What? I don't like it.
It's sticky all over...
See? The helm is slippery...
Watch out! Move out of my way, Fish-san!
Brook! Isn't that a mermaid?!
What?! Mermaid-san?!
I mean, a merman!
Oh...
What is he doing? Fishing, maybe?
I don't care anymore...
Let's get closer!
I'm not interested...
What? Brook!
Forget it.
Brook!
Boy! What do you want?!
Get away!
Go away! No, my hands are slipping!
You're Pedro, aren't you?
I saw you five years ago, too...
Oopsy!
You silly rabbit!
Garchu!
Stop!
Yes!
Big Bro Tablet!
You'd better pay attention!
Diable Jambe!
Flambage Shot!
Gum-Gum...
...Eagle Bazooka!
Shark Brick Fist!
Thanks, Jimbei!
Don't mention it! Keep luring Zeus!
Okay!
It's you again...
So persistent...
It's not over yet!
That idiot who lost his life
by the deadly roulette that day...
Was his name Zepo?
I'll let you see him in hell now!
Die!
You-gara...
...have no right to call
my partner an "idiot"!
Hey, everyone! Don't get separated!
Or we'll never see each other again!
Okay!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Luffy, stop Carrot!
All right!
Is everyone okay?
Seems like it!
Cake!
You rats!
The Sun guy is back!
Go deep into the forest!
But if we just run without a plan,
they might get ahead of us again!
You're right...
Oh, I have an idea!
Listen! I'll jump up and tell you
the direction of the ship!
That way, even if they change the landscape,
we'll be fine, right?
Yeah, you're right!
Okay, I'm going!
I won't let you do it!
Are you okay, Carrot-chan?
Uh-huh, I'm okay.
Seems like...
...it's not gonna be that easy.
Leave it to me!
--Pedro, will you be okay?
--Who do you think I am?
Awesome!
Beast Sword!
Karajishi!
There it is!
It's that way!
Okay!
That's our Pedro!
I'll guide you from above!
--Okay, let's go!
--Yeah!
I won't let you get away!
Duck!
Take this!
Watch out!
You...!
Cake!
Is this it?
I'll have it!
Zeus!
It's a delicious cloud!
What?
Is that...
What is it?!
So delicious!
My Weather Egg is inside of Zeus...!
What is he doing?!
Hey, Zeus!
Sanji-kun! Carry me and run!
Okay, Nami-san!
Everyone, run as far as you can, too!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Do you have a plan?
Uh-huh!
Stop!
I'm counting on you, Zeus!
Zeus Breeze...
What the?!
...Tempo!
Big Mom's attacks stop!
However, from deep in the dark
underground, a creepy voice echoes!
Meanwhile, Pudding shows a new side!
She lets her girly mind go crazy
and shares with Sanji a plan to work miracles!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Coincidental Reunion! Sanji
and the Lovestruck Evil Pudding!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!