My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
After failing to kill Big Mom,
Luffy and his allies escaped
from the Whole Cake Chateau
and continue heading towards the Sunny.
Wedding...
...cake!!
Maybe because she didn't get to eat
the cake at the wedding!
Luffy and the others were running desperately
while shaking off attacks from the family...
Gum-Gum...
...Eagle Bazooka!
Diable Jambe!
Flambage Shot!
But they suffered even more onslaughts
from Big Mom.
Duck!
"A Coincidental Reunion!
Sanji and the Lovestruck Evil Pudding!"
We're almost there.
I know!
There it is!
It's the Sunny!
I'm glad that it's safe!
Luffy and the others are already there,
it seems!
Let's hurry up!
Hey, guys!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Why are they...
...On board our Sunny?
I'm sorry. Your friends aren't here. Lick!
Zeus Breeze...
...Tempo!
Don't tell me Luffy and the others are...
Is that...
Seems like Mama finished them off with Zeus.
Mama'll be here.
Lick!
The Straw Hat and his allies are dead.
Now if we can lead Mama to Pudding
and let her eat the cake, everything'll be okay.
Things are going smoothly.
He's saying such a thing but
they'll be fine, right?
Yeah, I'm sure they will!
Lick! I guess your friends are dead...
That's never the case
for Luffy-san and the others!
That's right! They'll be back!
And what are you two gonna do?
Even if you can take back the ship at the risk of your lives,
no one'll return.
If you wanna get out of here on that submarine,
I don't mind letting you go, if it's just the two of you.
Oh, we appreciate your concern.
But...
...no thanks.
Kung Fu Point!
Get off of the ship, you bastards!
It's our Sunny!
Do you want to fight?
Of course!
We'll save the Sunny!
I guess you want to die. Lick!
Let's get started! A fully-standing show!
Yeah!
That was so powerful!
My Climate Baton can't generate
such strong lightning!
With that much power...
--Where's Big Mom?
--She must've been hit directly!
She's probably in that giant hole!
Did we happen to take down Big Mom?!
What is it?
Where's this sound coming from?
Wedding...!
Big Mom's voice?!
I thought so...
Cake!
Is she alive?!
She's not someone who'll get beaten
that easily...
She's climbing up!
Is the hole too deep for her to climb out?
Let's run while she's at it!
Yeah. While Big Mom can't move!
No, she's already on her way...
--The ground is...
--No way!
There's no stopping for Big Mom
when she has a Hunger Pangs attack!
Wedding...
...cake!
Oh no! Run!
Wedding...
No... The ground's gonna crack open!
Here she comes!
Run!
B-Bring...
...the cake!
Here I go!
Okay, baby?
Brook!
For now, I want you to call me...
...Soul King!
This is the real scream of my soul!
Soul King!
A skeleton with a strange skill, huh?
How long are you gonna keep fighting?
Your friends have already died.
Of course, I'll keep fighting
until I get the ship back...
Otherwise, I'll have no words of apology
to my friends when they get here!
What a waste of energy!
Soul...
...Parade!
I've been frozen?!
Ice Burn!
How can you keep standing on ice?!
I'm a...
...reindeer!
I thought you were a raccoon dog!
No, I'm not!
Good job!
Thanks to you!
The forest is... What happened?!
Is everyone okay?!
Rabian, go faster!
Okay!
I'm sorry, Big Sis, for asking this...
That's okay! It's been a long time
since we made a cake together!
On top of that...
You're going?! Are you kidding?!
Bege! Didn't I tell you?!
The Straw Hats saved my young sister, Lola's life!
But, Chiffon, it's dangerous! I'm worried!
He's right-rero!
You must escape with us-rero!
Oh, I'm sorry. That was too loud...
We can't leave without you, Ma'am!
Come back, Chiffon!
Dangerous?! Yes, I'm fully aware of it!
"Thank you for saving Lola."
It's so easy to just say the words!
Whether you really mean it or not will be proven
when the person you're indebted to is in trouble!
You're right, but...
That's how you do your duty,
right, darling?
If something happens to me,
please take care of...
...Pez for me!
Chiffon!
Ma'am!
I have to save Nami and the others
and return to my family!
Big Sis! There he is!
Pudding? Were you listening?
S... Sanji-san is...
S... S...
Sanji...
S...
Sanji's there! That fool!
Say what?!
I know you guys have it!
Straw Hat!
She's coming up!
Can't we do something?!
It's no use! Just run!
Give it to me!
Straw Hats!
--What?
--Pudding! Chiffon!
Oh, Pudding! What's wrong with you?!
You fooled us!
To stop Mama's Hunger Pangs attack...
See? We should've tied her up
in the first place!
To stop Mama's...
But why's Chiffon with her?!
I thought she ran away with Bege's group!
--To stop...
--Wanna fight?!
No, I don't! Listen to me!
Pudding-chan, you're okay!
I'm glad that your pretty self isn't hurt!
So lovely! So lovely!
Pudding, get it together!
Oh, no! Mama's coming!
Mama!
We have no time!
Pudding, get right to the point!
Okay!
Sanji-san...
Pudding-chan...
I'll save you at any price...
Price...
P...
Pathetic! You fools!
You're not gonna make it!
Even if you escape by ship,
Mama will chase you to the farthest sea
and sink you to the ocean floor!
What did you say, you bastard?!
That is not it, Pudding!
What are you talking about?!
You're right! You're right!
What am I saying?!
Listen!
Mama believes that you guys stole the wedding cake
she really wanted to eat!
What?! We don't have a cake!
I know! But right now, Mama would chase you
even across the water until she gets the cake!
That's right! So, Sanji! Come here!
Watch as your friends get killed by Mama
and go through hell!
That is not it!
What are you talking about?!
You're right! I wanna disappear!
If that's what you came to say,
go away, you fools!
Wait a minute! That wasn't it!
Black-Leg Sanji!
What?
Pudding told me you're good at
making sweets, too!
Yeah, I'm excellent at any kind of cooking!
Okay! Then, help us bake the cake!
We'll make the cake which is the only thing
that can stop Mama!
And we'll help you guys escape!
Chiffon! Why?!
I wanna pay my debt to you for saving Lola!
And I'll risk my life to do it!
Thank you, Chiffon!
Uh-huh!
Hmph! Maybe that's how we end up!
But unlike my sister, I'm not doing it for you!
The cake that I was gonna bake for myself
happened by chance to be the one Mama craves now!
A-A-And I just passed by here by coincidence!
I didn't know you guys were here!
S-So it's not like I came all the way to stop her
because I didn't want you to die, Sanji...
...san!
Her personality is like a roller coaster!
I see! That's good!
Where can we bake the cake?!
What?
Cho... Choco... Cho...
We have extra supplies of the ingredients
at Chocolat Town!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
First, we'll go to Chocolat Town
and bake the cake as fast as we can!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
Then, we'll carry it on a ship
and deliver it to you!
And we'll let Mama who comes after you
eat the cake.
That way, we can distract her attention from you!
So hang in there until that time!
Is she coming?!
Wedding...
Once you sail out to sea,
you'll have enemies in front of you, too!
But I believe you guys can endure it!
We will!
Then, I'll come with you!
--What?!
--Yeah, hop on quickly!
W-W-Wait!
Who said you can ride it, idiot?!
Th-There's no space!
Don't take my place!
Cake!
She surfaced!
The cake you guys will bake
is the only hope to stop Big Mom!
Uh-huh!
Guys!
I'm gonna leave you for now
but I promise I'll return!
Uh-huh!
Okay!
Yeah, I know you will!
Hey!
Pudding!
Chiffon!
Oh no! She's gonna do it again!
Get away!
What are you doing right there?!
Luffy! See you at sea!
I'm counting on you, Sanji!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Katakuri and Perospero!
Big Mom's strongest lackeys attack the Sunny!
The sweet and horrific Candyman seeps into
Chopper and Brook's bodies to take their
lives, leaving them in a desperate situation.
Will Luffy be able to make it in time?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save the Sunny! Fighting
Bravely! Chopper and Brook!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!