My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
In order to escape from the Whole Cake Island,
Luffy and his allies finally reached the Sunny.
However, Sweet General Katakuri and the others
who were there waiting blocked their way!
While Big Mom closes in
and the grand fleet of Tarte ships led by Amande
narrows its encirclement,
Perospero covered the Sunny with candy
and restrained its movement.
Did you see the power of Candy Wave?!
I'm a perfectionist!
To let the Sunny flee, Pedro...
Roger said, "Everyone has their own turn"!
What are you talking about?
This is my turn!
This will break all of your-gara magic spells, right?
Bombs?!
Stop, you fool!
What are you thinking?!
Goodbye.
Pedro!!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
"I'll Be Back!
Luffy, Deadly Departure!"
Pedro!
Don't tell me Big Bro Peros is...
Oh, no! Mama and Perospero-sama...
...Got involved in the explosion!
The candy of his special ability
is starting to melt!
I can't believe he sacrificed himself...
How dare you, Pedro!
I thought I was gonna die!
Are you guys okay?!
No, Carrot!
Let go of me! Let me get back to where Pedro was!
Maybe he's still alive!
No! You saw that explosion...
He saved us!
We've had no chance to survive
up until now!
You have to understand Pedro's reasoning!
Please!
Ready to fly, Nami?!
Yes, it's all set!
Chopper! Brook! Are you with us?
Oh?
Jimbei!
Yes, they're with us!
Set sail, you guys!
If we waste this moment...
we'd make Pedro ashamed of us!
We'll get out of here no matter what!
At any price!
Why is everyone...
...so heated up?!
Go away, Big Mom Pirates!
Carrot!
Come on! Is that all you've got?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Don't hold back! Try to strike harder!
You can master swordsmanship
after you dedicate all of yourself!
Oops...
Get up! Get on your feet, Carrot!
And take the sword!
Until you-gara become a full-fledged swordswoman,
I'll teach you with all my might!
She-gara have no aptitude for swords.
Pedro! It's none of your business.
Carrot will become a strong swordswoman
under my guidance.
There is more than one way to get stronger.
There must be a way that's better suited for her.
No, no! You're too soft, Pedro!
Training should push you to your limits
and break you!
That's so annoying.
If you think everyone's like you-gara,
you're totally wrong.
What?!
Can I take her-gara under my care?
Of course, only if she's interested.
What is this?
Take a fighting pose.
That's more suited for you-gara.
You-gara can float in the air for quite a while.
If you take advantage of that and your Electro,
you-gara can acquire your own strength and way of fighting.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Attack me. I'll be your training partner.
All right!
I thought I couldn't become strong.
I can't believe there's a suited skill for me.
Thanks to you, Pedro.
It doesn't matter how you fight.
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Everyone has their own turn.
Carrot...
You'll have your turn, too.
Don't worry...
I know you can do it...
I'm sure you can...
Electrical...
As long as I'm here, I won't let you set sail!
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Everyone has their own turn.
I know you can do it...
I'm sure you can...
Wait, Pedro!
Don't go!
I'm sorry, Pedro...
You took the trouble to teach me...
I can't believe I'm completely helpless...
I have to live up to the expectations you had...
that made you sacrifice yourself for our escape...
Pedro... I'm sorry...
Get your foot off of Carrot!
Carrot! Leave him to me!
Luffy...
I hope you're strong enough to kick me out...
We'll set sail! I'm the captain of this ship!
Gum-Gum Elephant Gun!
--Nami!
--I know!
Okay! While they're at it...
The sails can stay like that.
Towards the northwest, Coup de Burst!
Azimuth: 45 degrees to northwest!
Pitch: 35 degrees!
Three cola barrels are loaded.
Agitate the energy!
What is this vibration?!
By shaking the cola barrels up and down,
we're tapping the energy of the carbonation!
I see...
I certainly can't attack others
If you do that.
This way, you can't stop it
even if you know what'll happen!
Those fools... I won't let them get away...
I'll avenge Big Bro Peros!
All ships, prepare to fire towards the enemy ship!
Adjust the angle of elevation!
Shark-chan, come back!
Chopper-san, could you grab it over there?
Let's pull it close to the Sunny before they start attacking!
All right!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Let's pull it close before Big Mom comes!
Jimbei-san, thank you!
Tie the rope to the bar!
Give us a hand, Nami!
Sorry! I'm not done here yet!
--She's coming...
--...This way!
Nami! Not yet?!
I know! A little more to go!
Be careful with my brother and Mama!
Aim at its bow!
Okay! Fire!
--She's coming...
--...This way!
Nami! Not yet?!
I know! A little more to go!
Okay! Fire!
They're firing at us one after another!
--We're in trouble!
--Nami!
The cola energy has reached its maximum!
Now! Go!
Coup de...
Wait!
What's wrong?!
Big Mom!
Oh, no! We gotta get going!
Huh? What?
I can't use the Coup de Burst!
--Nami!
--What's the matter? I thought it'd fly!
I think cola has leaked due to the impact!
What?!
--They're coming!
--Let's bring them down!
No problem!
Good job, you guys! Let me have a go, too!
Jimbei, wait!
I'll go load cola so could you take my place?
Please!
What?!
Don't worry. We have a Tone Dial
with an audio recording of Franky for these occasions.
Th-This?!
Franky's navigation system, activate.
O... Okay...
Second round, prepare to fire!
Maintain your aim.
Oh, good... Seems like it's not broken.
It's just one of the barrels fell on the floor...
All ships are prepared to fire for a second round!
Fire!
They fired again!
Chopper-san, let's bring them down no matter what
until the cola energy is filled up!
Yeah!
When the barrel of cola is loaded,
push the lever forward!
All right!
It's starting to move! I gotta hurry!
Where is it...? The wedding cake!
What are you doing?!
Don't bite our Sunny!
Damn! If it goes on like this...
Idiot! Go away!
Big Bro, I'm here to save you!
Carrot! Hang on. Can you get up?
Yes... Nami, thank you.
Where is it?!
Big Mom!
We're really in trouble!
We have to get out of here before the ship is destroyed!
Is that... Pedro?! Is he alive?!
Damn! Pedro, that bastard!
--That's not Pedro!
--No...
Oh, man... I felt my blood freeze...
My Candy Armor is destroyed completely...
No way... Why is he-teia alive?!
Seems like all the shots of the second round
were intercepted!
Third round! Hurry up and load!
L-Let go of me!
Nami! Carrot!
Jimbei!
Brook!
Chopper!
Listen to me!
I'll be back! I'll leave the rest to you!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
When the lever returns to its original position,
the filling is complete!
All right, everyone! Hang onto something!
I got it!
We're ready anytime!
We're ready, too!
Okay, here we go!
Don't let them get away! Fire!
Now!
Everybody! Don't forget to shout it!
Coup de...
...Burst!
Super!
Guys! Did it go well?!
Fly away at max speed!
Okay!
This is Amande.
The enemy ship fled
to the sky.
The sky?!
Hey, where's Luffy?!
--That's Straw Hat!
--Run!
MIRROWORLD
You succeeded...
Here, I can pummel you as much as I want!
--The path to the ship!
--He cut it off himself!
So that's a captain's determination...
But you're no match for me.
This place will be your graveyard.
I'll go back to the Sunny!
After I take you down!
Unbelievable power and speed, as well as
Haki of the Color of Observation that allows him to see the future!
The Big Mom's Pirates' most formidable agent,
Katakuri's extraordinary fighting strength!
To save his friends,
Luffy faces his biggest-ever challenge!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Man with a
Bounty of Billion! The Strongest Sweet General, Katakuri!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!