My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Stamp!
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
Is that it?
No way!
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro butsukeatta yorokobi mo
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
Are you gonna show your power next?
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida kawakashita setsunasa mo
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
Give up already.
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
That's a gigantic fist!
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Gum-Gum...
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
...Elephant...
...Gun!
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Katakuri-sama's is even bigger!
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the morning when the light comes in
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
Did I do the "Elephant Gun" right?
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Are those...?!
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
In order to escape from
the Whole Cake Island,
In order to let the Sunny escape
from the Whole Cake Island,
Luffy and his allies
finally reached the Sunny.
Luffy stayed in the Mirroworld by himself
and held off Katakuri.
...became separated but kept fighting
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
However, Sweet General Katakuri
and the others who were there
However, he got overwhelmed by Katakuri's strength.
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Having cut off his retreat, Luffy continues the fierce
one-on-one dual he
There are still some mirrors on the ship,
aren't there?!
waiting blocked their way!
Gum-Gum...
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
--What?!
--Maybe in the boys' room or the bathroom?!
Then, Pedro sacrificed himself
along with Perospero so that
...Giant...
challenged Sweet General Katakuri to.
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
Break them all! To pieces!
...Axe!
Luffy and the others could escape.
Are you out of your mind?!
How would you come back, then?!
Gum-Gum...
We are hope
The allies who he saved suppressed their sorrow
and prepared for the Coup de Burst.
Now, you guys, keep shooting!
There will be no victory in your future.
...Red Hawk!
We're gonna keep shooting, Joscar.
Set sail, you guys!
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
Yes, we are, Marscar.
If we waste this moment
we'd make Pedro ashamed of us!
Nami! Hurry up and break the mirrors!
All of them!
Luffy promised Nami and the others
to rendezvous,
It leads anyone to the peak of happiness...
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
But...
but his every attack is foreseen by Katakuri
An army of enemies is on its way!
I can't stop them by myself!
I'll make you taste true sweetness!
Listen to me!
who uses the Haki of the
Color of Observation.
I'll be back! I'll leave the rest to you!
T-True sweetness?!
Let me focus just on this guy!
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
Okay, here we go!
Meanwhile, Sanji started making the wedding cake
in order to calm Big Mom down.
Coup de...
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
...Burst!
There is no future for you!
All right!
Let's start baking!
For those who saved Lola!
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Nami-san! Why did you break the mirror?!
For Sanji-san!
"The End of the Deadly Battle?!
Katakuri's Awakening in Anger!"
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Just break them all!
All the mirrors on the ship!
I'll make my special extremely-fluffy
chiffon cake!
You succeeded...
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
But...
Do you wanna get in Luffy's way?!
I must help Sanji-san and the others get away!
Here, I can pummel you as much as I want!
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
With my very sweet chocolate!
It's the Captain's orders! Hurry up!
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Keep hanging on, guys!
"The Man with a Bounty of Billion!
The Strongest Sweet General, Katakuri!"
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
I'll show them!
Gum-Gum...
My bold cooking!
We are hope
Learning that the Sunny was still on the run,
Katakuri ordered it set on fire.
...Hawk Twin Pistol!
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
"The Threat of the Mole!
Luffy's Silent Fight!"
What an idiot!
I can't believe he broke the mirror himself!
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
Are you trying to sacrifice yourself
and let your friends escape?!
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
Leave them alone!
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
There are still some mirrors!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
I thought you were in a one-on-one duel with me,
Straw Hat.
I found one, Joscar!
--Don't be silly!
--Who do you think you're talking to?!
I found it, too, Marscar!
Now, burn down Straw Hat's ship!
Katakuri-sama's bounty is
one billion, fifty-seven million berries!
Let's do it, Joscar!
He's the strongest of the Sweet 3 Generals!
Let's do it, Marscar!
Roger!
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Make sure to find any kind of mirror!
Stop!!
You're dangerous, Straw Hat Luffy...
That was close!
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
Even though it was reckless,
"The Green Room!
An Invincible Helmsman, Jimbei!"
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
there aren't that many people who
have caused this much damage...
Shoot!
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
...on the Big Mom Pirates.
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
If I let you get away,
you'll be a bigger threat to Mama.
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
But in terms of ability,
you're on a way lower level than me...
Stop!
No, you stop.
What?!
Leave my little brother and sisters alone!
What's going on?!
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
I've got to take care of you now.
I'm not gonna be defeated!
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
This is the last one!
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
I'll teach you that there's always
somebody better than you.
I won't let you do it!
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
Are they alive?!
Big Bro Peros said they took care of them...
Here I go!
That's our brother!
I guess the ship sank and the mirrors were
shattered by the water pressure, Joscar!
Yeah, I guess that's it, Marscar!
"A Hard Battle Starts!
Luffy vs. Katakuri!"
Gum-Gum...
Mochi Thrust!
...Jet Pistol!
Something is not right...
Is that all you've got?
Hey!
Gum-Gum...
Hey, Luffy!
What?
...Jet Pistol!
This time, he's got two giant fists!
Are you okay?!
Gum-Gum...
Chopper!
Jet Twin Pistols!
...Grizzly...
We need to talk so get away from the enemies!
So pathetic...
...Magnum!
How much longer are you gonna
go on disgracing yourself?
Okay!
If I really wanna dodge...
Ouch!
Are you guys alright?!
I can dodge forever.
Hey! Straw Hat is running away!
Katakuri-sama's are even bigger!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
What happened?!
The candy guy said the Sunny sank!
Damn you!
We thought it'd sink, too!
But Jimbei was awesome!
Gum-Gum...
...Eagle Bazooka!
A mirror!
Stop right there!
Hey, Nami!
He can't do anything like that!
Jimbei, can you hear me?!
You can't get away!
Where did Straw Hat go?
Somebody! Respond!
Katakuri-sama!
Why are we heading towards the wave?!
Jimbei!
ON THE SEA IN TOTTO LAND
Gum-Gum...
Hold on to the ship tightly!
...Hawk Axe!
A surprise attack is...
...useless.
Gum-Gum...
I can't believe it! He's controlling the sloop
like it's his own limb!
How annoying the way he moves!
--We can't see him!
--Is this what he wants?
...Giant...
...Axe!
Gum-Gum...
I've never seen such a helmsman!
...Jet Spear!
Wedding...
Hawk Gatling!
If it weren't for Jimbei,
He's gone!
...cake!
No! Katakuri-sama!
we'd all have...
--Katakuri-sama!
--No way!
...drowned in the sea!
Incoming on the right!
Jimbei! Port to avoid!
We're all fine, Luffy!
Brace for impact!
Katakuri-sama's foot is even bigger!
Okay!
He never learns!
Luffy-san!
We broke all the mirrors on the ship!
You bastard!
Okay! That's good!
There will be no victory in your future.
Now the enemies can't invade the ship
but you can't come back, either!
The second round, loaded!
Gum-Gum...
Yeah, that's okay! I'll figure something...
Fire!
I don't see anyone coming after us.
...Grizzly Corkscrew Magnum!
No, you can't!
You don't even have a plan!
Katakuri-sama wins!
It's going to rain...
Listen carefully, Luffy!
You see how strong Sweet
General Katakuri-sama is?!
Hey! Luffy!
Let me hear you if you're there!
He's not in the same class with
just another squirt like you!
Oh, no! They keep firing!
Sanji-kun is baking the cake
at Cacao Island now!
He went into the Mirroworld...
That's where we're heading!
Taking Katakuri...
What?!
Guard Point!
We'll get there in 10 hours at the earliest!
Luffy...
Around 1 AM!
That must've finished him!
No one can survive after getting such a...
So as soon as you kick that guy's ass,
Someone broke the mirror!
We can't go in like this!
look for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
And we'll see you there!
Swallow Banderole!
Let's trust our captain!
He said he'd be back!
Damn! I can't get it off!
Yeah!
Uh-huh!
Speaking of being missing...
I don't see Pedro-san, either.
Is something wrong, Luffy?
Not yet... No...
Are you listening?
--Oh, you're right...
--Did he go somewhere?
Did he go into the Mirroworld with Luffy-san?
Hey! Can you hear me?! Somebody!
What? Luffy?!
I'm sorry.
Nami!
Pedro is... Pedro is...
I told them that I'd threaten you
and force you to help me make the cake.
Luffy, it's me! You alright?!
Damn! I can't hit him with my Haki...
There are still some mirrors on the ship,
aren't there?!
--Carrot?
--Did something happen?
I can't hit him without my Haki!
Never mind, Pudding.
That's the position I'm in now.
--What?!
--Maybe in the boys' room or the bathroom?!
Luffy!
Yeah!
Hey! Stay focused!
Hey, guys, what's the matter?!
On top of that, he's able to
hit me precisely where I dodge.
It's burning up!
We're gonna shoot, Joscar.
This is doubling my fatigue.
Yes, we are, Marscar.
Chopper, Brook, listen carefully.
It's burning! It's burning!
I feel the same.
The thing is... Pedro is...
It just makes things complicated
so quit smiling at her!
No one's ever evaded my attacks like that.
Luffy?! What about mirrors?!
It's stressing me out!
Pudding! Pudding, pull yourself together!
Don't you wanna save Sanji?!
Break them all! To pieces!
Are you out of your mind?!
How would you come back, then?!
I do!
You're an eyesore! Why don't you get wrapped up
in Rabian and hide yourself, Sanji...
I don't know but it should be all right!
Yeah, okay.
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
I'll figure something out!
...san!
Sniff, sniff...
Maybe he's in trouble!
I smell something!
Please respond!
You tried to take the Mole away from me...
How beautiful she is in her wedding dress!
I don't have a nose though!
Luffy!
Are you okay, Luffy?!
Damn! I almost got it!
I feel sorry for her.
Her wedding was messed up.
Luffy-san!
What?
But even with that sad look,
she's still lovely!
The room is on fire!
What's wrong?!
Oh! The Minister of Fluff!
How is this happening?!
Chi... Chiffon-sama!
What?!
Flaming arrows from inside the mirror!
Cannon-shots from behind!
Everyone, don't worry!
Big Sis Chiffon is not a key figure in the rebellion!
One thing after another!
My eyes are spinning!
Oh, I don't have eyes to spin though!
The responsible one is
her husband, Gang Bege!
Never mind! Let's put it out, Brook!
Okay...
Willow Mochi!
Now, you guys, keep shooting!
We're gonna keep shooting, Joscar.
Wh-What's the matter?!
Crap!
Yes, we are, Marscar.
Oh, no!
Gum-Gum...
We don't have time!
Enough, you idiots!
...Eagle Bazooka!
Let's go to the Sweets Factory now!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Well done, Pudding! She distracted him!
Luffy!
Well, Pudding-sama,
I can't believe what happened today...
Who could expect the happy wedding would be
ruined by Straw Hat Luffy's invasion and Bege's treason!
D-Dammit!
It serves you right!
That Sanji guy was a terrible humbug, too!
Now, shoot it up!
Stop...
What's done is done.
This is it...
I'm sure you're having a hard time!
Sir, the milk, bananas and yogurt
that you ordered have arrived!
No way...
You're kidding... right?
I wonder how angry Mama is.
Oh, thanks! Bring them here!
No matter how many times you dodge,
I'll just foresee further...
Yes, she's mad and hungry.
Yes, sir!
INSIDE CHOCOLAT TOWN'S SWEETS FACTORY
We have to rush! We can't waste any time!
No... No...
Oh, no!
In addition, she's in her Hunger Pangs attack
and could destroy this country.
I can't get out!
Pedro-san...
Oh, how horrible...
Die...!
Pedro-san...
Is everything ready?
Yes! About an hour ago,
31 chefs were dispatched from the Whole Cake Island.
Pedro-san sacrificed himself...
Luffy?
You're fine, right, Luffy-san?!
It's my fault!
What's the matter, Luffy?!
Oh, Pudding-sama!
If I had protected the Sunny to the end!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
There's no time for you to collapse!
W-We have a problem!
We're 30 grams short of butter!
It's because... I was weak!
What?!
I grabbed the Mole!
Even though it was only with my legs!
Oh, please! We can't make it in time
if we order it now!
With our pride as Head Chefs of
the Whole Cake Island,
Even if it's just 30 grams,
it'll change the taste.
How absurd!
let's do it!
We can't stop Mama then...
If we were... If we were...!
What should we do?
Flowing Mochi!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring... Clank!
--Don't worry!
--What?
Do we have prunes?
Katakuri, it's me.
Y-Yes, we do...
Good. Let's turn them into a puree
and use it as substitute.
You escaped death, Big Bro Peros.
If we were stronger...
What?
Yes, barely.
Add some baking powder
and reduce the amount of sugar.
What happened to Straw Hat's underlings?
Believe or not,
That'll compensate for the lack of butter.
they launched their ship and
escaped our encirclement.
Wh-What the?!
Uh-huh. You're right.
Everyone! Hurry up!
I'm chasing them with Mama now...
The floor has turned into mochi!
Yes, ma'am!
Hurry up and get there, guys!
We're walking on the water.
Sanji-san...
I'll probably be there soon
and get tired of waiting!
They're tenaciously trying to flee
but we'll catch up to them in no time.
In addition, you can cut back on calories.
This is what Doflamingo did!
So it turns out to be better for ladies.
Yeah!
Amande and the others' fleet
will be here soon, too.
See you later, guys!
Listen, fledgling!
Leave the crying to our enemies.
Yeah!
No matter how much they struggle,
they have no chance.
Pudding-sama!
I told you that there's no time to collapse!
Our pursuers will be here soon!
Let's keep an eye out!
We should not get upset.
Devil Fruit abilities have...
H-How dependable!
That's what I'd expect from Pudding-sama's husband!
...yet another stage to
them called "Awakening"!
Roger!
Let's go to the observation deck, Carrot!
How is it over there?
I heard Straw Hat challenged you.
Okay, Chobro!
Hey, Jimbei-san!
What?!
You two truly are a perfect match!
How could you say such a cold thing?!
Yeah...
The ability will awaken rarely
and begin to affect things other than its user's body!
He's down on the floor, pathetically.
You knew Pedro-san the shortest out of all of us,
that's why--
Per... fect... mat... ch...
I'm just telling you not
to lose your concentration!
I'll finish him off right here.
You really are an ideal husband and wife!
Of course, my ability has been awakened...
We had our backs against
the wall at the coast...
hus... band... and... wife...
He knew the place was extremely dangerous
so he had been preparing to sacrifice himself.
Oh, no!
Pudding-sama!
It's no use.
With elasticity and viscosity like this,
you're immobilized.
I told you to stop! We're running out of time!
This is...
...Pedro's victory!
SWEETS FACTORY, CHOCOLAT TOWN
"I'm not gonna die here"...
Should I just chop you up?
That's what you'll say...
How much damage did the enemy take
because of you guys?!
Or should I let you suffocate in the mochi?
We've been expecting you, Pudding-sama!
Is that all you have to say before you die?
How would you like to die?
We're the 31 Head Chefs
of the Whole Cake Island!
I'm not gonna die!
It's an unprecedented major blunder to them!
Luffy!
Luffy! Are you okay?!
WCI: 31!
Your strength really drove Big Mom
into the corner!
Gear Four?
Those of you who'll march into the ship!
Follow me!
Big Sis Chiffon and I are going to make
the only wedding cake that can stop Mama.
That's interesting.
Don't you hear Pedro's
voice inside you saying...
Oh, no!
Please assist us.
Yes, ma'am! We're already
making preparations!
"Keep going"?!
Pudding-sama was the bride
so she was affected the most by what happened...
Nami! Hurry up and break the mirrors!
All of them!
I'm not gonna die here!
But...
You can count on me!
I'm not gonna let Mama destroy our country!
An army of enemies is on its way!
I can't stop them by myself!
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Pudding-sama!
Let me focus just on this guy!
Luffy sensed it instantly...
I can't believe she's overcoming the pain
and overseeing the cake-making herself!
and decided to take the enemy on
all by himself.
It's strange...
She's literally a goddess of salvation!
Katakuri is worth over a billion!
It's all or nothing!
Huh?
We haven't got the location
of the Straw Hats' ship...
Good luck!
SWEET CITY
Go ahead and get inside with Rabian.
Nami! We have a problem!
What are the Territory Slugs doing?!
It's not over yet!
Okay.
We can't get away!
Please, everyone! Listen to me!
We're still in Totto Land!
Shut up, Pekoms!
Haven't we gotten any updates
on Straw Hat and the others-soir?
I need you to do me a favor!
Just stop crying already!
Soon, we will be chased by the pirate queen of the country,
Big Mom!
We're going to risk our lives and bake the cake
that will influence the fate of our country!
Could it be that they made
it out of our territory?
Big Bro Pedro!
That's impossible!
We really need to concentrate!
I feel pity for him...
And the enemy fleet can attack us at any time
from any direction!
Once they take to sea, the surrounding
Territory Slugs will sense them for sure!
His childhood friend who was like a
So, please don't look inside the factory
under any circumstances while we're at it!
brother to him chose death
by a deadly bombing-bon...
On top of that, Mama and our siblings
have set out, too, chasing them.
He was our enemy!
Until you get out of the territory
where Big Mom reigns,
Yes, ma'am!
Bon...
And no matter who it is,
don't let anyone look inside!
It's pointless to die here!
The dawn of the new world is coming!
A high wave!
you can't lose your concentration!
Isn't Pedro inside of you saying that?!
They have no chance against our encirclement.
What?!
Yes, ma'am!
I hope so...
We understand! Pudding-sama!
I have to go back!
Believe in your family!
You there...?
Thank you all!
The Germa Kingdom is about to fall, too!
This will break all of your-gara
magic spells, right?
Good luck, Pudding-sama!
Bombs?!
I'm very sorry.
Goodbye.
This way, they won't see Sanji-san...
I was way out of line.
And now, I must deal with those
who will work with us!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
--Nami, give us directions!
--Okay!
Head Chefs! Come inside one by one!
I won't let you get away!
I'm shocked, too-amour...
Sanji-kun and the others will come to us
from Cacao Island
Nami! What's wrong?!
so we don't wanna miss each other.
I saw Pedro begging for his life in tears
five years ago-bon.
This...
There'll be a strong wind soon.
It's a tailwind!
Go to ruin, Germa!
We'll have your scientific technology!
Bouche, head chef of the first kitchen,
reporting for duty.
...might be it for us...
So starboard!
Hard a starboard!
That same man preferred to sacrifice his life
in order to let them set sail.
Catch the wind on the starboard side
and head straight west!
There's no cure for a fool!
--We'll take the shortest way!
--Roger!
Stay still.
Do you think you can burn me
with such a small flame?
So what?
I'll go replenish the
cola that was just used!
I'm gonna modify your memories... Edit!
Act as tough as you like now!
Big Bro...
I'll stand guard!
Huh?
--Hey, let me down.
--Okay!
Maybe we're still underestimating
Straw Hat Luffy-issant!
Candy, candy... sluggie-gie!
Here you go!
The Germa Kingdom ends today!
Okay!
I'm in position!
That must've been a tough ride.
Uh-huh!
INSIDE THE FACTORY
We've no time so I drew a
blueprint of the cake en route.
Let me monitor the currents!
What's your point?
My point is that we should be careful-bon!
What?! Do you remember it?!
Mama'll never be done in by a punk like him!
Pretty much.
You're saying that Straw Hat Luffy is
that much weaker?
No way! Maybe you could remember the shape
but how could you even tell the ingredients without tasting it?
Of course!
She's in a different class as a pirate!
No one dies because they want to.
Can you still say so
looking at Mama's crashed chateau?
What do you mean by that?!
What's happening there?!
Most deaths...
By smell...
It was just an accident!
...come unwillingly.
Seriously?!
Hey! Guys!
So it was an accident and now the Slugs
are failing to surveil by chance?!
You will...
Now, hurry up! Every minute counts!
Straw Hat!
They're coming from six o'clock!
die here soon!
I thought it'd take them longer!
If we get swallowed up by it, we're dead!
Pudding-chan dressed as a chef
is as cute as ever!
What?! So are you saying that
it's all their plan?!
They're the ships from earlier!
Oh, yeah! The Coup de Burst!
A person?!
What?!
We can't use it!
We don't have enough cola!
At the very least,
N-No way...
He's right!
Why don't you drop dead already, Straw Hat?!
since they arrived, unexpected
incidents have kept occurring-jour!
Pudding-sama, are you all right?!
Pedro, I'm sorry!
You sacrificed yourself to save us but...
Let's do it, Pudding-sama's husband!
Branch!
It's Brulee!
Cake!
Huh? Me?
Don't think that you can beat him
just with your spirit, punk!
Come here!
I edited out the incident
from the memories of the chefs.
No way... I don't...
I don't think that's possible...
An arrogant champion will
be knocked off his feet!
Big Bro Katakuri isn't
just an unbeatable man!
That means they think the wedding went off
without a problem and...
Big Mom is walking on the water!
In order not to bring shame to Mama
by any remote chance,
He's a superhuman who's never once
been on his back since he was born!
...w... we are... m... married!
Come on! That's ridiculous!
we'd better dispatch a forceful fleet
to the outermost part of our territory-amour!
But...
That's not the water... That's...
Stop it, Brulee!
...the wedding cake was ruined
due to unexpected weather.
The moment he was born,
he stood on his feet
...candy?!
and slept on a chair,
the legend says!
Mama got mad so we have to
hurry and make the cake again.
She's walking on a large
block of moving candy!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY
- BEGE AND THE OTHERS
He's never once lied down in his life!
He's a man who looks down on the ground!
That's how I overwrote their memories.
--Using candy?!
--Hey, does that mean...
I see.
The enemy fleet is approaching
from behind-rero!
Their memories of the time that they first made the cake
became clearer now so it'll help us remake it.
FIRETANK PIRATES - NOSTRA CASTELLO
Everyone, listen!
He's always noble!
The only person who can make those...
Calm and strong!
Here they come!
My cake!
He's perfect in every way!
It must be... him-teia!
Who came up with this blueprint
and recipe for the cake?!
That's who our Big Bro Katakuri is!
CHARLOTTE CUSTARD - SIXTH
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Lick...
We have the enemy ship in our range!
I did.
Sir, you wrote this?!
Candy Sea Slug!
Wait! Wait, wait!
All right! Start firing!
He's the masterpiece of Charlotte
and it's presumptuous for a short-ass like you...
Yeah. Let me know if there are any mistakes.
Where did Zeus go?
Wait a minute, Mama!
It's his job to carry Mama across the sea!
It's perfect!
If you do that,
the cake will sink into the sea, too!
...to even fight him!
You even got right the
secret ingredient which
Don't tell me...
Mama!
Executive Chef Streusen-sama
spent a week coming up with!
Shut up! Go away!
Bring the ship about quickly!
Prepare to fire the bow chaser!
But that's okay... I now have a reason
to pay them back, too.
--Hurry up!
--Okay!
I heard you were skilled
but you sure are something!
Pedro even sacrificed his own life!
And as husband and wife,
this cake-making will be...
D-Does this look okay, Jimbei-san?!
Yes, that's good enough!
Husband and wife?!
Fire-rero!
...your first joint work, strangely enough.
But it's impossible!
You're trying to trim all the sails on the ship single-handedly!
Well, I can just substitute my lost right arm
with candy but...
What are you trying to
do to my little sister?!
Yeah, it will be. I feel awkward.
Dammit! Fire the second round!
Husband and wife...
Nami! How is the wind?!
Every time I see my right hand
Big Bro!
You okay, Missis-sama?!
M... Missi...
melted by the heat of a cup
when I drink hot tea in the afternoon,
A strong wind is coming from the south!
Missis-sama!
Shoot!
Missis-sama! Missis-sama!
All right!
Stay with us, Missi...
What are you going to do, Jimbei?!
I'll remember... the Jaguar Mink's face!
Stop! She's gonna die!
Tart 20 and 25 got hit!
What?!
What? Hurry up and make repairs!
He called us husband and wife! Oh my!
We got a chance! Get away while we can!
Am I right, Napoleon?
Nothing is more humiliating than that.
Hey!
What? Suddenly, he said, "Hey" to me...
I'm gonna tack the ship quickly!
The Straw Hats are big-time criminals
in our country anyway.
What?!
Maybe it's not so bad to have a husband
who wears the pants in the house.
You must be kidding! Why do you wanna
turn the ship?!
Mochi Thrust!
They have no future.
No, but it's important to start things right.
We'll enter the Green Room!
The enemy ship moved out of range!
How should I make...
I-If you act like my master,
I'll kill you, Sanji...
Here we go! Here we go!
...his friends suffer to feel satisfied?!
Humph... They can't lose us!
Give it to me!
The Territory Slugs in the sea will
pick up their location soon!
I need some stuff in a hurry.
Non-homogenized milk, sugar beets,
bananas, black sesame,
Ouch...
GERMA KINGDOM
roasted soy flour, yogurt.
A lot of it.
That was close!
Yes, sir!
You bastard!
...san!
Everyone! It's a race against time
until the cake is complete!
Chiffon-chan, you bake
the giant chiffon cake.
All right! I'll show you
the ultimate Dosmar move!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Huh? Why, why, why?
I almost got crushed!
Pudding-chan,
you handle all the chocolate tempering.
Everyone's gone!
I really wanna eat fire!
I'm losing my strength...
Green Room?! What is that?!
You have two hours and forty minutes!
Oh, is that a party trick?
This trident is called Mole!
Why are we heading towards the wave?!
Jimbei!
Shut up!
It certainly is a fight against time.
I wanna eat thunderclouds, too...
When we get there,
I'll add my secret ingredient!
Wedding...
Your hand or your foot?
Name the body parts you can most do without.
SEA WITHIN THE TERRITORY OF TOTTO LAND
It leads anyone to the peak of happiness...
...cake!
Oh... So Lola-chan from Thriller Bark
was a master at making chocolate!
I'll sever them for you!
I'll make you taste true sweetness!
That's right. Lola was the Minister of Chocolate
running Cacao Island...
T-True sweetness?!
I see! By "Green Room," you mean "heaven"!
Please start with his head, Big Bro!
In three hours, we'll load the incomplete cake
on a ship and leave Cacao Island.
But ever since she left,
that seat has remained empty.
I got him!
Shut up, you fool!
Doctor! I'm finally coming to meet you!
Oh, why is that?
And as we let it cool down,
we'll decorate it on the ship.
Because everyone's favorite candidate here
keeps rejecting the offer...
Wh-What?!
It's over! This is impossible! It's not surfing!
Before we meet up with Luffy and the others
being chased by Big Mom, at the Sunny,
Right, Pudding?
Pedro!
B-Because, to me...
we'll finish making the greatest cake ever!
Big Sis Lola is the only Minister of Chocolate
for Chocolat Town!
I see. That sounds efficient.
Gum-Gum...
--But at a pace like that?
--No matter how you look at it, that's impossible!
Hold on to the ship tightly!
And I'm hoping she'll be back someday...
...Giant Rifle!
I'll chop you up!
We gotta do it!
Do you want Mama to destroy the country?!
I know what you mean but...
Splash!
There!
I'm sorry! We'll follow you!
Oh?
Damn you!
Oh? Oh? Oh?
You're selling us short...
Could I be mistaken?
All right!
You think you can bring Germa down
with that level of power!
Let's start baking!
No...
POUND - CHIFFON AND LOLA'S FATHER
I-I think that's my daughter!
For those who saved Lola!
I was listening!
What's wrong?! What happened?!
You shouldn't sell me short, either!
I've still got my best card!
Hey! Hey!
For Sanji-san!
Straw Hat!
I'll make my special extremely-fluffy
chiffon cake!
To where you guys are trying to rendezvous!
Hey!
Are you guys alright?!
Hey, can you hear me?!
What?!
I must help Sanji-san
and the others get away!
Hey! Straw Hat is running away!
She's gone now...
Somebody! Say something!
With my very sweet chocolate!
Chiffon...
Seems like he was talking to someone...
It's not just a wind!
Hey! Get out of there already, Pudding!
Keep hanging on, guys!
Nusstorte's special tornado decoration!
I won't let him get away!
Huh?
We'll get there in 10 hours at the earliest!
Around 1 AM!
N... No way!
I'll show them!
I'm wearing a wedding dress now!
My bold cooking!
Look for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
And we'll see you there!
Go to hell, Germa!
If I sit on the carpet with that man,
Don't mess with me!
How he died was so pathetic!
people will think that we're newlyweds
who just had a wedding!
That Pedro guy.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Are we in heaven? It's beautiful...
Straw Hat! You saw it too, right?
Clank.
What people?
Big Bro Peros!
This is a hell of a ship!
You never know who's watching!
And it bothers me if they think so!
I guess he tried to kill me
by sacrificing his worthless life,
Do you wanna play with a wave again, Mama?
The Green Room is a brief "wave room"
that forms inside a collapsing wave.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
It.. It... It really bothers me, okay?!
Come on! Let's do it!
but I'm very much alive as you hear.
Clank.
I feel bad about it but don't fall.
Mama, are you listening?
To children of the Fish-Man Tribe,
it was a perfect place to play!
This is Nusstorte from Germa's ship.
So he died for absolutely nothing!
Right?!
What?! Their ship hasn't sunk yet?!
S-Shut up!
Big Bro! How did it go with Germa?!
Then, this space is...
Oh! How kind he is!
He's worried about me!
We crushed them with ten thousand soldiers.
Their kingdom is devastated!
Are you sure, Brulee?!
It is decided that you're gonna die in vain, too,
just like Pedro.
Yeah, I heard their voices!
No way...
Why don't you let him kill you already?
Lick.
Who do you think you are?!
Whether I fall or not isn't your business!
But the candy monster made a high wave
and swallowed them!
Oh!
That's my brother! But that was reckless...
We're inside the wave?!
Clank.
How did they escape?!
With our strength, it was a piece of cake...
Hey, Brulee.
There's Cacao Island!
We're gonna sail through it! Hang on!
Alright! Let's start making the cake
as soon as we arrive!
Oh, Big Bro.
I don't know how they did it!
Oh, you're full of confidence, Big Bro!
Hey! Did you hear what I said, Sanji...
Just wake up already.
Our soldiers can't go anywhere if you're sleeping.
But I'm sure they're alive and will
emerge at Cacao Island around midnight!
...-san!
Okay.
Just when I thought he saved his crew valiantly,
look how he is now.
By the way, Big Bro...
That's what they promised Straw Hat Luffy.
It's no mistake!
Hawk Gatling!
You didn't destroy the manufacturing
system for the clones, did you?
You got a nice ship and a good navigator!
What they don't know is...
B...
B... Big Bro!
...that it's our final destination, too!
--Don't tell me Katakuri-sama is...
--...Under attack?!
If you can control it well, this ship is invincible!
Of course not.
That's what we wanted all along.
Mama! The cake that you crave
is in Chocolat Town, Cacao Island!
I can't believe it! He's controlling the sloop
like it's his own limb!
But other than that, it's
completely destroyed.
Can't wait, right?
That's how it should be!
I've never seen such a helmsman!
Damn Germa! They were doomed
the moment we had them in our sights!
I lied to her out of desperation,
You couldn't beat me
with your speed and power.
You're cool, Jimbei!
but if I take her there like this,
I'd be able to cover it up!
What happened to the Straw Hats?
So we're not gonna die?!
What are you gonna use next, Straw Hat?
Actually, we let them take to sea.
I'm following your lead on this...
Pudding is baking the cake at Cacao Island!
They're heading due west...
Am I doing it wrong?
Whatever happens, everything will be settled!
Well, it's only a matter
of time before we get them.
Yay!
How boring. You're gonna just use both.
I'll leave it to you!
I thought we weren't gonna make it!
Yeah, good job!
But this way, it's more efficient.
That's impressive, Jimbei-san!
Clank.
Very impressive, Jimbei!
And that's how it is...
You must know your capabilities by now.
So Luffy-kun and the others are okay.
Gum-Gum...
Wedding cake!
Hm? Nami?
What should we do now?
...Elephant Gatling!
That's our Katakuri-sama!
Mama, it's that way, huh?!
Straw Hat only has two arms
but Katakuri-sama has dozens!
Bubble, bubble... Sluggie-gie...
Let's go! Set sail!
Wait a sec! That's Nuts Island!
He's throwing ten times more punches!
Roger!
Too slow!
Wedding...
Muscle Balloon!
Whoa-whoa, what are you doing?!
Mama! Their ship isn't heading there!
The cake will be delivered to Cacao Island!
...cake!
Katakuri-sama, that's so brutal!
Too light!
Wedding...
--No, Mama! Stop!
--...cake!
Well, who cares...
That serves those little punks right!
Don't go that way!
You have no ability that's better than mine!
My lie was swallowed by the sea along with their ship!
Why do I have to just stand here and watch...
Lick!
This is Perospero. Hey, Katakuri.
...when I know you'll upgrade your power?
We took care of all of them!
You're quite tough.
I'm not gonna get beaten by you!
What?!
Hey, Nami! Brook! Carrot!
It's no use!
Chopper! Jimbei!
But I guess you see now.
Gum-Gum...
Oh, no!
As I said before, in terms of ability,
We were gonna invade the ship now!
anything you can do, I can do better.
The plan's aborted, guys!
...Red Hawk!
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
It seems like the ship has already
sank into the sea.
You're inferior to me in speed
and power and everything.
I'm telling you that I'm
not underestimating you!
But it's strange, Big Sis.
The other side of the mirror
doesn't look like it's underwater.
Straw Hat finally gave up.
What a pathetic end.
Look!
Rubber won't lose to mochi!
No way!
But, just to make sure, shoot one more.
Brulee! Take those soldiers
and go set fire or something to Straw Hat's ship.
Don't push your luck!
Okay!
Mirror Mochi!
Big Sis Brulee!
What? Those are mochi, too?!
We found a mirror that
links to Straw Hat's ship!
MARSCARPONE - 34TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
JOSCARPONE - 29TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Wow! The mirror! Big Sis, it suddenly broke!
Oh, no! Once they come down on me,
I'll be buried alive!
There must be one or two more!
What? What? What's going on?!
Yes, you'll be choked!
All right! Let's shoot flaming arrows
at Straw Hat's ship!
I can't see Straw Hat now, either!
You're dead!
Don't tell me he can move
as fast as Katakuri-sama!
No one's ever gotten away from my mochi!
I hope they get done in by Mama
while in a frenzy from the fire.
Give up!
Straw Hat.
Are you trying to compete?
Gum-Gum...
Yikes!
I'm not gonna lose!
...Thor Elephant Gun!
Gum-Gum...
Here's a finishing touch...
Give me the mirror!
...Hawk Stamp!
Nami-san! Why did you break the mirror?!
Leave them alone!
Luffy-san can't come back to the ship without it!
I thought you were in a one-on-one duel with me,
Straw Hat.
Is that it?
No way!
Let me focus just on this guy!
He disappeared again!
Take that!
I'm sorry that I have to wrap it up this way...
I was getting a little irritated!
Just break them all!
All the mirrors on the ship!
Now, burn down Straw Hat's ship!
Since it took me a lot of
time and trouble to beat you,
But...
I'm 40 minutes late for today's merienda.
Do you wanna get in Luffy's way?!
I knew Katakuri-sama is
in a different league!
I told you that I could see them!
Roger!
It's the Captain's orders! Hurry up!
Are you ready, Joscar?
The suffering won't last long...
I am, Marscar.
Goodbye, Straw Hat...
Are you gonna show your power next?
Now, shoot them!
There is no future for you!
Give up already.
Stop!!
The barrage of Katakuri's deadly attack,
Willow Mochi, corners Luffy!
The Emperor of the Sea
Big Mom's enormous power
A duel between Luffy and Katakuri begins!
Katakuri comes to finish Luffy off!
The "merienda," the time of day when
Katakuri concentrates his mind,
takes place in a forbidden shrine.
allows her to control even
the raging sea as she likes!
Luffy is unable to do
The Gum-Gum power that has
brought down tons of enemies
anything against Katakuri
who launches attacks in waves with
There is only one piece of a mirror that allows Luffy and his crew
to promise to reunite.
When a big wave as tall as a
battlement comes for the Sunny,
and the undefeated Mochi-Mochi power clash directly!
It's a holy ritual which even
his siblings have never seen!
his deadly trident, Mole!
Without seeing the light of hope for victory,
Nami and the others think
death is unavoidable,
For his deeply-worried crew,
Captain Luffy shows his chivalrous spirit!
Power vs. power, against the
strongest-ever enemy Katakuri,\
The furious Luffy closes in on the
invincible superhuman Katakuri's hidden secret!
the Mochi-Mochi Fruit's formidable
awakened power finally catches Luffy!
but Jimbei takes the helm and goes into action
for the sake of the crew!
luffy throws an all-out, giant punch!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Threat of the Mole! Luffy's Silent Fight!"
"The Green Room! An Invincible Helmsman, Jimbei!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hard Battle Starts! Luffy vs. Katakuri!"
"The Forbidden Secret! Katakuri's Merienda!"
"The End of the Deadly Battle?!
Katakuri's Awakening in Anger!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!