My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
In order to escape from
the Whole Cake Island,
Luffy and his allies
finally reached the Sunny.
However, Sweet General Katakuri
and the others who were there
waiting blocked their way!
Then, Pedro sacrificed himself
along with Perospero so that
Luffy and the others could escape.
The allies who he saved suppressed their sorrow
and prepared for the Coup de Burst.
Set sail, you guys!
If we waste this moment
we'd make Pedro ashamed of us!
Listen to me!
I'll be back! I'll leave the rest to you!
Okay, here we go!
Coup de...
...Burst!
You succeeded...
Here, I can pummel you as much as I want!
"The Man with a Bounty of Billion!
The Strongest Sweet General, Katakuri!"
What an idiot!
I can't believe he broke the mirror himself!
Are you trying to sacrifice yourself
and let your friends escape?!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
--Don't be silly!
--Who do you think you're talking to?!
Katakuri-sama's bounty is
one billion, fifty-seven million berries!
He's the strongest of the Sweet 3 Generals!
You're dangerous, Straw Hat Luffy...
Even though it was reckless,
there aren't that many people who
have caused this much damage...
...on the Big Mom Pirates.
If I let you get away,
you'll be a bigger threat to Mama.
But in terms of ability,
you're on a way lower level than me...
I've got to take care of you now.
I'm not gonna be defeated!
I'll teach you that there's always
somebody better than you.
Here I go!
Is that all you've got?
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Jet Twin Pistols!
If I really wanna dodge...
I can dodge forever.
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
...Eagle Bazooka!
Stop right there!
Where did Straw Hat go?
Katakuri-sama!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Axe!
A surprise attack is...
...useless.
--We can't see him!
--Is this what he wants?
Hawk Gatling!
--Katakuri-sama!
--No way!
Brace for impact!
I don't see anyone coming after us.
It's going to rain...
Hey! Luffy!
Let me hear you if you're there!
He went into the Mirroworld...
Taking Katakuri...
What?!
Luffy...
Someone broke the mirror!
We can't go in like this!
Let's trust our captain!
He said he'd be back!
Yeah!
Uh-huh!
Speaking of being missing...
I don't see Pedro-san, either.
--Oh, you're right...
--Did he go somewhere?
Did he go into the Mirroworld with Luffy-san?
Pedro is... Pedro is...
--Carrot?
--Did something happen?
Hey, guys, what's the matter?!
Chopper, Brook, listen carefully.
The thing is... Pedro is...
No way...
You're kidding... right?
No... No...
Pedro-san...
Pedro-san sacrificed himself...
It's my fault!
If I had protected the Sunny to the end!
It's because... I was weak!
If we were... If we were...!
If we were stronger...
Leave the crying to our enemies.
We should not get upset.
Hey, Jimbei-san!
How could you say such a cold thing?!
You knew Pedro-san the shortest out of all of us,
that's why--
I'm just telling you not
to lose your concentration!
We had our backs against
the wall at the coast...
He knew the place was extremely dangerous
so he had been preparing to sacrifice himself.
This is...
...Pedro's victory!
How much damage did the enemy take
because of you guys?!
It's an unprecedented major blunder to them!
Your strength really drove Big Mom
into the corner!
Don't you hear Pedro's
voice inside you saying...
"Keep going"?!
Luffy sensed it instantly...
and decided to take the enemy on
all by himself.
Katakuri is worth over a billion!
It's all or nothing!
It's not over yet!
We're still in Totto Land!
Soon, we will be chased by the pirate queen of the country,
Big Mom!
And the enemy fleet can attack us at any time
from any direction!
Until you get out of the territory
where Big Mom reigns,
you can't lose your concentration!
Isn't Pedro inside of you saying that?!
I'm very sorry.
I was way out of line.
--Nami, give us directions!
--Okay!
Sanji-kun and the others will come to us
from Cacao Island
so we don't wanna miss each other.
There'll be a strong wind soon.
It's a tailwind!
So starboard!
Hard a starboard!
Catch the wind on the starboard side
and head straight west!
--We'll take the shortest way!
--Roger!
I'll go replenish the
cola that was just used!
I'll stand guard!
Okay!
I'm in position!
Uh-huh!
Let me monitor the currents!
They're coming from six o'clock!
I thought it'd take them longer!
They're the ships from earlier!
A person?!
N-No way...
Cake!
No way... I don't...
I don't think that's possible...
Big Mom is walking on the water!
Come on! That's ridiculous!
That's not the water... That's...
...candy?!
She's walking on a large
block of moving candy!
--Using candy?!
--Hey, does that mean...
The only person who can make those...
It must be... him-teia!
Lick...
Candy Sea Slug!
Where did Zeus go?
It's his job to carry Mama across the sea!
Don't tell me...
But that's okay... I now have a reason
to pay them back, too.
Pedro even sacrificed his own life!
Well, I can just substitute my lost right arm
with candy but...
Every time I see my right hand
melted by the heat of a cup
when I drink hot tea in the afternoon,
I'll remember... the Jaguar Mink's face!
Am I right, Napoleon?
Nothing is more humiliating than that.
The Straw Hats are big-time criminals
in our country anyway.
They have no future.
How should I make...
...his friends suffer to feel satisfied?!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Huh? Why, why, why?
Everyone's gone!
I really wanna eat fire!
I'm losing my strength...
I wanna eat thunderclouds, too...
SEA WITHIN THE TERRITORY OF TOTTO LAND
Oh... So Lola-chan from Thriller Bark
was a master at making chocolate!
That's right. Lola was the Minister of Chocolate
running Cacao Island...
But ever since she left,
that seat has remained empty.
Oh, why is that?
Because everyone's favorite candidate here
keeps rejecting the offer...
Right, Pudding?
B-Because, to me...
Big Sis Lola is the only Minister of Chocolate
for Chocolat Town!
And I'm hoping she'll be back someday...
I know what you mean but...
Oh?
Oh? Oh? Oh?
Could I be mistaken?
No...
POUND - CHIFFON AND LOLA'S FATHER
I-I think that's my daughter!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
She's gone now...
Chiffon...
Hey! Get out of there already, Pudding!
N... No way!
I'm wearing a wedding dress now!
If I sit on the carpet with that man,
people will think that we're newlyweds
who just had a wedding!
What people?
You never know who's watching!
And it bothers me if they think so!
It.. It... It really bothers me, okay?!
I feel bad about it but don't fall.
S-Shut up!
Oh! How kind he is!
He's worried about me!
Who do you think you are?!
Whether I fall or not isn't your business!
There's Cacao Island!
Alright! Let's start making the cake
as soon as we arrive!
Hey! Did you hear what I said, Sanji...
...-san!
Hawk Gatling!
--Don't tell me Katakuri-sama is...
--...Under attack?!
I'm following your lead on this...
Am I doing it wrong?
But this way, it's more efficient.
That's our Katakuri-sama!
Straw Hat only has two arms
but Katakuri-sama has dozens!
He's throwing ten times more punches!
Katakuri-sama, that's so brutal!
You're quite tough.
But I guess you see now.
As I said before, in terms of ability,
anything you can do, I can do better.
You're inferior to me in speed
and power and everything.
Rubber won't lose to mochi!
I can't see Straw Hat now, either!
Don't tell me he can move
as fast as Katakuri-sama!
Are you trying to compete?
I'm not gonna lose!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Stamp!
Is that it?
No way!
He disappeared again!
I knew Katakuri-sama is
in a different league!
Are you gonna show your power next?
Give up already.
A duel between Luffy and Katakuri begins!
The Gum-Gum power that has
brought down tons of enemies
and the undefeated Mochi-Mochi power clash directly!
Power vs. power, against the
strongest-ever enemy Katakuri,\
luffy throws an all-out, giant punch!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hard Battle Starts! Luffy vs. Katakuri!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!