Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Stamp!
Is that it?
No way!
Are you gonna show your power next?
Give up already.
That's a gigantic fist!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant...
...Gun!
Katakuri-sama's is even bigger!
Did I do the "Elephant Gun" right?
Are those...?!
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
It's fluttering higher and higher
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
Why did you give up on your search?
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
Limitless power surges
kagirinaki chikara umareru
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place that I want to go with you
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
The sea route that we take
susumiyuku kouro nara
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
crushes my helpless heart
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
I'm wanting you
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
Close your eyes and listen carefully
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Let's look for your answer
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
We are hope
At the broad, blue end of the world
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
There is a place I have to return to with you
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
We will be forever
boku tachi wa eien ni
decided long ago in the past
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
"A Hard Battle Starts!
Luffy vs. Katakuri!"
This time, he's got two giant fists!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly...
...Magnum!
Katakuri-sama's are even bigger!
He can't do anything like that!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Axe!
No! Katakuri-sama!
Katakuri-sama's foot is even bigger!
There will be no victory in your future.
Katakuri-sama wins!
You see how strong Sweet
General Katakuri-sama is?!
He's not in the same class with
just another squirt like you!
That must've finished him!
No one can survive after getting such a...
Not yet... No...
I'm sorry.
I told them that I'd threaten you
and force you to help me make the cake.
Never mind, Pudding.
That's the position I'm in now.
It just makes things complicated
so quit smiling at her!
Pudding! Pudding, pull yourself together!
Don't you wanna save Sanji?!
I do!
You're an eyesore! Why don't you get wrapped up
in Rabian and hide yourself, Sanji...
Yeah, okay.
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
...san!
How beautiful she is in her wedding dress!
I feel sorry for her.
Her wedding was messed up.
But even with that sad look,
she's still lovely!
Oh! The Minister of Fluff!
Chi... Chiffon-sama!
Everyone, don't worry!
Big Sis Chiffon is not a key figure in the rebellion!
The responsible one is
her husband, Gang Bege!
Okay...
Wh-What's the matter?!
Crap!
Oh, no!
We don't have time!
Let's go to the Sweets Factory now!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Well done, Pudding! She distracted him!
Well, Pudding-sama,
I can't believe what happened today...
Who could expect the happy wedding would be
ruined by Straw Hat Luffy's invasion and Bege's treason!
That Sanji guy was a terrible humbug, too!
What's done is done.
I'm sure you're having a hard time!
I wonder how angry Mama is.
Yes, she's mad and hungry.
In addition, she's in her Hunger Pangs attack
and could destroy this country.
Oh, how horrible...
Is everything ready?
Yes! About an hour ago,
31 chefs were dispatched from the Whole Cake Island.
With our pride as Head Chefs of
the Whole Cake Island,
let's do it!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring... Clank!
Katakuri, it's me.
You escaped death, Big Bro Peros.
Yes, barely.
What happened to Straw Hat's underlings?
Believe or not,
they launched their ship and
escaped our encirclement.
I'm chasing them with Mama now...
We're walking on the water.
They're tenaciously trying to flee
but we'll catch up to them in no time.
Amande and the others' fleet
will be here soon, too.
No matter how much they struggle,
they have no chance.
How is it over there?
I heard Straw Hat challenged you.
Yeah...
He's down on the floor, pathetically.
I'll finish him off right here.
SWEETS FACTORY, CHOCOLAT TOWN
We've been expecting you, Pudding-sama!
We're the 31 Head Chefs
of the Whole Cake Island!
WCI: 31!
Big Sis Chiffon and I are going to make
the only wedding cake that can stop Mama.
Please assist us.
Yes, ma'am! We're already
making preparations!
Pudding-sama was the bride
so she was affected the most by what happened...
You can count on me!
I'm not gonna let Mama destroy our country!
Pudding-sama!
I can't believe she's overcoming the pain
and overseeing the cake-making herself!
She's literally a goddess of salvation!
Good luck!
Go ahead and get inside with Rabian.
Okay.
Please, everyone! Listen to me!
I need you to do me a favor!
We're going to risk our lives and bake the cake
that will influence the fate of our country!
We really need to concentrate!
So, please don't look inside the factory
under any circumstances while we're at it!
Yes, ma'am!
And no matter who it is,
don't let anyone look inside!
Yes, ma'am!
We understand! Pudding-sama!
Thank you all!
Good luck, Pudding-sama!
This way, they won't see Sanji-san...
And now, I must deal with those
who will work with us!
Head Chefs! Come inside one by one!
Bouche, head chef of the first kitchen,
reporting for duty.
Stay still.
I'm gonna modify your memories... Edit!
--Hey, let me down.
--Okay!
Here you go!
That must've been a tough ride.
INSIDE THE FACTORY
We've no time so I drew a
blueprint of the cake en route.
What?! Do you remember it?!
Pretty much.
No way! Maybe you could remember the shape
but how could you even tell the ingredients without tasting it?
By smell...
Seriously?!
Now, hurry up! Every minute counts!
Pudding-chan dressed as a chef
is as cute as ever!
What?!
Pudding-sama, are you all right?!
Let's do it, Pudding-sama's husband!
Huh? Me?
Come here!
I edited out the incident
from the memories of the chefs.
That means they think the wedding went off
without a problem and...
...w... we are... m... married!
But...
...the wedding cake was ruined
due to unexpected weather.
Mama got mad so we have to
hurry and make the cake again.
That's how I overwrote their memories.
I see.
Their memories of the time that they first made the cake
became clearer now so it'll help us remake it.
Who came up with this blueprint
and recipe for the cake?!
I did.
Sir, you wrote this?!
Yeah. Let me know if there are any mistakes.
It's perfect!
You even got right the
secret ingredient which
Executive Chef Streusen-sama
spent a week coming up with!
I heard you were skilled
but you sure are something!
And as husband and wife,
this cake-making will be...
Husband and wife?!
...your first joint work, strangely enough.
Yeah, it will be. I feel awkward.
Husband and wife...
You okay, Missis-sama?!
M... Missi...
Missis-sama!
Missis-sama! Missis-sama!
Stay with us, Missi...
Stop! She's gonna die!
What?!
He called us husband and wife! Oh my!
Hey!
What? Suddenly, he said, "Hey" to me...
Maybe it's not so bad to have a husband
who wears the pants in the house.
No, but it's important to start things right.
I-If you act like my master,
I'll kill you, Sanji...
I need some stuff in a hurry.
Non-homogenized milk, sugar beets,
bananas, black sesame,
roasted soy flour, yogurt.
A lot of it.
Yes, sir!
...san!
Everyone! It's a race against time
until the cake is complete!
Chiffon-chan, you bake
the giant chiffon cake.
Pudding-chan,
you handle all the chocolate tempering.
You have two hours and forty minutes!
It certainly is a fight against time.
When we get there,
I'll add my secret ingredient!
It leads anyone to the peak of happiness...
I'll make you taste true sweetness!
T-True sweetness?!
In three hours, we'll load the incomplete cake
on a ship and leave Cacao Island.
And as we let it cool down,
we'll decorate it on the ship.
Before we meet up with Luffy and the others
being chased by Big Mom, at the Sunny,
we'll finish making the greatest cake ever!
I see. That sounds efficient.
--But at a pace like that?
--No matter how you look at it, that's impossible!
We gotta do it!
Do you want Mama to destroy the country?!
I'm sorry! We'll follow you!
All right!
Let's start baking!
For those who saved Lola!
For Sanji-san!
I'll make my special extremely-fluffy
chiffon cake!
I must help Sanji-san
and the others get away!
With my very sweet chocolate!
Keep hanging on, guys!
I'll show them!
My bold cooking!
How he died was so pathetic!
That Pedro guy.
Straw Hat! You saw it too, right?
I guess he tried to kill me
by sacrificing his worthless life,
but I'm very much alive as you hear.
So he died for absolutely nothing!
Right?!
It is decided that you're gonna die in vain, too,
just like Pedro.
Why don't you let him kill you already?
Lick.
Clank.
Hey, Brulee.
Oh, Big Bro.
Just wake up already.
Our soldiers can't go anywhere if you're sleeping.
Okay.
Just when I thought he saved his crew valiantly,
look how he is now.
B...
B... Big Bro!
You couldn't beat me
with your speed and power.
What are you gonna use next, Straw Hat?
How boring. You're gonna just use both.
You must know your capabilities by now.
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gatling!
Too slow!
Too light!
You have no ability that's better than mine!
Straw Hat finally gave up.
What a pathetic end.
Brulee! Take those soldiers
and go set fire or something to Straw Hat's ship.
Okay!
Big Sis Brulee!
We found a mirror that
links to Straw Hat's ship!
MARSCARPONE - 34TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
JOSCARPONE - 29TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
There must be one or two more!
All right! Let's shoot flaming arrows
at Straw Hat's ship!
I hope they get done in by Mama
while in a frenzy from the fire.
Yikes!
Give me the mirror!
Leave them alone!
I thought you were in a one-on-one duel with me,
Straw Hat.
Take that!
Now, burn down Straw Hat's ship!
Roger!
Are you ready, Joscar?
I am, Marscar.
Now, shoot them!
Stop!!
The Emperor of the Sea
Big Mom's enormous power
allows her to control even
the raging sea as she likes!
When a big wave as tall as a
battlement comes for the Sunny,
Nami and the others think
death is unavoidable,
but Jimbei takes the helm and goes into action
for the sake of the crew!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Green Room! An Invincible Helmsman, Jimbei!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!