kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
In order to let the Sunny escape
from the Whole Cake Island,
Luffy stayed in the Mirroworld by himself
and held off Katakuri.
There are still some mirrors on the ship,
aren't there?!
--What?!
--Maybe in the boys' room or the bathroom?!
Break them all! To pieces!
Are you out of your mind?!
How would you come back, then?!
Now, you guys, keep shooting!
We're gonna keep shooting, Joscar.
Yes, we are, Marscar.
Nami! Hurry up and break the mirrors!
All of them!
But...
An army of enemies is on its way!
I can't stop them by myself!
Let me focus just on this guy!
Nami-san! Why did you break the mirror?!
Just break them all!
All the mirrors on the ship!
But...
Do you wanna get in Luffy's way?!
It's the Captain's orders! Hurry up!
"The Threat of the Mole!
Luffy's Silent Fight!"
There are still some mirrors!
I found one, Joscar!
I found it, too, Marscar!
Let's do it, Joscar!
Let's do it, Marscar!
Make sure to find any kind of mirror!
Shoot!
What?!
What's going on?!
This is the last one!
Are they alive?!
Big Bro Peros said they took care of them...
I guess the ship sank and the mirrors were
shattered by the water pressure, Joscar!
Yeah, I guess that's it, Marscar!
Something is not right...
Hey!
Hey, Luffy!
Are you okay?!
Chopper!
We need to talk so get away from the enemies!
Okay!
Are you guys alright?!
Hey! Straw Hat is running away!
What happened?!
The candy guy said the Sunny sank!
We thought it'd sink, too!
But Jimbei was awesome!
Why are we heading towards the wave?!
Jimbei!
Hold on to the ship tightly!
I can't believe it! He's controlling the sloop
like it's his own limb!
I've never seen such a helmsman!
If it weren't for Jimbei,
we'd all have...
...drowned in the sea!
We're all fine, Luffy!
Luffy-san!
We broke all the mirrors on the ship!
Okay! That's good!
Now the enemies can't invade the ship
but you can't come back, either!
Yeah, that's okay! I'll figure something...
No, you can't!
You don't even have a plan!
Listen carefully, Luffy!
Sanji-kun is baking the cake
at Cacao Island now!
That's where we're heading!
We'll get there in 10 hours at the earliest!
Around 1 AM!
So as soon as you kick that guy's ass,
look for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
And we'll see you there!
Damn! I can't get it off!
Is something wrong, Luffy?
Are you listening?
Luffy!
Yeah!
Hey! Stay focused!
Maybe he's in trouble!
Please respond!
Luffy!
Are you okay, Luffy?!
Luffy-san!
Willow Mochi!
Luffy?
You're fine, right, Luffy-san?!
What's the matter, Luffy?!
Hurry up and get there, guys!
I'll probably be there soon
and get tired of waiting!
Yeah!
See you later, guys!
Our pursuers will be here soon!
Let's keep an eye out!
Roger!
Let's go to the observation deck, Carrot!
Okay, Chobro!
"I'm not gonna die here"...
That's what you'll say...
Is that all you have to say before you die?
I'm not gonna die here!
SWEET CITY
Haven't we gotten any updates
on Straw Hat and the others-soir?
Could it be that they made
it out of our territory?
That's impossible!
Once they take to sea, the surrounding
Territory Slugs will sense them for sure!
On top of that, Mama and our siblings
have set out, too, chasing them.
They have no chance against our encirclement.
I hope so...
Believe in your family!
The Germa Kingdom is about to fall, too!
Go to ruin, Germa!
We'll have your scientific technology!
There's no cure for a fool!
Do you think you can burn me
with such a small flame?
Act as tough as you like now!
Huh?
The Germa Kingdom ends today!
No one dies because they want to.
Most deaths...
...come unwillingly.
You will...
die here soon!
He's right!
Why don't you drop dead already, Straw Hat?!
Branch!
It's Brulee!
Don't think that you can beat him
just with your spirit, punk!
Big Bro Katakuri isn't
just an unbeatable man!
He's a superhuman who's never once
been on his back since he was born!
Stop it, Brulee!
The moment he was born,
he stood on his feet
and slept on a chair,
the legend says!
He's never once lied down in his life!
He's a man who looks down on the ground!
He's always noble!
Calm and strong!
He's perfect in every way!
That's who our Big Bro Katakuri is!
He's the masterpiece of Charlotte
and it's presumptuous for a short-ass like you...
...to even fight him!
Shut up! Go away!
What are you trying to
do to my little sister?!
Big Bro!
Mochi Thrust!
Ouch...
That was close!
I almost got crushed!
This trident is called Mole!
Your hand or your foot?
Name the body parts you can most do without.
I'll sever them for you!
Please start with his head, Big Bro!
Shut up, you fool!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Rifle!
I was listening!
Straw Hat!
To where you guys are trying to rendezvous!
Are you guys alright?!
Hey! Straw Hat is running away!
Seems like he was talking to someone...
I won't let him get away!
We'll get there in 10 hours at the earliest!
Around 1 AM!
Look for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
And we'll see you there!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Big Bro Peros!
Do you wanna play with a wave again, Mama?
Come on! Let's do it!
Mama, are you listening?
What?! Their ship hasn't sunk yet?!
Are you sure, Brulee?!
Yeah, I heard their voices!
But the candy monster made a high wave
and swallowed them!
How did they escape?!
I don't know how they did it!
But I'm sure they're alive and will
emerge at Cacao Island around midnight!
That's what they promised Straw Hat Luffy.
It's no mistake!
What they don't know is...
...that it's our final destination, too!
Mama! The cake that you crave
is in Chocolat Town, Cacao Island!
Can't wait, right?
I lied to her out of desperation,
but if I take her there like this,
I'd be able to cover it up!
Pudding is baking the cake at Cacao Island!
Whatever happens, everything will be settled!
Wedding cake!
Mama, it's that way, huh?!
Wait a sec! That's Nuts Island!
Whoa-whoa, what are you doing?!
Mama! Their ship isn't heading there!
The cake will be delivered to Cacao Island!
Wedding...
--No, Mama! Stop!
--...cake!
Don't go that way!
I'm not gonna get beaten by you!
It's no use!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Don't push your luck!
Give up!
Straw Hat.
Gum-Gum...
...Thor Elephant Gun!
I told you that I could see them!
There is no future for you!
Katakuri comes to finish Luffy off!
Luffy is unable to do
anything against Katakuri
who launches attacks in waves with
his deadly trident, Mole!
Without seeing the light of hope for victory,
the Mochi-Mochi Fruit's formidable
awakened power finally catches Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The End of the Deadly Battle?!
Katakuri's Awakening in Anger!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!