kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
kimi to honki de kokoro
butsukeatta yorokobi mo
The joy of letting our true
feelings fly at each other
warai korogete namida
kawakashita setsunasa mo
The pain from how we laughed
our heads off to dry our tears
tsunagi awasete kaze no naka Ah
We connect them together and in the wind Ah
hatameiteiru yo takaku takaku
It's fluttering higher and higher
Why sagasu koto wo akirameta no
Why did you give up on your search?
Why hitori tatakai tsudukeru no
Why do you keep fighting by yourself?
nee, donna mirai kakugo shita no
Say, what kind of future did you prepare for?
yume wa mou te ni shita no
Have you fulfilled your dream?
kimi e no omoi ga takanatte
My heart throbs at the thought of you
kagirinaki chikara umareru
Limitless power surges
motomeru naraba dokomademo
kawaranu kizuna furikazasou
As long as you wish, we'll
brandish our unchanging bond
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to mezashitai basho ga aru
There is a place that I want to go with you
susumiyuku kouro nara
The sea route that we take
tooi mukashi mou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
mada todokanai kimi no koe ga
Your voice that hasn't reached me yet
muryoku na mune wo oshitsubusu
crushes my helpless heart
boku wa kimi wo motometeiru kara
I'm wanting you
hikari sashikomu asa wo shinjite iyou
so I'll keep believing in the
morning when the light comes in
me wo tojite mimi wo sumashite
Close your eyes and listen carefully
sagashi dasou kimi no kotae wo
Let's look for your answer
michi wa kanarazu tsuduiteiru
yo mada mitakoto no nai umi e
The road always continues towards
the sea that you've never seen
We are hope
aoku hiroi sekai no hate ni
At the broad, blue end of the world
kimi to kaeru beki basho ga aru
There is a place I have to return to with you
boku tachi wa eien ni
We will be forever
tooi mukashi sou kimeteita
decided long ago in the past
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...became separated but kept fighting
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Having cut off his retreat, Luffy continues the fierce
one-on-one dual he
challenged Sweet General Katakuri to.
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Luffy promised Nami and the others
to rendezvous,
but his every attack is foreseen by Katakuri
who uses the Haki of the
Color of Observation.
There is no future for you!
"The End of the Deadly Battle?!
Katakuri's Awakening in Anger!"
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Twin Pistol!
That was close!
Mochi Thrust!
So pathetic...
How much longer are you gonna
go on disgracing yourself?
Ouch!
You can't get away!
How annoying the way he moves!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Spear!
He's gone!
He never learns!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Corkscrew Magnum!
Damn! I can't hit him with my Haki...
I can't hit him without my Haki!
On top of that, he's able to
hit me precisely where I dodge.
This is doubling my fatigue.
I feel the same.
No one's ever evaded my attacks like that.
It's stressing me out!
You tried to take the Mole away from me...
Damn! I almost got it!
Gum-Gum...
...Eagle Bazooka!
This is it...
No matter how many times you dodge,
I'll just foresee further...
Oh, no!
I can't get out!
Die...!
I grabbed the Mole!
Even though it was only with my legs!
How absurd!
Flowing Mochi!
Wh-What the?!
The floor has turned into mochi!
This is what Doflamingo did!
Listen, fledgling!
Devil Fruit abilities have...
...yet another stage to
them called "Awakening"!
The ability will awaken rarely
and begin to affect things other than its user's body!
Of course, my ability has been awakened...
Oh, no!
It's no use.
With elasticity and viscosity like this,
you're immobilized.
Should I just chop you up?
Or should I let you suffocate in the mochi?
How would you like to die?
I'm not gonna die!
Gear Four?
That's interesting.
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
It's strange...
We haven't got the location
of the Straw Hats' ship...
What are the Territory Slugs doing?!
Shut up, Pekoms!
Just stop crying already!
Big Bro Pedro!
I feel pity for him...
His childhood friend who was like a
brother to him chose death
by a deadly bombing-bon...
He was our enemy!
Bon...
It's pointless to die here!
The dawn of the new world is coming!
I have to go back!
This will break all of your-gara
magic spells, right?
Bombs?!
Goodbye.
I'm shocked, too-amour...
I saw Pedro begging for his life in tears
five years ago-bon.
That same man preferred to sacrifice his life
in order to let them set sail.
So what?
Big Bro...
Maybe we're still underestimating
Straw Hat Luffy-issant!
What's your point?
My point is that we should be careful-bon!
Mama'll never be done in by a punk like him!
You're saying that Straw Hat Luffy is
that much weaker?
Of course!
She's in a different class as a pirate!
Can you still say so
looking at Mama's crashed chateau?
It was just an accident!
So it was an accident and now the Slugs
are failing to surveil by chance?!
What?! So are you saying that
it's all their plan?!
At the very least,
since they arrived, unexpected
incidents have kept occurring-jour!
An arrogant champion will
be knocked off his feet!
In order not to bring shame to Mama
by any remote chance,
we'd better dispatch a forceful fleet
to the outermost part of our territory-amour!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY
- BEGE AND THE OTHERS
The enemy fleet is approaching
from behind-rero!
FIRETANK PIRATES - NOSTRA CASTELLO
Here they come!
CHARLOTTE CUSTARD - SIXTH
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
We have the enemy ship in our range!
All right! Start firing!
Bring the ship about quickly!
Prepare to fire the bow chaser!
Fire-rero!
Dammit! Fire the second round!
Shoot!
Tart 20 and 25 got hit!
What? Hurry up and make repairs!
We got a chance! Get away while we can!
The enemy ship moved out of range!
Humph... They can't lose us!
The Territory Slugs in the sea will
pick up their location soon!
GERMA KINGDOM
You bastard!
All right! I'll show you
the ultimate Dosmar move!
Oh, is that a party trick?
Shut up!
I got him!
Wh-What?!
I'll chop you up!
There!
Damn you!
You're selling us short...
You think you can bring Germa down
with that level of power!
You shouldn't sell me short, either!
I've still got my best card!
What?!
It's not just a wind!
Nusstorte's special tornado decoration!
Go to hell, Germa!
Don't mess with me!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
This is Nusstorte from Germa's ship.
Big Bro! How did it go with Germa?!
We crushed them with ten thousand soldiers.
Their kingdom is devastated!
Oh!
That's my brother! But that was reckless...
With our strength, it was a piece of cake...
Oh, you're full of confidence, Big Bro!
By the way, Big Bro...
You didn't destroy the manufacturing
system for the clones, did you?
Of course not.
That's what we wanted all along.
But other than that, it's
completely destroyed.
That's how it should be!
Damn Germa! They were doomed
the moment we had them in our sights!
What happened to the Straw Hats?
Actually, we let them take to sea.
They're heading due west...
Well, it's only a matter
of time before we get them.
I'll leave it to you!
Yeah, good job!
Clank.
And that's how it is...
So Luffy-kun and the others are okay.
What should we do now?
Let's go! Set sail!
Roger!
Muscle Balloon!
Why do I have to just stand here and watch...
...when I know you'll upgrade your power?
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
I'm telling you that I'm
not underestimating you!
Mirror Mochi!
What? Those are mochi, too?!
Oh, no! Once they come down on me,
I'll be buried alive!
Yes, you'll be choked!
You're dead!
No one's ever gotten away from my mochi!
Here's a finishing touch...
I'm sorry that I have to wrap it up this way...
I was getting a little irritated!
Since it took me a lot of
time and trouble to beat you,
I'm 40 minutes late for today's merienda.
The suffering won't last long...
Goodbye, Straw Hat...
The "merienda," the time of day when
Katakuri concentrates his mind,
takes place in a forbidden shrine.
It's a holy ritual which even
his siblings have never seen!
The furious Luffy closes in on the
invincible superhuman Katakuri's hidden secret!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Forbidden Secret! Katakuri's Merienda!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!