Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and
his family from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting in their own places
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
...kept fighting separate battles
...kept fighting in their own places
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Katakuri cornered Luffy
with his awakened Mochi-Mochi Fruit ability.
Having cut off his retreat, Luffy
continues the fierce one-on-one dual
Sanji started to transport the wedding cake
so as to fend off Big Mom's Hunger Pangs attack.
Luffy challenged Sweet General Katakuri
to a one-on-one dual
Having cut off his retreat,
Luffy continues the fierce one-on-one dual
he challenged Sweet General Katakuri to.
but since his Gear Four ran out,
he tried to ride it out in safety someplace else.
Goodbye, Straw Hat...
But Oven caught Chiffon, Bege's wife,
who was helping bake the cake, on a charge of treason.
Mirror Mochi!
You can get...
What? Those are mochi, too?!
I ate the mochi!
...hit, too!
What?!
You're dead!
What's with the pirate battles in this place?!
I have to eat something every time to win?!
To save Chiffon who is in trouble,
Bege headed for Cacao Island.
No one's ever gotten away from my mochi!
--Help!
--You fool!
Big Brother!
Chiffon, here I come!
Why were you there?!
Wait! Straw Hat!
Oh, doughnuts!
Meanwhile, Luffy is on the run
waiting for his Haki to be replenished.
So delicious, doughnuts!
I'm sorry that I have to wrap it up this way...
I was getting a little irritated!
However, that place was Nuts Island
where Big Mom was wreaking havoc.
I won't give you one more inch...
We're going back to square one.
Delicious to the hole, doughnuts!
Where are you?! Straw Hat!
"A Man's Way of Life!
Bege and Luffy's Determination as Captains!"
Since it took me a lot of time and trouble to beat you,
I'm 40 minutes late for today's merienda.
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others learn
that Luffy is in trouble...
Big Mom?
You saw me eating!
Where is the... cake?!
Big Bro Katakuri is a superhuman!
He's never been defeated!
What should we do?!
Goodbye, Straw Hat...
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others...
Those who have seen my true self...
Ikoku Sovereignty!
It's done!
Then today,
The ultimate cream - Simsim Whip!
...can't be left alive!
he'll lose for the first time.
"The Forbidden Secret!
Katakuri's Merienda!"
To save some time, we'll
finish the cake on the ship!
"Another Crisis!
Gear Four vs. Unstoppable Donuts!"
Let's get together with the Sunny
that's on its way here, A.S.A.P.!
I'm starting to understand...
...your ability.
Here we go!
It's my turn to say...
Let's take down Big Mom
who's causing our friends pain!
"Luffy Fights Back!
The Invincible Katakuri's Weak Point!"
This is it.
I won't lose!
That was close!
Thank goodness there was a mirror.
"The Rebellious Daughter, Chiffon!
Sanji's Big Plan for Transporting the Cake!"
I'll win!
I don't want anybody to bother me
until I regain my Haki.
Where is it?!
Gear Four!
Big Brother!
Wedding cake!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, you fool! Stop shouting!
Pâtissiers!
Yes, sir!
Rainfall Mochi!
We're on our way!
Brulee's here!
Power Mochi!
Run!
Oh, no... If nothing is done,
Nuts Island will be destroyed!
Shut up, you bastard!
Rhino...
Bounce-Man!
Katakuri-sama! That was
an incredible victory!
...Schneider!
You're strong but not unbeatable!
Mama, listen to me!
Of course, your win was
inevitable from the beginning!
Neither the cake nor the Straw Hats are here!
I can't fight you yet!
Help, Big Bro!
But we were concerned
whether you could eat today's snack!
Where are we?
I told you...
Hey, Branch!
Gum-Gum...
It's Brulee!
We were all ready and
waiting at three o'clock!
What's happening?
I won't give you one more inch!
Straw Hat is...
Prepare to fire!
CACAO ISLAND - NEAR THE PORT
Birdlime Mochi!
Shoot!
Gum-Gum...
Straw Hat?!
We know that you're a
perfectionist who wants to
What?!
Straw Hat?! Brulee?!
have your merienda at a fixed time
every day so we feel your regret!
Big Sis Amande!
...Kong Gun!
What?! Straw Hat Luffy the pirate?!
Father! We can't take it anymore!
I don't need your compliments or consolation...
Prepare my merienda.
Damn! Can't get it off!
Why is he here?!
This is not a time to whine! Hang tough!
Mama, look! Straw Hat is right there!
Yes, sir!
E-Excuse me...
Oh, good boy, good boy, good boy!
Straw Hat!
Rainfall Mochi!
The thing is, your tea...
You can see Mommy soon!
Why's Big Mom here?!
I thought she was chasing
after the Sunny on the sea!
...became cold after 40 minutes...
Help, Mama!
Peek-a, peek-a, peek-a...
...boo!
Man! He became strong again!
Papa...
Iced tea is fine.
Gum-Gum...
Oh, how cute, how cute!
How generous!
Watch very carefully!
There are two prominent types of Haki!
...Kong Gun!
But we're proud of today's sweets!
Papa will save Mommy no matter what!
Here are your merienda today!
Mama!
--Watch out!
--Don't worry.
Donuts!
For Katakuri-sama who is himself perfect!
He's trying to hit me with his trunk
from the right.
Power Mochi!
We made them from the perfect ingredients!
Oh, no! She's coming this way!
Straw Hat! Where is the cake?!
By using lots of the finest Corioli cacao
that we bought on the black market
It's the power to feel other's
presence more strongly -
and rich cow's milk that's
been pastured at a Sky Island
I told you I don't know!
called Haki of the Color of Observation!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
Mama, Big Bro Peros! Help me!
managing to keep its
dortisol level under nine,
Let go of her!
I can't believe Bege is taking such reckless action!
Luffy can beat even Katakuri!
we made this sweet chocolate doughnut!
If you enhance this power, you can tell
where your invisible enemy is,
Candy Wall!
What we've got to do now is...
And for this one,
He cares about you quite a lot!
we whipped the highest grade cream
which we got from the Minister of Cream
...make the greatest cake ever, right?
and how many there are,
and what their next move will be.
Big Bro! Please stop!
- Opera-sama the other day,
and made an icing, then gorgeously decorated the doughnut,
I have no mercy for someone
who betrayed her family!
Gear Three!
Next, the Haki of the Color of Arms.
Your stupid friend...
topped with sweet strawberries!
This power is the same as
wearing invisible armor.
...will be destroyed completely
at the hands of Big Bro Katakuri!
--Connect me to the speaker!
--Yes, sir!
It's a feast for your eyes as well!
Gum-Gum...
What's more, we prepared a doughnut
kneaded through with the Celestial Dragons' favorite sugar,
Sanji!
Old man!
...Giant Pistol!
Pudding-chan.
Bege!
in order to make the spicy taste of Meylon cinnamon
stand out and so on...
It's okay. Let's make the cake.
It's me! Oven!
It's no good! I can't break it without Haki!
This is our first joint project, isn't it?
Oven?!
I just caught your accomplice, Chiffon,
on Cacao Island.
They all have the richest taste possible
and we're pretty sure you'll be satisfied!
If the armor is hard enough,
it can be used as the offensive power.
Lick.
What?!
--Rero?!
--Madam has been caught?!
...san!
Please enjoy the extra-special sweetness!
It's surrounding us!
Whoa! Pudding-sama is steaming!
Ouch! I'm a rubber man
so I shouldn't feel pain!
We just left town and are heading
to the port now!
--Did someone bake her?!
--No way!
This is an efficient part of this power.
I used so much Haki in the
battle against Straw Hat...
So you guys should come straight to the port just as you are
and surrender yourselves!
Slow Waltz!
Pudding-sama!
Other than exploiting their weak point,
this Haki of the Color of Arms is...
Yikes!
NUTS ISLAND
To take care of his crew who are on the run,
Big Sis! Don't cut me!
It's no use fighting!
...the only effective countermove
against Devil Fruit power-users.
Our armed soldiers are
expecting you at the port!
I need to take in enough energy.
What's the matter, Amande-sama?
My Famous Sword Shirauo is craving blood...
Suffer like hell before you die.
I got a call saying that Mama is heading
this way having her Hunger Pangs attack.
Logia-type Devil Fruit power-users seem
almost invincible because of their fluid body
I guess when they tried to transport the cake by ship,
Oven got in their way.
Sugar is a source of power!
I can't fight you guys now!
What?!
but you can hit them solidly.
The islanders are in danger!
I obey the law.
Evacuate them immediately!
I thought that you were invincible!
I'm gonna consume it.
Yes, ma'am!
Even if she's my little sister,
I'm not gonna hesitate!
Wedding...
If you do something strange,
that's it.
Mirror! Mirror!
Because the Color of Arms should allow me
to hit someone solidly!
Mama...
Rero?!
Candy, candy... sluggie-gie!
Bege! Everyone! Just turn around and run!
Big Bro Peros!
This candy is in my way!
And it should work even for Logia-users, too!
Candy Slug!
I came here out of my selfishness!
If you get caught, we'll all be executed anyway!
Cake!
You guys should survive even if I die!
Mama! Like I said, that's Nuts Island!
Give it to me!
But my attacks went through your body!
Wedding...
Cake!
Mama! Mama!
I have to keep running
until I regain my Haki!
--Ca...!
--Mama!
I was wrong!
You can get...
...ke!
I was always hated by Mama...
Listen to me! This is not the place!
...hit, too!
And you guys are...
CACAO ISLAND
It's my island!
...the only true family I have!
Mama?!
Where is it?!
It's all set! We must leave, mister!
She's acting strange!
Even your iron-tight Armament Defense...!
Okay.
--I'm going to enter the shrine...
--Yes, sir!
Straw Hat!
Don't let anyone in.
It's her Hunger Pangs!
Mister, why are you in disguise?
I can break it in Gear Four!
Of course not! No one will bother you!
Take your time!
Stop! The cake isn't here! Mama!
Because I'm shy.
So someday...
Huh?
Gum-Gum...
...take revenge for me!
Give me my cake!
...Leo Bazooka!
Ma'am, what are you saying?!
Clear the way, everyone!
We're taking the cake to the port!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank.
Ma'am!
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Oh, whoa!
They baked it in such a short time?!
It's already assembled!
--Montd'Or-sama.
--What?
And it smells really good!
Stop talking nonsense!
You got a call from Custard-sama.
When it's complete,
I'm sure Mama will love it!
Custard was chasing after Bege, wasn't she?
Chiffon!
The smell makes me happy!
Are we in heaven?!
Oven!
This is Montd'Or. Did you take care of Bege?
We'll soon be arriving at the port!
We'll enter the port as you say!
Well...
Gum-Gum...
He's so vigilant...
That's what I expected from Pudding-sama
and Chiffon-sama!
We lost their ship.
Bege?!
And WCI: 31!
What?!
...Culverin!
So just don't hurt Chiffon!
No one has ever seen him eat something...
The Territory Slugs aren't sending us
the location of the ship!
Honey...
--Huh?! It's not just us?!
--What?!
Alright! Mama's coming!
How sensitive he is.
When eating, people let their guard down.
What's so remarkable
isn't your mochi ability!
We haven't got the location
of the Straw Hats, either!
We gotta run!
Pudding-sama! Chiffon-sama!
But even teatime in which
we can relax with others,
But your Color of Observation,
isn't that right?!
Are you serious?!
Please take care!
Anyway, look for Bege!
Listen! Don't let him get away no matter what!
Pez...
he makes into a time to concentrate his mind
and get nutrition by himself stoically...
Ma'am!
You just wait, Big Mom.
Okay!
I'll let you taste the ultimate cake!
Clank.
Ma'am!
Hey! Check on them right away!
That's our warrior who is worth over a billion
and serves as the backbone of the Big Mom Pirates!
Guys!
What?
I said "Check on the Territory
Slugs in the sea"!
All right!
He's totally in a different class
from the captain of the weak little pirate group...
You're too soft, Bege.
Yes, sir!
What the hell is happening?!
It's gonna cost you your neck!
ON THE SEA - NOSTRA CASTELLO
Uh?
What's wrong?
Wasn't it there?
Bege's ship is coming!
What?
I was expecting more of them to chase us!
Straw Hat's hand...
All soldiers! Prepare to be on alert!
--Was it?
--Didn't you imagine it?
What's going on?
Maybe, they're not getting our location-rero.
Fleet! Separate into right and left flanks
and block their escape route!
Oh! That's surely my daughter!
Territory Slugs?
Rero.
--Wh-What the?!
--What's going on?!
Yes, sir!
Gum-Gum...
Chiffon! It's no mistake!
If there are Territory Slugs,
the Transponder Snails should react.
...Rhino Schneider!
--The mochi is moving!
--Like I can't see it?!
--Why is it moving?!
--How do I know?!
But there's no reaction at all-rero.
Wait, Pudding!
I've never heard of anything like this!
He's...
But that's great. Keep it at maximum speed!
Big Bro Oven! Keep out of our way!
We're surrounded by enemy ships!
Pudding, where are you gonna take that cake?
Rush towards Cacao Island!
Father! What should we do-rero?!
Let's take the shortest
way to pick up Chiffon!
I heard you were gonna ambush the Straw Hats
and Mama in her Hunger Pangs
attack here on this island!
--Yeah!
--Rero!
I see Bege's ship!
What?! Straw Hat!
We'll finish the cake on the ship
and stop Mama at sea!
I guess he's coming to surrender
without a fight as he promised.
--He wasn't dead?!
--How did he get out of that giant mochi?!
Big Bro Katakuri...
...is a superhuman who's
never once been on his back!
At sea?!
I ate the mochi!
Oven-sama's carriage is arriving at the port!
Do you wanna let the rampaging Mama
come ashore at Chocolat Town?!
What?!
What's with the pirate battles in this place?!
I have to eat something every time to win?!
Boy, they sure are stupid!
If we can contact Big Bro Peros,
we can meet up at sea!
Only you can eat that much!
Look! Bege is coming to see you!
Hey! Where did he go?!
Big Sis!
I'm begging you, Big Bro! Please stop!
This is it!
You mean Katakuri-sama?
It's too late, Pudding.
We can't go back!
Don't let anyone in.
Yeah, you're right.
They should've kept running!
Too bad! He's not here now!
I understand. My dear
little sister, go ahead.
ON THE SEA - SUNNY
Gum-Gum...
He left the Mirroworld earlier!
Bege!
No one's coming after us!
Great! Thank you, Big Bro Oven!
...Kong Organ Gun!
He has important business!
Now, shall we go, too?!
It's very strange.
Someone has to be chasing us in this territory!
Father! We're finally at the island!
But Chiffon!
Goodbye!
What do you think is happening?
I feel the "voice" of someone strong there!
This must be a trap!
You can't go any farther!
Don't worry! We won't lower our guard
even for a moment!
Big Sis Chiffon!
Oh, no! The Color of Observation?!
You figured it out...
He's eating doughnuts.
Oh, that's terrible, Oven-sama!
Sniff, sniff.
Listen, Carrot!
Don't miss any sign of someone chasing us!
That's impressive.
The Color of Observation?
How could you do that to your little sister?!
No, he just has a good nose...
Okay! Count on me, Chobro!
You're right. I'm just changing my own shape
and evading efficiently...
That jerk! He must be relaxing
thinking he won!
It's none of your business!
This is our family's problem!
Good luck!
No way! A fool like you can't understand him!
Let them take the cake to the port!
By the way, I wonder if Aladdin and the others
are okay...
He is talking to the god of war
and to himself in the shrine now!
Yes, sir!
They're entering the port at last!
Now, engrave the sight of his sail unfurled for the last time
in your memory.
Big Sis Chiffon!
I hope they got away just fine...
It's a holy time.
No one can disturb... him...
Chiffon-chan...
What?!
Your husband will never take to sea again!
Mama is raiding Nuts Island?!
What do you mean by that, Big Bro Peros?!
Chiffon...
How could you appear in front of me?!
Well, I mean...!
You know what your husband tried to do...
Montd'Or-sama! We have a problem!
What is it this time?!
We already have enough problems!
don't you?!
Wh-What the...?
By looking into the sea...
we found out a terrible truth...
I can do that by seeing
the future with my Haki.
Hey, where are you going?!
I just lost my cool a little bit...
Even if you're family,
treason is an inexcusable crime!
The thing is...
--What?!
--Cock-a?!
...so I gave you chances to attack.
Oven-sama!
All the Territory Slugs are gone?!
Stop it, Big Bro Oven!
The Color of Observation can't be utilized
if you're not calm.
--Why?!
--Are they all dead-jour?!
Wait, Pudding-chan!
If you go now, you'll be
seen as a traitor, too!
Not a single one left?!
After all, that idiot got intimidated!
I don't know...
What?
That's what I expected from
the captain of a weak little pirate group!
There were tens of thousands of them!
How could they be gone all of a sudden?!
Ah! He's worried about me!
How many years has it been
since I last got punched?
He's only good at running away!
M-Maybe they were kidnapped?
But I can't reveal myself
and fight, either...
By who, you idiot?!
In that case, the enemy ships
can go wherever they like!
--Is he coming back?!
--Why?!
Do something!
I can see why my little brother Cracker
got beaten...
I've lost weight!
L-Like what...?
Huh?! Is that how a human body works?!
What fools.
What should I do?!
Find out why they're gone! Hurry up!
We did it! Father!
All right! I'm all ready now! Let's go!
...just a little bit now.
Y-Yes, sir!
The biscuit guy, huh?
Stop!
Unstoppable Donuts!
Go away, go away!
Stay away from the shrine!
Gum-Gum...
Give it to me!
Cake!
...Elephant Gun!
Come on, let's sing together!
Sea Slugs!
It's not mochi this time?! Screw you!
Big Bro Peros, stop her! It's my town!
Katakuri-sama! We're very sorry!
Rero!
Rhino...
When we stop working
Mama, you're way out of line!
You're ruining the town!
it's exciting!
How dare you!
I won't let you get away! Straw Hat!
Don't forget that you're totally surrounded!
Guarding? No!
Don't you wanna get sunk?!
Reporting? I forbid!
Oh, doughnuts!
Singing is...
--What?
--What?!
Whaaat?!
...okay!
Power Mochi!
Burn it into your memory, Pez.
Damn! The town is all messed up!
Yes, you should not be working!
This is the way Papa lives.
Father!
CHOCOLAT TOWN'S SWEETS FACTORY
That's the rule of a day-off!
I want you to move fast but don't rush!
Hm? Where did Straw Hat go?!
Quickly but carefully!
Good job!
It's pointless if we
can't make a superb cake!
Now what are you gonna do?!
I'll go along with you, Bege!
Roger!
Man, that was really close!
Ah, Sanji-san... How dependable he is...
Power Mochi!
Does this help you even a little bit?
But if Big Mom is here, that means
Pudding-sama! Pudding-sama!
Jimbei...
Nami and the others got away
safely at that time, right?
Pudding-sama!
I'm sorry!
No, no! I have to focus on cooking now!
What you just verified is...
Chiffon-sama! The test cake is done!
In any case, I need to rest now
until I regain my Haki!
...that I'm unbeatable as long as I keep my cool,
isn't that right?
Oh, it looks good!
Do you wanna try?
Bege!
Huh? What... What?!
You'll drop your guard again!
You're an enemy...
How is it?
Mmm... That's what I expected
from you, Chiffon-chan!
I wanna eat this for the rest of my life!
...that I can beat!
Seems like you're shrinking...
You're so sweet!
Oh, it's on your cheek.
Oh, yeah! Time's up for Gear Four!
I dropped Branch!
Where did she go?! That fool!
Okay, I stop!
ON THE SEA - THE SUNNY
I won't give you one more inch...
Pudding-sama...
I'm not jealous! I'm not jealous at all!
Hey! Come out! Where are you?!
Thank you for telling me!
We're going back to square one.
I can't use Haki for 10 minutes!
CACAO ISLAND
Ships!
Are you doing alright, Pudding-chan?
The Big Mom Pirates are catching up to us!
So I have to make it as far away as possible!
He's worried about me!
What kind of an idiot comes out like that
when being told to!
What's going on inside?
CHOCOLAT TOWN'S SWEETS FACTORY
Are they okay?
Roger! The time has come!
A power upgrade for a limited time, huh?
Pudding-sama!
Come out, Branch!
Uh-huh! Just running around is dull!
I'm counting on you!
What the?
Flowing Mochi!
It's Brulee!
I'm not an easy contender
who'll miss that opportunity!
Let's attack them!
It's going well.
If we can keep up like this...
Prepare to attack!
Damn...
Th-That's...
I'm counting on you guys, too!
There you are!
Yeah, leave it to us! Let's do it, Carrot!
What have I done?!
We're arriving at Cacao Island.
I'll never lose you again! Without you,
I can't travel through mirrors!
Carrot?
Pudding-sama has already started making the cake
at the Sweets Factory.
Oh, no!
Carrot! Where are you?!
Damn! You're a demon! A devil! A brute!
I'll go see how it's going as soon as we arrive.
Tell them so!
I really need 10 minutes!
Without Haki, I can't even compete against him!
Yes, sir!
Now, I gotta find a mirror!
Bring me roasted soy flour and yogurt!
There's one! Let's go, Branch!
It's Brulee!
Man! I can't lose him!
Carrot! There you are!
This is bad! This is really bad!
A big battle is just starting!
Baking powder! Stat!
How disappointing. It's over already?
Until Sanji comes,
we gotta hold out somehow!
CHARLOTTE EFFILER - FIFTH
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
Don't worry! You got me!
Big Sis Effiler!
Go to hell!
Count on me!
I'll return them all to you! Fire Salute!
Oh, no!
Carrot? Are you listening?
Pudding-sama, you got a call!
Not now. I'm busy.
Hey, Chobro.
Let's run!
But it's from Brulee-sama.
Help me, Big Sis!
Hm?
Oh, doughnuts!
Wait!
What would you like to do?
Don't shoot me!
So delicious, doughnuts!
Put it there.
Is it a full moon tonight?
Delicious to the hole, doughnuts!
Pudding, are you there?
I can't fight them without Haki!
Hmmm?!
Big Sis Brulee, what's the matter?
By myself, I eat doughnuts!
Lying on my back, I eat doughnuts!
I won't forgive him!
How's it going with the wedding cake?
Power Mochi!
Damn!
It's going fine.
It'll be ready by the time Mama gets here.
A forbidden pleasure, a sense of guilt and...
Where can I find a mirror?!
Doughnuts!
CHARLOTTE MONDER - SECOND
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
I see. That's good.
This is a blissful time.
I found you-monder!
Doughnuts, doughnuts...
Oh, doughnuts!
The thing is, I wanna let you know
something concerning the Straw Hats.
This is Amande's island-monder.
I won't let you do whatever you like-monder.
Oh, no! Big Bro Oven is furious!
So delicious, doughnuts!
Get to the port!
Help! Big Sis Monder!
There's nowhere to run on the sea!
Let go of Brulee-monder!
I eavesdropped on their secret conversation.
Nor on the land!
Get off of the ship!
Gum-Gum...
...Branch!
So you chose to fight, Bege!
It's Brulee!
Whew, that was close!
All right. I'm gonna execute you!
That's my line!
Don't use me as a shield!
Oh no, Big Sis!
We can't put to the sea!
Please! Open the door!
What should we do with the cake?!
You won't get away-monder!
Gum-Gum...
...Branch!
Is that Brulee?!
Big Bro Katakuri is a superhuman!
It's Brulee!
Speed up!
--Branch!
--It's Brulee!
Go straight to the port!
--Branch!
--It's Brulee!
He's never once been on his back
since he was born!
Brulee!
We can't do that, Pound-san!
Please give up and step back.
Help! Big Brother!
It's Branch!
Oh! Oops...
He's a man who looks down on the ground!
Why can't you?
He's always noble!
Bege sped up!
--Help!
--You fool!
What?!
Pudding-sama told us strictly.
Calm and strong!
Big Brother!
What is he thinking?!
He's gonna crash into the port!
Why were you there?!
I just wanna see Chiffon even
if only for a little bit!
He's perfect in every way!
Wait! Straw Hat!
That's who our Big Bro Katakuri is!
Chiffon-sama?
Why isn't he slowing down?!
Dammit!
Who is that?
He's Mama's 25th ex-husband...
Brulee!
Where is it?! Mirror... Mirror!
Don't tell me it's a suicide attack!
Ah!
There he is!
Guys! Are you all prepared?!
Straw Hat!
You saw me eating!
--Yeah!
--Rero!
Where is the... cake?!
Keep it at maximum speed!
That was close!
Where are we?
The fight is still on!
Thank you, Branch!
Oh, no!
The ship is gonna smash right into us!
I knew it was her immediately!
It's Brulee!
Mama, watch out! Brulee's there, too!
Stop!
--Alright, Branch, I'll wait here...
--It's Brulee!
It's gonna crash into the bank!
...for a while until I regain my Haki!
You've got to be kidding!
Mama! It's Brulee!
Chiffon looked exactly the
same as when she was born.
It's Brulee!
Oh, no!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
What should I do? What should I do?
She's as cute as she ever was.
I want to see her and talk to her
even if only for a moment!
Chiffon-chan?
Wh-What the...?!
What?
Hey! Hey!
I'm... already determined...!
It's running on the coast!
My repayment won't be over
until I see Nami and the others leaving safely!
Isn't it a little noisy out there?
Bege!
Don't hold back! Get ready to shoot!
H-Have mercy!
Some guy is yelling, huh?
But no worries. No one can enter!
You traitor!
Wedding...
I didn't see it! I didn't see anything!
This is great!
I'll burn you along with your ship!
I'll... help making the cake until it's finished,
Big Bro!
I won't tell anyone!
Even if someone slits my mouth!
Stop!
What's wrong, Pudding?
Nothing. Big Sis Brulee, I'm listening.
Get out of my way, you little punks.
What did you say about my mouth?
They saved Lola's life...
I can't fulfill my duty like this!
So at 1 AM tonight,
Edged Mochi!
This isn't it!
Nooo!!
This Nostra Castello is...
the Straw Hats' ship that we lost
will emerge at Cacao Island where you are now!
Mama, stop! I'm running this town!
...amphibious!
This is not a quarrel between siblings
or teenage rebellion, Chiffon!
Mama! This is Nuts Island!
Here?! At 1 AM?
You're alive!
I'm sorry that I didn't wait until you died!
Neither the cake nor Straw Hat are here!
You're a traitor who tried to kill our queen!
Where are you?! Straw Hat!
I couldn't take it anymore!
The plan was to meet up with
Nami-san and the others at sea
I'd never expected I'd kill my sister...
and hand over the wedding cake...
Big Mom?
Stop, Big Bro!
Why do they wanna come to Cacao Island?
We need to set an example
for the others in this country!
Because that's where they're gonna rendezvous
with their stray captain Straw Hat Luffy!
Big Sis Chiffon!
You got changed.
Oh, no... Maybe I shouldn't be worried about
the consequences now!
Ouch!
There is a Color of Arms
that's better than yours!
It's quiet...
Get your hands off of Chiffon!
Oven-kun!
Unbelievably...
Don't think you can compete against me!
I'm here to pick you up, Chiffon!
I see... But it's no good.
Big Mom and everyone know the plan!
I'm gonna save you! My dear daughter!
All serene!
You're just a worm to me!
Bege!
All serene!
Who is he?!
The paddles turned into tank tracks!
Although...
But it's not gonna go smoothly like this.
I've never heard of such a gimmick!
Straw Hat Luffy will never
make it to Cacao Island!
She takes pride in being
the Emperor of the Sea!
Well, I've never told you!
Even so...
You fool!
I thought I tossed you into the sea!
we have no choice but to keep going now!
What do you mean?
He pushed his luck and challenged
Big Bro Katakuri to a one-on-one duel!
Yeah! In any case, we must get back to
the straight route we were on!
Why would I show my cards
to people who I plan on betraying?!
Whoever that is...
You asshole!
You think you can beat me.
You're right.
Shoot-rero!
If we can't meet up with Sanji-kun and the others
who'll bring the cake,
Stop being so confident!
in addition to being separated,
we'll have to deal with Big Mom's
wrath to the end of the world!
So he'll definitely be destroyed...
That serves him right!
Chiffon! Hand the cake over to us!
I'd better just save her quickly...
One, two!
What?!
It's impossible! The cake is gigantic!
...so no one can see!
How can you hand it over
to a ship at that speed?!
It's 4 PM now, right?
ALSO, ON THE SEA
To all the islands of Totto Land!
That means, in nine hours,
Hm? What?
Dispatch all Tart ships from each island
immediately!
the Straw Hats will arrive at Cacao Island
and wait for their captain who'll never appear.
Let's jump, Chiffon-chan.
What?
To save the Big Mom Pirates' prestige,
Mama in her Hunger Pangs, and Big Bro Peros
who are after them will be there, too.
What?! Whaaat?!
go after these three hateful pirate groups!
The carriage is in the air?!
Everyone will gather together!
What? Did he just knock Oven-sama down?!
The Straw Hats who wreaked enormous damage
on us, the Big Mom Pirates!
We can't afford to fail in that situation!
Who is that old man?!
Am I stronger than I thought?
What's going on?!
You take care of Mama, Pudding!
And the group that led it!
Those who have seen my true self...
Oh? Chiffon?
You're our only hope!
That's the Firetank Pirates who
betrayed our queen, Big Mom,
It obviously wasn't you!
What?!
...can't be left alive!
Count on me, Big Sis Brulee!
Black-Leg!
and schemed to assassinate her!
I'll stop Mama with the
greatest wedding cake ever!
Damn!
And then the disappeared Fish-Men, friends of
"First Son of the Sea"
Make room on the deck, Bege!
Who did that?!
Black-Leg...
I'm looking forward to it.
Sanji-san!
Jimbei who rose in revolt...
You're safe now, Chiffon-chan.
Oh, by the way,
Thank you!
The Sun Pirates!
even if the Straw Hats arrive
there sooner, don't worry.
Big Sis, you have to hide!
Those pirates are on the run
within the territorial sea of Totto Land now!
Pudding-sama!
O-Okay.
You can leave them to Big Bro Oven's troops
who just got there!
Somebody, help!
Let's rush to the sea!
Be quiet, Branch!
We're going to search for them?
What happened to the Territory Slugs?
It's Brulee!
CHIPS TOWN
He didn't dodge and got kicked!
What?! Big Bro Oven's here?!
Clear the way!
This is Chips Town! Straw Hat Luffy is here!
Well, I heard they're all gone.
Why?
Black-Leg saved me...
What?!
Let go of me!
MIRROWORLD
So what if I got kicked?!
Don't ever let them leave our territory!
But...
It's Oven-sama!
This is Chockfull Town!
Oven-sama!
Straw Hat has been spotted!
CHARLOTTE OVEN
4TH SON OF CHARLOTTE, MINISTER OF BAKING
What do you mean I can't enter the factory?!
Find them at any cost
Who was that big man?
What?! Chockfull Town this time?!
That's Pudding-sama's order...
SWEET CITY
I could ward it off easily!
and sink... every single one of them...
into the sea on the spot!
Straw Hat is emerging in different places!
Seems like he's running around the Mirroworld!
Even me?!
Yes, no one.
Well, if that's what my sister wants,
I'll accept.
Yeah!
Did Big Sis Brulee get caught again?!
The second attack didn't come right away!
Then why is it so noisy
in front of the factory?!
This is Green Town!
We have multiple calls from private residences
saying they saw someone suspicious!
What? Oh, that's because...
Huh? What's just happened?!
Hey! Chiffon!
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?!
There you are, Chiffon!
He's...
He just tried the whipped cream...
Don't, Big Bro Oven!
You little...
D-Don't tell me he poisoned...!
Wait! We need Big Sis Chiffon
to complete the cake!
What are you doing?! If you wanna escape,
why don't you go to Cacao Island already?!
What?!
Ask him.
S-Stop hurting me!
What? How do you know that?
Chiffon!
I-I could die...
I eavesdropped!
Everyone knows now!
Stop! Get your hands off of Chiffon...
Shut up, you prowler!
I could die happy because
it's so delicious...
I'm starting to understand...
D-Don't you remember me, Oven-kun?!
What?! Is it true?!
...your ability.
Just give up! You can't beat my brother!
She's more than just an ungrateful child...
--He almost died from tasting something good!
--Look how happy he is!
Huh? What do you think you understand?!
I remember you, my ex-stepdad.
I told you so many times!
Your ability is no match for me!
I'll burn you to the bone!
That whipped cream is
Sanji-san's secret ingredient!
I-I'm happy that you remember me.
True sweetness!
Haki wears out.
Prepare yourself, Chiffon!
I used to be your stepfather.
Here I go!
Stop it! Big Bro Oven!
It's done!
The ultimate cream - Simsim Whip!
If you do that, we can't stop
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack!
If the battle goes longer,
his Color of Observation will become weaker, too...
This time, I'll watch you dying!
That's why I must remove you.
I-I wanna try it!
What?
Mama will be here soon.
No, you can't taste it now.
You look dumb
but you're sharp at fighting.
I guess I gotta get out there!
Oh, Linlin will?!
Why?
Ring, ring, ring...
We can't lose a dependable ally like you.
Stop calling her that!
Gear Four!
But that's not good enough!
Ring, ring, ring...
If she hears about this,
she'll get madder.
Clank.
What is it?!
So I gotta get you as far away as possible
before she comes!
Oven-sama, we found Bege's ship!
Don't look with your eyes.
Feel other's presence.
Rainfall Mochi!
Don't fall before you even taste it!
Wh-What are you gonna do...?
Bege's ship is heading there,
towards Cacao Island!
Okay!
I just wanna see Chiffon even
if only for a little bit...
Our fleet is pursuing them!
We'll drive them to the port!
All right!
If cream like this has
been spread on a cake...
Come on!
Bege! You've got to be kidding!
Damn you!
Don't think of it! That'll kill you!
Don't lose your composure!
I thought he was heartless
but I guess he's coming to save you!
Feel how your enemy will move next...
Bounce-Man!
I wonder who's making noise out there.
....before he moves.
Bege?!
You're strong but not unbeatable!
The fluffy chiffon cake is finished, too,
Black-Leg!
Does it bother you?
Sanji-san! Were you listening?
Screw you!!
Yeah.
Luffy.
Okay!
Luffy-kun is in trouble!
I gave you lessons
Right.
but Haki becomes even stronger
in the heat of actual battle.
I can't believe he's challenging Big Bro Katakuri
to a one-on-one duel.
Hold it down!
It's so fluffy that it's gonna float!
That's too reckless!
Surround the ship!
Mine's finished, too!
I bet so.
The more you face tough enemies,
the stronger you'll be.
Big Bro Katakuri is a superhuman!
His bounty is over a billion!
The extremely sweet and smooth,
fresh chocolate that contains
Sanji-san's whipped cream!
There's only one enemy ship!
Drive it to the port!
He's never been defeated!
What should we do?!
Then today,
I wonder if I can see
slightly ahead into the future, too.
Put a lid on it! It's smooth enough
to spill out of the pot!
Get crushed!
Ya-hoo!
he'll lose for the first time.
What are you talking about?!
Don't push your luck, you short-ass!
It's five to six.
Everything is on schedule!
Boy, how reckless Chiffon is...
Is the ship ready?
Gum-Gum...
Yes, sir!
I wanna surpass him!
To save some time, we'll
finish the cake on the ship!
But that's my sweet honey!
...Kong Gun!
It's my turn to say...
Let's get together with the Sunny
that's on its way here, A.S.A.P.!
This is it.
Yes, sir!
Oh, good boy, good boy! I'm sorry!
You must be scared!
Okay!
I wanna defeat him at full strength!
The time has come!
I won't lose!
Here we go!
I'll win!
The man with...
Let's take down Big Mom
who's causing our friends pain!
Chiffon, here I come!
...a bounty of a billion!
Katakuri's ability against which
no attack stands a chance...
The cake-baking in order to take down
Big Mom finally comes to a climax!
Sanji, Bege, and the others cooperate to transport the cake.
Luffy keeps trying desperately to
evade attacks from the Big Mom Family!
Luffy runs around waiting for his Haki to
be recharged but Katakuri closes in on him!
Luffy finally finds out
its surprising secret!
What is Sanji's secret ingredient ?
the ultimate whipped cream's tremendous power?!
But the enraged Oven turns the sea into a burning hell
to block their way!
In the meantime, Sanji and the
others who are trying to deliver
Meanwhile, Chiffon is captured by Oven,
and Bege is surrounded by a great army.
A furious series of his Gear Four attacks corners Katakuri
aiming
the wedding cake confront
the man of heat, Oven!
Meanwhile, Luffy receives
Katakuri's fierce attacks again
When the ship catches fire and they are driven into a corner,
a savior emerges before them?!
The cornered Bege now takes a
big bet at the risk of his life!
at destroying the legendary
undefeated opponent!
When a furious punch is about to hit Chiffon,
Sanji finally takes action!
and as his Gear Four runs out
of time, he gets cornered!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Another Crisis! Gear Four vs. Unstoppable Donuts!"
"The Cake Sank?! Sanji and Bege's Getaway Battle!"
"Luffy Fights Back! The Invincible
Katakuri's Weak Point!"
"A Man's Way of Life! Bege and
Luffy's Determination as Captains!"
"The Rebellious Daughter, Chiffon! Sanji's
Big Plan for Transporting the Cake!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!