Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and
his family from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting in their own places
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Having cut off his retreat,
Luffy continues the fierce one-on-one dual
he challenged Sweet General Katakuri to.
You can get...
...hit, too!
I won't give you one more inch...
We're going back to square one.
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others learn
that Luffy is in trouble...
Big Bro Katakuri is a superhuman!
He's never been defeated!
What should we do?!
Then today,
he'll lose for the first time.
"Another Crisis!
Gear Four vs. Unstoppable Donuts!"
It's my turn to say...
This is it.
I won't lose!
I'll win!
Gum-Gum...
Power Mochi!
Rhino...
...Schneider!
I told you...
Gum-Gum...
I won't give you one more inch!
Birdlime Mochi!
Damn! Can't get it off!
Rainfall Mochi!
Man! He became strong again!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Donuts!
Power Mochi!
CHOCOLAT TOWN, CACAO ISLAND
Luffy can beat even Katakuri!
What we've got to do now is...
...make the greatest cake ever, right?
Your stupid friend...
...will be destroyed completely
at the hands of Big Bro Katakuri!
Sanji!
Pudding-chan.
It's okay. Let's make the cake.
This is our first joint project, isn't it?
...san!
Whoa! Pudding-sama is steaming!
--Did someone bake her?!
--No way!
Pudding-sama!
NUTS ISLAND
What's the matter, Amande-sama?
I got a call saying that Mama is heading
this way having her Hunger Pangs attack.
What?!
The islanders are in danger!
Evacuate them immediately!
Yes, ma'am!
Wedding...
Mama...
Candy, candy... sluggie-gie!
Cake!
Mama! Like I said, that's Nuts Island!
Wedding...
Mama! Mama!
--Ca...!
--Mama!
...ke!
Listen to me! This is not the place!
It's my island!
Mama?!
Where is it?!
She's acting strange!
Straw Hat!
It's her Hunger Pangs!
Stop! The cake isn't here! Mama!
Huh?
Give me my cake!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank.
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
--Montd'Or-sama.
--What?
You got a call from Custard-sama.
Custard was chasing after Bege, wasn't she?
This is Montd'Or. Did you take care of Bege?
Well...
We lost their ship.
What?!
The Territory Slugs aren't sending us
the location of the ship!
--Huh?! It's not just us?!
--What?!
We haven't got the location
of the Straw Hats, either!
Are you serious?!
Anyway, look for Bege!
Listen! Don't let him get away no matter what!
Okay!
Clank.
Hey! Check on them right away!
What?
I said "Check on the Territory
Slugs in the sea"!
Yes, sir!
What the hell is happening?!
ON THE SEA - NOSTRA CASTELLO
I was expecting more of them to chase us!
What's going on?
Maybe, they're not getting our location-rero.
Territory Slugs?
Rero.
If there are Territory Slugs,
the Transponder Snails should react.
But there's no reaction at all-rero.
I've never heard of anything like this!
But that's great. Keep it at maximum speed!
Rush towards Cacao Island!
Let's take the shortest
way to pick up Chiffon!
--Yeah!
--Rero!
ON THE SEA - SUNNY
No one's coming after us!
It's very strange.
Someone has to be chasing us in this territory!
What do you think is happening?
This must be a trap!
Don't worry! We won't lower our guard
even for a moment!
Listen, Carrot!
Don't miss any sign of someone chasing us!
Okay! Count on me, Chobro!
Good luck!
By the way, I wonder if Aladdin and the others
are okay...
I hope they got away just fine...
What?!
Mama is raiding Nuts Island?!
What do you mean by that, Big Bro Peros?!
Well, I mean...!
Montd'Or-sama! We have a problem!
What is it this time?!
We already have enough problems!
By looking into the sea...
we found out a terrible truth...
The thing is...
--What?!
--Cock-a?!
All the Territory Slugs are gone?!
--Why?!
--Are they all dead-jour?!
Not a single one left?!
I don't know...
There were tens of thousands of them!
How could they be gone all of a sudden?!
M-Maybe they were kidnapped?
By who, you idiot?!
In that case, the enemy ships
can go wherever they like!
Do something!
L-Like what...?
Find out why they're gone! Hurry up!
Y-Yes, sir!
Come on, let's sing together!
Sea Slugs!
When we stop working
it's exciting!
Guarding? No!
Reporting? I forbid!
Singing is...
...okay!
Yes, you should not be working!
That's the rule of a day-off!
Does this help you even a little bit?
Jimbei...
What you just verified is...
...that I'm unbeatable as long as I keep my cool,
isn't that right?
You'll drop your guard again!
You're an enemy...
...that I can beat!
Seems like you're shrinking...
Oh, yeah! Time's up for Gear Four!
Okay, I stop!
Thank you for telling me!
I can't use Haki for 10 minutes!
So I have to make it as far away as possible!
A power upgrade for a limited time, huh?
Flowing Mochi!
I'm not an easy contender
who'll miss that opportunity!
Oh, no!
I really need 10 minutes!
Without Haki, I can't even compete against him!
Man! I can't lose him!
This is bad! This is really bad!
How disappointing. It's over already?
Oh, no!
Power Mochi!
Is that Brulee?!
Help! Big Brother!
--Help!
--You fool!
Big Brother!
Why were you there?!
Wait! Straw Hat!
Dammit!
Brulee!
That was close!
Where are we?
Thank you, Branch!
It's Brulee!
--Alright, Branch, I'll wait here...
--It's Brulee!
...for a while until I regain my Haki!
It's Brulee!
Wh-What the...?!
Wedding...
Stop!
This isn't it!
Mama, stop! I'm running this town!
Mama! This is Nuts Island!
Neither the cake nor Straw Hat are here!
Where are you?! Straw Hat!
Big Mom?
You got changed.
It's quiet...
Unbelievably...
All serene!
But it's not gonna go smoothly like this.
She takes pride in being
the Emperor of the Sea!
Even so...
we have no choice but to keep going now!
Yeah! In any case, we must get back to
the straight route we were on!
You're right.
If we can't meet up with Sanji-kun and the others
who'll bring the cake,
in addition to being separated,
we'll have to deal with Big Mom's
wrath to the end of the world!
ALSO, ON THE SEA
To all the islands of Totto Land!
Dispatch all Tart ships from each island
immediately!
To save the Big Mom Pirates' prestige,
go after these three hateful pirate groups!
The Straw Hats who wreaked enormous damage
on us, the Big Mom Pirates!
And the group that led it!
That's the Firetank Pirates who
betrayed our queen, Big Mom,
and schemed to assassinate her!
And then the disappeared Fish-Men, friends of
"First Son of the Sea"
Jimbei who rose in revolt...
The Sun Pirates!
Those pirates are on the run
within the territorial sea of Totto Land now!
We're going to search for them?
What happened to the Territory Slugs?
Well, I heard they're all gone.
What?!
Don't ever let them leave our territory!
Find them at any cost
and sink... every single one of them...
into the sea on the spot!
Yeah!
Huh? What's just happened?!
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?!
He just tried the whipped cream...
D-Don't tell me he poisoned...!
What?!
Ask him.
I-I could die...
I could die happy because
it's so delicious...
--He almost died from tasting something good!
--Look how happy he is!
That whipped cream is
Sanji-san's secret ingredient!
True sweetness!
It's done!
The ultimate cream - Simsim Whip!
I-I wanna try it!
No, you can't taste it now.
Why?
We can't lose a dependable ally like you.
Don't fall before you even taste it!
If cream like this has
been spread on a cake...
Don't think of it! That'll kill you!
The fluffy chiffon cake is finished, too,
Black-Leg!
Okay!
Hold it down!
It's so fluffy that it's gonna float!
Mine's finished, too!
The extremely sweet and smooth,
fresh chocolate that contains
Sanji-san's whipped cream!
Put a lid on it! It's smooth enough
to spill out of the pot!
It's five to six.
Everything is on schedule!
Is the ship ready?
Yes, sir!
To save some time, we'll
finish the cake on the ship!
Let's get together with the Sunny
that's on its way here, A.S.A.P.!
Yes, sir!
Okay!
The time has come!
Here we go!
Let's take down Big Mom
who's causing our friends pain!
Luffy keeps trying desperately to
evade attacks from the Big Mom Family!
In the meantime, Sanji and the
others who are trying to deliver
the wedding cake confront
the man of heat, Oven!
When a furious punch is about to hit Chiffon,
Sanji finally takes action!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Rebellious Daughter, Chiffon! Sanji's
Big Plan for Transporting the Cake!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!