Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
You can't break it!
Hey! What're you doing?!
This smell is...
He's not here!
Which guy?
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies."
The skull mark is a symbol of faith!
That guy!
It's because you're pestering me!
That guy?
Like I said, just join us!
That tin bastard!
This is exactly what
I mean by pestering me!
Ahhh! That bastard!
It's him!
It's fun to be a pirate!
Huh?
I'll find him right away and finish him off!
Luffy!
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
I've had enough!
Just rest in there for a while!
It's a direct hit!
What's going on here?
Doctorine! There's a problem!
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
Hmm?
He's... Wapol is back!
Your injuries actually
aren't that light, either.
What have they done... to my castle?!
I'll save this country as a doctor one day.
"Zoan-Type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven-Form Transformation"
Doctorine...
Geez... What's his problem?
Hm?
Is that so...
Humph!
Huh?
Ahh! That bastard!
He called me...
Didn't you mean to say
"destroy the country"?
Why?!
That annoying mouth!
This is a winter island where
it's bitter cold year around.
He must've been blown away!
Such an idiot!
Wait!
his friend...
What is this guy?!
When did he steal the key?!
Cherry blossoms won't bloom here.
They will!
I was a hopeless thug and dying,
Look! Everything is as it
used to be! This is my castle.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
We're restoring the Drum Kingdom!
"When the Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith Flies Forever!"
but I lived on after seeing
those cherry blossoms.
Ahh!
I was able to have
a profound change of heart.
Just a moment, Wapol-sama!
On top of the castle...
Every human in this world can be saved!
Ahhh...
This smell is...
Hmm?
Huh?
This is no time to be in bed resting!
There's no disease in this
world that can't be cured.
Wapol!
I should get out of here
while Doctorine isn't around!
See? It didn't break!
What's that strange flag?
I couldn't take being stuck
here for three days.
What happened to the
Drum Kingdom's flag?!
What?! Can't be... He's stupid!
I raised this skull towards
all the diseases!
Huh?
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms
And The Will That Gets Carried On!"
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
I don't know who the heck
this pirate flag belongs to...
I burned that thing.
I got lucky! Looks like I can
leave without a problem.
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
but since this flag is a person's
pledge to risk his life...
So you show yourself, Dr. Kureha!
The last survivor of the doctor hunt!
it's not raised as a joke!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
When he found out that
Hiriluk had only 10 days to live,
This castle is no longer yours!
Wh-Who's... this guy?!
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
This isn't a place for rotten brats like you!
Chopper got quite upset.
This flag isn't something you can
just break while laughing foolishly!
You must be one of the Straw Hats!
Well, that was only natural.
Doctor... I...
Leave this country!
The Drum Kingdom has already died out!
But he took action in his own way...
He definitely looks like a bad guy!
Hm?
What'd you say?!
I found you!
No, that's not true at all!
Hey, monster! Come with us!
Incredible...
Wait!
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about!
So this is... a pirate!
I'm gonna beat the crap outta him!
What?! I'm wrong?! Really?!
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
That's right! I'm a navigator
who's just passing by here!
Hm?
Ah!
I'm gonna... die...
I will save this country as a doctor!
Oh, I see...
"Vs. Wapol's Corps!
The Power Of The Munch Munch Fruit!"
Are you all right, Dalton-san?!
Well then... see ya...
Yeah, I'm fine. I just felt
a little drained. That's all.
I will make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
Okay!
Gum-Gum...
I'll be fine if I get some rest.
W-Wapol-sama! It's Straw Hat!
What are pirates?
Hm?!
Pirates are incredible guys at sea.
Liar!
Hey, you guys!
Ah!
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
Hm?
...Pistol!
--No!
--You idiot! Wait!
Ah! D-Dr. Kureha!
It's cool to be a pirate!
There're tons of incredible guys at sea!
Hm?
Don't come this way! Go away!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
Are you happy, brats?
--Wapol-sama!
A lot of guards have been
absent recently. What's going on?
Take that injured guy
to the medical ward.
Well... they're out picking mushrooms
at the request of the Twenty MDs.
Ahh! You're that damn old hag!
--Hey, reindeer!
--Hmm?
Mushrooms?
I'm gonna beat these guys up now.
What do you wanna do?
They said there's some mushroom
that can cure anything...
And anyone else injured, too!
Did I gain some weight recently?
Y-Yes, Ma'am!
Then I'll do this...
Munch Munch Factory!
That was close...
Don't dilly-dally!
I...
What're you saying? You damn idiot!
Mushroom?
Do you want the same
experience as this man?!
Ah!
I'll eat myself!
Hmm?
Idiot! They'll see us!
If you wanna protect the flag that bad,
stay there forever to protect it!
Nami-san, you should have your
sickness treated all the way.
Doctor, about what they said...
How dare you bastards...
Quiet! If I don't escape from here now,
Ah! What's that?!
Why don't you stop... right there!
our departure for Alabasta
will be delayed by two days!
Over and over again... How many
times do you have to be in our way?!
Hmm?!
Do you wanna see Vivi keep suffering?!
Ow!
Stop grumbling, you two...
Looks like your backbone gave out...
Hmm? Why are they here?
and get back to the medical ward!
That's just natural.
You're moving around too much!
Ah!
H... He turned into a bucket!
Ahhhh!
Stop, doctor's orders!
Miraculous bone structure
shaping technique... complete!
I'm Usopp! Captain Usopp!
I will never shoot you!
What're you idiots doing?!
Just stand there and watch!
I'll blow him to bits along with that flag!
Don't ever come back here!
Since I had someone injured with me then,
I ran, as there was no other choice.
Slim Wapol!
Time to get blown away, Straw Hat!
But this time... I don't
have to hold back any more!
I won't let you escape.
No!
Stop it!
Hmm, you bastard!
That's the idea! Get him, reindeer!
I did a terrible thing to you...
As I thought, his injuries have gotten
worse... since he overexerted himself.
How dare you suddenly attack Wapol-sama,
the king of the Drum Kingdom!
At least see my cherry blossoms.
I'll eat you first!
I found you!
That's right! He's the king!
They'll be my last big work.
Wapol-sama! Watch out!
How dare you do such a
thing to his Excellency,
the most excellent ruler of all
the citizens on this island!
Now... Dalton...
Who cares! You guys tick me off!
The little brat is showing his guts
as if he's a fully grown man...
Where's the key to this arsenal?
You know where it is, right?
Hey young man. You know them?
Huh? Was he that skinny before?
Yeah, I do! He's that annoying mouth!
The annoying mouth pirate!
Key to the arsenal...
Why do you need such a thing?
Ahh!
Sorry. I won't let you lay
your finger on Wapol-sama!
That annoying mouth?
Well... here we go again!
He keeps getting in my way! He ate part
of our ship and attacked my friends!
It's none of your business.
Luffy... Why is my jacket all beaten up...?
That key was... always carried
by Wapol from long ago.
I won't let him get away
with it any more!
Before that, aren't you
cold in that getup?
So if it's still the case, it flew
off with Wapol into the sky...
Ahh!
How much do you think I paid
for this jacket?! 28,800 berries!
Huh?
Really, there are some strange
creatures in this world.
See?
What?! Is that right?! Oh darn...
Didn't they say he was the king?
He isn't a pirate?!
Seems like you're that "yeti" the citizens
got worked up about at one time.
And that's the price
after I talked them down!
Doctorine...
Hm?
I'm sorry, but that guy shot a bomb
at me! I couldn't help it!
That's what you just realized?!
About the treatment fee for our crew...
Humph! What an idiot! It seems
he finally realized his rudeness.
would you make it all free?
Also, would you discharge me right away?
You must really have spent your
whole life disliked by everyone.
Wapol-sama is the king
of the Drum Kingdom.
Dammit! I don't have much time left!
Geez... but oh well. I'll forgive you.
You poor monster. Why's a loner like
you trying to save this country?
When he met you before, he was temporarily
a pirate for his own reasons. That's all.
Did you ask just for the heck of
it knowing it's all impossible?
I didn't expect it to come back in
good shape when I let you borrow it.
As my fee, I'll take the entire
cargo and money on your ship.
He's done being a pirate
Don't make me laugh!
Shut up! Even if I don't have friends,
I can still fight!
and is going back to being the king
of this castle and country.
As payment for the damages,
you owe triple that amount plus some.
And you'll stay here and rest
at least for two more days!
Hey, this place is cold!
The total is 100,000 berries.
Consider it a loan.
That's what I've been saying!
As long as Doctor's flag exists, I will...
Nami-san, she's right!
You should be treated all the way!
It's 50 degrees below, you know!
Ahh! Don't tell me you
expected this to happen!
They're making light of us!
You do have friends!
I'll be fine since I don't feel like I'll die!
Wapol-sama!
That can't be a reason!
I'm really mad now... Straw Hat!
I am your friend!
That's it, you bastards!
Ah...
Darn! His body sure is made tough...
Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!
I'll bite you off!
You need the key to the arsenal, right?
Um, could you hold on a minute?
Luffy went to get some clothes.
That's what I told you, right?!
Look! Believe it or not,
this is the arsenal!
What?! Why do you have that key?!
He's gone?!
I'm the only one who has
the key to this room.
Let me ask you a question.
Is that the real one? How'd you get it?!
He... stretched earlier... His arm...
I will fight!
Naturally, there are a wide
variety of weapons in here.
I stole it.
Just like pirates do!
What?!
Straw Hat!
Yeah, he stretches...
it's because he's a rubber man.
You've got guts dictating
terms to me like that.
When I eat them up and make them
Wh... What's that?
part of my body using
Munch Munch Shock,
You are really an unbelievable girl.
Are you okay?!
It's a monster!
you'll witness a horrific human weapon!
I'm just fine...
since I'm a rubber man.
Okay then... You don't have
to pay my fee. But that's all.
A rubber man?!
To sum up, the rebel old hag and some
of the Straw Hats are in this castle.
I found it! The Amiudake mushroom...
Hey, reindeer. Can you finish that guy?
I can't accept the other term as a doctor.
That's the one!
Once we eliminate all of them, there won't
be anyone else impudent enough to defy me.
Someone like that is a piece of cake.
Now, be prepared. The door will open!
It'll be scary!
Wait a sec! If that's the case, I can't
give the key to you! Give it back!
But...
Then it's decided.
The key to that horrific door is...
My opponent is the annoying mouth!
how can I get across?
gone!
Precisely.
Listen, girl.
This will become the bright day
of the Drum Kingdom's restoration.
I have to leave this room
now to take care of things.
How dare you, Straw Hat,
flying around like that!
There's a drawer chest with
my coat in the back room.
I'll start with you, Dr. Kureha!
I won't hesitate any longer!
You've got quite the nerve settling
in the castle during our absence...
No, this isn't over yet.
And it's not like I'm posting guards...
You can take me down?!
Huh, you monster?!
Ah! He's running away! Wait!
and even flying a strange flag!
Also, that young man's backbone
treatment is already complete.
I made this castle Hiriluk's grave.
I've got another trump card.
How dare you...
But listen, don't you dare escape!
Oh, it's just the key to the arsenal.
Old hag! I will fight...
You guys, come with me.
I need you for heavy lifting.
I wasn't really interested
in such a run-down castle,
It would've been nice if it
were a key to a treasure room.
Dammit!
Shut up and watch!
Yes, Ma'am!
If you keep moving around, you won't
be able to walk on your own anymore.
How disappointing...
but this reindeer insisted on
flying Hiriluk's flag up there.
I'm close... I'm so close!
Nami-san!
Don't worry. When push comes to shove,
my reindeer can handle things.
Good! You're safe!
I raised this skull towards
all the diseases!
She told me to wear her coat, take
Sanji-kun and escape using this chance.
What happened?! Why're you crawling
like that, Sanji-kun? Are you all right?
Nami-san, you're that concerned about me?!
Yeah... that's how it sounded to me, too.
Skull...
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
My name is Tony Tony Chopper!
Hmmm...
Doctor...
If I get enveloped in that warmth...
It's a name that the world's
greatest doctor gave me!
I'm sorry... I lost...
one of your precious books...
I will save this country as a doctor!
Don't!
Even if Doctor forgave you,
Nami...-san...
I won't forgive you for
laughing at how he lived!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
What... happened to you?
Wait! Wait, wait!
I sure ran around a lot.
Night came before I even knew...
Doctor fought to save this country...
by raising that flag...
Mushroom...
Dammit! The upper levels
are full of snow, too!
I don't hear voices any more...
Looks like they're gone...
Medicine...
I won't let them get away
with this...! I won't!
I'm the one who'll show
no forgiveness! I'll stomp you!
I'll make them all experience
how great the king is!
That's an Amiudake mushroom!
This is for the best...
I can't leave this place...
You... got it for me?
Take me to the patients!
I came to save the Twenty MDs!
Rumble Ball!
Please live... Please live, Doctor...
The power of Drum is my power.
It's a full moon tonight...
I wanna be a doctor.
Please teach me how to be a doctor.
Dalton-san! Dalton-san! Wake up!
I'll use the ultimate weapon
of the Drum Kingdom...
--Hey! Reindeer!
You still don't get it?!
It was a trap!
As you can see,
the Twenty MDs are just fine!
--Hm?
--Hey! Reindeer!
Please! Dalton-san!
--Hm?
--Let's be pirates together!
--No way! They're still looking for me!
I'll fight, too... just like pirates do!
Vivi...
the Tin Titan Royal Crown
Seven Barrel Cannon!
Hey! Dalton-san! Dalton-san!
Hey, Luffy. Just give it up.
Dalton is still alive.
He hasn't shown up even after
all our efforts to find him.
So that was all...
Do you think a reindeer
can become one, too?
The Twenty MDs!
He doesn't wanna be a pirate.
Good... So none of them are sick?
I've now cornered you! Be prepared!
His body is frozen. That's all.
Humph! It's you who's
corndered, Straw Hat!
You can! You can!
That's not true.
I wanna take him with us!
Will you leave him in our care?
I was convinced...
that this was a national crisis...
You can! You can be a great doctor...
Time to be blown away!
Like I said, that's what you want, right?!
Doct- I can't breath...
Hey, there are doctors.
So it was just a trick...
It's not that I don't wanna go...
because you have such a kind heart...
I thought I heard that there weren't
any doctors in this country...
Reindeer!
Huh...?
Come out, reindeer!
These guys're called the Twenty MDs
and they exclusively work for Wapol.
Hey... when do you think a person dies?
You idiot!
But I won't go. I can't go!
I'm not like those guys!
Doctor!!
In other words, they're bad doctors!
That's right! We can't trust you!
When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart?
Chess! Kuromarimo!
Leave Dalton-san in your care when
you gave in to Wapol... to the king?!
No... When he's attacked
by an incurable disease?
Is the doctor hunt going well?!
Yes sir. Most of the doctors
have already been exiled.
Hm?
What're you going to do to Dalton-san?!
No... When he eats a deadly
poisonous mushroom soup?
Reindeer!
Hm?
Most?
If you want to save him,
just do what we say!
There are two that
we haven't captured yet.
No!
A bird's nest...!
That Dr. Kureha and...
We are still doctors.
Snow Birds!
Tony-kun!
the quack, Hiriluk.
A man dies when people forget him...
Even though we were forced to give
in by Wapol and his men's power,
What'd you say?!
Hey, let's be pirates together! Okay?!
we've always worked to advance
our medical research...
How dare you make fun of me!
Oh, yeah! I've come up with a good idea!
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
for the patients in this country!
--Hmm?
It's not possible.
Send an official notice to the citizens.
The Twenty MDs have all... fallen ill...
Yes, it is since it's fun!
The citizens' sickness of the
heart will be cured as well...
Hey, you don't make sense.
It was because a certain quack
taught us not to give up.
Why're you crying... Dalton-kun?
But...
Does the Amiudake mushroom soup...
taste good?
I'm surprised to see a rope connected
to the castle from a place like this...
We can't lose any more...
stupid men like him!
But I'm a reindeer!
I have antlers and hooves!
Ahhh! Darn, this tastes terrible!
I wonder... if it's
the same for a country...
A young man in town found it by accident.
What?!
This isn't something that
any living thing can eat!
Yeah, if there's someone
to pass it on to...
This place used to be Dr. Kureha's house!
I even have a blue nose!
The effect of the Rumble Ball
lasts 3 minutes.
Oh no...
Don't be so down.
Good medicine doesn't taste good.
Can you guys heal the scar in his heart?
I'll take you down in 3 minutes!
3 minutes?!
This means it's working.
You can't defeat me at all,
much less in 3 minutes!
This is a great view!
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom can't kill me.
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate, but...
Thank you, Chopper.
Yeah... Hey, isn't this
a little overcrowded?
3 minutes? That's amazing!
We can't let Dalton-san
go alone when he's injured!
3 minutes? That's amazing!
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
We'll fight, too!
Huh?!
Hmm?
W-Well, I get it. But we'll
never get there like this!
I had... such a good life!
I can't become your friend! So...!
We'll be able to see something interesting.
Dammit! Let me fight, too!
Huh?
Good-bye, quack...
So I just came to say thank you...
Paddle! Paddle harder!
Rumble!
Dalton-san, don't push too hard.
What... did you say you could do?!
Thank you, Chopper!
I do appreciate you guys.
Wapol...
What's that?
Who do you think you are, Dalton?
I did it...
Thank you for asking me to join you.
What?
I finally did it... This is it!
"There's no medicine that
can cure fools" you say...?
Marimo's Snow Melting Arrow!
I'll stay here, but...
This reaction... I've waited
for it for 30 years...
Did you just call me a fool?
Walk Point! Leg boost!
You think you've become an emissary of
justice who saves people or something?!
one day... if you feel like it,
stop by agai...
I did it, Chopper!
My research succeeded!
Shut up! Let's go!
Whoa!
Don't be so full of yourself!
You're just a retainer!
This castle is where Doctor died...
Humph! Just a transformation?!
I was expecting something more!
I wasn't wrong! I wasn't! I wasn't!
He died trying...
to save this country...
In other words, you have
the powers of a devil fruit.
A week or so in this cell will probably
make you realize your mistake.
Zoan-type, just like Dalton!
A reindeer human, huh?!
So this place is...
this place is Doctor's grave!
I'd imagine an impulsive rebellion
wouldn't last so long.
Heavy Point! Weight Boost!
Grave?! That stupid doctor's?!
You don't ask people to join you
by telling them to "shut up."
I'm a human reindeer!
I can now make cherry blossoms
bloom on this winter island!
Same difference!
I know everything about the three-form
transformation you Zoan-types use.
You're an excellent guard
the citizens trust.
Reconsider it, Dalton.
Marimo's Super Surprise Quattro Hammer!
How dare you violate my sacred castle
with that scum doctor's flag!
Listen. I'm going out,
but you stay put and rest here.
I've seen all your forms.
Thanks to that idiot doctor Hiriluk,
you just got caught up in a little fantasy!
Okay.
Burn down that flag already!
See you later!
Looks like you're a
power fighter like Dalton.
Giving up your status
and destroying the country...
Doctor was happy...
But there's no way you can...
What good will that do you?!
I won't let you make it
inside this castle...
I cured a human's disease!
Jumping Point! Jump Boost!
I'll forgive you, if you can just say...
...outpower me!
Hmm?!
Hmm?
Never!
You'll be able to become
a good doctor. I'll guarantee it.
Wapol-sama... he is...
"I'm sorry" to me, the king, Dalton-kun.
That's right! From that time...
He jumped! He can really jump!
Hey, Nami! Are you really okay?
Whoa!
The monster...
that followed the stupid doctor!
What?! What's that form?!
Do you know... that the entire
country is a madhouse right now?
I'm fine! I'm feeling great!
That flag... is Doctor's faith!
To hell with status! To hell with the king!
--Hey, let's go to say good-bye
--There! To commemorate our reaching here,
Wasn't his "human-animal form" the little
reindeer from earlier?! How impudent!
Yeah, I know.
--to that old lady doctor and acorn pops, too.
--There! To commemorate our reaching here,
So I won't let you take it down!
About the Twenty MDs falling ill,
right? Ridiculous!
--to that old lady doctor and acorn pops, too.
--I built Snow Queen V!
Guard Point! Fur Boost!
--Don't be silly.
--I built Snow Queen V!
--Hey, how dare you kick
I'm the king! I'm the king of
the Drum Kingdom! I'm the king!
Never!
--Let him be alone with Doctorine.
--Hey, how dare you kick
So what brought you here today?
--Let him be alone with Doctorine.
--Snow Queen V! How disrespectful!
--He lived with her alone for 6 years.
Show them no mercy!
We're going into the castle!
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
Ahh, I refuse.
It'll sure be a tearful farewell...
Take down every single one of them!
I haven't asked anything yet!
This is it for you.
Doctorine acts like that in front of us,
Are you gonna fight, too, old lady?
What's this dust?
It doesn't matter...
if you're a king or god...
but she is actually a kind person.
Old lady?
That's my 30 years.
Ugh!
If they're more than you guys
can handle, I'll give you a hand.
Hmmm... Really?
Again?!
That's the medical science
that I've finally completed!
It doesn't matter who's
great or who's not great!
Whoa!
Then, we're really leaving here
without saying anything to her, huh?
Appreciate that...
It's an all-purpose medicine that can
cure the country's sickness of the heart.
Wapol-sama! Please leave them to us!
After all, I'm a pirate.
Of course. Once Chopper comes,
we'll go down the mountain
We'll clean up the small fries right away!
You've lived 30 fruitless years.
Good work.
Doctorine!
and set sail immediately... to Alabasta!
Can't be... I hit him dead on!
It does matter, Straw Hat!
So, why are you showing it to me?
The Drum Kingdom is a member
of the World Government.
It won't work!
You're fine with that too, right, Vivi?
There isn't enough dust.
I don't have much time left, either.
I was sure that Zoan-types
had a limit of three forms.
Yeah, if a doctor comes with us...
Hey hey hey, you with the afro.
Now listen. This is a world-class offense!
I want you to make cherry
blossoms bloom in my place.
A doctor?
What kind of brother are you,
throwing an afro at a lady?
What the heck are you?
Okay then, I'll get the ropeway ready.
Ridiculous! Why do I have to-
The Rumble Ball is a drug
And one more thing!
Like I said, that doesn't matter, either!
This is my own fight!
that messes up the wavelength
of the devil fruit's transformations.
Please teach medical science to Chopper.
Hey, Luffy! Give me a hand.
I didn't realize there was
a ropeway... That's amazing!
Hey, you're getting it now.
He wants to become a doctor.
During my 5 years of research,
I found 4 more transformation points.
That's enough!
--He's a reindeer and monster,
but he'll certainly become a good doctor!
Y-You damn Straw Idiot...!
--Why would I...
--He's a reindeer and monster,
but he'll certainly become a good doctor!
You fell for it...
3 transformations plus 4.
Huh?
I'll digest you!
Seven-form transformation?
He's a nice guy with a kind heart.
Ah! What?! I can't shake it off!
Try and eat me.
Sev...
He risked his life
to make medicine for me!
What's this afro?! Static electricity?!
Now, hurry up and take them out!
Not yet! Munch Munch Shock!
Tongue Cannon!
What's the big deal with the
number of transformations?!
Please! Help him become a doctor!
Once they're outside
the gate, line them up!
A... A seven-form transforming
interesting reindeer!
Exactly!
Ah! His tongue became a cannon!
What nerve you have!
Ahh! Dammit! Come off! Dammit!
Disappear!
Dr. Kureha!
What's the matter with him?
You want me to take care of your
stupid research and strange pet?!
Ahh!
Hm?
Ohhhhh... it's cold! It's cold!
What are we taking so many
cannons out of the arsenal for?
Looks like his happiness exceeded its limit
after hearing seven-phase transformation.
You should know that I'm not someone
who'll sympathize with a man
Clothes! Clothes!
You bastard... What happened
to your fight against me?!
Just hurry up and take them out!
Clothes! Clothes! Clothes!
just because he's not long for this world!
Where're the clothes?!
Get out of here!
What's going on outside?
It seems noisy...
It's cold outside! Where're my clothes?
I didn't ask that. I asked
what was happening outside.
Yeah... I know...
We've known each other a long time.
Hm?
Ahh, it's a fight.
Oh? It seems there are
some patients missing.
I see... You guys're okay, right?
Yeah, so stay in bed.
I'm counting on you...
They escaped...
disobeying your order...
You can use my clothes.
To hell with seven-phase transformation!
What? Your clothes're ugly.
I won't be deceived by such a sham!
They're cooler than yours.
I see... What am I going
to do with them...?
Really? Well, I guess it's
all right if they're warm.
It's not a sham!
Dalton-san! Please hang in there!
Alrighty!
What should we do?
Oh... I wondered what
the fuss was about...
Dalton-san! Dalton-san!
That bastard! I'll beat up
that annoying mouth!
Dalton-san!
It's not like you, Hiriluk...
throwing in the towel already...
Doctorine!
Arm Point! Arm Boost!
I'm... I'm all right.
Doctorine!
I don't have much time left...
That idiot! He wouldn't!
I have something to talk about with you!
Dalton-san...
What do you mean?!
The Twenty MDs fell ill!
Chopper, where have you been?
Who'll treat this country's sick people?!
Go downstairs and help
them take the cannons out.
At least give us access to medicine!
I'll make sure... to end this country!
Talking to us won't do anything!
Listen, Doctorine!
I'm gonna be a pirate.
--Even doctors get sick!
Dammit!
--Out of my way!
--Even doctors get sick!
--Ahh! Hiriluk?!
To hell with history!
--Out of my way! Out of my way!
--Ahh! Hiriluk?!
What's with this afro? It doesn't
come off! It doesn't come off!
I'm going with them!
Let me tell you one thing.
My iron hooves can smash even rocks!
What?!
Hey hey, wake up, Dalton.
I'm going out to sea.
That bastard is crazy!
I'll join them as a ship's doctor
and travel around the world!
There're lots more coming!
Governance is about caring
for your country... you say?
Take the ropeway out.
Amazing!
Take me to the castle.
Marimo's Static Cling!
Don't be ridiculous!
How impudent, you bastard!
Where's Hiriluk?!
Governments don't need to have a heart.
Now listen. You're my only assistant!
You don't have to run away!
I know about you!
What the hell are these things?!
They're damn gross!
This'll show you! Marimo's Surprise...
He's right. What's important is the system.
Who do you think taught you medicine?!
Hey, reindeer! Don't just watch! Help me!
I'm asking you where the quack went!
Quattro Axe!
Or are you saying you don't
feel any gratitude towards me?!
Okay!
Ah!
D-Doctor got better
so he went to the town...
Take these off quick!
They're really gross!
Snow Splitting Blade!
Th-That's not true!
I do appreciate you, Doctorine!
On top of that, they're plain! Too plain!
Wh... What're you doing?!
Got better? He doesn't get better.
Ahh! They're now stuck on me!
I'm giving them back to you!
He can't be cured with
the current medical science.
I also love this land
where I met Doctor and you!
Let me go! Stop it!
Ah! Don't give them back to me!
Keep at least one!
Hey... The castle wall got hollowed out!
That's not true! Look at this!
I currently have many patients to treat!
No! They're gross!
Humph! Then you can stay here.
They're gross to me, too!
He's fine now because he ate this!
Throw him into the sea!
If he resists, you can kill him.
Stop it! Don't give them to me!
You can't live in a fine castle
like this no matter where you go.
That's... an Amiudake mushroom!
--What the heck are you guys doing?
Tsk! He dodged it.
--Ahh! Stop it!
--What the heck are you guys doing?
Hey, let me go! Please!
This is an all-purpose medicine!
So he's fine now!
Humph! They know nothing about teamwork.
Then, how about... this?!
My patients are waiting for me.
Doctor said that he felt
full of energy, too!
Pirates are good for nothing!
You'll end up dead in no time.
I'll tell you one thing.
Please!
Omnidirectional Snow Splitter!
I will learn to be a doctor from Doctor.
Despite their plain look,
those Static Marimos burn flashily.
To hell with state control!
That's okay!
Hmm?! Oh no!
He's going to burn these afros!
Don't talk so cocky!
Here you go!
Okay... Hey! Where're you going?!
I've never heard of a mere
reindeer going out to sea.
Good... So none of them are sick?
Decoy plan!
D-Decoy plan? Am I the decoy?!
That's right. I'm a reindeer!
But I'm a man, too!
What was that for?!
What happened to your
high spirits from earlier?!
Check mate!
You can't win if you just
keep dodging, you know!
Ah! Ow! Ow! Snow! Snow! Snow!
You stupid reindeer!
What's wrong with wishing
the country to have a heart?!
That mushroom is...
You sure talk big...
In any case, I won't allow it.
Move!
Wapol-sama!
If you wanna leave that bad,
you have to get through me first!
Darn it!
D... Dalton-san... What're you...
Chopper!
Brain Point! Brain Boost!
extremely poisonous!
Whoa... This is really warm!
Once you eat it, you'll be
dead within half a day!
It's not that I was just dodging.
Doctorine...
Dynamite!
Luffy!
Huh?
Grab my leg from there!
Listen, everyone.
What?
Your leg? Sure!
When we get to the castle and once
I get inside, lay on the ground.
I was looking for your weak spot.
A crybaby like you is a man?!
Like this?
That's why that idiot...
What?!
Okay then! Don't let your hands go!
This will finish you. Scope!
Hmm? Got it!
Don't make me laugh!
Arme de l'Air Assault... Gum Shoot!
That can't be true.
I looked it up in a book...
Doctorine... But they...
Are you worried about him?
Shut up! Let's go!
though I lost that book...
I'm not worried about him at all!
It's a mushroom that can defeat diseases!
A... A beam!
He'll definitely shoot a beam!
He's a pirate!
understand...
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
Shut up!
He won't, you idiot!
Shut up! It's definitely a beam!
That's right! There was a skull right
next to the Amiudake mushroom picture!
I won't allow you to have your way!
I don't care what anyone says,
it's a beam!
What an idiot!
He let his guard down!
--What else could it be?! It's a beam!
--How can you know?! Huh?!
Doctor also said he got better!
--I just know! It's a beam! Beam!
--How can you know?! Huh?!
--Then what kind of beam?!
I should use this chance...
Actually, that's you.
There's no way he'll die! You're a liar!
Wh-What?!
You were looking for
my weak spot?! So what?!
One, two...
Come back, Chopper!
Paddle faster! Hurry up!
What?! What're you going to do?!
Seconds count!
Hey, let me go!
Wait!
Gum-Gum...
He was happy about your thoughts.
Hm? It seems noisy...
That was okay I guess...
Bowgun!
I don't have a blind spot!
The skull in the book indicates poison.
Well, no matter what's going on,
You're a transforming idiot
who can't even attack!
Th... Thank you. You guys're amazing...
we'd better take the cannons in
this arsenal outside the castle,
That's a lie!
That's not a lie! Remember it!
You're the one who'll be finished!
Ah! Hey Luffy! You jerk!
Isn't that Nami-san's jacket?!
or Dr. Kureha will throw a
spear or something at us.
There's no medicine that can work
for all diseases in this world.
Yeah... Look! He's still alive,
though the hippo flew away.
Don't be silly...
That's why doctors exist!
I found it!
Wait!
Hm?
That's not true!
Listen. You can't save people
just by being kind!
I won't let you escape!
His jaw!
Take it off! You jerk!
Chopper!
Wapol-sama, are you all right?
If you want to save them, then
learn medical knowledge and skills!
They're stronger than we thought.
We underestimated them!
Doctorine...
Come back!
Yeah... It seems...
that it's finally come...
What's going on?
It's noisy inside the castle.
Without skill, you can't save anyone!
I can no longer let them live!
Those bastards!
Gee, how thoughtless...
What?!
Why can't they be quiet when
others are saying farewell?
the end of the long nightmare...
I'll show them... the true power
of the Munch Munch Fruit!
Wapol-sama!
End...
Where'd he go?!
I'm sorry, Doctorine!
But I wanna see the world!
I'll show them... Munch Munch Factory!
You idiot...
This country is sick right now.
Hoofprint...
Oh, he stood up!
Would a normal person stand
up after taking that attack?
Its citizens, king, and the
government, too, are all sick.
His body's made tough!
People suffer from a sickness of the heart.
What do you think someone
like you can do at sea?!
Chess! Call out what I ate today!
I'll definitely save this country
using medical science one day.
Are you gonna live in a fantasy
just like that quack did?!
...Roseo!
Wapol-sama! Hiriluk is
heading to this castle!
Yes sir!
So he got tricked!
Well... you ate one butter-sauted
cannon and one raw cannon on the ship.
You're wrong! It wasn't a fantasy!
Get out of here, quack!
What an idiot!
Never come back!
Doctor's research had
actually been completed!
Is he serious? Why? What for?
Also cannonball and gunpowder salad as
well as a toasted house in the village.
Run, Chopper!
Whoa!
Hey, he's coming...?! Hm?!
He'll no longer come back to this house.
What kind of stuff do you eat?!
What?!
When it comes to omnivores,
this guy takes the cake.
What's going on?! He's being chased!
Looks like he decided the
castle is his graveyard...
Wait and see... Food soon
becomes my blood and flesh...
3 minutes.
Hey! The ropeway is rea... Hm?
All right, reindeer!
You're pretty good, reindeer! Amazing!
Take me to the patients!
I came to save the Twenty MDs!
Everyone! Get on the sleigh!
We'll go down the mountain!
Ahh!
He's gonna do something!
Shut up!
You'd better be prepared if
What?
you're gonna meddle with
someone else's skull flag!
What an idiot! You still don't get it?!
What?!
Huh?
What's that?
--Gum-Gum...
--Ahh!
Munch Munch Shock!
It was a trap! As you can see,
the Twenty MDs are just fine!
Doctor...
Hey, look...
You came here to die, Dr. Hiriluk...
Wapol House!
What the heck is that?
--Dalton-san!
Ah! That's the witch's sleigh!
A house?!
Sweet!
In any event, let's go up the mountain,
Usopp-san, Mr. Bushido!
Why did he come here?
It's too soon to be surprised.
Now this is the king's technique!
--Hold on a sec!
--Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum...
--I'll give you status and a medal!
--Ahh!
Huh?
Guards, ready...
Munch Munch Factory!
Look! There's someone on top of the castle!
I can't just sit around and wait!
I'm worried what happened to Luffy-san
and the others in that big avalanche!
Ahh!
--Ahhhh!
What the...
Nami-san has a very high fever!
If anything happened...
So that was all...
Doctor...
H... He's eating his own men!
Good... So none of them are sick?
You're worried about Nami...
He's eating his own people!
On top of that, you're worried about
Dalton-san as well as Alabasta, huh?
The kingdom is...
I was convinced...
that this was a national crisis...
The Drum Kingdom is...
Vivi, calm down! You're carrying
too many burdens on your shoulders!
So it was just a trick...
What?
Then... I'll make you vice-king...!
Humph! If it was really a national crisis,
I wouldn't want someone like you!
Nami is with Luffy and Sanji.
I'm sure she's okay.
about to fall!
Pay no attention. Execute him!
...Bazooka!!
They'll be fine! I believe in them!
Don't bother. You guys can't kill me.
That's right... He's right...
He stopped moving...
Feast your eyes on this!
Come out, miraculous union!
Huh?
Hey... when do you think a person dies?
Usopp-san believes in his friends.
--Huh?!
--What?! Union?!
That's why he can be so calm.
When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart?
Thank you, Usopp-san. I...
What was that?!
No... When he's attacked
by an incurable disease?
I am the strongest warrior
of the Drum Kingdom...
It was Dr. Kureha's reindeer.
For you, it's just that you're afraid
of going up the mountain, isn't it?
The ones on the sleigh
were those pirates!
B... But I heard that there're things
like a yeti and bear-bunnies there!
No... When he eats a deadly
poisonous mushroom soup?
What happened up there?!
What the heck happened to Wapol?
Is Dalton-san okay?!
Then say so from the start!
No!
It'll be fine. It's Luffy we're
talking about. He'll make it work.
The Drum Kingdom
was defeated by the skull.
Chessmarimo!
A man dies when people forget him...
Well... isn't that just one
riding on the other's shoulders?
I can't help it if I'm scared!
Any problem with that?!
That felt good! Hey, do it again!
Dalton-san!
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
Sweet!
W-Wait!
You idiot! We're setting sail right away!
What's sweet about it?!
I-I thought I'd die...
Don't let your guard down.
The citizens' sickness of the
heart will be cured as well...
Hm? Where am I?!
Ahh! Dalton-san!
Hmm?
Dalton-san!
Ah, Sanji-san! You came to?
If they were really weak,
a stupid act like exiling doctors...
Would someone please tell me
who the heck this guy is?!
Why're you crying... Dalton-kun?
Dalton-san! You can't!
would've been stopped by the citizens.
Get out of my way! We can't
let Wapol in the castle! Never!
I wonder... if it's the same for a country...
Alright, then! I'll go check.
Don't worry. You can come later.
Was it okay to bid farewell like that?
Yeah, if there's someone
to pass it on to...
Don't tell me you're
heading to the castle!
Ahhh, Zoro's going ahead of me again!
Serious power, activated!
Hey hey, Dalton! What're you crying for?
In your condition... that's reckless!
A pet I was taking care of is being
taken in by someone else. That's all.
When will I fight if I don't fight now?
The Drum Kingdom's Constitution, Article 1!
If Wapol goes back to being the king,
this country will become rotten forever!
Soon a monster will come here.
He's my son. Don't hurt him.
I don't like... tears...
"Those who don't do as the
king wishes should die."
That sums up this country!
There's no way you can fight
in that condition!
It's because this country is my country...
and this castle is my castle.
Hey, let go!
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom can't kill me.
We're no match for them, either...
Alright! I got your back.
--Come with me!
--Ow!
Hey, if you're scared, you can come later!
We have to prepare a flashy send off!
I will settle this! No matter
how dirty I have to play!
Of all the flags,
don't fly that quack's flag!
Hm?
Ouch...
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I'm not scared!
Because I'm...
It will ruin the castle!
I had... such a good life!
I finally did it... This is it...
What?!
I've waited for this reaction for 30 years...
Luffy!
Good-bye, quack...
Ah?! Zoro! Usopp!
Doctor! It wasn't just a fantasy, right?!
Thank you, Chopper!
Your research was completed then, right?!
Ah!
Or, was that a lie, too?
Get on my back.
I'll take you to the castle.
I did it, Chopper! My research succeeded!
A pirate flag...
Hey, reindeer. That flag...
What'd you do that for, you jerk?!
You don't need to be modest!
Did you lie because I'd be sad
if you died without saying so?
Oh, it's you guys!
I don't wanna waste your
determination. That's all.
Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!
"Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!"
Usopp-san...
Since I recognized the
clothes you're wearing,
Please say it again, Doctor!
That's what I told you, right, Chopper?!
I thought you were one of them.
Hold on, okay? I will take you...
to the castle now...
So you guys came up, too.
Usopp, didn't you say
you couldn't come up?
Are you ready, young men?!
Yes, Ma'am!
Usopp-san...
Don't be silly!
Fire!
If I see a mountain in front of me,
I climb it. I'm that kind of guy.
Listen, Kureha. This dust is...
But coming up this cliff
was quite an adventure.
You bastard... you attacked Doctor's flag!
Hey, Usopp-kun. I really don't
think this is going to work...
He blew himself up! What an idiot!
We came up by ropeway. Luffy-san,
It'll work! I'll take you there!
Dr. Kureha! What in the world...?
are Nami-san and Sanji-san okay?
Doctor... tried to save even you!
Just shut up and watch.
You're gonna fight for the country, right?!
You're gonna settle this, right?!
--Yeah, they're fine now.
--Now, get it together...
Chopper...
--Ahh, I'm glad to hear that!
--Now, get it together...
--We were also attacked by
Don't worry. I'll definitely take you there!
--Ahh, I'm glad to hear that!
--a huge condor on our way!
Don't hold a grudge against humans.
The noises are coming from the castle!
Man was I surprised.
Ahh!
Hm? Has Wapol started
fireworks or something?
What's that?!
It's a monster!
But then I was like,
Shoot him! Shoot him!
Idiot! They're cannon noises!
--I'm glad...
--or maybe I should say,
This country is sick right now.
Ahhh!
Geez... that moron...
What's happening?!
just what you'd expect from me...
The king also suffers from
a sickness of the heart.
Wait!
Watch out for the cannonballs!
--So,
--The moment it flew at his heart,
Dammit! We can't see
anything since it's night!
--what were you doing
on top of the castle?
--The moment it flew at his heart,
We just have to go up the mountain, right?
Dr. Kureha! We shot all of them!
Leave... Leave here!
--what were you doing
on top of the castle?
--Captain Me dodged as if dancing
Hmm?
--I was beating the crap out of the king.
--Captain Me dodged as if dancing
Zoro...
Why? Doctor, a guy like
him isn't worth saving!
Light them up!
--I was beating the crap out of the king.
--and quickly rode on the flying condor!
When you can't even defeat me...
--You jerk! You jerk! Usopp Punch!
--Then as I suspected... the one who
--and quickly rode on the flying condor!
--Ow! Ow! What're you doing?!
--You jerk! You jerk! Usopp Punch!
--flew far into the sky earlier was Wapol!
--It was actually me!
you can't possibly defeat them!
--flew far into the sky earlier was Wapol!
--I put a rope around its neck and said,
--You beat him...?!
--Yep! Why?
--I put a rope around its neck and said,
I was just about to use my serious power!
For laughing at
Hiriluk's death, I apologize!
--Yep! Why?
-- "My name is Captain Usopp!"
Amazing...
Yeah... I know.
So what about his two top men?
Hmm?
Yeah...
--Serious Power!
I... I won't hit you...
so leave this country!
Without enough power,
you'll just die in vain...
The reindeer beat them up.
--Whoa, amazing, amazing...
--Serious Power!
It's so beautiful...
Those two... A reindeer did...?
Wait! If you're willing to
go that far to get there...
--How's that? Are you guys amazed?
This is the answer that
I found spending 30 years.
Don't sacrifice yourselves
any longer for this country...
--Oh yeah! Usopp,
--How's that? Are you guys amazed?
What're you saying, Chopper?!
You think he'll just listen to you?!
--listen! I found a new friend!
--Check me out!
...there's a ropeway to the castle.
What a fantastic sight this is...
Can't be. There's no rope
connected to the castle any more.
Hm? What?
Please...
But... after all...
Huh?
I can't understand what
that idiot was thinking...
Reindeer...
There's one. Someone has
reattached a white rope...
Humph!
Ah!
Reindeer...?
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Chopper!
You let him get away, Dalton.
...from a big tree at the
edge of Gyasta to the castle!
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
Shut up! You still don't get it?
Gyasta?
The only man who tried to save
this sick country has just died.
That's the name of the town
that Dr. Kureha headed last.
Hey, annoying mouth!
Get out of here, quack!
Huh?!
Dammit! I thought lizard
eyeballs would work...
When everyone gave up and despaired,
Blue nose...
Hey, Luffy!
Straw Hat!
a kind doctor who tried
to save this country died!
Huh?
Where is that guy?
Wait!
Listen. This red dust isn't ordinary dust.
That guy?
So what if someone like that dies?
You were a fake pirate, right?
For laughing at Hiriluk's death, I apologize!
He's not here!
Which guy?
I saw the path that this country
should take. It should die out.
You don't know what
this pirate flag means
This will attach to the
white snow in the air
That tin bastard! He's disappeared!
Without enough power,
you'll just die in vain...
Ahhh! Ahhh! Ahhh!
and make vivid pink snow fall.
because you were fake pirates
who didn't even risk your lives!
As long as we stay here,
it can't be rebuilt because....
That guy...
even if medical care progresses...
What that flag means, Straw Hat?
He came up on the haired hippo.
He wouldn't go down on his own.
Don't sacrifice yourselves
any longer for this country...
even if the research
on medicine continues...
Stupid pirate flags have no meaning!
When on earth did he...
there's no medicine that can cure fools!
While you were fascinated by
the transformations, of course!
Doctor...! Doctorine...!
That's why you're hopeless!
I let you have your say...
You made me really angry!
You are that reindeer...
What'd you say?!
That bastard! I'll find him
right away and finish him off!
A pirate flag isn't something
that you can raise as a joke!
I see... You've been fighting
all this time since then!
Don't tell me he got into
the castle from somewhere...
What an idiot! If it weren't for a joke,
there's no way I, the king, would raise it!
Please... please teach me to be a doctor!
If that's the case, Nami-san will be...
Don't put that stupid flag
back up when I take it down!
Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the all-purpose medicine!
That bastard! If he lays
his hands on Nami-san,
Thank you.
--Hold it!
--I'll gut him 100 times!
Drum will definitely...
Dodge it! Watch out!
Geez, does he want to die?
I'll become a doctor who can cure
anything! I'll cure even a country!
You can't break this flag!
definitely be reborn...
Doctorine...
Hmm?
Because... Because... there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured!
Luffy!
It's a direct hit!
He called me...
Hm?
He must've been blown away!
Such an idiot!
Ah!
his friend...
Wh-What's that strange creature?!
A-A reindeer? No...
Call me... Doctorine.
See? It didn't break...
I will never shoot you!
That's a... m-m-m-mons...
My name is Dr. Hiriluk! I'm a doctor!
Hey, stop it!
C... Can't be! He's stupid!
Ahhh! It's a monster!
Where're you, annoying mouth?!
Tony Tony Chopper.
That's a cool name, isn't it?
I won't... die...
I don't know who the heck
this pirate flag belongs to...
That's what I'll call you.
Seems like my fever is
coming down quite a bit.
I will carry on his will...
Chopper, you'll be able to become
a good doctor. I'll guarantee it.
but since this flag is a person's
pledge to risk his life...
Don't call him a monster!
At this rate, it's likely that
I can go back to the ship soon.
He's the new friend I was talking about!
it's not raised as a joke!
What?! That thing is?!
So for the 6 years since then...
Tony-kun has been studying under you...
He got shocked and ran away!
What am I doing?!
This flag isn't something you can
just break while laughing foolishly!
This is no time to be in bed resting here!
Vivi is waiting for me!
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
Wait! Monster!
Yeah... I taught him everything I know...
Hey!
I had... such a good life!
Reindeer!
Doctorine! Doctorine!
Hey, wait!
What the heck is going on here?!
Ahh! That bastard!
Hey! Reindeer!
Thank you, Chopper!
Is this really my Drum Castle?
Incredible...
You're my friend!
So this is... a pirate!
I've finally returned!
What have they done to my castle?
Hey! Reindeer!
That annoying mouth!
--You're definitely my friend!
Now, we're restoring the Drum Kingdom!
--Doctor...
--You're definitely my friend!
They won't get away with this!
It won't break... Never...
--Doctor...
--Hey!
--This is for the best, right?
Doctorine! There's a problem!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
I will chew up every single one of them!
--This is...
--Wait!
Wapol is back!
Wait! Reindeer!
The skull is a mark of faith!
No way I'd wait!
Is that so...
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Hey, Chopper! What's the matter?
I should get out of here quickly
while Doctorine isn't around!
I won't hit you, so leave this country!
That reindeer is amazing.
He transforms one form after another!
Doctorine, thanks for teaching me
medical science all this time.
How long are you gonna be in a daze?
That bastard! I'll find him
right away and finish him off!
Come here and dance! Sing!
He can really jump.
It's no use, Chopper.
You think he'll just listen to you?
Shhhh! Leave him alone for now!
Although I experienced many hardships,
A beam's next! He's gonna shoot a beam!
If he lays his hands on Nami-san,
I'll gut him 100 times!
I love this country where
I met Doctor and you.
He won't, you idiot! H-hey, hold on a sec!
He's experiencing what it's like
to set out on a journey as a man.
Wapol! You don't know what this flag
means because you were fake pirates!
Where did that tin bastard go?
Oh no! He looks like a bad guy!
What? He's not here!
When on earth did he...
But I'm leaving. I'm going out to sea!
Okay, then! Let's toast to our new friend!
I've cornered you, annoying mouth!
While you were fascinated by
the transformations, of course!
I wanna see the world with my own eyes!
Dalton-san's got dynamites!
The skull is a mark of faith!
Where're you, annoying mouth?!
Don't talk so cocky.
Yeah!
I have no idea what's going on here.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Goodbye Drum Island!
I'm Going Out to Sea!"
"Zoan-Type Devil Fruit!
Chopper's Seven-Form Transformation"
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies."
"Vs. Wapol's Corps!
The Power of the Munch Munch Fruit!"
"When The Kingdom's Rule Ends!
The Flag of Faith Flies Forever"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!