Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Hey! What're you doing?!
It's because you're pestering me!
Like I said, just join us!
This is exactly what
I mean by pestering me!
It's fun to be a pirate!
I've had enough!
Just rest in there for a while!
Hmm?
Your injuries actually
aren't that light, either.
Geez... What's his problem?
Huh?
Why?!
Wait!
What is this guy?!
When did he steal the key?!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
This smell is...
Huh?
Wapol!
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms
And The Will That Gets Carried On!"
When he found out that
Hiriluk had only 10 days to live,
Chopper got quite upset.
Well, that was only natural.
But he took action in his own way...
I'm gonna... die...
I will make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country!
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
A lot of guards have been
absent recently. What's going on?
Well... they're out picking mushrooms
at the request of the Twenty MDs.
Mushrooms?
They said there's some mushroom
that can cure anything...
Mushroom?
Ah!
Hmm?
Idiot! They'll see us!
Doctor, about what they said...
I will never shoot you!
Don't ever come back here!
I did a terrible thing to you...
At least see my cherry blossoms.
They'll be my last big work.
Well... here we go again!
Dammit! I don't have much time left!
Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!
That's what I told you, right?!
I will fight!
Just like pirates do!
I found it! The Amiudake mushroom...
That's the one!
But...
how can I get across?
Dammit!
I'm close... I'm so close!
Doctor...
I'm sorry... I lost...
one of your precious books...
What... happened to you?
Mushroom...
Medicine...
That's an Amiudake mushroom!
You... got it for me?
Please live... Please live, Doctor...
I wanna be a doctor.
Please teach me how to be a doctor.
I'll fight, too... just like pirates do!
Do you think a reindeer
can become one, too?
You can! You can!
You can! You can be a great doctor...
Doct- I can't breath...
because you have such a kind heart...
You idiot!
Chess! Kuromarimo!
Is the doctor hunt going well?!
Yes sir. Most of the doctors
have already been exiled.
Most?
There are two that
we haven't captured yet.
That Dr. Kureha and...
the quack, Hiriluk.
What'd you say?!
Oh, yeah! I've come up with a good idea!
--Hmm?
Send an official notice to the citizens.
The Twenty MDs have all... fallen ill...
Does the Amiudake mushroom soup...
taste good?
Ahhh! Darn, this tastes terrible!
What?!
This isn't something that
any living thing can eat!
Oh no...
Don't be so down.
Good medicine doesn't taste good.
This means it's working.
Thank you, Chopper.
Huh?!
Hmm?
Huh?
What's that?
I did it...
What?
I finally did it... This is it!
This reaction... I've waited
for it for 30 years...
I did it, Chopper!
My research succeeded!
I wasn't wrong! I wasn't! I wasn't!
I can now make cherry blossoms
bloom on this winter island!
Listen. I'm going out,
but you stay put and rest here.
Okay.
See you later!
Doctor was happy...
I cured a human's disease!
Hmm?
You'll be able to become
a good doctor. I'll guarantee it.
Do you know... that the entire
country is a madhouse right now?
Yeah, I know.
About the Twenty MDs falling ill,
right? Ridiculous!
So what brought you here today?
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
Ahh, I refuse.
I haven't asked anything yet!
What's this dust?
That's my 30 years.
That's the medical science
that I've finally completed!
It's an all-purpose medicine that can
cure the country's sickness of the heart.
You've lived 30 fruitless years.
Good work.
So, why are you showing it to me?
There isn't enough dust.
I don't have much time left, either.
I want you to make cherry
blossoms bloom in my place.
Ridiculous! Why do I have to-
And one more thing!
Please teach medical science to Chopper.
He wants to become a doctor.
That's enough!
--He's a reindeer and monster,
but he'll certainly become a good doctor!
--Why would I...
--He's a reindeer and monster,
but he'll certainly become a good doctor!
He's a nice guy with a kind heart.
He risked his life
to make medicine for me!
Please! Help him become a doctor!
What nerve you have!
You want me to take care of your
stupid research and strange pet?!
You should know that I'm not someone
who'll sympathize with a man
just because he's not long for this world!
Get out of here!
Yeah... I know...
We've known each other a long time.
I'm counting on you...
It's not like you, Hiriluk...
throwing in the towel already...
I don't have much time left...
That idiot! He wouldn't!
What do you mean?!
The Twenty MDs fell ill!
Who'll treat this country's sick people?!
At least give us access to medicine!
Talking to us won't do anything!
--Even doctors get sick!
--Out of my way!
--Ahh! Hiriluk?!
--Out of my way! Out of my way!
That bastard is crazy!
Take the ropeway out.
Take me to the castle.
Where's Hiriluk?!
You don't have to run away!
I know about you!
I'm asking you where the quack went!
D-Doctor got better
so he went to the town...
Got better? He doesn't get better.
He can't be cured with
the current medical science.
That's not true! Look at this!
He's fine now because he ate this!
That's... an Amiudake mushroom!
This is an all-purpose medicine!
So he's fine now!
Doctor said that he felt
full of energy, too!
I will learn to be a doctor from Doctor.
What was that for?!
You stupid reindeer!
That mushroom is...
extremely poisonous!
Once you eat it, you'll be
dead within half a day!
What?
That's why that idiot...
That can't be true.
I looked it up in a book...
though I lost that book...
It's a mushroom that can defeat diseases!
That's why I raised this skull
towards all the diseases!
That's right! There was a skull right
next to the Amiudake mushroom picture!
Doctor also said he got better!
There's no way he'll die! You're a liar!
Paddle faster! Hurry up!
Seconds count!
He was happy about your thoughts.
The skull in the book indicates poison.
That's a lie!
That's not a lie! Remember it!
There's no medicine that can work
for all diseases in this world.
That's why doctors exist!
That's not true!
Listen. You can't save people
just by being kind!
If you want to save them, then
learn medical knowledge and skills!
Without skill, you can't save anyone!
You idiot...
Wapol-sama! Hiriluk is
heading to this castle!
So he got tricked!
What an idiot!
Is he serious? Why? What for?
He'll no longer come back to this house.
Looks like he decided the
castle is his graveyard...
Take me to the patients!
I came to save the Twenty MDs!
What?
What an idiot! You still don't get it?!
It was a trap! As you can see,
the Twenty MDs are just fine!
You came here to die, Dr. Hiriluk...
Why did he come here?
Guards, ready...
So that was all...
Good... So none of them are sick?
I was convinced...
that this was a national crisis...
So it was just a trick...
Humph! If it was really a national crisis,
I wouldn't want someone like you!
Pay no attention. Execute him!
Don't bother. You guys can't kill me.
Huh?
Hey... when do you think a person dies?
When a bullet from a
pistol pierces his heart?
No... When he's attacked
by an incurable disease?
No... When he eats a deadly
poisonous mushroom soup?
No!
A man dies when people forget him...
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
The citizens' sickness of the
heart will be cured as well...
Why're you crying... Dalton-kun?
I wonder... if it's the same for a country...
Yeah, if there's someone
to pass it on to...
Hey hey, Dalton! What're you crying for?
Soon a monster will come here.
He's my son. Don't hurt him.
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom can't kill me.
I had... such a good life!
Good-bye, quack...
Thank you, Chopper!
He blew himself up! What an idiot!
Ahh!
What's that?!
It's a monster!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
Ahhh!
Wait!
Leave... Leave here!
When you can't even defeat me...
you can't possibly defeat them!
For laughing at
Hiriluk's death, I apologize!
Without enough power,
you'll just die in vain...
Don't sacrifice yourselves
any longer for this country...
Please...
Huh?
You let him get away, Dalton.
Shut up! You still don't get it?
The only man who tried to save
this sick country has just died.
When everyone gave up and despaired,
a kind doctor who tried
to save this country died!
So what if someone like that dies?
I saw the path that this country
should take. It should die out.
As long as we stay here,
it can't be rebuilt because....
even if medical care progresses...
even if the research
on medicine continues...
there's no medicine that can cure fools!
I let you have your say...
You made me really angry!
Please... please teach me to be a doctor!
Please... teach me to be a doctor!
I'll become the all-purpose medicine!
I'll become a doctor who can cure
anything! I'll cure even a country!
Because... Because... there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured!
Call me... Doctorine.
I won't... die...
I will carry on his will...
So for the 6 years since then...
Tony-kun has been studying under you...
Yeah... I taught him everything I know...
Doctorine! Doctorine!
Ahh! That bastard!
I've finally returned!
That annoying mouth!
Now, we're restoring the Drum Kingdom!
Doctorine! There's a problem!
Wapol is back!
Is that so...
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
I won't hit you, so leave this country!
It's no use, Chopper.
You think he'll just listen to you?
Wapol! You don't know what this flag
means because you were fake pirates!
The skull is a mark of faith!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Vs. Wapol's Corps!
The Power of the Munch Munch Fruit!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!