Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Sanji started to transport the wedding cake
so as to fend off Big Mom's Hunger Pangs attack.
But Oven caught Chiffon, Bege's wife,
who was helping bake the cake, on a charge of treason.
To save Chiffon who is in trouble,
Bege headed for Cacao Island.
Chiffon, here I come!
Meanwhile, Luffy is on the run
waiting for his Haki to be replenished.
"A Man's Way of Life!
Bege and Luffy's Determination as Captains!"
Where is the... cake?!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
That was close!
Thank goodness there was a mirror.
I don't want anybody to bother me
until I regain my Haki.
Big Brother!
Oh, you fool! Stop shouting!
Brulee's here!
Shut up, you bastard!
I can't fight you yet!
Help, Big Bro!
Prepare to fire!
CACAO ISLAND - NEAR THE PORT
Shoot!
Father! We can't take it anymore!
This is not a time to whine! Hang tough!
Oh, good boy, good boy, good boy!
You can see Mommy soon!
Peek-a, peek-a, peek-a...
...boo!
Papa...
Oh, how cute, how cute!
Papa will save Mommy no matter what!
I can't believe Bege is taking such reckless action!
He cares about you quite a lot!
Big Bro! Please stop!
I have no mercy for someone
who betrayed her family!
--Connect me to the speaker!
--Yes, sir!
Bege!
It's me! Oven!
Oven?!
I just caught your accomplice, Chiffon,
on Cacao Island.
What?!
--Rero?!
--Madam has been caught?!
We just left town and are heading
to the port now!
So you guys should come straight to the port just as you are
and surrender yourselves!
It's no use fighting!
Our armed soldiers are
expecting you at the port!
I guess when they tried to transport the cake by ship,
Oven got in their way.
I obey the law.
Even if she's my little sister,
I'm not gonna hesitate!
If you do something strange,
that's it.
Rero?!
Bege! Everyone! Just turn around and run!
I came here out of my selfishness!
If you get caught, we'll all be executed anyway!
You guys should survive even if I die!
I was always hated by Mama...
And you guys are...
...the only true family I have!
So someday...
...take revenge for me!
Ma'am, what are you saying?!
Ma'am!
Stop talking nonsense!
Chiffon!
Oven!
We'll soon be arriving at the port!
We'll enter the port as you say!
Bege?!
So just don't hurt Chiffon!
Honey...
Pez...
Ma'am!
Guys!
All right!
You're too soft, Bege.
It's gonna cost you your neck!
Bege's ship is coming!
All soldiers! Prepare to be on alert!
Fleet! Separate into right and left flanks
and block their escape route!
Yes, sir!
We're surrounded by enemy ships!
Father! What should we do-rero?!
I see Bege's ship!
I guess he's coming to surrender
without a fight as he promised.
Oven-sama's carriage is arriving at the port!
Boy, they sure are stupid!
Look! Bege is coming to see you!
Big Sis!
I'm begging you, Big Bro! Please stop!
It's too late, Pudding.
We can't go back!
They should've kept running!
Bege!
Father! We're finally at the island!
They're entering the port at last!
Now, engrave the sight of his sail unfurled for the last time
in your memory.
Your husband will never take to sea again!
Oven-sama!
What fools.
We did it! Father!
Rero!
How dare you!
Don't forget that you're totally surrounded!
Don't you wanna get sunk?!
Burn it into your memory, Pez.
This is the way Papa lives.
Father!
Good job!
Now what are you gonna do?!
I'll go along with you, Bege!
Bege!
ON THE SEA - THE SUNNY
Ships!
The Big Mom Pirates are catching up to us!
Roger! The time has come!
Uh-huh! Just running around is dull!
Let's attack them!
Prepare to attack!
I'm counting on you guys, too!
Yeah, leave it to us! Let's do it, Carrot!
Carrot?
Carrot! Where are you?!
Carrot! There you are!
A big battle is just starting!
Until Sanji comes,
we gotta hold out somehow!
Don't worry! You got me!
Count on me!
Carrot? Are you listening?
Hey, Chobro.
Hm?
Is it a full moon tonight?
Hmmm?!
I won't forgive him!
Oh, no! Big Bro Oven is furious!
Get to the port!
There's nowhere to run on the sea!
Nor on the land!
Get off of the ship!
So you chose to fight, Bege!
All right. I'm gonna execute you!
Oh no, Big Sis!
We can't put to the sea!
What should we do with the cake?!
Speed up!
Go straight to the port!
Bege sped up!
What is he thinking?!
He's gonna crash into the port!
Why isn't he slowing down?!
Don't tell me it's a suicide attack!
Guys! Are you all prepared?!
--Yeah!
--Rero!
Keep it at maximum speed!
Oh, no!
The ship is gonna smash right into us!
Stop!
It's gonna crash into the bank!
You've got to be kidding!
It's running on the coast!
Bege!
Don't hold back! Get ready to shoot!
You traitor!
This is great!
I'll burn you along with your ship!
Get out of my way, you little punks.
This Nostra Castello is...
...amphibious!
I'm here to pick you up, Chiffon!
Bege!
The paddles turned into tank tracks!
I've never heard of such a gimmick!
Well, I've never told you!
Why would I show my cards
to people who I plan on betraying?!
You asshole!
Shoot-rero!
Chiffon! Hand the cake over to us!
What?!
It's impossible! The cake is gigantic!
How can you hand it over
to a ship at that speed?!
What?! Whaaat?!
The carriage is in the air?!
What's going on?!
What?!
Black-Leg!
Make room on the deck, Bege!
Sanji-san!
Pudding-sama!
Somebody, help!
Be quiet, Branch!
It's Brulee!
CHIPS TOWN
This is Chips Town! Straw Hat Luffy is here!
Let go of me!
MIRROWORLD
This is Chockfull Town!
Straw Hat has been spotted!
What?! Chockfull Town this time?!
SWEET CITY
Straw Hat is emerging in different places!
Seems like he's running around the Mirroworld!
Did Big Sis Brulee get caught again?!
This is Green Town!
We have multiple calls from private residences
saying they saw someone suspicious!
What are you doing?! If you wanna escape,
why don't you go to Cacao Island already?!
What? How do you know that?
I eavesdropped!
Everyone knows now!
What?! Is it true?!
Just give up! You can't beat my brother!
Haki wears out.
If the battle goes longer,
his Color of Observation will become weaker, too...
You look dumb
but you're sharp at fighting.
But that's not good enough!
Don't look with your eyes.
Feel other's presence.
Okay!
All right!
Come on!
Damn you!
Don't lose your composure!
Feel how your enemy will move next...
....before he moves.
Luffy.
I gave you lessons
but Haki becomes even stronger
in the heat of actual battle.
The more you face tough enemies,
the stronger you'll be.
I wonder if I can see
slightly ahead into the future, too.
What are you talking about?!
Don't push your luck, you short-ass!
I wanna surpass him!
I wanna defeat him at full strength!
The man with...
...a bounty of a billion!
Sanji, Bege, and the others cooperate to transport the cake.
But the enraged Oven turns the sea into a burning hell
to block their way!
When the ship catches fire and they are driven into a corner,
a savior emerges before them?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Cake Sank?! Sanji and Bege's Getaway Battle!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!