Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy returned to the Mirroworld
where Katakuri was waiting.
Sanji is transporting the wedding cake
so as to fend off Big Mom's Hunger Pangs attack.
After moving the wedding cake to Bege's ship,
Returning to the Mirroworld
with the fiery goal of taking down Katakuri,
In the battle raging in the Mirroworld,
Luffy suffered fierce attacks
from Katakuri who had recovered his composure...
Sanji and the others tried to escape from Cacao Island
but Oven stood in their way.
Luffy plunged himself into
another desperate battle.
I...
...while trying to enhance
his Haki of the Color of Observation.
However, Oven, barging into the carriage carrying the cake,
caught Chiffon,
...came to defeat you!
Gum-Gum...
Came to defeat me?
I will boil you all to death!
and commanded Bege who was trying to meet up with
Sanji and the others, to surrender.
Focus... I need to focus more...
You're not given...
They were saved by Chiffon's father Pound
who happened to be there.
Mochi Blade Bullet!
...such an option!
Meanwhile, at the Sunny
which has been sandwiched by the big enemy fleet...
Meanwhile,
on the ship heading towards Cacao Island,
Right!
Congratulations...
...on your marriage!
Sanji was infuriated by Bege
who tried to poison the cake.
Carrot... So beautiful...
What fools.
Chiffon!!
Listen to me, Bege...
Burn it into your memory, Pez.
How mystic...
Meanwhile, Luffy regained his Haki and
went back to the Mirroworld where Katakuri was waiting.
Damn...
You're free to do the assassination...
His Color of Observation is unbelievable!
This is the way Papa lives.
But you have to wait
until I satisfy my guest!
Meanwhile, Luffy moved out of the Mirroworld
waiting for his Haki to be replenished...
Even if you just ran away,
since I'm your opponent,
He's surely... strong!
I feed anyone who wants to eat!
That's what cooks do!
no one would've jeered at you.
Meanwhile, his friends on the Sunny
were cornered by Big Mom.
I wonder if I can see
slightly ahead into the future, too.
Why did you come back?
At the same time, while the Sunny was trying to
shake the enemy fleets,
However, Nami and Brook caused
Zeus to discharge a bolt
What are you talking about?!
Don't push your luck, you short-ass!
"Sulong!
Carrot's Big Mystic Transformation!"
Big Mom descended.
and gave a tremendous blow to Big Mom.
I wanna surpass him!
No way!
I wanna defeat him at full strength!
Big Mom!
Where's my wedding cake?
"Break Through!
The Straw Hat's Mighty Sea Battle!"
The man with...
You chose death over the shame of
others thinking you ran away?
...a bounty of a billion!
Stand back, guys!
Get ready to even abandon the ship!
Chose death?
"The Cake Sank?!
Sanji and Bege's Getaway Battle!"
Or you've noticed
that you're no match for me
But...
Unstoppable Donuts!
and come to beg to be our ally?
Oh... I'm so hungry.
But nothing else can satisfy me.
Damn, it's the technique he used before!
Beg?
I almost... I almost can see his next move...
Cut the crap...
Where is it?!
I...
I can see it, Straw Hat...
10 minutes has passed.
...came to defeat you!
Where is the wedding cake?!
Your future is in darkness!
--No! The Sunny...!
--Oh, no!
Did he run back to his crew?
Nine-headed Mochi!
How can we kick out such a monster?!
Shut up!
Power Mochi!
Came to defeat me?
That's okay.
My future is...
He can't get away from Mama anyway...
You're not given...
...mine to decide!
"Finally, They Clash!
The Emperor of the Sea vs. the Straw Hats!"
...such an option!
"Dark King's Direct Precepts!
The Battle Against Katakuri Turns Around!"
FLOUR TOWN, WHEAT ISLAND
I don't get it...
The difference in power is obvious.
That scared me!
I won't let you get away!
Why do you wanna get up?
Straw Hat!
You know you can't win
so why do you keep fighting?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Damn...
Shut up!
Before we got Big Mom and the others off of our tail,
our path ahead has been blocked...
What are you doing?
Carrot!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Who's fleet is it that's in our way?!
Why?
I...
Mirrors are...
FLOUR TOWN, WHEAT ISLAND
Armament Hardening!
Hang on!
No, you stop making me repeat myself!
If this goes on, there'll be
no mirror left in this town!
There is nothing you can do to defeat me.
I didn't expect him to fight this long
against Katakuri-sama in the Mirroworld...
That writing...
It says "Daifuku"!
Is Straw Hat Luffy that strong?!
What?! So it's him...
There's nothing you can do now!
I'll beat you at any cost!
If I remember right,
he was at the Tea Party...
Power Mochi!
Gum-Gum...
Handclap Mochi!
Th-The cake is...
You got nowhere left to run,
you damn Straw Hats...
...flying in the air...
...Giant...
...Bazooka!
This will be your graveyard...
Bavarois-sama!
A fleet led by Daifuku-sama has arrived
ahead of us!
Gum-Gum...
It's not working!
...Giant Rifle!
And we have reinforcements from behind!
Behind?
Unstoppable Donuts!
I still can't see it!
That's...
How about this?
Power Mochi!
Hurry up, Bege!
We keep getting reports on mirror-breakings
from various islands.
A fleet of reinforcements led by Sweet
General Smoothie-sama has arrived!
Unstoppable Handclap Mochi!
Back off, guys!
SWEET GENERAL SMOOTHIE
14TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Make room on the deck!
It's already 9:30 PM-soir.
Y-Yes! Father!
In addition, the flag ship which
Smoothie-sama is commanding,
It's been almost 12 hours
since the attack on the Tea Party!
CINNAMON - 16TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
CITRON - 15TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Black-Leg! Alright, come on!
has Citron-sama and Cinnamon-sama
on board as well!
What's going on? Dammit!
They're quite irritated.
That many of them?!
Who the hell is that?!
Of course, they are.
If by any chance they let the Straw Hats flee,
But with them, we're invincible!
With just one leg...
Is he a chef?!
it'll be a disgrace to
the Emperor of the Sea.
All right. Let's do it, guys!
Yeah!
Okay! Let's go!
Well, as a newspaper magnate,
it's better for me because it'll make a good cover story.
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Everyone! Prepare for the impact!
Guys!
Smoothie's fleet is coming from behind!
I'll break you this time!
Guys...
Do you wanna know something interesting?
On top of Daifuku,
even Sweet General Smoothie is here, too...
Hey, stop!
That'll reduce the Straw Hats' chances to survive!
Tart ships.
Dodge to the left!
Spread out and block their way!
What is it, Stussy-sama?
To the right!
Roger! 15 degrees to starboard!
15 degrees to starboard!
At the Tea Party, Linlin revealed...
Sluggie-gie!
Focus... I need to focus more...
...the Tamate Box from the Ryugu Palace.
Hey, Big Bro Peros,
why are you taking so much time for a rat?
Mochi Blade Bullet!
She got it...
...from Straw Hat Luffy, didn't she?
Can I just sink them?
Do as you like. Lick...
So what?
The cake made it!
That Tamate Box...
Right!
You guys are so ostentatious!
Mama is gonna go to Cacao Island
where Pudding is waiting anyway.
...contained explosives.
That was amazing, Black-Leg!
Up!
Are you sure-bon?
Mochi Blade Bullet!
What's this good smell?
Yes, I saw it by accident
when the chateau was caught in the blast.
Prometheus...
It seems like Mama's getting thinner.
O-Only Germa could do that!
Zeus...
Lick...
I'm not Germa!
Mama?
Those assholes...!!
Wedding cake!
Thanks for your work.
I can't get a spare minute to focus!
Brother Peros!
Mama's acting strange!
All ships, prepare to fire!
Lick. Yeah I know!
She's gotten thinner and is breathing weirdly!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Rifle!
Right!
Bege! Pez!
Up!
Are you alright, honey?
As soon as their ship
comes within your range,
Wall!
Unstoppable Donuts!
Yes...
Back!
shoot it up!
Prometheus... Zeus...
Oh, no...
Daifuku's ships are preparing
to fire their cannons!
You're always so reckless...
Napoleon!
What happened to Zeus and Prometheus?!
I don't think we're in their range yet...
I'm calling them over now!
Thank you!
It's been almost eight hours
since her Hunger Pangs attack started!
Even if we try to move aside,
they'd block us from all sides.
S-Sanji...
Damn...
We've never been unable to stop it
for this long
...sa...
His Color of Observation is unbelievable!
Pudding-sama! Stay with us!
Jimbei, let's keep advancing
without slowing down!
and never seen her getting that hungry!
But we're up against Daifuku's ship...
He controls a genie and is tough to beat!
How long will you continue
attacking recklessly?
He's surely... strong!
Even we have no idea
what's gonna happen to her...
Unstoppable...
I can do that by seeing
the future with my Haki.
...Handclap Mochi!
To find a way out of this situation,
we must go straight!
I won't stand for that!
I just lost my cool a little bit...
She's truly an unknown monster now.
Lick.
Right. Let's prepare ourselves.
I'm not gonna let them get away!
...so I gave you chances to attack.
Oh, no!
Oven-sama! Please get out of the way!
Is she gonna make it to Cacao Island?
I'll liven it up taking a Rumble Ball!
Go closer so I can jump onto their ship!
The Color of Observation can't be utilized
if you're not calm.
Don't you know who I am?!
By the way, Brother Peros,
Gum-Gum...
I got a call saying that Pudding is
transporting the cake this way now!
I'll stop that!
Fighting at close range...
It's gonna be tough.
...Elephant Gun!
If I can calm down...
--Mm-hm.
--Let's go!
Oh, really?! She's literally our savior!
You still try to resist,
Well, there's a problem, Big Bro!
but I'll just get rid of you.
Calm down... Calm down!
It certainly is Pudding
who is transporting the cake...
Come on!
Focus! Focus!
They'll come into our range soon.
but the ship is... Bege's, they said...
SQUISH!
Unstoppable Mochi Blade Bullets!
Oh... he's perfect and cool as always.
He got run over!
Fire all our shells at them.
Lick? Did you say Bege?!
Don't take my paddle ship lightly.
--Yeah!
--It's our chance!
Big Bro Katakuri!
Why is the cake that'll save our country
on the assassins' ship?!
And...
Hey, use faceless shells.
...haven't you gotten a
clear shot yet, sniper?
Well, I've been shooting at him
without being noticed...
I-I don't know!
While Mama is in that condition,
they're uncontrollable.
Oh, good boy, good boy, Pez.
I know it was a little too loud...
What do you mean you don't know?!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY
--Oh, please!
--Daifuku-sama!
But he's moving so fast!
What are we gonna do?! We can't trust that cake anymore!
Shut up!
IN THE TERRITORY - BEGE'S SHIP
Damn!
Gee! You're useless!
So crappy!
He's still there...
If we don't take out Straw Hat soon,
Big Bro Katakuri will bring him down.
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Coat more evenly there!
--Peek-a-boo!
--Who is that guy? A peeping Tom?
Everyone!
Who's head is going to be patted by Big Bro?!
Everyone has their own turn.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Wedding cake!
That's poison. Just pour it in already!
Carrot...
Of course, it's Flampe-sama's!
Did you hide it in here?!
Huh? What's the matter, Pez?
You-gara'll have your turn, too.
I thought so!
Wait, Big Mom!
Don't worry...
I know you-gara can do it...
I don't see it!
It looks like she's happy.
I'm sure you-gara can...
It's not here!
I have 41 older brothers.
Be careful! They'll start shooting!
Stop! You won't find the cake on this ship!
And 40 of them vote for
the Best Little Sister Award.
Yeah, I know!
What are you doing, Black-Leg?!
We wanna set sail towards
the southeast, Bege.
That's my line! Screw you!
BEST LITTLE SISTER AWARD
Okay...
Chobro!
What?!
I'll never ever allow you to poison the cake!
We should just run through the town like this
and get to the sea.
Everyone!
No way... That can't be true!
FLAMPE
I won!
Everyone loves me!
Let me handle Daifuku and the others!
Big Mom will eat this cake for sure.
Pudding!
My son told me that it's here!
That means I'm a much-loved little sister!
I'm sure I can help you!
We'll have to run over some chocolate houses.
Knowing that, what kind of idiots would we be
not to put in poison or explosives!
If it's not, I have to
kill my eldest son myself!
Carrot?!
C. FLAMPE (AGE 15) - 33RD DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
(PRESIDENT OF THE KATAKURI FAN CLUB
AND SUICIDE SQUAD CAPTAIN)
What?!
I have to be the king of the little sisters!
In order to sail out all together,
we have no choice!
Because it's...
We can get rid of one of the Four Emperors!
So cute!
...a full-moon tonight.
Can't you see how big this chance is?!
Sh-She remembers!
Everyone wants to be Big
Bro Katakuri's favorite!
Don't tell me you'll become Sulong?!
Are you trained for it?!
Shut up! This is a challenge
where we put our pride as cooks on the line!
But he's an icon for all
his 38 younger sisters!
If you're lying,
Don't do anything shitty!
We'll defeat the enemy with flavor!
Don't worry... Pedro trained me.
you'll pay with your lifespan!
Even all his younger brothers admire him.
There are too many rivals!
Huh?! Stop dreaming!
I know what he'd say now...
Just how lucid is she right now?!
Big Mom's eaten all kinds of delicious sweets
from around the world up until today
So I wanna help him now to earn some points!
"Leave it to me."
What a waste.
I'll fix them later.
and you have to make a cake
that'll surpass her expectations!
If Carrot is going,
I'm going with her!
I thought I could cover it up!
I know how you feel, Flampe-sama!
Houses can be rebuilt.
So can families.
Leave it to me, Chobro!
That's impossible!
We wanna be liked by Katakuri-sama, too!
That's right! If we can't make that,
we'll be dead!
Yeah. Of course it'd be best
if they didn't break down...
I may not look it
but I'm a member of the Musketeers.
I don't care about you guys!
It seems like Big Bro's plan has failed...
Everyone, man the cannons!
I'm looking forward to it!
This is my house now.
When we got here,
he didn't seem like himself.
You were too optimistic, Big Bro Peros...
We'll shoot salvos and sink it quickly!
Even if you succeed,
she won't let us walk away alive!
And I have this many new family members.
Are you saying my son's a liar?!
Wait for my cue!
Ma'am!
But now he's as cool as always!
Cut the crap!
I guess you don't know who she used to be!
What do you mean, Pedro?
Hey, Napoleon!
I can't stand to see him having a hard time
against his enemy in the first place!
One day, you'll see how important it was...
Yes, Mama!
Mark my words, you'll regret not killing her
when you had the chance...
Let's do it!
...to save Luffy and the others here
and let them set sail!
Every moment should be total perfection!
You bastards!
Don't use cannons!
Cognac!
I'll burn you and cut you in half!
You might blow up the cake!
Or I'll be disappointed!
I'll fight...
A big flaming sword!
They're gonna get to the sea!
Don't let them escape!
...on your-teia behalf...
You're right.
No chance! Get away, Jimbei!
But he's not having a hard time now.
Fleet, head for the southeast of the island!
Pedro!
Go to hell!
We're on our way!
It's just that the enemy's persistent!
Father!
Kairagi Glaze!
Mama-mash!
What did you do to him?!
He must've received mortal wounds
dozens of times but he keeps getting up.
Black-Leg!
What did you shove into his mouth?!
Alright! We got off of Cacao Island!
What a fool!
What the?!
Ask him!
He's absorbing Cognac!
Hooray!
Laughable.
Jimbei!
Father!
I... I could die...
What is that?
The Tart ships are far behind of us-rero.
Black-Leg, you bastard, I knew it!
Don't think...
How many times will you get up?
No one can catch up to this paddle ship now.
It's so delicious that I could die!
This cream!
...you can overpower me, you damn shark!
Thank you, Bege. You saved us.
Until I...
What?! He almost died from deliciousness?!
...beat your ass!
I didn't do it for you guys, Black-Leg!
Father, I'm relieved-rero!
Jimbei-san!
Father!
--Oh, no!
--Jimbei!
Listen to me, Bege...
Isn't it peculiarly hot?
Yeah, it is.
You're free to do the assassination...
Father, the sea doesn't look right-rero!
But you have to wait until I satisfy my guest!
Where is it?! Give me the cake!
Gum-Gum...
I'm starving to death!
...Hawk Stamp!
I feed anyone who wants to eat!
That's what cooks do!
Carrot!
Stop, Big Mom!
--Fish are floating to the surface!
--They're boiled by the heated water?!
Carrot is in that room!
With the right amount of salt,
they probably taste good...
If you want me to stop...
--Pudding-sama!
--Why are you collapsing?!
Did he try to dodge?
We'll get boiled next, idiot!
Nami!
Did you eat the cream, too?!
Tell me where it is!
Just don't pay her any mind!
There's only one guy capable of this...
Why aren't they dying?!
Oh, damn...
It feels like I got hypnotized or something!
Look!
Nami!
Your...
I'm fine!
Maybe this cake will work for Big Mom, too...
Tsk! I knew that he wouldn't die
just by getting run over by a ship...
...eyes!
Oh, no! The sail caught
fire from Big Mom's head!
Bege! I'm using my cooking skills on this
for the first time in a long while!
Tropical Torment!
Believe in the power of sweets!
With my Heat-Heat Fruit,
Where did you hide...
Yeah... Okay...
I will boil you all to death!
Get away, Nami!
That massive cake?!
Now, let's hurry up!
Have you finished coating the cake?!
It's hot!
A little more to go!
It's simmering-rero!
Guard Point!
Her eyes are red...
She looks like a different person...
Chiffon-sama!
Two chefs fell victim to the sweet smell!
We have other issues!
Carrot... So beautiful...
Oh, no! The temperature of the chocolate
will change!
Guys! Keep your wits about you until it's done!
Chopper!
How mystic...
Well, well...
The whipped cream will melt, too!
Yes, ma'am!
Oh, she looks pretty amazing...
That means...
I don't understand.
Falling down itself is already shameful.
Stay safe... Nami-san, I'm on my way!
Look what you've become!
You're rarer than ever.
If nothing is done,
the cake for Big Mom will be ruined!
I'd like to see her panties...
I'll definitely add you to
my collection of strange beasts!
Is that what Duke Dogstorm was talking about?
That fool, what is he thinking?!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY - PROMETHEUS AND ZEUS
You little chubby raccoon!
Boiled fish won't make Big Mom happy!
But when we actually fought,
I-I'm not a raccoon! I'm a reindeer!
it turned out like this against Jack's unit
which was just a part of Kaido's army!
--Which way?
--Straight!
I'm sensing Napoleon's signal!
What happened?!
This is your fault, Prometheus.
We went all the way back for you to eat the wildfire!
The paddles got broken by the heat!
Once I get the wedding cake,
I'll make both you and Soul King my own!
But we won't let it happen again!
We won't repeat the same failure!
Rero-rero! Does he wanna sink our ship?!
Who do you think hurt me that bad, Zeus?!
Let go of me! The cake is not here
and I'm not your plaything!
Did Oven-sama forget how
important this cake is?!
We have an ace up our sleeve too.
If we fight again,
we'll show them the true power of the Mink Tribe!
You were manipulated by the enemy woman!
Chopper!
It's okay...
It's gonna be okay...
Oh! If the ship sinks,
maybe my lie will go down with it!
We're special Homies who were
created from Mama's soul!
Sink...
This must be the ace he was talking about
at that time...
Sink!
If the Straw Hats lose the ship,
they'll be virtually wiped out.
If you betray her on account of your appetite again,
I won't forgive you!
The true power of...
...the Mink Tribe!
I know it's irritating.
I'm sorry... But those thunderclouds were good!
The ship...!
You tried to get up so I didn't let you.
The ship is gonna burn up!
You're acting strange...
Why do you suddenly start laughing and stuff, Pez?!
Do you really understand?!
You tried to throw a left punch
so I hit your left shoulder.
--We can't steer the ship!
--We're drifting away!
Who the hell are you?
You tried to throw a right punch
so I hit your right shoulder.
All of this shows you're just an idiot
who can't do anything but feel frustrated...
IN THE TERRITORY - THE SUNNY
The sea route is opening up!
We can break through the enemy line!
Oven-sama! Watch out!
That's how it is when your every move is
read by someone.
Carrot is amazing!
Chopper! We must protect this ship!
Stop!
The ship...!
But making you feel
frustrated is not enough...
The ship is gonna burn up!
Yeah!
D-Don't tell me that's...
Left kick or right kick...
No, they're coming back!
We have a problem, Daifuku-sama!
Thunder Charge!
Now, where is the wedding cake?
I'll hit you before you do anything.
It's a full moon tonight!
The Mink girl in the enemy group...
Swing Arm!
And I'll keep at it until
your heart bursts in half.
Let go of me!
...became Sulong!
Chopper!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
We have to put out the fire!
I'll handle them!
Water! Water!
Guys! Prepare for a close-quarters battle!
If I'm correct, Pedro was from Zou,
the Phantom Island...
Ocean Current...
Let's punch through!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
I guess she's from the same place...
...Shoulder Throw!
Every attack has an intent.
Oven-sama!
And a hint.
What's going on?
Carrot-san, wonderful!
Who is that?
She's gonna fall into the sea!
Carrot!
Oven-sama's old enemy?
Hey! The skeleton's running on the sea!
Don't worry.
Just stop him!
I must keep up with her, too!
Huh?! What the...
She just flew up from the surface!
Don't attack blindly, Luffy.
Cool!
Pound!
That's not all...
Y-You're quite tough...
Here she comes! Shoot her down!
What happened?!
Yes, sir!
--Don't lower your guard!
--She's a fighter of Zou! She must be exceptional!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Damn! Suddenly, the water...!
You fool!
Shoot! Shoot!
Are you trying to kill your stepson?!
Lullaby Parry!
I'll bring her down!
What?!
Oh, good!
--Wh-What the?!
--They fell asleep?!
Father! The water temperature is dropping!
The fire has been extinguished...
Mama!
Don't hold back! Take her out!
Retract the paddles!
Let's sail through this heated area quickly!
That can't be true, Mama!
Zeus got killed!
Jimbei-san!
Yes, sir!
Let's hurry up and get out of here!
Mama!
Yes, ma'am!
Get off of this ship, Big Mom!
We did it!
We gained some time!
Let's make some headway now!
If that's what you want...
Damn! Shoot!
Hurry up, Brook!
Give me the cake!
Okay!
My grandchild whose name I don't even know.
Grab this!
Fish-Man Karate Hidden Technique!
Are you happy?
I got you!
Let your father and mother care for you...
Vagabond Drill!
I'm back!
Yay! Welcome back!
I couldn't do that for my kids...
Brook, well done!
We tried to minimize the damage,
but it's quite bad.
Not yet? Not yet?
I'm passing out! I have to stop soon.
How many ships left?
Damn that little rabbit!
Oh, yeah.
Genie-uine Rage Split!
I recovered something.
Linlin, you gave birth!
Oh, Zeus!
He-teia saved me the work!
Hey!
I-Isn't it dangerous?!
We'll get her this time!
Yeah... Lola and Chiffon...
What's going on? Chopper!
I don't think he still has that energy...
They're twins.
Is she capable of that?!
Mama!
Twins?! I wanna hold them.
Oh, where am I?
What?!
Nice to see you again, Zeus.
Damn little rat!
You've already served your purpose.
Are you gonna stop our ships
by beating all soldiers in the fleet?!
Yay! He kicked her out!
Nice... to... see you... too...
Jimbei, you're amazing!
While you're at it, your ship will sink!
So it's no use fighting...
--Thank goodness!
--You did it!
Go away.
As I recall, you tried to...
What?
Guys!
Linlin?
If we allow them to wreck the ship anymore,
...strike me with lightning earlier.
What are you talking about?
The wheel?!
how will we face Luffy and the others?!
I'm their father! We're...
S-She broke the wheel!
I'm sorry...
Don't slow down!
If "sorry" were enough,
there would be no need for sheriffs or the Navy.
"Family"?
Don't overestimate yourself.
Oh, no! Where is this ship going?!
Once Perospero and the others
catch up to us, that'll be it!
Genie...!
That little rat!
--Yeah!
--Okay!
Carrot-san!
Count on us!
I bet you got it wrong...
Guillotine!
I'm sorry but...
I didn't mean to become your friend
from the start.
...Big Mom will stand up again in no time!
Linlin!
Go to hell, brat!
They're my children!
What?
I'm sorry, Pedro...
I guess this is it for me...
Let me ask you again.
Screw that little rabbit...
Please!
--How's Carrot?
--She's okay!
I wanna hold them at least once!
Do you wanna be my servant or...
Let's lose them at full speed!
I hope I helped Luffy and the others...
Let's go, Genie!
Linlin!
...do you wanna die?
...even a little bit.
What can I do for you, Master?!
Think about it carefully.
They're... my children...
Mama, are you okay?
That little rabbit... I'm gonna chop her up!
Yeah!
Mama! Mama!
That was 26 years ago...
That wasn't so bad, Jimbei!
I'll teach you...
...a thing or two!
Chiffon...
I'm so happy to see you even just once.
Shut up...
Here she comes!
Mama!
Baron Corpse!
Oh! I have an idea!
I'm glad that you're okay!
It seems like you're being chased,
Chase them, Prometheus!
To the best of my poor ability,
I put everyone on the other ship to sleep!
Yes, Mama!
but I'm glad that you look happy...
I'll slice it up!
You've already done enough.
Let's go back!
That's a good idea, Mama!
Daifuku-sama! You're putting us in danger!
Then, I'm sure I'll find it!
Every attack has an intent.
Don't attack blindly, Luffy.
Where are you aiming, Genie-san?
You saved me! Thank you!
What's the matter, Pez?
No, thank you!
The wedding cake!
You'll be fine!
We're leaving the hot sea soon!
How do you turn back?
I won't let you get away!
It extended this time!
If she swings it around...
Come this way!
I can change back by shading my eyes
from the moonlight.
The ship will be finished!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
At least she's not on the ship anymore!
Hats or shades...
Or simply by closing my eyes...
How aggravating!
Alright, Zeus-chan...
Genie-uine Rage Split!
Gum-Gum...
You like them, right?
Full moonlight raises our spirits!
...Twin Jet Pistol!
Stop, Mama!
Please stop! Daifuku-sama!
Those are...!
Shut up!
That little...
Black Ball!
You were really beautiful!
Why did I give birth to twins?!
That rat! She got another wheel!
All right!
It's delicious! It's
delicious! So delicious!!
You're probably a failure just like Lola!
How's that, Rayleigh?
What a cunning little rabbit!
Carrot... Are you alright?!
Don't get carried away.
You've only accomplished the first step.
Stop...!
Yeah...
Yum-yum!
Thank you!
You helped us out of a tight spot!
Kids who don't serve a purpose for me
aren't my family!
Next,
That's right! Now, help yourself!
She's jumping from one ship to another
and making them attack each other!
I'll be your opponent.
We were surrounded by the enemies
and our ship was almost sunk!
What should I do?!
Ouch!
That's really amazing...
Humph! The same trick doesn't work twice!
Yeah! That's awesome, right?!
She's like a little sister to me!
You have no time to rest!
If you can't dodge 100 times, you're not allowed to eat.
Well done! That's my little sister, Carrot!
Don't show your stupid face to me!
When the moon cycle and the weather
are in their favor,
What?!
Don't try to fool me, you temptress!
Sounds terrible? Then, focus!
I'm happy that I could help.
they become quite strong.
Can I stay in a room where I can't see the moon?
It's alright. Daddy and Mommy are right here.
Nami!
The moon cycle and the weather?
Mm-hm...
Of course! Leave it to us
and get some rest!
I've always been worried.
There you are!
They say if the Minks look at the clear moon
on a full moon night,
It's me.
Ouch!
Oh, please!
Did you have hard days?
Your opponent doesn't always
come from the front.
Oh, before you go,
could I see your panties...
their wilder nature that remains
deep in their memories wakes up.
Did you have lonely days?
Quit it!
It's easy to read animals' minds
since they show all of their emotions.
That's right... I don't have any flesh
so lightning doesn't affect me.
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there for you
on those days...
People call their white, ferocious look...
But humans are different...
We can defy expectations and cheat others.
Big Bro Peros!
Big Bro Daifuku can't fight anymore!
Oh?
...Sulong, the Moon Lion!
His fleet is drifting away!
I know it's late,
Do you wanna fight me, Soul King?!
How useless Daifuku is!
but let me say this.
Sulong?!
GROWWWL
Their actual transformation makes them lose themselves
and attack others at random
Ouch!
I'm sorry that I don't know when to give up!
Congratulations...
...on your marriage!
Mama... Are you really alright?!
so it's rather troublesome.
Chiffon!!
For others and themselves...
What?!
For themselves? What do you mean by that?
There they are...
I'm hungry, Rayleigh!
They're coming, Mama!
If the Minks can't control it,
it'll wear them out after just a single night of fighting
Will your enemy stop attacking you
because you're hungry?
No way!
Zeus! Prometheus!
We're on our way!
and they'll die.
How hard her skin is!
--We got out of it-rero!
--Let's keep this up and lose them!
Every attack has an intent.
What?!
Die?!
Ow!
And a hint.
It's a double-edged sword...
The fighting technique could cost them their life.
M-Mama?! She's like a different person...
The cake just barely made it through.
I remember that you couldn't even
make a scratch on me with your sword!
She moved like a feather...
Is that because she got too hungry?!
I smell something delicious.
Carrot-san...
It's so smart of her to take away their wheels!
Let's hurry up! We don't have time!
That's my dinner. Don't pay it any mind.
Lick. How many years has it been
since the last time I saw Mama move so swiftly?!
You're right... So could I at least...
We'll start decorating!
--Okay!
--Yeah!
...see your panties?!
Now, I'll go and back her up
before it becomes a close quarters battle!
ON THE SEA - THE SUNNY
Give me the wedding cake!
There you are!
--Back her up?
--You're gonna fall into the sea!
Big Mom is coming!
Give me the cake!
Huh?!
There!
Don't worry...
What?!
Napoleon!
Transform into a sword!
Yes, Mama!
Don't attack blindly, Luffy!
Oh, yeah! He can run on water!
Because he's light!
B-B... B-B-Big Mom?!
Rayleigh, that hurts!
I feel your anger!
Okay.
It's done!
No matter how you look at it,
she's too strong for us!
We'll leave securing the sea route ahead to them
and keep moving forward at full speed!
That's Haki, too!
Three-Pace Hum...
Sharpen your senses!
What should we do?!
...Soul...
Ouch!
--Mm-hm!
--Yeah!
Maybe we'd better run here...
Feel your enemy's presence!
What the hell is that?!
Stop!
...Notch Slash!
Mama...
I feel your anger!
If we stop, that'll be the end!
Let's just run!
Bavarois-sama!
We have their ship in our range!
Straw Hat!
Our only target was you, Zeus!
Every attack has an intent.
All right! Guys, shoot it up!
--Here we go!
--I'll go first!
Ow, ow, ow! Damn!
I let my guard down!
I'll get them!
And a hint.
Oh? Who's our enemy?
Stay with us, Zeus!
It's the Straw Hats!
What is that fool doing?
The enemy behind us caught up?!
Oh, yeah! But I don't see the straw hat!
Positive Charge Black Ball!
Okay! I'll fight, too!
Excuse me! Where did the Straw Hats go?!
Discharge and feel better, Zeus-chan!
Sharpen your senses.
They went that way!
What?!
You...!
--Let's go! It's that way!
--Thanks for your kindness!
No way!
Th-This is...
Big Mom!
Oh! I can't go any farther!
What did she turn into?!
What is it?!
--What were they?
--I don't know.
Where's my wedding cake?
Idiots!
Stand back, guys!
Get ready to even abandon the ship!
Why are all of those shells so useless?!
Unstoppable Donuts.
What's going on?!
Feel your enemy's...
As you know, when Mama isn't in her right mind,
they become undisciplined!
But...
...presence...
Oh... I'm so hungry.
Let me go!
No, me!
Don't...
Bavarois-sama! I can do it!
But nothing else can satisfy me.
...attack blindly...
CHARLOTTE BAVAROIS -
TWENTY-SIXTH SON OF CHARLOTTE
Unstoppable Mochi Blade Bullets!
Fall into despair, Straw Hat.
Damn...
Where is it?!
Haki becomes even stronger...
Mama hasn't slowed down...
We're at full speed, too!
...in the heat of actual battle.
Where is the wedding cake?!
Did he just...
The more you face tough enemies,
the stronger you'll be.
Why can't we catch up to them?!
--No! The Sunny...!
--Oh, no!
Well, they have Jimbei
who knows sea inside and out...
How can we kick out such a monster?!
Bavarois-sama! We just got a call!
Here they come!
Guys!
Every attack...
What's the matter, Carrot?!
There are a bunch of ships ahead!
...has an intent!
Unstoppable Donuts!
Power Mochi!
What?!
Oh, no! We're sandwiched!
No way!
Nine-headed Mochi!
Gum-Gum...
You're holding your own
against me for this long...
Wedding cake!
I admit you have quite a lot of prowess,
Straw Hat.
Every attack...
Haki becomes even stronger...
...has a hint!
I don't get it...
But no matter how hard you try,
you can't beat me.
...in the heat of actual battle.
The difference in power is obvious.
Take this!
Why do you wanna get up?
Unstoppable Donuts!
You know you can't win
so why do you keep fighting?
The more you face tough enemies,
Shut up!
the stronger you'll be.
Damn, it's the technique he used before!
Gear Three!
I almost... I almost can see his next move...
Don't make me repeat myself!
I can see it, Straw Hat...
We just got together again.
Don't get too wild.
I...
No, you stop making me repeat myself!
There is nothing you can do to defeat me.
Even if you just ran away,
since I'm your opponent,
Still not so frequently...
Your future is in darkness!
no one would've jeered at you.
Nine-headed Mochi!
Shut up!
Why did you come back?
I'll beat you at any cost!
What are you doing?
But he's beginning to see the future
in the same way I do.
My future is...
...mine to decide!
Surrounded by a grand fleet led by Daifuku and Smoothie,
the Sunny faces a dire predicament.
Luffy still can't see the future and
Coming under Mom's fierce attack,
Mom catches up to the Straw Hats
who are trying desperately to get away!
Using her Sulong power,
keeps ending up on the wrong end
of Katakuri's fierce attacks!
Carrot fights off the approaching ships
of Daifuku's fleet one after another.
Nami and the others desperately
fight against her
She destroys everything she can!
The Sunny catches fire!
There seems to be no chance
of his winning anymore.
but they are in danger of extermination!
Brook joins her and just when they think
they have repelled all the enemies,
However, just then,
inheriting Pedro's spirit,
Will Sanji who holds the key to
their fate complete the cake
But that is when Jimbei's Fish-Man Karate technique blasts off!
The battle between the Straw Hats and Mom now begins!
However, when Luffy gives an enraged war cry
Carrot transforms into her alternate form
which looks ferocious but beautiful under the moonlight!
and make it in time to save his friends from
the greatest crisis they've ever faced?!
Big Mom at the apex of her hunger shows
a stunning evolution!
and the memory of Rayleigh returns,
a miraculous turnaround begins!
The fateful moment approaches!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Break Through! The Straw Hat's Mighty Sea Battle!"
"Finally, They Clash! The Emperor of the Sea vs. the Straw Hats!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sulong! Carrot's Big Mystic Transformation!"
"Finally He Returns!
Sanji, the Man Who'll Stop the Emperor of the Sea!"
"Dark King's Direct Precepts!
The Battle Against Katakuri Turns Around!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!