Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
Yes! We've got Super Powers
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
Yes! We've got Super Powers
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
Always and forever...
eien ni...
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
Yes! We've got Super Powers
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Big Mom goes after the wedding cake
and chases Bege's ship.
Sanji headed to Cacao Island with Pudding.
Luffy continues fighting a hard battle
in the Mirroworld.
The Sunny was driven to the wall by Big Mom.
However...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy's gonna emerge in the middle of
fleets and armies.
Damn! I let my guard down!
And Nami and the others found out their destination,
Cacao Island, is surrounded by an enemy fleet...
It was fun, guys...
I'll save our captain at any cost!
Positive Charge Black Ball!
Now, give me the cake...
Katakuri found out that his little sister Flampe
was shooting Numbing Needles
Discharge and feel better, Zeus-chan!
At Cacao Island, Oven waits for Luffy
in front of the only mirror
I came up with just one idea
to get through Cacao Island.
Guys!
Sanji-kun and the others
baked the cake and returned!
and revealed his true face to her.
You...!
that he kept intact on the island.
What's so funny, you idiots?!
Meanwhile in the Mirroworld,
Wedding cake!
All the while, more forces are massing.
Luffy was fighting an all-out battle against Katakuri
when something unusual occurred.
Th-This is...
We still have an hour and a half.
What is it?!
Why did you lower your guard?!
When the time comes, they're finished!
Don't patronize fighting men!
Luffy, continuing a hard fight against Katakuri,
remembers what Rayleigh taught him.
In the Mirroworld, Luffy's Color of Observation
started working.
There are some strong people
who can see slightly ahead into the future.
"One Man's Determination!
Katakuri's Deadly Big Fight!"
If you wanna laugh at that silly shit...
Nami and the others on the Sunny
were able to shake the savage pursuers,
The future?!
you're gonna have to laugh at me, too!
What are you gonna do when you face them?
but Big Mom came after them again.
Did he see the future again?!
The two-year training won't
take you to that level...
Chase them, Prometheus!
So lame!
They're tough to beat.
Yes, Mama!
"Lurking in the Darkness!
An Assassin Targeting Luffy!"
Agreed! Disappointed!
It depends on what kind of guy he or she is.
In the Mirroworld,
It's even annoying to lay eyes on you two!
What? Your opponent's character?!
Does that matter to you?
a newly emerged enemy is secretly attacking Luffy
who is in a fight against Katakuri.
I'll shoot highly venomous needles
to strike through your hearts this time!
I've never thought of it like that.
It seems like it'll be over soon at last...
With his back against the wall,
Luffy remembers Rayleigh's precept.
Do it! Do it!
Of course, it does.
I won't forgive you!
Both of you, be ready for it this time!
That bloodied, disgusting monkey...
You're quite the character.
Every attack has an intent.
The people on the sidelines are annoying.
There's no time for you to rest.
And a hint.
Flampe-sama! They'll find us!
They can't stay on their feet anyway!
What?
B-But the way that monkey stands up...
Don't attack blindly, Luffy.
We'll get on to the next training.
Come on!
Take this.
Okay!
It's like a newborn fawn!
So shaky!
"Finally He Returns!
Sanji, the Man Who'll Stop the Emperor of the Sea!"
I'll teach you everything I can.
Come on, don't make us laugh!
There, look!
The Color of the Supreme King?!
He's so lame, all bloody and weak,
That monkey's using it, too?!
"A Fist of Divine Speed!
Another Gear Four Application Activated!"
A weakling like him...?!
Take this!
but he stands up again and again!
Gum-Gum...
I no longer think...
...that you're that much weaker than me.
...Hawk Stamp!
He stands up so shakily and gets taken down
Oh, really?! I'm glad!
then becomes shaky again!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
Thank you!
Is it...
But...
Flampe?
Yeah, that's right.
...I'll win!
...over now?!
Willow Mochi!
Still not so frequently...
Don't tell me...
But he's beginning to see the future
in the same way I do.
Yeah, I'll accept the challenge.
I'll wrap it up!
Big Bro is looking this way!
If you can withstand this...
"Wake Up!
The Color of Observation Able to Top the Strongest!"
He's so perfect and so cool!
Mochi Blade Bullet!
I already gave you my answer...
Unstoppable Donuts!
Oh, Katakuri-sama is coming this way!
Is he gonna use Nine-headed Mochi?!
Stop getting up. You have no chance!
What?!
Well done! You're really
a good girl, Flampe...
This fool's Color of Observation is
getting as good as mine!
There, there.
This is it...
Which one will he use?!
He'll praise me!
Yeah...
He still isn't able to see...
I'm not ready for it yet!
Gear Four!
...in the same way I do.
Bounce-Man!
It doesn't matter how close you get to my level...
I'll use both!
I see. It was you, Flampe.
Mochi Thrust!
Ho...
By coating yourself with the Haki of the Color of Arms,
you hardened your skin
What?
I'll keep aiming for the same goal!
What the...?
and the tension of your
rubber has increased, too.
You stopped him with your
favorite silent blowgun.
That's not all!
I have to get rid of him soon
or something unexpected could happen!
In the intense battle,
his concentration broke up for a moment.
I'll flatten you!
Mochi...
I thought it was odd...
Hmm, using the protean elasticity of rubber,
you enable yourself to fly...
...Thrust!
Mochi...
I can do more than just fly!
Gum-Gum...
But I still attacked him,
punched a hole in his stomach and left a deadly wound!
...Kong...
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
...Gun!
I can't believe that even the explosion of the chateau
was Straw Hat's plot...
I see...
Do you think I'd want
that sort of dishonorable victory?!
By unleashing the elasticity of
rubber that's been enhanced by
If he's that great a schemer...
Nthe Color of Arms at once, your
attack gets more powerful...
Look at that, Flampe-sama!
The fawn stands up again!
something unexpected could happen-soir!
Right!
Bounce-Man is aptly named...
You idiot! I won't let that happen!
Hey, don't make me laugh!
--His legs are shaky!
--Like a fawn!
But...
Did he see the future again?!
To all fleets of Totto Land!
...that's not enough.
Alright!
All available ships turn out to Cacao Island
immediately!
The easiest way to learn is through pain.
Now, Katakuri-sama's gonna win for sure!
Go to hell! Straw Hat!
And make that place the
Straw Hats' graveyard!
Of course!
Gum-Gum...
It's my perfect Big Bro's...
Don't let them get away!
...Elephant Gun!
...perfect victory!
ON THE SEA IN THE TERRITORY
- BEGE AND THE OTHERS
Flampe.
Did you do it?
What's wrong?
You can't get up after just one blow?
Don't get up.
We know what you guys are up to.
That's right, Big Bro!
Bege! What are you up to?!
I did it!
Damn!
Why's the cake on your ship?!
1 AM at Cacao Island...
I'm the most considerate and the cutest
among your sisters, right?!
There's no time for you to cry in pain.
Of course, you guys will be wiped out
before reaching Cacao Island.
We'll deal with Mama's Hunger Pangs attack...
The perfect one and
the world's greatest Big Bro's favorite is...
We'll let her eat the cake
and take care of her.
Gum-Gum...
What's waiting for you are my little brothers
and their fleets.
...me!
...Rhino Schneider!
Don't lie, you traitor!
What did you put in the cake?!
Pat my head and tell me I'm a good girl!
So it's the same even if you're able to
get out of here.
Where are you?!
Big Bro!
Nothing. Didn't you know
Pudding made the cake?
Chestnut Mochi!
What are you hitting?
What's so funny, you idiots?!
But...
Oh, yeah! Where's Pudding?!
I'll emerge from a mirror...
You don't have to worry about
Mama or Pudding at all.
Gum-Gum...
Unstoppable Donuts!
Ho!
Relax and focus on Straw Hat.
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Organ Gun!
--You son of a...
--Clank.
I guess you can see more now...
Why are you talking like
it's someone else's problem?
But...
Hey, Bege!
Grizzly Magnum!
Oh, shoot!
Let's pursue Bege, Bavarois!
ON THE SEA - BEGE'S SHIP
What's wrong?
Power Mochi!
What?!
I forgot to pipe roses of whipped cream...
Look at them! I'm one-hundred percent sure
that they're scheming to kill Mama.
Why can't I hit him?!
The Haki of the Color of Observation?!
...on the top of the cake!
What are you gonna do?
Maybe Pudding's already been killed.
What?!
Dammit!
What were you doing?!
I know there wasn't much time,
That fool!
But Big Bro Peros!
What about Straw Hat's ship?!
but you should've been more careful!
It'll sink at Cacao Island anyway! And...
RUSUKAINA ISLAND, TWO YEARS AGO
What do we do? The decoration of the cake is
complete already...
Katakuri-sama!
Gear Four!
Ring, ring, ring...
Focus, Luffy.
--Who do you think is going after Straw Hat's ship?
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
W-Why?!
We can't climb up there now...
Oh, yeah!
I'm so sorry!
--Answer!
--Ring, ring... Clank.
It's okay!
Are you on the trail of Straw Hat's ship,
Smoothie?!
I'll do it!
CHARLOTTE SMOOTHIE - 14TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
(ONE OF THE SWEET 3 GENERALS)
--Give me a pastry bag!
--Yes, sir!
Yeah, I am, Big Bro.
When men are fighting...
Sky Walk!
Are you starting to sense things?
I don't quite get it...
You guys keep tracking down Straw Hat's ship!
don't patronize them!
You've dodged 20 consecutive attacks now.
There is still a long way to go, Luffy.
Bavarois and I are going
to chase Bege and Mama!
Stay away! Don't touch me!
Ouch!
You got distracted by the noise.
Squeeze every last drop of life out of them!
Katakuri-sama!
--Wow!
--So beautiful!
Dammit!
I guess it'll still be a while until you dodge 100 times.
All right! It's done!
Torment them
and plunge them into an abyss of fear!
--Yes!
--Finally!
If you wanna laugh at that silly shit...
The greatest wedding cake ever,
made to stop Big Mom, is finished!
Roger that.
you're gonna have to laugh at me, too!
You better hurry or you'll die of hunger!
Clank.
Don't remind me of food...
He should've just let me handle it
from the start...
Snake-Man!
Alright, let's continue.
Big Bro Peros is getting distracted...
It smells so great...
I feel faint-rero.
Okay!
One! Two! Three!
There's nothing left to say!
CHARLOTTE CITRON - 15TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
It doesn't need to be poisoned!
Four! Five!
It would've been much easier
to stay at Cacao Island,
Snake-Man?
Seems like it's different from the one before.
eating chocolate and drinking tea...
I hope Big Mom will drop dead
from deliciousness!
Your Color of Observation
sure is something...
They're so impatient. Men are stupid.
So lame!
That's why I'll use...
CHARLOTTE CINNAMON - 16TH
DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Damn...
...something faster!
Great! We made it in time!
Who's there?
Why is he making such a simple attack
after all this time?
Pudding-sama!
Agreed! Disappointed!
Well, don't say that.
What?!
Come on, that's gross!
I got your blood on me!
Go away, you guys...
Hey, are you guys okay?!
What the hell?!
The chefs are collapsing one after another!
Always noble, calm, strong
and perfect in every way!
I don't want any food.
Everyone, prepare to fight!
What's going on?
They must've worked really hard!
Rayleigh says no food so I shouldn't eat.
Before they reach Cacao Island,
we'll sink Straw Hat's ship!
That's who we admire!
Why is it coming from the side?
But you stabbed your own stomach...
Yeah!
Pudding-chan! Chiffon-chan!
But thanks.
So lame!
You're not Big Bro Katakuri!
Mm-hm!
I couldn't do it without your help.
Thanks!
What was that?
Mm-hm!
Oh yeah. Guys,
Where did it come from?!
call up your friends
and help me with my training!
With this cake,
They know where we'll meet up with Luffy?!
How pathetic!
I can save my friends for sure!
I dodged it for sure!
What?!
You look like a pelican eel!
Then, that means Cacao Island is now...
Pelican eel!
Yeah, it's probably surrounded by fleets
ambushing us!
I see... That's how it works!
You don't know that!
Yeah, the cake is done,
Stop, Flampe-sama!
I can't keep a straight face!
Alright, bring it on!
Oh, no...
but your friends could be dead already!
Ho-hum... I'm so disappointed!
Chase him, Python!
They're considering us tough enemies
which they don't usually do.
Even if they're alive,
you don't know whether Mama'll like the cake or not!
It's no use!
Cacao Island will be our last
and biggest challenge here!
Whoa, there's a pelican eel!
It's pointless to transport this crappy cake,
Sanji...
It accelerates even after it expanded.
Stay away!
He's bizarrely strong like a monster!
We'll rescue Luffy no matter what
and get out of here!
...san!
Gum-Gum...
Run!
You didn't mean that, right, Pudding?!
...Jet...
Okay! I'm doing fine.
But we have no chance
if we face their fleets directly.
...Culverin!
Oh! No, I didn't mean it!
What am I saying?!
Hey! Say something!
In any case, I've got to go...
Look at yourself!
Wait!
Wedding cake!
It's far from over!
Rumble! Monster Point!
Are you hurt?
I will stop her!
What the hell is that?!
Are there only monsters on that ship?!
Napoleon! Extend yourself!
I can't believe you slip...
Yes, Mama!
I'm stronger and faster than you!
Take a picture! Let everyone know!
Chopper! Brook! Jimbei!
If we can hold out here, then...
The way that loser looks!
Catch up to him!
Oh, this is it.
Straw Hat!
Yeah, I know!
You don't have to say it.
Mm-hm!
My plan is going very well!
Until that moment comes,
endure no matter what!
E-Excuse me! I'm sorry, Katakuri-sama...
Since I can hide my presence so perfectly,
even Big Bro Katakuri hasn't noticed my support!
I'll bring the most wonderful cake ever
and stop Mom...
57! 58! 59!
I'll beat you up,
Katakuri-sama, look this way!
He really looks like a pelican eel.
and emerge from a mirror...
Buzz Cut Mochi!
Your reaction is getting quite quicker now...
The perfect Big Bro that everyone admired,
Charlotte Katakuri...
They're...
60!
...counting on me to do it!
The mochi is so sticky...
...is now dead!
Big Brother!
67!
From all members of your fan club
to all islands of Totto Land,
68! 69! 70!
...and I can't get it off!
I'll cut you in half!
71! 72! 73!
I'll spread it all over the country!
Cloven Rose, Palm!
All right! Keep it up!
How dare you spill your blood on me
and threaten me, everyone's favorite!
Cling!
The thing is, at that time, I...
Now, who is the perfect Big Bro?!
You're so uncool!
I feel dizzy!
Oh, I didn't know that, Flampe!
Chopper!
74! 75! 76!
I'm even ashamed to say
I'm your biological sister!
You're such a considerate, good girl!
Gust Sword!
Stop! What are you doing?!
That's my most-beloved sister.
Get me down!
Damn! I can't pull myself apart!
You're almost there, Luffy!
You ruined the Tea Party and I won't forgive you, either,
Straw Hat!
Soul Parade!
94! 95! 96!
This is it, Straw Hat!
Oh, I'm so commendable! So cute!
97! 98!
As I thought,
I have to be the king of the little sisters!
Cognac!
99!
Stop!
100...
On that last one,
I was completely hiding my presence...
Dammit!
Just a moment of carelessness...
How did you dodge that?
Chopper! You can't fight anymore!
I couldn't sense your presence...
and the fight will be decided!
I've got no choice! Come on, Big Mom!
But I kind of felt that you smiled.
I at least can dive into the sea
taking you with me!
It's even annoying to lay eyes on you two!
Okay, let's eat something.
I'm sure that you know that!
I'll shoot highly venomous needles
to strike through your hearts this time!
Yay...
You're full of spirit.
Straw Hat!
Then, can you still take
me with you like this?
Do it! Do it!
I won't forgive you!
Both of you, be ready for it this time!
The people on the sidelines are annoying.
They can't stay on their feet anyway!
Why did you lower your guard?!
No... way...
I have Cacao Island in sight!
Rabian, hurry up!
When it's that massive,
even the sea water won't work!
Count on me!
So that's the soul of the Emperor of the Sea!
Mochi Anemone!
The Color of the Supreme King?!
--Stop!
--What?
That monkey's using it, too?!
Now, try to get away as far as you can!
A weakling like him...?!
Are you okay?
If nothing is done,
we'll get burned up along with the Sunny!
Shut up!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
Oops!
Don't touch me like that!
It's annoying! Jeez!
It's a shame because we've made it this far!
And Sanji-kun will be here soon!
Anyway...
It was fun, guys...
Now, give me the cake...
Look at all those ships.
It's a massive fleet that
can destroy the island.
If we get caught, we'll be killed-rero!
What's this...
We have the cake.
Luffy...
Headed up by Big Bro Oven,
so many top officers of the family have gathered.
...delicious smell?!
They can't just attack us!
It seems like your Color of Observation has
the strength of sensing feelings from people and animals...
ON THE SEA - BEGE AND THE OTHERS
When Prometheus gets that
big, he can't move quickly.
If they notice me, we'll be in trouble.
You probably aren't even aware of this...
We'll reach Liqueur Island soon!
Until our captain returns,
I don't wanna create a ruckus on the island.
Huh? You sure?
If you can do that,
We have to land without being noticed
somehow.
It wasn't hard at all.
That's because we fixed the paddles in time.
I'm sure you'll be able to sense
your opponent's moves, too.
Good job, guys!
Thanks! That's kind of you!
Land at the dark spot as quick as you can.
Can you do it, Rabian?
Uh-huh.
There are some strong people
who can see slightly ahead into the future.
We'll dump the cake at Liqueur Island
and go on the great escape-rero!
That ship...
Yeah! I'll fly very low over the sea surface
under their radar.
Give it to me!
Yeah, that sounds good.
The future?!
Not yet.
What are you gonna do when you face them?
Guys!
Lie down on me.
What's wrong, Chiffon?!
Is this what you wanted, Chiffon?
--Yeah.
--Okay.
The two-year training won't take you to that level...
LIQUEUR ISLAND
NUTS ISLAND      FLUFFY ISLAND
CACAO ISLAND
Liqueur Island is too close!
Let's lure them to Fluffy Island!
The ship's here!
Yes! Thank you, Bege!
I'll make sure you won't get thrown off.
The cake is on it!
They're tough to beat.
Hey! Are you out of your mind?!
But we took on quite a headache!
--We're ready.
--Here we go!
If Mama who's now suffering from the Hunger Pangs attack
eats the cake at Liqueur Island and comes to her senses,
It depends on what kind of guy he or she is.
To be honest, getting away is more important
than the assassination now!
What? Your opponent's character?!
Does that matter to you?
Sanji-kun and the others
baked the cake and returned!
What are you saying, Bege?!
there is still enough time for her to
catch up to Nami and the others' ship!
Oh, Sanji!
I've never thought of it like that.
Sanji-san!
We decided to let Nami and the others
get away safely!
Mama!
So what?! We've already done enough!
Of course, it does.
We can't just give up halfway
because we wanna survive!
We're gonna die! Look!
You're quite the character.
Sanji-san...
It smells so sweet!
It sure does! Like when you can't escape...
That's how you pay your debt!
Mama is even hungrier now!
There it is, Black-Leg. It's your ship!
Mm-hm!
I think you'll have hard times...
Rero!
Are you okay?
Don't worry! Believe in the cake's flavor!
Damn Prometheus.
He became gigantic with Big Mom's soul!
Oh... Oh my...
Black-Leg is really an amazing cook!
If possible, I wanna keep holding his hand...
There's no time for you to rest.
And riding on top of the giant Prometheus,
I see Big Mom-rero.
Man! That's what I love about you, Chiffon!
What?
Sorry. You don't wanna be seen as
husband and wife.
We'll get on to the next training.
Come on!
Father! Beyond them, it's...
I wanna eat it!
Ma'am!
Okay!
...Perospero and...
...Bavarois...
Wedding cake!
Plus, Smoothie and the others!
That's right! Stop doing unnecessary things!
They're being chased by
quite a troublesome fleet!
I'll teach you everything I can.
I wanna eat it already!
Let's shake them off, guys!
Their ship's taken heavy damage, too!
Yeah!
We're gonna land!
Wedding cake...
Ready to aim, guys!
I wanna eat it! I really wanna eat it!
Yeah!
We're up against Big Mom!
Keep your guard up!
--Do you understand, Chiffon?
--Yes.
But if you have a chance,
fill her with bullets!
Let's go to Fluffy Island.
It's Smoothie-sama's ship!
You weren't listening!
Dammit!
Smoothie-sama!
Yeah!
I'll pay my debt to Straw Hat and the others
even if it costs me my life!
Citron-sama! Cinnamon-sama!
Rero!
That's what I decided!
So I'll go even by myself!
Nami-san! I'm here to save you!
Are you ready? Straw Hats...
Change course!
We'll head to Fluffy Island!
Anyway, they must've been chased by
Big Mom and Perospero for hours...
Another fleet is on our tail!
Burning Mochi!
What?!
It's Sweet General Smoothie's ship!
That's my wife!
I'm impressed that they survived!
They don't even have their captain to lead them!
Big Mom left and now it's a Sweet General!
I love you even more, Chiffon!
It's that woman who squeezes everything...
Nami-san!
Let's go, guys!
There's someone on the bow!
Don't you feel that strange energy?
Big Sis Smoothie!
Okay, Father!
That's not Haki...
Why are they coming on Bege's ship?
How long will it take to Cacao Island?
I'll see you then.
Be careful, Sanji.
If your punch contradicts
the future that I see...
A little more than three hours!
THE SUNNY
Yeah.
Hm? Someone's dancing on the bow!
D-Don't come close! Stay away! Sanji...
We'll arrive there at 1 AM
exactly as we promised.
Forget about it.
What really matters is the cake!
...san!
But we have no idea where or when
Luffy will emerge on Cacao Island
I'll leave the Sunny to you guys!
We're entering the crucial stage!
I'll just top it...
Lick!
They surely recreated the wedding cake
that we saw at the wedding!
Yeah!
Pudding-chan, take me to Cacao Island.
As a result, your future will be shattered
and we can't even warn him!
Don't tell me what to do!
You can't act like a bossy husband!
and you'll be finished, too...
If Mama likes the flavor,
her Hunger Pangs attack will stop! But...
I came up with just one idea
to get through Cacao Island.
That's all there is to it...
Sanji!
...San!
Oh? What was that?
...there's Bege!
I'm sure that the cake is poisoned!
You hear me, don't you?!
--Carrot!
--Are you okay now?!
Straw Hat!
I'm sorry, everyone... I was sleeping.
What should I do?! What should I do?!
No need to apologize!
You did great, Little Sis!
Oven-sama! Fleets are arriving one after another
to surround the island!
Thanks to the sweet smell,
she's broken off her onslaught...
Does that happen to Cat Viper and Dogstorm, too,
when they see the full moon, Little Sis?!
Do we really need that many?!
I don't think Katakuri-sama will
let Straw Hat get away...
I thought...
Uh-huh!
...I was gonna die...
Damn!
Both Master Cat Viper and Duke Dogstorm
can become way stronger than me!
I don't know! Ask Tamago and Montd'Or!
It hurts!
Should we destroy the cake?!
We need them all, Big Bro Oven!
This is so tough!
Yeah?!
Well, if we do that, there'll be
no stopping Mama's attacks and
Can you believe this?!
I'm hungry!
That big explosion of the chateau
was intentional, too!
the country will be ruined!
Oh, but if she dies eating the poisoned cake,
both the country
What?!
Even though he's a Rookie and they're a small group,
don't underestimate them!
and the pirate group are doomed!
If we let them escape, we'll suffer shame!
What should I do?!
Which should I choose?!
Watch and tell me which direction
their attacks come from!
Don't worry...
We'll get them right here for sure!
What are you saying?!
Got it!
I said everything on my mind!
No!
Hey, Black-Leg!
Listen! About three hours from now,
at 1 AM,
I feel better now!
You got yourself a deal!
We'll have this cake.
Fall down, Katakuri!
the separated members of the Straw Hats
will meet up here at Cacao Island.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Culverin!
As you wish, we won't do anything
until Mama eats it and gets filled up...
Punch Mochi!
Think of it as your last chance
to kill them all!
I need more and more liquid.
But...
Yes, sir!
...I'm free to do anything after that, right?
If by any chance Straw Hat appears,
he'll come out of a mirror on the island!
You hurt your own men!
You're going too far!
Do as you like. Our mission was to
calm Big Mom down with the cake.
The Straw Hats! I won't let them get away!
Everyone, go home
and break all the mirrors in the town!
What's that?!
Is she a Giant?
We can stop her!
You're an enemy who's aiming to kill Mama!
Didn't you hear me?! Just do it!
Could I see your panties...
We're ready, Sanji!
Please! Even precious ones?!
Stop it! You perverted skeleton!
I, as the head of the Sweet 3 Generals...
...San!
Coming.
He's a power-user. If you have a mirror
that you don't wanna break, sink it into the sea.
Hurry up, you fool, if you don't wanna die!
It's coming again!
Dodge to the right!
No.
Pudding!
You can salvage later! Anyway...
I just wanna...
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Take care of yourself!
This is to be the only unbroken
mirror on this island!
Straw Hat!
Again, to the right!
Go, Python!
Are you happy now?
Burning Mochi!
What is it?
Yes, very...
Jimbei, to the left!
When you have someone who
loves you like you love them,
No exceptions!
I can still fight!
the world will never be the same.
Damn Jimbei!
Don't let your happiness go.
If anyone allows Straw Hat to
get out of their mirror,
Me, too!
Yeah, don't you either.
I'll execute their whole family!
Me?
Hurry up!
Stay alert! I'm depending on your directions!
Y-Yes, sir!
Count on us!
Don't think you can get away, Straw Hat!
Goodbye, Big Sis...
Don't worry! I'll take responsibility!
Oh, she became even bigger!
To you, this is no exit...
Rabian! Super fast!
Thank you, Pudding-chan.
You've been helping me this whole time.
It's the entrance to hell!
Go fast so Big Bro Peros
and Big Bro Bavarois won't notice!
Cut it out!
Smoothie! This ship can't hold up!
Move over!
Move over to the edge, Sanji...
Okay!
This will sink them!
Damn!
...san!
We'll be seen as husband and wife!
It's coming!
By who?
My wedding cake!
What's next?
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
There it is!
A-Anyway...
That's so big!
Is this really gonna work out?!
It'll sink us!
I finally found it! Let's go!
Interesting.
Luffy's gonna emerge in the middle of
fleets and armies.
Dodge to the right, Jimbei!
Bring it on!
Here I go!
Yes!
Mama!
I'll save our captain at any cost!
Wedding cake!
What are you doing?
Gum-Gum...
Why did you let up?!
--There she comes! Starboard!
--Yes, sir!
...Black Mamba!
Go southwest at full speed!
We'll head toward Liqueur Island!
How goes it with the mirrors?
I was just starting to think highly of you...
As you ordered, we made them get rid of them all.
Your brothers and sisters are
arriving one after another.
Lick?
but you disappointed me!
Perospero-sama!
The ship with the cake changed its course!
Everyone, hang on tight!
Okay.
11:36 PM
Tsk! They're so persistent!
Why?!
I can't believe this many members of the family
have assembled here at Cacao Island.
Mama is being lured by the cake
and started chasing Bege's ship!
How cautious are they about Straw Hat Luffy?!
Straw Hat's ship and Bege's ship...
By splitting up,
they're trying to divide us...
Lick!
How many enemies? Tens of thousands?
I think they're less than 10.
Hey! I'm back!
What?! I'm gonna take a nap.
BROWNIE - 32ND SON OF CHARLOTTE
--Sanji-kun!
--Sanji-san! Pudding-san!
Wake me up when something happens!
Yes, sir!
Sanji!
The Worst Generation, huh?
We were hanging by a hair!
I thought we were done for! Thank you!
SNACK - 25TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
(FORMERLY ONE OF THE SWEET 4 GENERAL)
BOUNTY: 600 MILLION BERRIES
I'm sorry...
I can't let them have their way anymore.
I'm glad that you're okay!
I didn't notice even one of her needles...
I was foolish, too.
With the pride of the former Sweet General...
Fairness isn't a given in a pirate fight...
I think I saw it!
Thump!
JOCONDE - 27TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Summoning all forces to fight such a small group...
I love you, too! Nami-san!
Did I imagine it?
...brings shame to the Emperor of the Sea, Big Mom.
It's my fault because I couldn't dodge them!
Imagining is fine.
By the way, Sanji-san,
why were you on Bege's ship?
Or is Straw Hat Luffy that formidable?
The Color of Observation
is an extension of imagination!
One more attack and it'll be over, Straw Hat!
It's a long story...
Where is his ship headed?
Are you serious, Big Bro Oven?!
We don't know what Mom will do
after she eats the cake...
36-40TH SONS AND 30-34TH DAUGHTERS OF CHARLOTTE
DECUPLETS
It's like a festival!
You have to be able to
sense it instinctively!
Looks like fun!
I'm gonna take you down
at any cost, Katakuri!
So they're taking the cake
to the nearest island.
Instinctively?!
Shut up! I know you have nothing to do!
Just go along!
What? So they took it upon
themselves to be bait?!
Damn Straw Hat... He humiliated us at the Tea Party.
CHIBOUST - 29TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
Why is he doing that?!
I'll get revenge by killing him!
He hasn't given up on killing her.
That one again!
I'll put you out of your misery!
RAISIN - 33RD SON OF CHARLOTTE
When we were deployed as the enraged army,
I see. That sounds like Bege.
No need to!
we should've killed him.
This ship's safety is the only thing
that matters to me.
Then, we wouldn't have bitten the dust at the Tea Party.
YUEN - 35TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
If he lures Mom, I can't ask for more...
Usually we can easily discern an invader's movements...
MYUKURU - 25TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Anyway...
SHAKKY'S RIP-OFF BAR
It's taken a lot of damage...
It's so inconvenient without the Territory Slugs!
I'm sorry. I should've done better...
Now I remember.
But our preparations are thorough
and we still have an hour and a half.
What are you talking about?!
If it weren't for you, we probably would have...
He stands up again!
When the time comes, they're finished!
Look how his feet shake.
Let's talk later.
I'm really glad that you're okay.
I wonder if Monkey-chan's doing alright.
I no longer think...
All right! Another shot!
...that you're that much weaker than me.
It's approximately an hour before the appointed time of
By the way,
where are Pedro and Carrot-chan?
12:05 AM
I don't know...
This time, I'll give you a Numbing Needle
that's 10-times more effective than the last one!
Oh, really?! I'm glad!
the Straw Hats' rendezvous at Cacao Island.
You always used to say that.
Thank you!
"Only those who are living in the present
can make a new epoch."
Um...
But...
Oh, th-they're sleeping inside!
They both got exhausted from fighting...
...I'll win!
Did I say that?
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
Big Bro Peros, what should we do?!
A monkey who doesn't know when to give up.
Is it...
Straw Hat's ship or Mama,
which one should we chase?!
Yeah, that's right.
Drop dead already!
Don't play dumb...
...over now?!
We won't let the Straw Hats get away,
but Mama's side has Bege.
He's the mastermind who fooled us, betrayed us,
and tried to kill Mama!
Numbing Needle!
Rise above it, Luffy...
We can't let him get away...
Yeah, I'll accept the challenge.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
This is... Bege...
Gum-Gum...
I'll wrap it up!
Bege!
Buzz Cut Mochi!
What? He dodged my silent needle?!
If you can withstand this...
...King Cobra!
I already gave you my answer...
Rainfall Mochi!
You can't get away now!
But he fell!
Go!
This is it...
Yeah...
It seems like it'll be over soon at last...
Gear Four!
That bloodied, disgusting monkey...
Take this.
Snake-Man!
After spending all their strength and collapsing,
both Luffy and Katakuri can't even move an inch!
Luffy desperately tries to keep up with Katakuri
but he still can't strike back.
Snake-Man, a new Gear Four form, is finally unveiled!
When Katakuri finds out what is up with Luffy,
he stabs his stomach with the Mole
The tables are turning against him
and he is under attack by Katakuri!
The Straw Hats hold out hope for Luffy's victory
and wait for him at Cacao Island!
Finally exercising his Color of Observation,
Luffy aims to bring down Katakuri.
Luffy who has evolved stunningly and Katakuri,
and reveal his secret which he has been hiding
for some time.
the formidable man
who sees into the future, get into the last deadly struggle!
As the appointed time approaches,
will it be Luffy or Katakuri
Stake everything on this duel!
Will he be able to awaken his true ability
and land a full-power blow?!
However, an assassin, Flampe,
sneaks up to attack him!
Against the determined Katakuri,
will Luffy be able to stand up?
It's going to be a battle that no one has ever seen before!
who stands up and becomes the true winner?!
The unanticipated enemy corners Luffy again
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Wake Up! The Color of Observation Able to Top the Strongest!"
"One Man's Determination! Katakuri's Deadly Big Fight!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
and Katakuri's formidable
weapon, Mole, strikes upon him!
"A Fist of Divine Speed! Another Gear Four Application Activated!"
"Finally, It's Over! The Climax of
the Intense Fight against Katakuri!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Lurking in the Darkness!
An Assassin Targeting Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!