Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Damn! I let my guard down!
Positive Charge Black Ball!
Discharge and feel better, Zeus-chan!
You...!
Th-This is...
What is it?!
Nami and the others on the Sunny
were able to shake the savage pursuers,
but Big Mom came after them again.
Chase them, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
In the Mirroworld,
a newly emerged enemy is secretly attacking Luffy
who is in a fight against Katakuri.
With his back against the wall,
Luffy remembers Rayleigh's precept.
Every attack has an intent.
And a hint.
Don't attack blindly, Luffy.
"Finally He Returns!
Sanji, the Man Who'll Stop the Emperor of the Sea!"
Take this!
Still not so frequently...
But he's beginning to see the future
in the same way I do.
Mochi Blade Bullet!
Unstoppable Donuts!
Is he gonna use Nine-headed Mochi?!
Which one will he use?!
He still isn't able to see...
...in the same way I do.
I'll use both!
Mochi Thrust!
Did he see the future again?!
Alright!
Don't get up.
We know what you guys are up to.
1 AM at Cacao Island...
Of course, you guys will be wiped out
before reaching Cacao Island.
What's waiting for you are my little brothers
and their fleets.
So it's the same even if you're able to
get out of here.
But...
I'll emerge from a mirror...
Why are you talking like
it's someone else's problem?
Oh, shoot!
ON THE SEA - BEGE'S SHIP
What's wrong?
I forgot to pipe roses of whipped cream...
...on the top of the cake!
What?!
What were you doing?!
I know there wasn't much time,
but you should've been more careful!
What do we do? The decoration of the cake is
complete already...
We can't climb up there now...
I'm so sorry!
It's okay!
I'll do it!
--Give me a pastry bag!
--Yes, sir!
Sky Walk!
--Wow!
--So beautiful!
All right! It's done!
--Yes!
--Finally!
The greatest wedding cake ever,
made to stop Big Mom, is finished!
It smells so great...
I feel faint-rero.
There's nothing left to say!
It doesn't need to be poisoned!
I hope Big Mom will drop dead
from deliciousness!
Great! We made it in time!
Pudding-sama!
What?!
Hey, are you guys okay?!
The chefs are collapsing one after another!
They must've worked really hard!
Pudding-chan! Chiffon-chan!
I couldn't do it without your help.
Thanks!
With this cake,
I can save my friends for sure!
You don't know that!
Yeah, the cake is done,
but your friends could be dead already!
Even if they're alive,
you don't know whether Mama'll like the cake or not!
It's pointless to transport this crappy cake,
Sanji...
...san!
You didn't mean that, right, Pudding?!
Oh! No, I didn't mean it!
What am I saying?!
In any case, I've got to go...
Wait!
Wedding cake!
Rumble! Monster Point!
I will stop her!
What the hell is that?!
Are there only monsters on that ship?!
Napoleon! Extend yourself!
Yes, Mama!
Chopper! Brook! Jimbei!
If we can hold out here, then...
Yeah, I know!
You don't have to say it.
Mm-hm!
Until that moment comes,
endure no matter what!
I'll bring the most wonderful cake ever
and stop Mom...
I'll beat you up,
and emerge from a mirror...
They're...
...counting on me to do it!
I'll cut you in half!
Cloven Rose, Palm!
Chopper!
Gust Sword!
Soul Parade!
Cognac!
Stop!
Chopper! You can't fight anymore!
I've got no choice! Come on, Big Mom!
I at least can dive into the sea
taking you with me!
You're full of spirit.
Then, can you still take
me with you like this?
No... way...
When it's that massive,
even the sea water won't work!
So that's the soul of the Emperor of the Sea!
Now, try to get away as far as you can!
If nothing is done,
we'll get burned up along with the Sunny!
It's a shame because we've made it this far!
And Sanji-kun will be here soon!
It was fun, guys...
Now, give me the cake...
What's this...
...delicious smell?!
That ship...
Guys!
The ship's here!
The cake is on it!
Sanji-kun and the others
baked the cake and returned!
Oh, Sanji!
Sanji-san!
Mama!
It smells so sweet!
There it is, Black-Leg. It's your ship!
Damn Prometheus.
He became gigantic with Big Mom's soul!
And riding on top of the giant Prometheus,
I see Big Mom-rero.
Father! Beyond them, it's...
...Perospero and...
...Bavarois...
Plus, Smoothie and the others!
They're being chased by
quite a troublesome fleet!
Their ship's taken heavy damage, too!
Ready to aim, guys!
Yeah!
We're up against Big Mom!
Keep your guard up!
But if you have a chance,
fill her with bullets!
Yeah!
Rero!
Nami-san! I'm here to save you!
Anyway, they must've been chased by
Big Mom and Perospero for hours...
I'm impressed that they survived!
They don't even have their captain to lead them!
Nami-san!
There's someone on the bow!
Don't you feel that strange energy?
That's not Haki...
Why are they coming on Bege's ship?
Hm? Someone's dancing on the bow!
Forget about it.
What really matters is the cake!
Lick!
They surely recreated the wedding cake
that we saw at the wedding!
If Mama likes the flavor,
her Hunger Pangs attack will stop! But...
...there's Bege!
I'm sure that the cake is poisoned!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Thanks to the sweet smell,
she's broken off her onslaught...
I thought...
...I was gonna die...
Should we destroy the cake?!
Well, if we do that, there'll be
no stopping Mama's attacks and
the country will be ruined!
Oh, but if she dies eating the poisoned cake,
both the country
and the pirate group are doomed!
What should I do?!
Which should I choose?!
Hey, Black-Leg!
You got yourself a deal!
We'll have this cake.
As you wish, we won't do anything
until Mama eats it and gets filled up...
But...
...I'm free to do anything after that, right?
Do as you like. Our mission was to
calm Big Mom down with the cake.
We can stop her!
We're ready, Sanji!
...San!
Coming.
Hurry up, you fool, if you don't wanna die!
Pudding!
Take care of yourself!
Are you happy now?
Yes, very...
When you have someone who
loves you like you love them,
the world will never be the same.
Don't let your happiness go.
Yeah, don't you either.
Me?
Goodbye, Big Sis...
Rabian! Super fast!
Go fast so Big Bro Peros
and Big Bro Bavarois won't notice!
Okay!
My wedding cake!
There it is!
I finally found it! Let's go!
Yes!
Mama!
Wedding cake!
--There she comes! Starboard!
--Yes, sir!
Go southwest at full speed!
We'll head toward Liqueur Island!
Lick?
Perospero-sama!
The ship with the cake changed its course!
Why?!
Mama is being lured by the cake
and started chasing Bege's ship!
Straw Hat's ship and Bege's ship...
By splitting up,
they're trying to divide us...
Lick!
Hey! I'm back!
--Sanji-kun!
--Sanji-san! Pudding-san!
Sanji!
We were hanging by a hair!
I thought we were done for! Thank you!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Thump!
I love you, too! Nami-san!
By the way, Sanji-san,
why were you on Bege's ship?
It's a long story...
Where is his ship headed?
We don't know what Mom will do
after she eats the cake...
So they're taking the cake
to the nearest island.
What? So they took it upon
themselves to be bait?!
Why is he doing that?!
He hasn't given up on killing her.
I see. That sounds like Bege.
This ship's safety is the only thing
that matters to me.
If he lures Mom, I can't ask for more...
Anyway...
It's taken a lot of damage...
I'm sorry. I should've done better...
What are you talking about?!
If it weren't for you, we probably would have...
Let's talk later.
I'm really glad that you're okay.
By the way,
where are Pedro and Carrot-chan?
Um...
Oh, th-they're sleeping inside!
They both got exhausted from fighting...
Big Bro Peros, what should we do?!
Straw Hat's ship or Mama,
which one should we chase?!
We won't let the Straw Hats get away,
but Mama's side has Bege.
He's the mastermind who fooled us, betrayed us,
and tried to kill Mama!
We can't let him get away...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
This is... Bege...
Bege!
Rainfall Mochi!
It seems like it'll be over soon at last...
That bloodied, disgusting monkey...
Take this.
Finally exercising his Color of Observation,
Luffy aims to bring down Katakuri.
However, an assassin, Flampe,
sneaks up to attack him!
The unanticipated enemy corners Luffy again
and Katakuri's formidable
weapon, Mole, strikes upon him!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Lurking in the Darkness!
An Assassin Targeting Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!