Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Big Mom goes after the wedding cake
and chases Bege's ship.
And Nami and the others found out their destination,
Cacao Island, is surrounded by an enemy fleet...
I came up with just one idea
to get through Cacao Island.
Meanwhile in the Mirroworld,
Luffy was fighting an all-out battle against Katakuri
when something unusual occurred.
Why did you lower your guard?!
"One Man's Determination!
Katakuri's Deadly Big Fight!"
Flampe-sama! They'll find us!
B-But the way that monkey stands up...
It's like a newborn fawn!
So shaky!
Come on, don't make us laugh!
There, look!
He's so lame, all bloody and weak,
but he stands up again and again!
He stands up so shakily and gets taken down
then becomes shaky again!
Flampe?
Don't tell me...
Big Bro is looking this way!
He's so perfect and so cool!
Oh, Katakuri-sama is coming this way!
What?!
Well done! You're really
a good girl, Flampe...
There, there.
He'll praise me!
I'm not ready for it yet!
I see. It was you, Flampe.
You stopped him with your
favorite silent blowgun.
In the intense battle,
his concentration broke up for a moment.
I thought it was odd...
Mochi...
...Thrust!
But I still attacked him,
punched a hole in his stomach and left a deadly wound!
Do you think I'd want
that sort of dishonorable victory?!
Look at that, Flampe-sama!
The fawn stands up again!
Hey, don't make me laugh!
--His legs are shaky!
--Like a fawn!
Now, Katakuri-sama's gonna win for sure!
Of course!
It's my perfect Big Bro's...
...perfect victory!
Flampe.
Did you do it?
That's right, Big Bro!
I did it!
I'm the most considerate and the cutest
among your sisters, right?!
The perfect one and
the world's greatest Big Bro's favorite is...
...me!
Pat my head and tell me I'm a good girl!
Big Bro!
What's so funny, you idiots?!
That fool!
Katakuri-sama!
W-Why?!
When men are fighting...
don't patronize them!
Stay away! Don't touch me!
Ouch!
Katakuri-sama!
If you wanna laugh at that silly shit...
you're gonna have to laugh at me, too!
So lame!
Agreed! Disappointed!
Come on, that's gross!
I got your blood on me!
What the hell?!
Always noble, calm, strong
and perfect in every way!
That's who we admire!
But you stabbed your own stomach...
So lame!
You're not Big Bro Katakuri!
How pathetic!
You look like a pelican eel!
Pelican eel!
Stop, Flampe-sama!
I can't keep a straight face!
Ho-hum... I'm so disappointed!
Whoa, there's a pelican eel!
Stay away!
He's bizarrely strong like a monster!
Run!
Hey! Say something!
Take a picture! Let everyone know!
The way that loser looks!
E-Excuse me! I'm sorry, Katakuri-sama...
Katakuri-sama, look this way!
He really looks like a pelican eel.
The perfect Big Bro that everyone admired,
Charlotte Katakuri...
...is now dead!
From all members of your fan club
to all islands of Totto Land,
I'll spread it all over the country!
How dare you spill your blood on me
and threaten me, everyone's favorite!
Now, who is the perfect Big Bro?!
You're so uncool!
I'm even ashamed to say
I'm your biological sister!
You ruined the Tea Party and I won't forgive you, either,
Straw Hat!
It's even annoying to lay eyes on you two!
I'll shoot highly venomous needles
to strike through your hearts this time!
Do it! Do it!
I won't forgive you!
Both of you, be ready for it this time!
The people on the sidelines are annoying.
They can't stay on their feet anyway!
The Color of the Supreme King?!
That monkey's using it, too?!
A weakling like him...?!
If we get caught, we'll be killed-rero!
We have the cake.
They can't just attack us!
ON THE SEA - BEGE AND THE OTHERS
When Prometheus gets that
big, he can't move quickly.
We'll reach Liqueur Island soon!
It wasn't hard at all.
That's because we fixed the paddles in time.
Good job, guys!
Thanks! That's kind of you!
We'll dump the cake at Liqueur Island
and go on the great escape-rero!
Yeah, that sounds good.
Not yet.
What's wrong, Chiffon?!
LIQUEUR ISLAND
NUTS ISLAND      FLUFFY ISLAND
CACAO ISLAND
Liqueur Island is too close!
Let's lure them to Fluffy Island!
Hey! Are you out of your mind?!
If Mama who's now suffering from the Hunger Pangs attack
eats the cake at Liqueur Island and comes to her senses,
there is still enough time for her to
catch up to Nami and the others' ship!
So what?! We've already done enough!
We're gonna die! Look!
Mama is even hungrier now!
I wanna eat it!
I wanna eat it already!
Wedding cake...
I wanna eat it! I really wanna eat it!
--Do you understand, Chiffon?
--Yes.
Let's go to Fluffy Island.
You weren't listening!
I'll pay my debt to Straw Hat and the others
even if it costs me my life!
That's what I decided!
So I'll go even by myself!
Change course!
We'll head to Fluffy Island!
What?!
That's my wife!
I love you even more, Chiffon!
Let's go, guys!
Okay, Father!
I'll see you then.
Be careful, Sanji.
THE SUNNY
Yeah.
D-Don't come close! Stay away! Sanji...
...san!
I'll leave the Sunny to you guys!
We're entering the crucial stage!
Yeah!
Pudding-chan, take me to Cacao Island.
Don't tell me what to do!
You can't act like a bossy husband!
Sanji!
...San!
Oh? What was that?
--Carrot!
--Are you okay now?!
I'm sorry, everyone... I was sleeping.
No need to apologize!
You did great, Little Sis!
Does that happen to Cat Viper and Dogstorm, too,
when they see the full moon, Little Sis?!
Uh-huh!
Both Master Cat Viper and Duke Dogstorm
can become way stronger than me!
Yeah?!
Watch and tell me which direction
their attacks come from!
Got it!
No!
I need more and more liquid.
You hurt your own men!
You're going too far!
The Straw Hats! I won't let them get away!
What's that?!
Is she a Giant?
Could I see your panties...
Stop it! You perverted skeleton!
It's coming again!
Dodge to the right!
Again, to the right!
Jimbei, to the left!
Damn Jimbei!
Stay alert! I'm depending on your directions!
Count on us!
Don't worry! I'll take responsibility!
Oh, she became even bigger!
Smoothie! This ship can't hold up!
This will sink them!
It's coming!
That's so big!
It'll sink us!
Dodge to the right, Jimbei!
Everyone, hang on tight!
Tsk! They're so persistent!
I'm sorry...
I didn't notice even one of her needles...
I was foolish, too.
Fairness isn't a given in a pirate fight...
It's my fault because I couldn't dodge them!
I no longer think...
...that you're that much weaker than me.
Oh, really?! I'm glad!
Thank you!
But...
...I'll win!
Luffy desperately tries to keep up with Katakuri
but he still can't strike back.
The tables are turning against him
and he is under attack by Katakuri!
Will he be able to awaken his true ability
and land a full-power blow?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Wake Up! The Color of Observation Able to Top the Strongest!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!