Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy continues fighting a hard battle
in the Mirroworld.
Katakuri found out that his little sister Flampe
was shooting Numbing Needles
and revealed his true face to her.
What's so funny, you idiots?!
Don't patronize fighting men!
If you wanna laugh at that silly shit...
you're gonna have to laugh at me, too!
So lame!
Agreed! Disappointed!
It's even annoying to lay eyes on you two!
I'll shoot highly venomous needles
to strike through your hearts this time!
Do it! Do it!
I won't forgive you!
Both of you, be ready for it this time!
The people on the sidelines are annoying.
They can't stay on their feet anyway!
The Color of the Supreme King?!
That monkey's using it, too?!
A weakling like him...?!
I no longer think...
...that you're that much weaker than me.
Oh, really?! I'm glad!
Thank you!
But...
...I'll win!
"Wake Up!
The Color of Observation Able to Top the Strongest!"
It doesn't matter how close you get to my level...
I'll keep aiming for the same goal!
I'll flatten you!
Go to hell! Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Chestnut Mochi!
Gum-Gum...
Unstoppable Donuts!
I guess you can see more now...
But...
Grizzly Magnum!
Power Mochi!
RUSUKAINA ISLAND, TWO YEARS AGO
Focus, Luffy.
Are you starting to sense things?
I don't quite get it...
You've dodged 20 consecutive attacks now.
There is still a long way to go, Luffy.
You got distracted by the noise.
Dammit!
I guess it'll still be a while until you dodge 100 times.
You better hurry or you'll die of hunger!
Don't remind me of food...
Alright, let's continue.
Okay!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five!
Damn...
Who's there?
Go away, you guys...
I don't want any food.
Rayleigh says no food so I shouldn't eat.
But thanks.
Oh yeah. Guys,
call up your friends
and help me with my training!
Alright, bring it on!
Okay! I'm doing fine.
Are you hurt?
Oh, this is it.
57! 58! 59!
Your reaction is getting quite quicker now...
60!
67!
68! 69! 70!
71! 72! 73!
All right! Keep it up!
74! 75! 76!
You're almost there, Luffy!
94! 95! 96!
97! 98!
99!
100...
On that last one,
I was completely hiding my presence...
How did you dodge that?
I couldn't sense your presence...
But I kind of felt that you smiled.
Okay, let's eat something.
Yay...
Luffy...
It seems like your Color of Observation has
the strength of sensing feelings from people and animals...
You probably aren't even aware of this...
Huh? You sure?
If you can do that,
I'm sure you'll be able to sense
your opponent's moves, too.
Uh-huh.
There are some strong people
who can see slightly ahead into the future.
The future?!
What are you gonna do when you face them?
The two-year training won't take you to that level...
They're tough to beat.
It depends on what kind of guy he or she is.
What? Your opponent's character?!
Does that matter to you?
I've never thought of it like that.
Of course, it does.
You're quite the character.
It sure does! Like when you can't escape...
I think you'll have hard times...
There's no time for you to rest.
What?
We'll get on to the next training.
Come on!
Okay!
I'll teach you everything I can.
Burning Mochi!
You're an enemy who's aiming to kill Mama!
I, as the head of the Sweet 3 Generals...
No.
I just wanna...
Straw Hat!
What is it?
I can still fight!
Me, too!
Thank you, Pudding-chan.
You've been helping me this whole time.
Cut it out!
Move over!
Move over to the edge, Sanji...
...san!
We'll be seen as husband and wife!
By who?
A-Anyway...
Is this really gonna work out?!
Luffy's gonna emerge in the middle of
fleets and armies.
I'll save our captain at any cost!
How goes it with the mirrors?
As you ordered, we made them get rid of them all.
Your brothers and sisters are
arriving one after another.
Okay.
11:36 PM
I can't believe this many members of the family
have assembled here at Cacao Island.
How cautious are they about Straw Hat Luffy?!
How many enemies? Tens of thousands?
I think they're less than 10.
What?! I'm gonna take a nap.
BROWNIE - 32ND SON OF CHARLOTTE
Wake me up when something happens!
Yes, sir!
The Worst Generation, huh?
SNACK - 25TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
(FORMERLY ONE OF THE SWEET 4 GENERAL)
BOUNTY: 600 MILLION BERRIES
I can't let them have their way anymore.
With the pride of the former Sweet General...
JOCONDE - 27TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
Summoning all forces to fight such a small group...
...brings shame to the Emperor of the Sea, Big Mom.
Or is Straw Hat Luffy that formidable?
Are you serious, Big Bro Oven?!
36-40TH SONS AND 30-34TH DAUGHTERS OF CHARLOTTE
DECUPLETS
It's like a festival!
Looks like fun!
Shut up! I know you have nothing to do!
Just go along!
Damn Straw Hat... He humiliated us at the Tea Party.
CHIBOUST - 29TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
I'll get revenge by killing him!
RAISIN - 33RD SON OF CHARLOTTE
When we were deployed as the enraged army,
we should've killed him.
Then, we wouldn't have bitten the dust at the Tea Party.
YUEN - 35TH SON OF CHARLOTTE
Usually we can easily discern an invader's movements...
MYUKURU - 25TH DAUGHTER OF CHARLOTTE
It's so inconvenient without the Territory Slugs!
But our preparations are thorough
and we still have an hour and a half.
When the time comes, they're finished!
It's approximately an hour before the appointed time of
12:05 AM
the Straw Hats' rendezvous at Cacao Island.
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
Is it...
Yeah, that's right.
...over now?!
Yeah, I'll accept the challenge.
I'll wrap it up!
If you can withstand this...
I already gave you my answer...
This is it...
Yeah...
Gear Four!
Snake-Man!
Snake-Man, a new Gear Four form, is finally unveiled!
Luffy who has evolved stunningly and Katakuri,
the formidable man
who sees into the future, get into the last deadly struggle!
It's going to be a battle that no one has ever seen before!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Fist of Divine Speed! Another Gear Four Application Activated!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!