Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Sanji headed to Cacao Island with Pudding.
Luffy's gonna emerge in the middle of
fleets and armies.
I'll save our captain at any cost!
At Cacao Island, Oven waits for Luffy
in front of the only mirror
that he kept intact on the island.
All the while, more forces are massing.
We still have an hour and a half.
When the time comes, they're finished!
Luffy, continuing a hard fight against Katakuri,
remembers what Rayleigh taught him.
There are some strong people
who can see slightly ahead into the future.
The future?!
What are you gonna do when you face them?
The two-year training won't
take you to that level...
They're tough to beat.
It depends on what kind of guy he or she is.
What? Your opponent's character?!
Does that matter to you?
I've never thought of it like that.
Of course, it does.
You're quite the character.
There's no time for you to rest.
What?
We'll get on to the next training.
Come on!
Okay!
I'll teach you everything I can.
"A Fist of Divine Speed!
Another Gear Four Application Activated!"
What's the matter, Straw Hat?!
Is it...
Yeah, that's right.
...over now?!
Yeah, I'll accept the challenge.
I'll wrap it up!
If you can withstand this...
I already gave you my answer...
This is it...
Yeah...
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
Ho...
By coating yourself with the Haki of the Color of Arms,
you hardened your skin
and the tension of your
rubber has increased, too.
That's not all!
Hmm, using the protean elasticity of rubber,
you enable yourself to fly...
I can do more than just fly!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
...Gun!
I see...
By unleashing the elasticity of
rubber that's been enhanced by
Nthe Color of Arms at once, your
attack gets more powerful...
Right!
Bounce-Man is aptly named...
But...
...that's not enough.
The easiest way to learn is through pain.
What's wrong?
You can't get up after just one blow?
Damn!
There's no time for you to cry in pain.
Gum-Gum...
...Rhino Schneider!
Where are you?!
What are you hitting?
Ho!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Organ Gun!
Why can't I hit him?!
The Haki of the Color of Observation?!
What are you gonna do?
Dammit!
Gear Four!
Snake-Man!
Snake-Man?
Seems like it's different from the one before.
Your Color of Observation
sure is something...
That's why I'll use...
...something faster!
Why is he making such a simple attack
after all this time?
What's going on?
Why is it coming from the side?
What was that?
Where did it come from?!
I dodged it for sure!
I see... That's how it works!
Chase him, Python!
It's no use!
It accelerates even after it expanded.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Culverin!
It's far from over!
I'm stronger and faster than you!
Catch up to him!
Buzz Cut Mochi!
The mochi is so sticky...
...and I can't get it off!
I feel dizzy!
Stop! What are you doing?!
Get me down!
Damn! I can't pull myself apart!
This is it, Straw Hat!
Dammit!
I have Cacao Island in sight!
Rabian, hurry up!
Count on me!
--Stop!
--What?
Are you okay?
Shut up!
Oops!
Don't touch me like that!
It's annoying! Jeez!
Anyway...
Look at all those ships.
It's a massive fleet that
can destroy the island.
Headed up by Big Bro Oven,
so many top officers of the family have gathered.
If they notice me, we'll be in trouble.
Until our captain returns,
I don't wanna create a ruckus on the island.
We have to land without being noticed
somehow.
Land at the dark spot as quick as you can.
Can you do it, Rabian?
Yeah! I'll fly very low over the sea surface
under their radar.
Lie down on me.
--Yeah.
--Okay.
I'll make sure you won't get thrown off.
--We're ready.
--Here we go!
Sanji-san...
Are you okay?
Oh... Oh my...
If possible, I wanna keep holding his hand...
Sorry. You don't wanna be seen as
husband and wife.
That's right! Stop doing unnecessary things!
We're gonna land!
Dammit!
If your punch contradicts
the future that I see...
I'll just top it...
As a result, your future will be shattered
and you'll be finished, too...
That's all there is to it...
You hear me, don't you?!
Straw Hat!
Damn!
It hurts!
This is so tough!
I'm hungry!
What are you saying?!
I said everything on my mind!
I feel better now!
Fall down, Katakuri!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Culverin!
Punch Mochi!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Go, Python!
Burning Mochi!
Damn!
What's next?
Interesting.
Bring it on!
Here I go!
Gum-Gum...
...Black Mamba!
One more attack and it'll be over, Straw Hat!
I'm gonna take you down
at any cost, Katakuri!
That one again!
I'll put you out of your misery!
No need to!
SHAKKY'S RIP-OFF BAR
Now I remember.
I wonder if Monkey-chan's doing alright.
I don't know...
You always used to say that.
"Only those who are living in the present
can make a new epoch."
Did I say that?
Don't play dumb...
Rise above it, Luffy...
Gum-Gum...
Buzz Cut Mochi!
...King Cobra!
You can't get away now!
Go!
After spending all their strength and collapsing,
both Luffy and Katakuri can't even move an inch!
The Straw Hats hold out hope for Luffy's victory
and wait for him at Cacao Island!
As the appointed time approaches,
will it be Luffy or Katakuri
who stands up and becomes the true winner?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally, It's Over! The Climax of
the Intense Fight against Katakuri!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!