Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
After defeating Katakuri
and meeting up with Sanji,
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
After defeating Katakuri
and meeting up with Sanji,
Luffy and the others who saved Sanji and his family
from the hellish Tea Party...
Luffy hurries to escape
from the Whole Cake Island!
...kept fighting separate battles
in order to meet up at Cacao Island.
Luffy and Sanji finally reached the Sunny
where their friends were waiting for them.
The Big Mom Pirates attacked Luffy furiously,
The duel between Luffy and Katakuri
finally came to an end.
In the Mirroworld,
Luffy and Katakuri's fierce battle continues.
Luffy finally defeated Katakuri
and with the help of Pekoms,
he escaped from the Mirroworld to Cacao Island.
but surprisingly, it was Germa 66
who came to the rescue.
With Germa's help,
they tried to sail away from Cacao Island,
Meanwhile, for Sanji and Pudding who are sneaking onto
but more enemy ships came
and surrounded them.
Sanji!
Cacao Island to meet up with Luffy,
Did you win?!
Sparking...
Yeah!
it's time to say goodbye.
However...
...Valkyrie!
SPARKING VALKYRIE
Could you do me a favor?!
Sanji headed for the Sunny carrying Luffy,
but the Big Mom Pirates attacked him.
No way!
Just one, for the last time...
Just when he was stuck in a critical situation,
those who came to save him were...
"A Captivating Flavor!
Sanji's Cake of Happiness!"
I wanna ask you a favor!
FLUFFY ISLAND
"Finally, It's Over!
The Climax of the Intense Fight against Katakuri!"
Winch Guillotine!
Are you gonna come back...
WINCH GUILLOTINE
You bastards!
Germa 66!
...to take down Big Mom someday?
"Pulling Back from the Brink!
The Formidable Reinforcements - Germa!"
Of course I am! Because I'll...
...become the King of the Pirates!
You're seeing quite far into the future!
This is a lightspeed sword!
Damn Germa! Why are you here?!
Henry Blazer!
HENRY BLAZER
Let's go, Chiffon!
We can't stay here any longer!
If you stand in our way,
we'll take you out along with Straw Hat!
If he's gonna come out, it'll be in five minutes!
Not yet!
Come on now!
Almost...
Shoot!
Cake!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Pink Hornet!
Almost...
Chiffon!
Not yet!
Don't be difficult!
Yay!
Not yet!
Enough!
"A Desperate Situation!
The Iron-tight Entrapment of Luffy!"
There it is, Luffy! The Sunny!
Alright! I'm finally free now!
There's not even a scratch on them!
What's wrong with them?!
ON THE CACAO ISLAND
"The Last Hope!
The Sun Pirates Emerge!"
There'll be another pile
of scum when we're done.
I know Big Bro Katakuri will never, ever
get defeated by a short-ass like him,
Finally...
Finally, Mama will eat the cake!
Sanji.
Take the injured and
get off of the island already.
but in any case, it's impossible for Straw Hat
to get out of the Mirroworld without me!
Maybe all the islands will
be destroyed by Mama...
We don't need you here!
And Totto Land will be devastated...
I'm sorry, Straw Hat!
I'll join Big Bro Oven and the others,
They set us up.
We'll make them pay!
Or maybe due to the poison that
Straw Hat surely laced the cake with,
This whole island is our target, Sanji!
and kill every last one of the Straw Hats!
Mama will die!
You guys!
Or maybe a miracle will happen,
Four minutes to go...
Are they really modified humans
with iron skins?!
and Mama just stops!
CACAO ISLAND
Bring me a bazooka!
This moment will decide our fate!
It's 32 minutes before the appointed time of
Cake!
12:28 AM
That's...
the Straw Hats' rendezvous at Cacao Island.
Sanji!
Germa!
No one has come out yet.
I guess the battle is dragging on.
I thought that you were all dead!
How did you survive?!
Sanji-kun!
--Come on!
--Hurry up!
I'm sure it is!
Is there any chance of
Big Bro Katakuri losing?
You're almost there!
What do you mean?
Ten thousand soldiers led by Nusstorte
took over your kingdom!
What?! Any chance for Katakuri losing?!
Newji! Are you...
The Straw Hats' ship!
Yeah, the flies swarmed all over us
but we swatted them and dumped them into the sea.
Now, everyone's here!
...serious?!
Yay! They're back!
There's no chance!
She ate it!
What?!
Ouch!
Luffy!
Why did you hit me?! I'm Newsan!
I didn't say anything!
--Sanji!
--Luffy-san!
Here they are.
They dumped our Big Brothers and the others
into the sea?!
Luffy!
What daredevils!
What's going on here-soir?!
Katakuri will never be
defeated in his entire life!
I'm glad that you're okay!
I definitely got a call saying that
Germa's been destroyed!
I'm so happy! Really!
How is it?
He's right, you idiot!
I think they see us!
Big Bro Katakuri is simply a perfect man!
We crushed them with ten thousand soldiers.
Their kingdom is devastated!
He's been totally worn out...
How could they assemble that many ships?
Ouch! I'm Newshi!
There's only one ship on our side!
Well done! Luffy! Sanji!
What will happen?
Who was that, then?!
I'm sorry, Newsan, Newshi...
Doesn't it seem like overkill?!
I was so worried, Luffy!
Contact them-bon!
Garchu!
You can say it's logical.
Ouch!
Th-This is Montd'Or! Come in!
You owed us!
Even though it was unintended,
What?!
You guys... You kept me waiting so long!
Is it utter devastation?!
it's like we declared
that we were going to be there.
You fool! You fool!
Big Bro Nusstorte! Please come in!
But we haven't heard from him for a while...
It's weird.
Yeah, right!
Or a miracle?!
Big Bro Bassquarte! Big Bro Dosmarche!
Luffy... Did you beat Katakuri?
So they had to throw away their pride...
Even if they are the mighty Big Mom Pirates.
This is what I'd do if I were Straw Hat.
Whoever is there! Just come in!
His rendezvous with his crew
is at 1 AM here on Cacao Island...
Yeah!
--Wow!
--I'm so impressed, Luffy-san!
Just as I thought, unexpected things keep
Don't worry. It's gonna be alright!
Tart ships, go!
In other words, his crew won't get here
until 1 AM...
Sink Straw Hat's ship!
The man who baked it....
happening including Pekoms'
betrayal-vous plaît!
--He fell asleep?!
--The cuts and bruises are still fresh...
...is a true chef!
In that case, I'd capture Big Sis Brulee,
the only key to the Mirroworld,
How come Germa's fleet
appeared at Cacao Island-noir?!
Chopper-san, see to his wounds!
He's losing too much blood, isn't he?!
Here they come!
and wait out the clock
in the Mirroworld or on other islands!
What were you fools gonna do
with our scientific technology?
No! We're gonna die!
Yeah!
Luffy, hurry up!
Yeah! Big Sis Brulee has
actually gone missing!
You could do nothing!
Keep our distance from the island!
Hey, Black-Leg!
It'll take a full night if you do it that way!
You bastards!
All right!
That's right!
It's highly likely that Straw Hat Luffy
will run from the fight against Katakuri
--Going through this trouble is crucial!
--But we don't have time!
Sanji, you too. You got shot!
Sanji! Just go now!
Okay!
I'll do it in two hours!
and come out of this mirror at 1 AM sharp.
Oh, this is nothing.
You're kidding!
We must avoid being pinned down...
We won't let you get away!
Treat Luffy first.
Yeah, I see.
Black-Leg!
Big Sis Brulee's a bit dense
so she gets caught easily.
Sky Walk!
What should we do, Smoothie?!
Why are you smiling?!
Get serious, Black-Leg!
Akimeg, she might be listening
through the mirror.
Shoot him down!
We'll keep supporting from their aft!
They have nowhere to run.
Nice! We'll hit them soon!
Oh, oops!
Your ship and our country are at stake!
There's 30 minutes to go...
We need to stay alert.
The Totto Land Grand Fleet led by Snack is ahead of them
SQUARE WITH THE MIRROR IS                       THE SUNNY
OVEN'S ARMY
SMOOTHIE'S FLEET
They've caught up to us before we realized!
Bazookas! Ready to fire!
Come on out, Straw Hat!
What?!
I'm sorry...
We haven't lost them yet!
Treat him as we sail away!
Target - Black-Leg Sanji!
I'll chop you in half with my sickle!
and our fleet is behind them.
I couldn't help it because
I was picturing Big Mom's joyful look
while she exclaims "It's delicious"...
--One!
--Two!
Uh-huh!
Even if they make it to Cacao Island by any chance,
--Three!
--Four!
Go!
He's so sweet!
Big Bro Oven's army is waiting for them.
Joyful look?!
She's trying to kill you!
They're already trapped like rats.
Don't stop, Sanji!
PEANUT TOWN, NUTS ISLAND
Oh yeah.
This is the end of the line for them!
Black Bug!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Keep all the Transponder Snails connected!
Are they all soldiers?
We need intelligence from all angles.
Seems like that's the only mirror
that they kept intact...
Keep it up! A little more to go!
Certainly, Montd'Or-sama.
Slow Waltz!
What?!
Their ship came. Which means...
When Luffy comes out,
we gotta get out of here instantly...
It means Straw Hat will show up soon.
Or both of us will get killed...
I wanna slice him up already.
Damn! Germa!
Th-Thank you very much, Amande-sama!
Mama!
What happened?!
I'll get him!
When Luffy comes out,
that'll be our farewell then...
--What?!
--Who said you can go first?!
Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors!
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack
hasn't stopped yet.
Pudding-cha...
Prepare to fire!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Too far!
We're living in the
Emperor-of-the-Sea's territory
Do you hear me, Pudding-chan?
Shoot!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
that's supposed to be protected
by giving up our lifespans...
D-D-D... Don't look at me!
I wanna squash him already-yu!
The poison killed her?!
I can't believe that the
queen destroyed it herself...
Don't hold back! Shoot back!
I-I-I am listening to you!
Damn Straw Hats!
Sanji...
BEANIE-BEAN TOWN, MUNCHIE ISLAND
It's impossible... to
rebake the wedding cake...
...san!
Rescue crew, get to the island!
Save Mama!
Prepare yourself, you stupid brat!
...that took even the famous
Streusen-sama days to make!
Come on out, Straw Hat!
No, wait!
Looking back, we met in such an odd way...
Even Pudding-sama won't be able to
recreate it in just several hours!
Snack and the others are
under fierce attack by Germa!
Shouldn't we go help them?!
TABLE TOWN, CUTLERY ISLAND
The cake that Mama will
smack her lips over...
This is your fiancée.
Charlotte Pudding-sama!
Don't get distracted by that!
We've gotta focus on Straw Hat's ship!
Come on!
Hurry up, Luffy!
That's impossible!
We should get ready to evacuate!
Tell it to all ships around the island!
Let's get married tomorrow.
SHERBET TOWN, ICE CREAM ISLAND
Yes, ma'am!
DAY OF THE WEDDING
Let's get out of here before Mama arrives!
Help!!
Montd'Or and the others!
They must've been outsmarted by Germa!
Where is she now?!
Sulong?
You were outsmarted too, Big Bro Daifuku.
Fluffy Island!
That's right! Grr!
It's run by the Minister
of Fluff, Chiffon-sama...
Tsk! But I fought hard to catch up to you!
We Minks can transform into our primal form
by looking at the full moon!
Mama with her Hunger Pangs attack
is coming to this island!
FLUFFY ISLAND
Here, Pudding-chan...
Why are you letting their ship go?!
Corner them already!
Nothing will stop her!
But I've always been bad at it...
Thank you!
Chiffon-sama...
Why did she bring the cake to this town?!
I can transform into my Sulong form
but I'll become nothing but a beast.
Run!
Hey, Jimbei!
Tsk!
Shortly...
What do you think of Germa?
Are they enemies or allies to us?
A beast?
I'll run wild and destroy everything around me!
Shortly, Pudding-chan and I will...
All right!
All there's left to do
is let Big Mom eat it...
They could've gotten away.
Why bother coming to get us now?
No one's voice will reach me but...
Wedding...
...cake!
Bring me egg whites!
It's so delicious... that I could die!
But they stood up for us just for the time being, right?
How can we trust them?!
...there was one exception!
They're ready!
Give it to me!
Here!
That was Big Bro Pedro!
Thank you, Pudding-chan!
The sweetness is unbelievable!
Oh! Maybe Reiju-san came
to show me her panties...
--Ah!
--Oops!
L-Let me mix it this time!
This is it!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Okay, thank you!
Wedding cake!
Clank.
Hey, can you hear me?!
Sanji! We can't get any closer
to the island than this!
The ship...!
Of course, the flavor is important
but so is the presentation!
Stop, Pekoms!
I know! Sail by the harbor at full speed!
She stopped...
What about the poison?!
Okay!
I'm sure it was laced!
It just didn't work! That's our Mama!
I'll make it there while you're doing that!
It can't be helped. We must
say goodbye to you now...
Sanji-kun! How's Luffy?!
I got him! I don't have time now!
I'm counting on you, Nami-san!
You saved us so many times.
I had so much fun being with you,
Pekoms...
Black-Leg!
but I have to say goodbye soon...
Okay!
Thank you, Nostra Castello!
It's the look that you wished to see!
Thanks for everything!
Let's go, Jimbei! Starboard!
It's superb! This sweetness
Starboard!
Everything's gonna be all right!
I know it from somewhere else
Sanji!
For some reason, his voice alone could calm me down when I was out of my mind!
You can do it!
I fooled you and tried to kill you...
It's delicious!
Now, we gotta get off of the island!
Guys, get in the castle!
So don't thank me, Sanji-san!
I wanna apologize!
To all islands of Totto Land.
Pedro...
Crush Germa!
I really have to apologize!
The rampage is over!
Where did Black-Leg go?!
So there's no one left in this world
who can stop my rampage!
I can't see because of the dust!
Now, Chiffon. Get in!
Listen, Straw Hat. It's the full moon tonight!
By the work of the 35th daughter
of Charlotte, Pudding herself,
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack has stopped!
Hold Pez for me...
When I go out to Cacao Island
through the mirror,
Rero?!
I'm glad! I thought this island would be next
since we're so close to Cacao Island!
Hey, Chiffon!
Shut up!
I'll transform into my Sulong form!
I'm gonna watch it to the end.
There he is!
It was scary!
I run this island...
When I go out of control, that'll be your chance to escape from Cacao Island!
No! No! I did it again!
We're okay now!
Thank you, Bege!
I'm responsible for it!
Shoot him!
You're right! We're enemies!
You idiot! It's no use, Pekoms!
To you, our marriage was just a trap.
You damn traitor!
There is a force at Cacao Island
large enough to launch a war!
The whole thing was staged
by the Big Mom Pirates...
Even if you transform,
they'll take you down instantly and it'll be over!
Don't let him get away!
But...
That's right...
Don't let him get away at any price!
I'm gonna fall!
...maybe it was unpleasant for you...
Shut up, Brulee!
By using Chiffon-sama, who betrayed the country,
Pudding-sama saved Totto Land!
We're almost there, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat Luffy is the last
person we wanna forgive!
...but I'm glad that you played my fiancée!
There it is! My wedding cake!
Big Bro Pedro sacrificed himself!
No one else could do it!
No matter what, don't let it be in vain!
Grr!
Thank you, Pudding-sama!
I won't let anyone have it!
That's our Pudding-sama!
He didn't flee from Big Bro Katakuri
by throwing dust in his eyes...
No way!
Thank you, Pudding-sama!
MONTD'OR'S TACTICAL OPERATIONS CENTER
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Okay!
Big Bro Peros!
Thanks!
Big Sis Brulee?!
Now, do your work for us!
Please respond! How's Mama doing?!
Oh, I mean...
Do you wanna know
what really happened in the Mirroworld?
No...
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to insult you!
What?
And Bege?! The cake?!
Let's go!!
Things will get even crazier there than
they are at Cacao Island! Big Bro Peros!
It wasn't me.
No! Stop crying!
The perfect one,
Stop, tears!
The one who really saved everyone...
I-I'm sorry!
and the world's strongest and greatest...
ON THE SEA - BIG MOM AND THE OTHERS
Please come in, Big Bro Peros!
I didn't mean that, Pudding-chan!
...is someone very strong,
Yeah, I know!
It's coming from inside the mirror!
...our Big Bro Katakuri...
H-Hey, Sanji...
Help!!
and very, very kind...
...san...
I still have my eyes on
Mama, Bege, and the others!
He's someone I'll never forget...
Isn't that Big Sis Brulee?!
Could you do me a favor?!
Huh? What's wrong, Big Bro Peros?!
Just as we thought,
she was captured by Straw Hat.
He...
Just one, for the last time...
We came to say goodbye! Captain Jimbei!
That bastard!
Big Bro Montd'Or! This is Bavarois!
I wanna ask you a favor!
How could you be so reckless?!
Why didn't you just escape?!
Big Bro Peros left his wound untreated for too long
so he's become very weak!
...has been defeated by Straw Hat Luffy!!
He's coming! Aim and shoot!
The whole crew of the Sun
Pirates - we all agreed.
What?!
Now isn't the time to
bring this up... Lick...
Go back to Straw Hat's ship now.
Give it to me!
We, the Sun Pirates, will open up
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei's new sea route!
We're on the water near Fluffy Island now!
It's truly pandemonium here, too!
Chiffon and Bege finally let go of the cake!
What?!
Is that...?!
I got it!
Pekoms!
Katakuri...
The cake is at Fluffy Island! Lick!
Go away!
Your legendary undefeated record...
What?!
So cool!
In a few minutes, it'll come to an end!
...has been broken by that squirt?!
I'm Mystoms!
Shoot!
Pekoms! Why did you come out?!
12:37 AM
What?
Even if the cake is laced
with a deadly poison,
No way!!
Let's go, guys!
Okay!
D-Don't move, Big Mom Pirates!
we can't stop her now!
Big Bro won't lose!
W-What the?!
Katakuri-sama will never be defeated!
I-If you do something stupid,
It's flooded!
I'll blow your precious sister
Brulee's brains out! Grr!
He must've used some kind of dirty trick!
I can't forgive him!
There are three possible outcomes!
Someone punched holes in the bottom?!
One! By eating the poisoned cake,
There are Fish-Men in the water!
--Brulee!
--Big Sis Brulee!
Don't do it, Pekoms!
How could they be so sneaky?!
Mama dies!
Pekoms, what are you thinking?!
Come out, you damn Fish-Men!
Shoot him dead!
Why don't you calm down?!
Let go of Big Sis Brulee!
Help! Everyone!
Two! The poison doesn't affect Mama,
Cut him up!
You bastards!
My identity was going to be revealed
by transforming anyway...
but the cake tastes bad!
Yuck!
Damn!
In that case, it won't satisfy her
and she'll continue destroying the country!
I won't let the Straw Hats get away!
Pulverize him completely until
not a single bone is left!
It doesn't matter now!
Genie!
Yeah!
And three!
The poison in the cake doesn't affect her
and it tastes good!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
It would take a miracle
but it's the only way we can survive!
I'll keep Straw Hat alive!
Prepare yourselves!
Our fate is left up to the taste of the cake!
He's the guy who Big Bro Pedro bet on!
I'll...
This is the worst situation ever-soir!
We won't let you flee, Straw Hat!
...never...
Let the whole country know that!
...lose!
It's already known.
Mama is out of control now...
Look!
--I heard that Nuts Island has been devastated.
--What?!
No way!
He's trying to become a Sulong!
What's gonna happen to Totto Land?
--Don't do it, Pekoms!
--You'll be out of control!
It's like playing Russian
roulette with the cake-bon!
A path on the sea!
Damn you!
No!!
Hey! Where did Morgans and Stussy go?!
Straw Hat!!
Hold him down!
They left the island earlier.
It's too late...
What?!
Prepare yourself!
Capture them!
I won't forgive you!
If the worst happens,
the news will leak outside the country!
Hey!
You bastard!
Gee, what's this all about?
Yes, sir!
Make sure you don't let that newspaper bastard
leave the country at any price!
Coming out of the mirror was
neither Katakuri nor Straw Hat!
Go on, Jimbei!
He'll publish anything!
How dare you point a gun at my sister...
Advance!
This island is doomed!
Let's get out of here!
...for no reason?!
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
FLOOF TOWN, FLUFFY ISLAND
It's gonna be destroyed just
like Nuts Island by Mama!
Kill him, Big Bro Oven!
They've survived until this point!
12:40 AM
--Ouch!
--Big Bro!
Go ahead while we hold
them off, Captain Jimbei!
Chiffon-sama was brainwashed
by the traitor, Bege!
It's over, Straw Hat!
The Straw Hats!
We won't let you harm the Straw Hats' ship!
If you let them escape
despite your preparations for an all-out attack,
Heat...
it's gonna be headline news!
...Beating!
Chiffon! What are you talking about?!
Ouch!
Shut up, Morgans! You won't get the scoop!
No!
I'm doing this because I believe in the cake
made by Black-Leg.
Thank you!
Yay!
In order to avoid that at all costs,
Sparking...
Why didn't I notice?
we swallowed our pride
and sent tons of soldiers to Cacao Island!
I don't know who he learned from,
They disabled the enemy's
Territory Slugs for us, too.
...Valkyrie!
but his cooking skill might be higher
than the Executive Chef's!
SPARKING VALKYRIE
That's Straw Hat!
Even if Gold Roger, the former King of the Pirates,
comes out of the mirror,
They saved me even in the end.
we won't let him get away!
It's so delicious!
Only Jimbei's friends could do that!
Ichiji?!
Once we catch them all,
we'll chop their heads off and line them up,
Luffy!
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack
will stop here!
Yeah!
so put it on the front page tomorrow!
Thank you!
Guys!
To set an example!
You're a failure who deserves
to die, right, Sanji?!
Take care of Jimbei for us! Straw Hat!
You have bad taste...
That's so unnecessary...
Okay!
In that case, if he really dies,
will it make Father happy?
No way! In fact, it's too kind!
Vito! Gotti!
Fire!
Go look for a ship to escape now!
We'll get good news soon!
There's no way that one ship can
run through the grand fleet!
I'll take Chiffon with me later!
You are...
O-Okay-rero!
a failure.
Damn!
Got it!
Niji! We'll stop them here!
We paid off our debt to the Straw Hats.
12:43 AM
Take off, Sanji!
We lost our precious ship.
We won't let you do that!
Stop!
Merge!
Those fools of the Straw Hats!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
ON THE SEA - BEGE'S SHIP
I won't forgive them if they die
after all we've done for them!
Give me the cake!
This is Sanji!
Oh, Sanji!
Luffy...
The sails are on fire!
Big Bro Oven! Are you okay?!
...made it!
Put it out now! We're gonna sink!
Yes!
We can't go on-rero, Father! This is it-rero!
Oven-sama, don't you have
to stay on Cacao Island?!
We're gonna die before we
get to the island-rero!
Wedding...
Hand him over!
Let's trash the cake and flee, Father!
I left Germa to Brulee!
It's Straw Hat!
Black-Leg!
--Pekoms was hiding him!
--Get him!
Don't get flustered now!
I'm gonna take you down again-yu!
Rero?
These are heavy-metal
composite bullets that can
...cake!!
He threw dust in Big Bro Katakuri's eyes
and came out...
We've all come from different places...
easily punch holes through
Germa's Raid Suits!
That's pretty impressive!
I'm gonna go first!
Let's at least
Go teach them a lesson!
die together!
Ya-hoo!
Yes, ma'am!
Father!
Germa!
Look up!
I see it!
It wasn't smart to jump...
You're an easy target!
It's Fluffy Island!
Rero!
It's him again!
We're almost there!
Show your manliness, guys!
Just surrender!
Straw Hat!
Yeah!
Winch Guillotine!
WINCH GUILLOTINE
Big Bro Raisin!
12:45 AM
Who is that?!
Since you brought down Katakuri,
you're the last person...
Sanji!
Did you win?!
...I wanna let go alive!
ON THE SEA - THE SUNNY
Yeah!
I knew it!
Seems like they stopped attacking.
--They're trying to get away through the air!
--That's Black-Leg!
But we still can't lose them!
How simple...
There is an ambush at Cacao Island.
That's to be expected.
Fire!
We can use Geppo, too!
They'll probably start attacking again there
to sandwich us!
One!
Yonji?!
Two!
Go, Sanji!
Invade the castle!
What?! What should we do?!
Three!
Four!
Five!
I have no choice.
I'll negotiate with that big woman!
Huh?
You're such an eyesore!
What the...?
Excuse me! Could I see your panties...
Shoot! He's above the roofs!
Cut it out, you silly skeleton!
Germa's backing them up!
Straw Hat... Black-Leg...
Damn you, Judge!
I'll avenge Katakuri-sama!
I won't let anyone...
Okay... The negotiation failed.
Should we return fire?!
...break into Germa's castle!
No, don't bother!
I've got more in me!
We can make it there by 1 AM as we promised!
Germa is also fighting
the fleet at the harbor!
Isn't that right,
--Aim at Straw Hat's ship!
--Yes, ma'am!
But my concern is Brulee,
the key to escaping the Mirroworld.
Big Bro Pedro?!
I'll fight you!
To let them get away...
Bring it on!
Even if Luffy wins, he can't get out of there
without Brulee!
You're too slow. You'll
be filled with bullets!
Luffy is not the kind of person
to carefully calculate something like that.
Niji!
Let's go!
Germa!
Okay!
That's right! He can't!
Let's go!
He definitely can't! What should we do?!
First of all, we're not sure
if he knows what time it is...
This is a lightspeed sword!
He might not?!
Sparking Figure!
So much could go wrong...
...but we believe in you, Luffy!
Is that Pekoms?
Henry Blazer!
HENRY BLAZER
12:47 AM
Pekoms!
Tropical Torment!
What's so good about him?! Straw Hat Luffy!
Don't get in our way!
You should've been dead!
This is Emperor of the Sea
Big Mom's territory...
Oh, no! Oven-sama!
Those two will make it out of town!
How's that?
Once you enter,
you'll never be able to get out!
You risked your life
just to get him back?!
Out of town?!
Everyone, swim deeper into the sea!
He's unbelievably strong but
seems out of control!
It's too hot! I can't get near him!
He's just a wild beast!
There is no protection for you guys!
Are you alive, failure?
Sanji is Germa's failure!
Damn you!
And you have nowhere to run!
You give us nothing but trouble.
His skin doesn't work as a shield!
I didn't ask you to help me!
--Dammit!
--What should we do, Luffy?!
Even when he falls, he falls forward...
He works as a cook
because he has no pride in his royal blood!
Idiot.
Goodbye, failure!
Uh-huh...
But I won...
He's easily moved like an idiot
Let's...
Snack! Brownie! Joconde!
...advance!
and his soft mind makes him
put his life on the line for the weak!
Shoot them down at the harbor!
They're coming towards you!
Hey! Isn't someone talking to us
through the Transponder Snail?!
A failed soldier who is far from perfect...
Queen Mama Chanter will be
arriving at Cacao Island soon.
Stop, Pekoms!
Brownie-sama.
Who cares about that right now?
Listen carefully, Luffy!
That's all he is!
Shoot Straw Hat Down!
We'll get there in 10 hours at the earliest!
Pekoms...
Around 1 AM!
So as soon as you kick that guy's ass,
I think I can make it!
Everything's gonna be all right!
look for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
And we'll see you there!
Don't let him go any farther!
Prepare tear-gas canisters!
Big Bro...
Alright! Just in time!
We should just shear him
of his strength to fly!
What time is it now?
Fluffy
Munch
Gulp
What's the matter?!
Take... Straw Hat...
Stay with us!
Hey! Hey!
Goodbye! Thank you for your help!
Fluffy
Munch
Gulp
Get clear away... at any cost...
Why don't you say something?!
Fluffy
Germa!
Munch
Gulp
Straw Hat!
What...
Those who hurt my little brother...
Okay!
I'm surprised. Why did he suddenly start listing
all the good things about you?
...is this?!
--The dream flavor
--Flower! Flower!
I won't forgive them!
Are you gonna come back...
If I can... run away...
What?! He didn't mean it that way!
It's something that I've never seen
even in my wildest dreams
...to take down Big Mom someday?
What?!
I can't find words to describe it
...here in the East Blue...
What? What?
You guys are amazing!
Of course I am! Because I'll...
What's this flavor?
Why's that?
I'll never...
Why? Tell us!
...become the King of the Pirates!
Rotten puppies start dancing
...have to see...
The flavor is concentrated like...
...Dad's face again, right?
A pet cemetery!
Don't push your luck!
Make it so he'll never see the full moon again!
Pink Hornet!
You're seeing quite far into the future!
Nami! Look forward!
What?
That's Straw Hat! Shoot!
--It's sweet
--It's milky
No! Oh, please!
You're really a high-maintenance brother.
It's very rich and...
Reiju!
Jimbei! There is a massive fleet ahead!
When did they arrive?!
...risky!
They finally noticed!
There are tons of ships!
Oh, no! We got sandwiched again!
Don't ever let him go!
GERMA                          THE SUNNY
Pekoms!!
All their available ships
came around the island!
Step back!
--Look! Yes, it's a big fuss
--Ship! Ship!
We're surrounded!
Everything went all right...
You have only one chance!
Don't ruin it!
It's like when you throw a bomb
into an amusement park
Big Bro...
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
We're already in their attack range!
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
How is it possible?!
That's right!
Uh-huh!
We're coming from both the
front and back, rabbit!
Not paying attention....
Like your stomach is having...
...is disrespectful-yu!
Carrot-chan!
A big ceremony
The sea is broad! You'll...
You're between the fleet and the genie!
Genie-uine...
You'll definitely meet kind people someday!!
...Rage Split!
Black-Leg?!
Branch... Let's go...
When you're vastly outnumbered,
it's meaningless...
Sanji!
What? Branch?
Hey, Mother
There's a giant one!
...no matter how hard you struggle.
She escaped!
Can you taste this overflowing
happy sweetness?
Oh, no! I can't get out
of here without her...
There's no way that you're a failure.
It's over.
We finally got close enough
for my power to reach!
W-What should I do?
Dammit!
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life and
Now it looks like we're bullying them.
I don't have time...
Big Brother!
he was born with the spark of humanity.
What?!
Oh, yeah!
That child is you, Sanji.
How did they suddenly get this close?!
There's an explosion at the harbor!
Big Bro Katakuri!
It's the flavor of happiness...
HAPPY BIRTHDAY LINLIN
Look closely at the ships in front of us!
What's that?!
...from that time
Branch!
It's Brulee, Straw Hat!
Hey, what happened-nie?!
They're all paddle ships!
What kind of a dirty trick did you use
to take him down?!
Those ships at the shore are burning!
Happy Birthday!
So you brought down Katakuri!
What's going on?!
--No way!
--We can't get clear away then!
Linlin!
Is it a bombing?!
I can't believe it! Grr!
It's a fleet, Snack-sama!
This might be it for us!
Even though we struggled so much to make it this far...
Let's eat it together someday again
You are...
Who are they?!
I-It's...
Crush them all at once!
...Germa's fleet!
My name is Mystoms!
Run!!
Why are they here?!
MYSTOMS - A MYSTERY SAVIOR
Go!
--It's sweet
They're already trapped like rats!
Just sink them!
I thought they were fully destroyed several hours ago!
In order to get you out of here,
I've captured Brulee and have been waiting for you!
Don't look back!!
--It's milky
--It's very rich and...
Next! Prepare to fire!
So you're okay...
Sanji... My little brother
who is the kindest person in the world!
Germa 66!
MYSTOMS - A MYSTERY SAVIOR
Pekoms!
PEKOMS
Why are they here?!
...risky!
Reiju!
Yeah! Big Bro Pedro sacrificed himself
to save your lives!
Goodbye!
I won't let you lose it here!
Come on, Straw Hat!
Let's go to Cacao Island where your friends are!
The Straw Hats will be swallowed by the sea!
--Okay!
--Let go of me!
What?!
Hey Mother, do you think...
12:50 AM
What's going on?!
There it is! Cacao Island!
...I can do this?
How many are there?!
Everyone's happy
The sea surface is lifting up...
That's a massive fleet!
It's a peaceful utopia
Those who trouble Boss...
Sanji-kun! How is it over there?
Luffy's not here yet.
It doesn't discriminate by race
Don't get close to the fleet at the shore.
I won't forgive!
I'll bring Luffy to the ship somehow!
Straw Hat and Sanji got off of the island!
Fleet, come in!
If you try to leave, I'll kill you though
12:55 AM
Hurry up, Sanji!
Guys, are your weapons ready?!
It's a devilish contract
What?!
Dammit!
Sanji-kun...
Yeah!
He's a member of Hordy's group
from the Fish-Man Island...
The peaceful Totto Land
If he's gonna come out,
it'll be in five minutes!
Wadatsumi!
We're all family
It's Sanji!
What?
No way!
Here he comes, guys!
The gentle queen
Jimbei!
Sanji is carrying Luffy!
You bastards!
Thank you for what you did for us at the Tea Party,
Big Mom!
Yay!
You guys!
I knew he could do it!
Big Mom Pirates!
Luffy!
Germa 66!
We came to say goodbye! Captain Jimbei!
Why are you here?!
What a coincidence, Sanji.
No, "former"! Former Captain!
You fools! I'll make you pay for this!
There it is, Luffy! The Sunny!
We wanted to give these fools...
Isn't dinner ready yet, Sanji?
Until we leave this territory,
is it okay if we remain as your subordinates?!
It was delicious
...a crushing blow, too!
Thank you for the cake!
Come on now!
Jimbei!
Straw Hat Luffy!
How will Bege's last big gamble end up?!
Big Mom finally takes a bite of the cake!
Ichiji's sparking techniques, Niji's electric attacks,
and Yonji's monstrous power.
A huge watertight encirclement
is waiting for Luffy!
The Sunny sinks! It seems like
there is no more hope to escape.
All eyes throughout the country
are on Mom and the cake!
Will Sanji's cake bring
devastation of the country or a miraculous turnaround?
The furious members of Germa 66 show their true strength!
The Sunny enduring a barrage of bombs
is already reaching its limits!
However, the Sun Pirates' tricky
move opens up a new route!
Meanwhile, the Sunny is in a
joyous mood having Luffy back!
The time of the rendezvous has finally come!
And just like that unforgettable day, Reiju says goodbye.
However, Smoothie's cunning strategy puts them
in the greatest no-way-out danger ever!
As the whole nation watches breathlessly,
Jimbei who made his earnest pledge to Luffy challenges
Facing imminent danger,
Luffy and Pekoms take their chances at the risk of their lives!
Big Mom's voice echoes throughout the
archipelago as people witness a surprising outcome!
Will Sanji be able to reach the Sunny,
dashing
the final battle at the risk of his life!
through the air in the middle of the combat?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Last Hope! The Sun Pirates Emerge!"
"A Captivating Flavor! Sanji's Cake of Happiness!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Desperate Situation! The
Iron-tight Entrapment of Luffy!"
"The Man of
Humanity and Justice! Jimbei, a Desperate Massive Ocean Current"
"Pulling Back from the Brink!
The Formidable Reinforcements - Germa!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!