Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
After defeating Katakuri
and meeting up with Sanji,
Luffy hurries to escape
from the Whole Cake Island!
The Big Mom Pirates attacked Luffy furiously,
but surprisingly, it was Germa 66
who came to the rescue.
Sparking...
...Valkyrie!
SPARKING VALKYRIE
Winch Guillotine!
WINCH GUILLOTINE
This is a lightspeed sword!
Henry Blazer!
HENRY BLAZER
Pink Hornet!
There it is, Luffy! The Sunny!
"The Last Hope!
The Sun Pirates Emerge!"
Sanji!
Sanji-kun!
--Come on!
--Hurry up!
You're almost there!
Now, everyone's here!
Yay! They're back!
Luffy!
--Sanji!
--Luffy-san!
Luffy!
I'm glad that you're okay!
I'm so happy! Really!
He's been totally worn out...
Well done! Luffy! Sanji!
I was so worried, Luffy!
Garchu!
You guys... You kept me waiting so long!
Yeah, right!
Luffy... Did you beat Katakuri?
Yeah!
--Wow!
--I'm so impressed, Luffy-san!
--He fell asleep?!
--The cuts and bruises are still fresh...
Chopper-san, see to his wounds!
He's losing too much blood, isn't he?!
Yeah!
Sanji, you too. You got shot!
Oh, this is nothing.
Treat Luffy first.
Nice! We'll hit them soon!
They've caught up to us before we realized!
What?!
We haven't lost them yet!
Treat him as we sail away!
Uh-huh!
PEANUT TOWN, NUTS ISLAND
Keep it up! A little more to go!
Slow Waltz!
Th-Thank you very much, Amande-sama!
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack
hasn't stopped yet.
We're living in the
Emperor-of-the-Sea's territory
that's supposed to be protected
by giving up our lifespans...
I can't believe that the
queen destroyed it herself...
BEANIE-BEAN TOWN, MUNCHIE ISLAND
It's impossible... to
rebake the wedding cake...
...that took even the famous
Streusen-sama days to make!
Even Pudding-sama won't be able to
recreate it in just several hours!
TABLE TOWN, CUTLERY ISLAND
The cake that Mama will
smack her lips over...
That's impossible!
We should get ready to evacuate!
SHERBET TOWN, ICE CREAM ISLAND
Let's get out of here before Mama arrives!
Where is she now?!
Fluffy Island!
It's run by the Minister
of Fluff, Chiffon-sama...
Mama with her Hunger Pangs attack
is coming to this island!
FLUFFY ISLAND
Nothing will stop her!
Chiffon-sama...
Why did she bring the cake to this town?!
Run!
All right!
All there's left to do
is let Big Mom eat it...
Wedding...
...cake!
Give it to me!
The ship...!
It can't be helped. We must
say goodbye to you now...
You saved us so many times.
Thank you, Nostra Castello!
Now, we gotta get off of the island!
Guys, get in the castle!
Now, Chiffon. Get in!
Hold Pez for me...
Rero?!
Hey, Chiffon!
I'm gonna watch it to the end.
I run this island...
I'm responsible for it!
There it is! My wedding cake!
I won't let anyone have it!
No way!
MONTD'OR'S TACTICAL OPERATIONS CENTER
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Big Bro Peros!
Please respond! How's Mama doing?!
And Bege?! The cake?!
Things will get even crazier there than
they are at Cacao Island! Big Bro Peros!
ON THE SEA - BIG MOM AND THE OTHERS
Please come in, Big Bro Peros!
Yeah, I know!
I still have my eyes on
Mama, Bege, and the others!
Huh? What's wrong, Big Bro Peros?!
Big Bro Montd'Or! This is Bavarois!
Big Bro Peros left his wound untreated for too long
so he's become very weak!
What?!
Now isn't the time to
bring this up... Lick...
Give it to me!
We're on the water near Fluffy Island now!
It's truly pandemonium here, too!
Chiffon and Bege finally let go of the cake!
The cake is at Fluffy Island! Lick!
In a few minutes, it'll come to an end!
Even if the cake is laced
with a deadly poison,
we can't stop her now!
There are three possible outcomes!
One! By eating the poisoned cake,
Mama dies!
Two! The poison doesn't affect Mama,
but the cake tastes bad!
Yuck!
In that case, it won't satisfy her
and she'll continue destroying the country!
And three!
The poison in the cake doesn't affect her
and it tastes good!
It would take a miracle
but it's the only way we can survive!
Prepare yourselves!
Our fate is left up to the taste of the cake!
This is the worst situation ever-soir!
Let the whole country know that!
It's already known.
Mama is out of control now...
--I heard that Nuts Island has been devastated.
--What?!
What's gonna happen to Totto Land?
It's like playing Russian
roulette with the cake-bon!
Hey! Where did Morgans and Stussy go?!
They left the island earlier.
What?!
Capture them!
If the worst happens,
the news will leak outside the country!
Yes, sir!
Make sure you don't let that newspaper bastard
leave the country at any price!
He'll publish anything!
This island is doomed!
Let's get out of here!
FLOOF TOWN, FLUFFY ISLAND
It's gonna be destroyed just
like Nuts Island by Mama!
Chiffon-sama was brainwashed
by the traitor, Bege!
Chiffon! What are you talking about?!
I'm doing this because I believe in the cake
made by Black-Leg.
I don't know who he learned from,
but his cooking skill might be higher
than the Executive Chef's!
It's so delicious!
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack
will stop here!
Vito! Gotti!
Go look for a ship to escape now!
I'll take Chiffon with me later!
O-Okay-rero!
Got it!
We paid off our debt to the Straw Hats.
We lost our precious ship.
Those fools of the Straw Hats!
I won't forgive them if they die
after all we've done for them!
Wedding...
...cake!!
Fire!
Huh?
What the...?
Germa's backing them up!
Damn you, Judge!
Should we return fire?!
No, don't bother!
Germa is also fighting
the fleet at the harbor!
--Aim at Straw Hat's ship!
--Yes, ma'am!
What's so good about him?! Straw Hat Luffy!
This is Emperor of the Sea
Big Mom's territory...
Once you enter,
you'll never be able to get out!
You risked your life
just to get him back?!
Sanji is Germa's failure!
His skin doesn't work as a shield!
He works as a cook
because he has no pride in his royal blood!
Uh-huh...
He's easily moved like an idiot
and his soft mind makes him
put his life on the line for the weak!
A failed soldier who is far from perfect...
That's all he is!
Goodbye! Thank you for your help!
Why don't you say something?!
Straw Hat!
I'm surprised. Why did he suddenly start listing
all the good things about you?
What?! He didn't mean it that way!
What?!
You guys are amazing!
Why's that?
Why? Tell us!
Nami! Look forward!
What?
No! Oh, please!
Jimbei! There is a massive fleet ahead!
When did they arrive?!
They finally noticed!
There are tons of ships!
Oh, no! We got sandwiched again!
GERMA                          THE SUNNY
All their available ships
came around the island!
We're surrounded!
We're already in their attack range!
How is it possible?!
That's right!
We're coming from both the
front and back, rabbit!
Carrot-chan!
You're between the fleet and the genie!
Genie-uine...
...Rage Split!
Black-Leg?!
Sanji!
There's a giant one!
We finally got close enough
for my power to reach!
Now it looks like we're bullying them.
How did they suddenly get this close?!
Look closely at the ships in front of us!
They're all paddle ships!
--No way!
--We can't get clear away then!
This might be it for us!
Even though we struggled so much to make it this far...
Crush them all at once!
Go!
They're already trapped like rats!
Just sink them!
The Straw Hats will be swallowed by the sea!
What?!
What's going on?!
The sea surface is lifting up...
Those who trouble Boss...
I won't forgive!
What?!
He's a member of Hordy's group
from the Fish-Man Island...
Wadatsumi!
What?
No way!
Jimbei!
You guys!
We came to say goodbye! Captain Jimbei!
No, "former"! Former Captain!
Until we leave this territory,
is it okay if we remain as your subordinates?!
Jimbei!
Big Mom finally takes a bite of the cake!
Will Sanji's cake bring
devastation of the country or a miraculous turnaround?
As the whole nation watches breathlessly,
Big Mom's voice echoes throughout the
archipelago as people witness a surprising outcome!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Captivating Flavor! Sanji's Cake of Happiness!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!