Yes! We've got Super Powers
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Your dream is like a monster
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
will become your one and only treasure
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing in a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
To that planet where love combines with tears
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
The future gently brings a morning
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
eien ni...
Always and forever...
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Magical excitement connects friends
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Living your life to the fullest
bouken to yobou ka
Shall we call it an adventure?
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
raibaru tono kizuna
The bond with your rival
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Even failure is strangely charming
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
After defeating Katakuri
and meeting up with Sanji,
Luffy hurries to escape
from the Whole Cake Island!
Luffy and Sanji finally reached the Sunny
where their friends were waiting for them.
With Germa's help,
they tried to sail away from Cacao Island,
but more enemy ships came
and surrounded them.
However...
No way!
"A Captivating Flavor!
Sanji's Cake of Happiness!"
FLUFFY ISLAND
Let's go, Chiffon!
We can't stay here any longer!
Not yet!
Cake!
Chiffon!
Not yet!
Don't be difficult!
Enough!
Finally...
Finally, Mama will eat the cake!
Maybe all the islands will
be destroyed by Mama...
And Totto Land will be devastated...
Or maybe due to the poison that
Straw Hat surely laced the cake with,
Mama will die!
Or maybe a miracle will happen,
and Mama just stops!
This moment will decide our fate!
Cake!
She ate it!
How is it?
What will happen?
Is it utter devastation?!
Or a miracle?!
Don't worry. It's gonna be alright!
The man who baked it....
...is a true chef!
Hey, Black-Leg!
It'll take a full night if you do it that way!
--Going through this trouble is crucial!
--But we don't have time!
I'll do it in two hours!
You're kidding!
Why are you smiling?!
Get serious, Black-Leg!
Your ship and our country are at stake!
I'm sorry...
I couldn't help it because
I was picturing Big Mom's joyful look
while she exclaims "It's delicious"...
He's so sweet!
Joyful look?!
She's trying to kill you!
Oh yeah.
Mama!
What happened?!
The poison killed her?!
Damn Straw Hats!
Rescue crew, get to the island!
Save Mama!
No, wait!
It's so delicious... that I could die!
The sweetness is unbelievable!
This is it!
Wedding cake!
She stopped...
What about the poison?!
I'm sure it was laced!
It just didn't work! That's our Mama!
Black-Leg!
It's the look that you wished to see!
It's superb! This sweetness
I know it from somewhere else
It's delicious!
To all islands of Totto Land.
The rampage is over!
By the work of the 35th daughter
of Charlotte, Pudding herself,
Mama's Hunger Pangs attack has stopped!
I'm glad! I thought this island would be next
since we're so close to Cacao Island!
It was scary!
We're okay now!
Thank you, Bege!
By using Chiffon-sama, who betrayed the country,
Pudding-sama saved Totto Land!
No one else could do it!
Thank you, Pudding-sama!
That's our Pudding-sama!
No...
It wasn't me.
The one who really saved everyone...
...is someone very strong,
and very, very kind...
He's someone I'll never forget...
We came to say goodbye! Captain Jimbei!
How could you be so reckless?!
Why didn't you just escape?!
The whole crew of the Sun
Pirates - we all agreed.
Go back to Straw Hat's ship now.
We, the Sun Pirates, will open up
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei's new sea route!
I got it!
Go away!
So cool!
Shoot!
Let's go, guys!
Okay!
W-What the?!
It's flooded!
Someone punched holes in the bottom?!
There are Fish-Men in the water!
How could they be so sneaky?!
Come out, you damn Fish-Men!
You bastards!
Damn!
I won't let the Straw Hats get away!
Genie!
Ocean Current...
...Shoulder Throw!
Look!
A path on the sea!
Go on, Jimbei!
Advance!
Go ahead while we hold
them off, Captain Jimbei!
We won't let you harm the Straw Hats' ship!
Thank you!
Why didn't I notice?
They disabled the enemy's
Territory Slugs for us, too.
They saved me even in the end.
Only Jimbei's friends could do that!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Guys!
Take care of Jimbei for us! Straw Hat!
Okay!
Fire!
Damn!
Niji! We'll stop them here!
We won't let you do that!
Merge!
Oven-sama, don't you have
to stay on Cacao Island?!
I left Germa to Brulee!
These are heavy-metal
composite bullets that can
easily punch holes through
Germa's Raid Suits!
Go teach them a lesson!
Yes, ma'am!
It's him again!
Straw Hat!
Since you brought down Katakuri,
you're the last person...
...I wanna let go alive!
Invade the castle!
I won't let anyone...
...break into Germa's castle!
I'll fight you!
Bring it on!
Let's go!
Okay!
Sparking Figure!
Tropical Torment!
Everyone, swim deeper into the sea!
It's too hot! I can't get near him!
There is no protection for you guys!
And you have nowhere to run!
--Dammit!
--What should we do, Luffy?!
Let's...
...advance!
Queen Mama Chanter will be
arriving at Cacao Island soon.
Alright! Just in time!
Fluffy
Munch
Gulp
Fluffy
Munch
Gulp
Fluffy
Munch
Gulp
What...
...is this?!
--The dream flavor
--Flower! Flower!
It's something that I've never seen
even in my wildest dreams
I can't find words to describe it
What? What?
What's this flavor?
Rotten puppies start dancing
The flavor is concentrated like...
A pet cemetery!
--It's sweet
--It's milky
It's very rich and...
...risky!
--Look! Yes, it's a big fuss
--Ship! Ship!
It's like when you throw a bomb
into an amusement park
Like your stomach is having...
A big ceremony
Hey, Mother
Can you taste this overflowing
happy sweetness?
Oh, yeah!
It's the flavor of happiness...
HAPPY BIRTHDAY LINLIN
...from that time
Happy Birthday!
Linlin!
Let's eat it together someday again
--It's sweet
--It's milky
--It's very rich and...
...risky!
Hey Mother, do you think...
...I can do this?
Everyone's happy
It's a peaceful utopia
It doesn't discriminate by race
If you try to leave, I'll kill you though
It's a devilish contract
The peaceful Totto Land
We're all family
The gentle queen
Big Mom!
It was delicious
Thank you for the cake!
The Sunny sinks! It seems like
there is no more hope to escape.
However, the Sun Pirates' tricky
move opens up a new route!
Jimbei who made his earnest pledge to Luffy challenges
the final battle at the risk of his life!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Man of
Humanity and Justice! Jimbei, a Desperate Massive Ocean Current"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!