Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
After defeating Katakuri and meeting up with Sanji,
Luffy hurries to escape from the Whole Cake Island!
The Great Pirate Era...
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
...is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
"The World is Stunned!
The Fifth Emperor of the Sea Emerges!"
At Fluffy Island, Big Mom finally comes to her senses
after eating the wedding cake.
"The Parting Time!
Pudding's Last Wish!"
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
It's so delicious... that I could die!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
We're in the clear. I see no pursuers.
The sweetness is unbelievable!
Do you think that
Jimbei-san and the others are okay?
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Well...
Hey, Luffy! What are you trying to do?!
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
Known as the Reverie, it
is now about to start.
This is it!
In any case,
we have to get out of Big Mom's territory.
I'm really serious!
Wedding cake!
I'm so pissed!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
The times are changing drastically now.
You're right.
I see. So Pedro...
Totto Land has been saved!
...died.
And the fleeing Sunny was relentlessly attacked
by the Big Mom Pirates.
"To the Reverie!
The Straw Hats' Sworn Allies Come Together!"
"Sabo Goes into Action!
All the Captains of the Revolutionary Army Appear!"
Oh, it didn't hurt at all!
My name is Pedro! Please help me...
That's a lie! Don't do such a stupid thing!
A PORT TOWN OF THE KINGDOM OF LULUCIA
GRAND LINE
I'm not scared of getting hurt!
Take me on your next voyage, Shanks!
Get them treated now...
Or they're gonna die!
Prepare to fire!
Damn.
Shoot them up!
My bounty has increased
because of Germa's name...
I wanna be a pirate, too!
The world is waiting for them!
It doesn't make me happy at all...
It was delicious.
Let's go!
We can't...
As if you could ever be a pirate!
Thank you for the cake!
Grab all their money and goods!
Why not?!
Hey, are you alright?
Luffy. Just being a good swimmer
doesn't mean you'd make a good pirate.
...ever let...
What's the Navy doing?!
Do your wounds hurt?
"The Man of Humanity and Justice!
Jimbei, a Desperate Massive Ocean Current"
I thought they came to help!
...those two die!
N-No...
I'm good at fighting, too!
How dare they destroy our ship...
My punches are like pistols!
This...
My bounty has decreased!
Oh, really?
Damn!
What's that supposed to mean?!
It's because he came to rescue me...
The end was too easy...
Look... It's 150 million berries...
He means you're too much of a kid, Luffy!
What?!
Seriously, you're as old as my own kid!
That's how those who rebel against Mama end up...
I don't think that this is
where you were supposed to die...
To hell with the Navy!
Really?! I thought it had increased
to 500 million not so long ago!
I'm not a kid! I'm a grownup!
Their king's gone to the Reverie.
All their able soldiers are accompanying him!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
150 million is lower than
your bounty two years ago!
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Well done, my brothers and sisters...
Wow! Thanks!
It's okay. It's okay, Sanji!
Is that possible?! Did you do something bad?!
An unguarded country is an
easy target for pirates!
See, you are a kid!
The Straw Hats have been wiped out!
Pedro made his own choice!
That wasn't fair, Shanks!
--Wouldn't that have increased it?
--Oh, that's right.
Don't blame yourself! Sanji!
Don't laugh!
Listen carefully!
That's how it should be! This is Mama's territory!
You-teia guys saved the Mokomo Dukedom
so we wanted to repay our debt!
I'm one of the Emperor of the
Sea Blackbeard's affiliates,
It's not so bad.
People won't come after you.
--We won't even let a bug get away!
--That serves you right, Straw Hat!
Nami-san, Luffy is our captain!
It could harm our prestige!
upon whom was bestowed the name "Peachbeard"!
PEACHBEARD - CAPTAIN OF THE PEACHBEARD PIRATES
BOUNTY: 52 MILLION BERRIES
Pardon us.
If it weren't for Pedro,
we'd all have died at that moment!
Remember my name!
Dammit! Why?!
We're mountain bandits.
But we ain't here to tear up the place.
Fear Blackbeard!
How are all the royal families?!
NAVY
Now, you guys, rip everything off of them
in Blackbeard's name!
Sell us some booze.
20 barrels oughta do.
No problems reported!
FLUFFY ISLAND
What about pirates?!
Mama! Mama!
So...
NEW MARINEFORD
I'm sorry. I just ran out of alcohol.
So far, 13 pirate groups
have attempted to kidnap...
Perospero-sama...
Hmm? That's odd.
...do you think you could just offer thanks?!
...royal family members, but we repelled them
before they approached the ships!
These pirates seem to be drinking something...
What is it, water?
Okay, give me your money!
Tell the patrol units to
stay alert at all times!
SAKAZUKI - ADMIRAL OF THE FLEET
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Get hold of yourself, Mama!
S-Stop...
My apologies.
Looks like we drank the whole place dry.
Yes, sir!
It's no use hiding!
We'll burn the whole town down!
I can't believe this...
Sorry! You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
I'm here to report, Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
Because this is how it's supposed to be!
She turned back to normal...
The Kingdom of Lulucia ship that was en route
Pudding made such an extraordinary cake...
Hey, come on! Let's get out of here!
to the Reverie has been attacked by pirates!
The king was unharmed
but Princess Comane has been kidnapped...
I know what kind of man he was.
I've never seen her with a look of bliss like that.
Lick.
What did I just tell you?!
Hey, catch that girl!
There's an eight million berry
bounty on my head, you know.
What are guards for?!
Stop right there!
One bottle ain't even enough for a bedtime drink!
Don't insult me!
Mama! You're our captain!
I need to inform you of the situation.
What do you have in your arms?
Check.
Now the floor's all wet!
Show me what you're holding so tightly!
First, Bege should still be around here...
RIKU DOLDO III - THE KING OF DRESSROSA
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Lick!
Oh, I'll do that!
ELIZABELLO II - THE KING
OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
This is...
It's no use thinking.
I'm happy...
Huh? Just milk?!
Psh! I thought that it was money...
Soul Pocus
She's not listening at all...
Grandfather-sama!
Soul Pocus
Oh well, I'll take it anyway.
CACAO ISLAND
--Hm? What's wrong, Rebecca?
--Look!
The words of soul
No... This is for the
children of the village...
Seems you like to clean.
Then maybe you'll find this more fulfilling.
ATTEMPTED ASSASSINATION OF BIG MOM
Have you read about Lucy?!
REBECCA - LADY-IN-WAITING OF DRESSROSA
Yes, I have.
Shut up!
Is that...?!
Oh, okay.
Not worth our time if they're out of booze.
With deep reluctance
Luffyland is doing great!
That's our boss!
Hm? Wait!
Let's go!
Why can't you just give this thing up?
Hey, that's not it!
The newspaper mentions us, too...
Later, wimps!
The ship is pulling away
on the tide with the wind
LEO - LEADER OF THE TONTA
CORPS, TONTATTA TRIBE
That's not the Straw Hats' ship!
Please give it back to me...
Folks, once we enter the Holyland,
don't talk about such things.
What?!
From the sea of the battle
I really need that milk...
That's the Sun Pirates' ship!
What? Why?
We're hugely indebted to him but
Bring us your money, too!
No way! It must've hit directly!
What? I don't have any...
Talk about lame, Boss!
the World Government and the
Navy see him differently.
Did they switch?!
He got you good!
I bet you have your Heavenly Tribute funds.
In that case, where did the Straw Hats go?!
You're right! He's a pirate!
Th-The Heavenly Tribute is what we have to pay
to the king and the Celestial Dragons...
Why are you laughing?!
Not only that but he's also coming to be considered
a very dangerous man now.
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
It's Cotton Candy Flurry!
We're scrimping and saving every day...
That means we're close to
the edge of the territory!
He's really something...
Oh yeah! I'll go show this to Viola-san!
Hurry up, Wadatsumi!
Carry it farther!
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
If I can't pay the Heavenly
Tribute, I'll be killed!
Let's do that!
you're not men - or pirates -
if you laugh after something like that!
What?! Your king sounds terrible!
It's going smoothly...
We'll make it out of Big
Mom's territory soon!
VIOLA - PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
I hope we can reach Mariejois
without a problem.
All right!
I can understand how you feel,
but he only spilled some booze on me.
Hey, guys, search!
They're hiding the Heavenly Tribute!
Yes.
Viola-san!
Mama came back!
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Are you sure?
Have you read about Lucy?!
This is the legendary ship
that Fisher Tiger made!
Whatever!
Yes.
Flower
They have money! Take all they've got!
Oh, okay...
--I'm sure!
--Okay!
I know it's not so easy to be them
It hasn't even been a month since he left Dressrosa
but he is becoming quite a figure.
Come on! Tell me where's your Tribute!
Hurry up! We don't have time!
Leave us alone... This town is poor...
But the flowers and the trees sing cheerfully
--Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
--Shut up!
Uh-huh.
P-Please don't take this money!
Let it go!
Wait, what're you eating?!
It's no mistake... Those are ships of
Dressrosa and Prodence Kingdom!
And they seduce us sweetly
Ow, ow, ow!
Somebody...
You didn't have to get hurt
if you'd just given it up!
No Navy guards!
Soul Pocus
That box! Did you eat what was in that box?!
Oh! I-I see Princess Viola!
Kill everyone who disobeys!
Y-Yeah...
She is as gorgeous as they say.
Spit it out! Right now! Every last bite!
It's a plot that the greedy Mama contrived
I'm begging you!
The girl she's with is also
a royal family member?
Please leave us alone!
What?! What?!
W-What're you doing, Shanks?!
If we kidnap them,
I wonder how much they'll pay us!
Shut up!
What do you think, Princess Comane?
Go, Morley...
What... was that?
He's gonna eat us!
Contact my daddy already!
He'll pay you as much as you want!
Who are you?
What you ate was the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Be patient.
The Gum-Gum Fruit is known as a Devil Fruit!
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
What the?!
Why is it shaking?
The fairy-tale prince and
Where are we?!
This is why I like royal families!
The beautiful princess
We're in Wadatsumi's mouth!
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
But you gotta wait a little.
We're greedy.
They're manipulated in a puppet show
where they're not attracted to each other
They'll never notice us because...
Let's run!
Eh?!
No way!
Is there something underground?!
You dumbass!
...we're hiding underwater!
--Sink them!
--Roger!
Even sweet nectar that draws us
with its flavor has a slyness
It's impossible to guard against a torpedo!
Dammit! Apologize!
How dare you make fun of Shanks and his crew!
They're in the water!
I wondered what it was
but that was the Giant Monk's hand!
What the?!
A giant trident?!
You're a lost cause, kid...
You can regret all this in the next life!
Chase the Giant Monk!
All ships! Come about 180 degrees!
Luffy!
Nothing in this world is
more fearful than sweetness
Please! Let him go!
I was wondering why the bar was empty...
Is it a Giant?
I won't let you get away! You damn Fish-Man!
One, two! One, two!
Captain-san!
One, two!
Looks like it's those mountain
bandits from before.
Hidden motives and misunderstandings
One, two!!
What happened?!
An enemy attack?!
Shanks!
--Get the cannons ready!
--Yes, sir!
Luffy! I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols?
A poorly performed play
at the risk of your life
A Giant emerged from the ground!
No! Don't worry!
Tropical...
Shut up!
I don't know why you're here,
but you'd best leave before you get hurt.
In a strange outfit!
...Torpedoes!
I'm glad that I made it. You're safe now!
What? Why is he wearing a miniskirt?
Any closer and he'll shoot your head off.
A-Are you a Navy soldier?
JUSTICE
Come on! Where are you looking?!
Wimp.
KOBY - CAPTAIN OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
I'm Koby, a captain of the Navy Headquarters!
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow your head off!
--Did it miss the target?!
--No way!
On our way there was candy
Why are you staring at me?!
Put your life on the line.
Are you that attracted to me?!
On our way back is a guillotine
Huh?!
We're gonna sink!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Why am I suddenly accused of something?!
What's this old man talking about?!
It's too hot!
Who won the big fight?
What the hell are you talking about?!
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
Just shoot! Shoot him to death!
You're parties from Dressrosa and Prodence.
You must be tired from your long journey.
What?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Stop it, boys!
Fish-Man Karate Hidden Technique!
There it is! Straw Hat's ship!
What just happened?
How did you get here?
Wada-kichi!
Vagabond Drill!
Shoot! Sink Straw Hat's ship!
Th-The Giants live underground?!
These bastards fight dirty!
I got here from a distant Navy ship.
I've never seen one before...
Dirty?
Cut the crap.
Who is he?
Don't be so mean!
Hang in there!
This ship was just targeted
from under the sea.
You think you're dealing
with saints or something?
Once Luffy and the others get out
of the territory, we can go, too!
Come on!
You're looking at...
Under the sea... You mean by a torpedo?!
How is it possible?!
He's pushing the ground around like clay!
Just go, you guys!
...pirates!
I'm glad they missed...
Don't be intimidated!
He must be a power-user!
Shut up!
You got nothing to do with this in the first place!
Straw Hat! I was a bad boy at the Fish-Man Island...
Yeah.
He's so strong...
Listen, bandits.
Helmeppo-san, how's it over there?
Now, what do you wanna do?
Whether I'm splattered with alcohol
or food or even spit on,
We caught the pirates!
I'm sorry!
You passive...
Hey, what happened to the Straw Hats?
...pieces of trash.
No words from our pursuit unit!
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
What? Trash?
I think they've lost them!
Look!
Intimidation Mega Monk!
What should we do?
HELMEPPO
LIEUTENANT COMMANDER OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Princess Comane from Lulucia is okay, too!
But...!
Idiot! Once they cross the border,
we won't be able to catch up!
No matter what the reason,
Excuse me!
Who are you... Who are you people?
You little...! Roast these jerks on a skewer!
I won't forgive them!
anyone who hurts my friends has to pay!
Of course, they'll get the
harshest punishment, princess!
Shanks...
Pudding, like always, make him love
you madly with your acting skills.
Anyway, what's wrong with your Color of Observation,
Koby?!
Has to pay, huh?! Lousy pirates!
But Boss Jimbei let me come along with him...
I-I thank him for that!
Kill them, men!
I didn't feel a torpedo anywhere at all.
Oh, my!
That's easily done, Mama!
Come on, wait a minute, Morley!
You're like a doll, Pudding.
I'll handle this. Should be easy enough.
A submarine...
That bastard...
What do you want?
A doll that I control.
You have to be careful with pirates these days...
That was close.
Outta my way! Sea Bonze!
I have a newly-invented weapon
but you went ahead!
You!
Mama... I'm not a doll...
So you're the famous Captain Koby!
Ouch!
Who are these people?!
What? From the Rocky Port Incident?!
Wadatsumi!
Don't get cocky, bandit.
Let's get married tomorrow.
Since Boss said that he wanted to
join the Straw Hats...
The incident was masterminded by Trafalgar Law,
one of the Worst Generation...
If you wanna fight us,
you better find yourself a warship or something.
No way...  Like all the others,
once you find out who I really am, you'll...
A murder of crows?!
We were determined!
You're the hero who protected the citizens
at that time.
You're my daughter but that creeps me out...
So strong!
Captain!
Dammit!
S-Someone is on the roof!
She's a monster!
Mama will kill everyone who wants to leave.
What?!
A smokescreen!
N-No, I'm not a hero!
"Let's get married!"
Luffy!
The crows are gathering together...
You sound exactly like him!
You're not just a daring guy
but also a fine young man!
Crap! I let my guard down! Luffy's gone!
So creepy!
Look! She's a freak!
Wow... This man must be strong...
Please stop!
Dammit! Let me go, you stupid ape!
I hope you die!
So what we can do is...
He doesn't even hold saving us
from the torpedo over our heads...
You want us to serve as Captain Jimbei's shield
and die?!
No one will love me.
You wish! You're the one who's gonna die!
How dare you harm the people
who don't fight back...
Thank you!
Oh, no...
Because I'm an ugly freak.
We can't all die here!
Someone has to survive and tell the story!
So long!
Oh! Luffy-san!
Like all the others,
once you find out who I really am...
Captain Peachbeard... Those four are...
I mean, it's Straw Hat Luffy!
The front-page article caught my eye.
Yeah, you're right.
...supposed to be scattered
around the world...
Somebody... Help...
Take a good look, Sanji...
at my creepy...
I won't blame you for running away!
Those who follow me, prepare yourselves for anything!
Do you wanna read it, Koby-san?
No, no. Well, I mean, you know...
They're the captains...
...of the Revolutionary Army!
...third eye!
W... W...
We won't let them get in the way of
Jimbei's new beginning!
"A great captain with 5,000 subordinates"...
What?!
What a beautiful eye!
"Destroyed Big Mom's castle"...
MORLEY - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
WESTERN FORCES
Hey, they're still staring at me.
"Took down the top officer
who is worth a billion"...
BELO BETTY - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
EASTERN FORCES
What?
Don't get panicky, scum!
We made up our minds!
"The fifth Emperor of the Sea"...
LINDBERGH - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
SOUTHERN FORCES
Let me use my new weapon!
Luffy-san's as cool as always!
KARASU - CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
NORTHERN FORCES
Get back, Wadatsumi!
We're here to put a stop to you.
He keeps moving forward!
All right! Let's start baking!
Koby-san?
The captains of...
...the Revolutionary Army...
Every time I see you in the newspaper,
I think of that day...
ON THE SEA OF THE NEW WORLD
Aladdin! You guys!
Shanks!
Go, Jimbei! Straw Hats!
I'm glad that you played my fiancée!
Get lost!
Oh, don't move, Luffy!
I'll have to wrap it all over again!
I slept great!
Sorry, sorry...
Pudding-chan!
Oh, yeah, Nami.
H-Hey, Sanji...
We celebrate your departure!
What?
Are you toying with us
even when you know we're pirates?!
I'm in your debt, Luffy.
Makino-san told me everything.
Isn't there anything about
the Revolutionary Army?
...san...
Man, I'm hungry! You got any food?
Could you do me a favor?!
You fought for us.
Let's see...
Listen when people are talking!
You damn kid!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
The Revolutionary Army...
Die!
"JUST ONE, FOR THE LAST TIME...
I WANNA ASK YOU A FAVOR!"
...is a mysterious organization
that works secretly to
But... Shanks...!
take down the World Government.
Let's go, guys!
Their goal is to free the
people who are suffering...
Your arm!
...under the World Government
headed by the Celestial Dragons.
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
What's the big idea?
I'm just glad you're alright.
--W-Who are you?!
--Me?
The leader of the Revolutionary Army...
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
...is Straw Hat Luffy's father,
That day, I got in a boat
on the outskirts of town to go fishing...
Monkey D. Dragon.
And...
...one of Luffy's two brothers,
Sabo, is working as the Chief of Staff
of the Revolutionary Army.
But it turned out the boat was
actually headed for a pirate ship.
You're leaving, then?
Yeah. It was a long stay,
but now we part ways.
It's been two years since...
When they were kids, Sabo
died in an incident...
In exchange for my life, I've
been forced to be a chore boy.
"THANK YOU."
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Well, yeah, but I won't ask
you to take me anymore!
That's what Luffy thought,
Man, you're dumb and stupid!
"GOODBYE..."
You're brutally honest...
but appearing in front of
him at Dressrosa was...
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
If you don't like it, then run away!
I-I can't! No way! No way!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
Just the thought of Alvida-sama finding me
frightens me and
Oh? Pudding-chan?!
I will, too!
makes my knees knock together!
You said that you wanted to ask me a favor...
Oh, you're a wimp, too?
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
Sabo!!
Shoot!
What is it?
Man, I hate you!
and I'm gonna find the greatest treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be...
Yeah... That's right...
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
...the King of the Pirates!
Thank you, Luffy!
If only I had the courage
to drift the ocean in a barrel,
I'm glad that you're alive!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
there's actually something
I want to do, too...
Those guys...
In that case, I'll leave...
Yeah?
Umm... What compelled you
to set out onto the sea, Luffy-san?
...this hat with you.
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
It seems like there isn't any article
about the Revolutionary Army.
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
Tropical Torment!
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
K-K-King of the Pirates?!
Okay...
According to the last issue,
I won't let you through!
their general headquarters that was veiled in mystery
for decades was destroyed...
Water Shot!
Ring, ring, ring...
Aladdin!
Big Bro Peros, come in!
Where's Mama now?!
Sabo...
Come bring it back to me someday.
Damn!
Montd'Or-sama!
We got a call from Cacao Island!
You were affiliated with Mama
but you kept betraying her!
Once you've become a great pirate.
Seems like there's a Territory Slug
at the border of the territory!
That's our promise, Luffy!
You fools don't deserve to live anymore!
It's too late!
There was a signal of a passing ship.
The Straw Hats' ship got out of the territory!
I guess we can start our top officers' meeting
without a problem,
Alright, I'm going now!
I'm happy to die!
But I'll be damned if I'm getting out of your way!
Dragon-san.
Yeah...
What did you say?!
We can't track them anymore!
It was the right decision
to relocate our general headquarters here.
The Straw Hats' ship sailed out of
the Totto Land territory!
Fish-Man Karate!
K-K-King of the Pirates?!
I was worried what would happen
when we lost Baltigo...
He's finally leaving, mayor.
I'm gonna miss him...
Four Thousand Brick Fist!
K... K...
Oh, there they are.
Did they get out?!
It brings dishonor to the village
to become a pirate.
K-King of the Pirates is the title given to the person
who obtains everything in this world!
Go back to your ships, Germa 66!
Mission accomplished!
What a nice day for setting sail!
You're finally here!
That's my husband!
That means seeking the great treasure of wealth,
fame, and power... the One Piece!
Here comes...
Heehaw!
I'll tear those damn Fish-Men limb from limb!
Roger that!
...our local Sea King!
Now, this is my country!
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM, PEACHY ISLAND
You don't know who you're messing with.
They're trying to fight us
with just those small numbers?
Roger!
No restraint is necessary, guys!
Look at this technique
I've been training for 10 years!
--Yup!
--Yup?!
Roger!
Pirates all over the world
are after that treasure!
Germa is withdrawing!
You can do as you like!
How idiotic!
Don't let them do that!
Gum-Gum...
Ivan-sama is right!
Me, too!
Catch them!
No way! No way, no way, no way!
Absolutely no way!
Keep firing at the water!
Barrage them with bombs!
...Pistol!
Where's our Chief of Staff?
There's no way you can stand at
the apex of this Great Pirate Era! No way! No way!
What? This is a crucial
time. Where did he go?
Don't worry.
Why did you hit me?
He's there...
I didn't wanna see you
lying down on your back, defeated.
Just because.
It's not about whether I can or not.
Don't back down!
Prove that you're a Sun Pirate!
What?
That will learn ya, stupid fish!
I'm gonna do it because I want to.
Let's start with finding a crew!
I've decided to be the King of the Pirates,
so if I die fighting for that,
Brulee.
I want at least 10 of them!
Why did you purposefully get up and fall on your back?
You were on your stomach first.
And the black flag!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
that's fine with me!
I wonder why...
Luffy...
Do you suppose I can do it, too?
But Brulee...
--If I'm prepared to die for it?
--Do what?
They say that I never lie down on my back
in my daily life...
I wonder what Luffy's doing right now...
Do you think even I could join the Navy?
Flooding is a sailing ship's weakness...
Bail the water out quickly!
His bounty has increased so much.
The Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
That's not true...
Hey, what are you reading?
Yeah, I know.
I've been watching you through mirrors.
Let me see!
The ship is getting heavy and slow...
Do you think I can do it?!
How should I know?
Repair the holes in the sails and catch the wind
at a proper angle,
No! I'll do it! If I'm gonna be a chore boy
for the rest of my life,
Luffy...
You've pretended to be...
then I'll break out of here
and advance as fast as you can!
Heehaw!
and catch even Alvida-sama... no, Alvida!
...some sort of perfect man
that no one'll mess with...
EMPORIO IVANKOV
A TOP OFFICER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
Straw boy is something!
It'll still take several hours
to get out of their territory!
Here you are!
...for us...
He sure is your son...
MONKEY D. DRAGON
LEADER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
--L-Luffy-san! Let's get out of here!
--Why?
Makino!
Mayor-san!
What are you doing, Jimbei?!
What are you trying to say?!
And...
I've been looking for you!
You saw how powerful her club is!
...I didn't know that Sanji
boy was Germa 66's prince!
Katakuri, if you hide that mouth,
you'll have friends.
Is something wrong?
In these waters, she's the most...
That fool is in the newspaper again!
He didn't mention it at all! How insolent!
I don't want any! This is me!
I'll just beat up those who laugh!
I'm the most what?!
Here! Look!
Luffy...
Th-Th-The...
Germa has been expelled from the World Government
because of that incident.
This is a huge deal!
A pelican eel!
Luffy!
The most ugly, cragged old hag ever!
I can't leave them behind!
There is a pelican eel!
Straw boy and Sanji boy...
Just as I expected,
I'm hungry!
I'll kick your asses!
What did you say?!
they're becoming the center of
attention in the Great Pirate Era!
I... I'm going to join the Navy!
And then I'm gonna beat up pirates!
INAZUMA - A TOP OFFICER
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
What's this?
Where did you get that?!
HACK - A SOLDIER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
The Straw Hats... I'm excited!
Do you even know what you're saying?!
Huh? It somehow got in my pocket.
Okay, I got it!
Oh my! Is it real?
I do! I'm gonna do what I want to do!
Anyway, the top officers are late.
KOALA - FISH-MAN KARATE ASSISTANT INSTRUCTOR
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
What is it?
--Oh, no!
--Hurry up!
Then we'll stay too!
Don't you remember that
Germa was using this to transform?!
--How did it happen?
--What is it?
I'm sure they're somewhere near by now...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna join the Navy...
I'll bring up the rear to cover you!
You're right...
And catch your lousy ass!
What's the matter?
Oh! I remember!
By the way, Sabo,
what have you been doing there?
--This is serious! Brulee is badly hurt!
--What?!
You damn pipsqueak!
I'm gonna transform with it!
If you're chased by that mother ship and the fleet now,
you'll never be able to get away!
Brulee!
Wait! I go first!
That's how Luffy-san and
I went out on a journey.
You kept looking and smiling at
Luffy-kun's article too much and
What... happened?
Sanji!
Let me bring up...
I'm gonna get rid of it!
got a cramp in your face, right?
I can't stand to watch the
Navy like this anymore! I...
It's nothing...
What?!
Are you stupid?!
...the rear!
Don't throw it away!
No, it's not nothing! Tell me!
What happened?!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
...want to be an honorable Navy soldier!
If you do, I'll go look
for it on the sea bottom!
This is Lindbergh!
Those who got beat by you
came for revenge, Katakuri!
That's impossible! You can't swim!
What's wrong? Everyone's waiting.
I'll pull it off and come back alive!
Is that so wrong?!
Luffy-san and I haven't known each
other long, but we are friends!
Is this Sabo? We're almost there.
It was in my pocket
so give it to me if you're gonna trash it!
Revenge?! On my sister?!
But there is trouble!
Mind if we're a bit late?
Why?! Why did she have to get hurt?!
No, let me have it! Please!
Right?
Yeah! We're gonna part ways,
but we'll always be friends!
No!
No. As long as you're okay.
But I wonder how it ended
up in Luffy-san's pocket.
Clank.
Oh, I'm so excited... All the top officers of
the Revolutionary Army will be here!
Pardon me!
Big Bro...
It must be Niji!
I guess he did it to annoy me.
It doesn't... hurt at all...
Is it true that you are pirates?!
I get to see Morley-sama!
You're fine just the way you are.
Yeah. We gained a member
and became a pirate group just now!
I love Betty-sama by far the most!
I don't wanna become stronger
via scientific technology, with this crap!
Sabo, we don't wanna waste any time.
Let's assemble now.
Don't forget, Jimbei!
Don't jump the gun, Sanji!
We appreciate that you saved our base
and this town from that tyrant!
No, fool! I...
Science is human power, too!
We better solidify our plan before they come.
I'm your captain now!
Why do you want it so bad?!
You're up, Chief of Staff.
If we put the Raid Suit on...
Brulee got hurt because of me...
However,
now that we know you are pirates,
Yeah...
At the upcoming Reverie, we'll finally...
in the name of the Navy,
we cannot stand by quietly!
I was too soft!
Here you come, Katakuri!
You will leave this town at once!
Maybe we can shoot beams!
Declare war....
SABO - CHIEF OF STAFF OF
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
Are you guys little kids?!
We've been expecting you.
Out of obligation,
we will refrain from contacting headquarters.
Genie-uine Rage Split!
Huh? What's that thing around your neck?!
...against the Celestial Dragons.
Franky is more than enough of
an unusual crewmember for us!
Well, guess we should go!
How could you cut my sister's face?!
So they're...
No! I want it!
Thanks for the food, lady!
What? Did you insult science?
...the captains of...
I won't stop the ship!
I'll never lower my guard again!
...the Revolutionary Army!
Nami-san!
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
There's no way I'd insult science!
Why are their four top officers here?!
I'll teach them what true fear is!
Aren't you part of their crew?
My Sorcerer's Climate Baton
is created from the science
Luffy!
Eh? I...
Gee, boys are so violent!
I'm...
of weather and Usopp's technology!
That's because they like you, dorky Giant.
Come on!
Brulee...
No way. That's gross!
Hold it!
How's Straw Hat doing?
I checked in with Sabo
so can we do it now, Betty?!
Well? Is he?!
It's great to be in the baton!
I know what he's done until now.
You can't stop me...
No doubt you'll think "That's good"
when you hear it.
Zeus! You really followed her! I can't believe
you chose appetite over loyalty to Big Mom!
No one's answering my question
and what is he mumbling about?!
Luffy-san! You wouldn't!
Thank you!
Can you see ahead into the future, too?
There was this reaaally fat pirate lady,
I think her name was Ahiruda.
Jimbei!
I got myself a powerful servant!
I won't forgive them!
N-Nami-san...
He just made it out of the territory...
Luffy-san!
I don't know why but he got pissed!
Don't die no matter what!
If they find out I was on a pirate ship,
I'll never get to join the Navy!
Zeus, just so you know...
I won't forgive him!
What are you gonna do, you pieces of trash?!
He gave you a hard time like this!
I've been serving her since
way before you started!
Man, she was an ugly hag!
Get killed or fight?!
But I get to live inside the baton
which she keeps with her all the time!
I was right.
And for two whole years, this guy was her--
Choose your own destiny!
Luffy and the others left the territory.
Let's retreat!
Please don't! Please don't!
Sanji-san... He's just
a mass of water vapor...
Is he still alive? That brat - Straw Hat?
Being a hero is someone else's problem?!
Retreat! Help the injured!
Germa! Let's go!
Y-Yes, he's sort of alive...
Now you've done it, you bastard!
But I just got a call saying
my brothers and sisters are fighting him at Cacao Island.
Maybe you can be a hero!
It's my turn!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
All right! Let's go!
Ouch!
He has nowhere to go!
Why isn't it working?!
Hey! You've gone too far. That's enough.
Germa 66! We'll withdraw!
If he's not completely dead, I'll go!
Hey! Stop crying!
I guess it only works when you do it!
Shoot, shoot!
Don't let them get away-nie!
Hurry up, Dark-spotted Candy Frog!
Do it for us!
It's very clear that you
guys aren't crewmates!
Shut up! I'm not Germa!
Be ready for it, Straw Hat...
Listen! "Germa 66"! "Vinsmoke"!
Now leave this town at once!
I'll take your soul, make vicious Homies out of it
and conquer you!
Don't ever say those names in front of me!
Damn Germa!
Thank you!
The townspeople picked up sticks!
Come on, that's hilarious!
On purpose...
--Please transform!
--L-Let go of me, you fools!
He did that on purpose...
Are you gonna fight us?!
Guys! The newspaper's here!
Their defense on the south side is poor.
Let's get through there!
For me...
Is there anything about us?
I don't know why but I'm inspired
and feel a surge of power!
He purposely got me riled up
to make me hit him...
Yes, sir!
Let's see...
A closeup of Luffy!
Let's drive the pirates out of here!
We escaped death...
What about Jimbei?
Do they mention what happened after we left?!
Life isn't all bad. Let's get away in peace.
We should fight and protect our country!
Um... Jimbei, Jimbei...
No, it doesn't say what happened after that.
That's right!
I'm worried about Germa-rero...
That's Betty's Pump-Pump Fruit power!
Please! Please!
Shut up!
It just says Luffy, Sanji, Jimbei, and Bege
attempted to assassinate Big Mom...
Let me join the Navy!
I'll gladly do chores or anything else!
Here she comes...
By waving her flag,
she can bring forth people's power from within!
What, Chiffon? You, too?
It says Luffy was the mastermind!
Betty is a flag-bearer of freedom!
If it means I can be a Navy soldier!
Yes, just a little bit.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
Mastermind?!
Now, advance!
Oh, a wanted poster!
Commander! I'm against the idea!
We'll see each other again, right, Nami?!
It's Mama!
I still don't fully trust this kid!
My bounty has increased
to 330 million berries!
Mama is here...
Mama is here!
There have been cases of Navy
soldiers being pirate spies!
Ha! I guess they don't know
it hurts when they get shot!
Really?!
Hm? How much was the Moss Head's?
We'll first need to conduct
a background check...
Don't get carried away!
I think Zoro-san's is...
I'm a man who will become a Navy officer!
...320 million berries!
Lind! Karasu! Back them up!
Jimbei...
Yes!
I guess they won't just let us go.
Got it!
Burn to death!
I beat you, damn Moss Head!
Take this!
Heat Beating!
Of course, we're ready for it!
It's just a number...
Cool Shooter!
I promised Luffy that I'd return alive.
Thank you!
I'll never forget all you've done for me!
They changed "only alive"
back to "dead or alive"!
--It's cold!
--My gun got frozen!
You bastards! Get out of here, pirates!
Let's all survive at any cost!
I've never heard of
a pirate being thanked by a Navy soldier.
We're at a critical stage!
Huh? What's the matter?
Don't back down! Cut them up!
My name...
Let's meet again sometime, Koby!
Yeah!
Take their weapons away!
Luffy-san...
All hands, salute!
It says "Vinsmoke Sanji"!
Are you okay, Aladdin?!
What?
Soul Pocus
Jimbei! You returned to us?!
I see... My bounty has increased
because of Germa's bad name!
GLOOM...
The crows took our swords!
No, I'm still a member of the Straw Hats.
Soul Pocus
Give them back!
In order to save my captain,
I stayed here!
Don't stop!
S-Sanji-san! Are you okay?!
Self-centered words
Fight against your fate!
Ugh! I see somebody's in a worse mood there!
Hey, Captain Koby! What are you doing?
Come back!
Oh, come on!
Go away!
When you're lured by a sweet cake
Yes, sir!
DOOM...
You're underestimating us!
L-Luffy!
What's the problem?!
If you say so, brother.
Thank you!
You must ask what they
want in exchange for it
What happened to them all of a sudden?
All of you must survive
Uh-huh.
Meanwhile...
You...!
Now, you'll soon arrive at New Marineford,
and send me off!
The milk!
Everyone is talking about the Reverie,
the meeting of the world's leaders...
so we'll escort you from here!
I know how strong you are
more than anyone!
There is no gain on our side
Give it back to me!
...that takes place in the Holyland of Mariejois
once every four years.
Let's use it to help the Straw Hats run!
Thank you.
Hey.
This is the Fish-Man Island
at 10,000 meters below the sea level.
What is it?
Do you like Lucy, Koby-kun?
Give them a treat or they'll
play a trick on you
You like Luffyland, right?
The Ryugu Kingdom.
No! H-He's our enemy!
They did it-jamon!
Yeah, right!
Jimbei finally joined Luffy-kun's group!
We won't tell anyone...
Let's have a chat.
L-Let go of me! I-I'm from the Navy!
--Let's get away!
--We'll make you pay for this!
I can't believe they picked a
fight with Big Mom together...
KING NEPTUNE - RYUGU KINGDOM
Nothing in this world is
more dreadful than sweetness
But you looked happy
when you were reading the paper.
Peachbeard... His bounty is 52 million...
RYUBOSHI                            MAMBOSHI
I wonder if they got away
on the same ship already.
--Th-That's because...
--Come on. Let's talk!
Jimbei and Straw Hat-fa-so-la-ti-do!
P-Please stop!
That's like nothing.
Oh, Luffyland is in this article here, too!
FUKABOSHI
He's just a crappy pirate who could
only target a country that was weak.
I think they did. It says Big
Mom is angry in the article.
Those bastards!
What?!
So you like him as we thought!
It's a maelstrom!
Then this country needs to be protected
by the Straw Hats now-jamon!
Blackbeard-sama will come after you...
Soul Pocus
I'm sorry but he doesn't
care about his subordinates.
What's going on?!
The selfish...
Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Why was this fool who screwed
up my important SMILE trade...
...Mama
Come on, boy! Shut up already!
KAIDO, KING OF THE BEASTS
ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
Shirahoshi!
PRINCESS SHIRAHOSHI
...at that old bag's place?!
I'll go to the Reverie with you!
Hey, you cowardly, weak and foolish people!
Brook! Go at full speed
and get as far as you can!
--Would you give me your lifespan?
--Or die?
If I don't, Luffy-sama
will call me weak again!
Understood!
If you turn him in to the World Government,
you'll get the bounty.
Soul Pocus
He won?!
I was waiting for you to say that!
That'll be 52 million berries.
When a Fish-Man gets serious,
it'll change the ocean current!
It's the queen's...
Huh?! When did I lose?! To who?!
Alright, come with us!
And that's...
...song
...all yours!
Okay!
--Oh my!
--The sea is...
I'm sure he wrote this article, Mama!
However, more so than the unstarted council
the news that Luffy, the young pirate,
I want you to have this, too.
Yeah... I'll teach you
a lesson, Morgans... No!
Life or dead?
The Revolutionary Army's contact information.
The current that the Fish-Men generated
is taking us away!
showed his teeth to Big
Mom, the Emperor of the Sea
I'll pay you back...
Shouldering the hopes of the Sun Pirates, Germa 66,
and those who lost their lives,
who has been reigning for decades,
CHARLOTTE LINLIN
BIG MOM, ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
You did great...
Jimbei...
Straw Hat!
has excited the world.
What?
This is what the article says.
Call us any time...
Emperor?
the Straw Hats finally made it out of
Emperor of the Sea Big Mom's territory.
MARSHALL D. TEECH
BLACKBEARD, ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
"One source says that Straw Hat Luffy...
It's too soon for you to be called that...
We'll never turn our back on
the weak who stand up.
Straw Hat Luffy is sailing away with Jimbei in the rear!
...already took seven powerful pirate groups
under his umbrella,
Our fleet is tied down completely
and has more than 5,000 subordinates
which makes him a great captain.
and we'll lose their ship soon!
RED-HAIRED SHANKS
ONE OF THE FOUR EMPERORS OF THE SEA
He is not only a sworn brother of Ace but
also of Sabo, the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army,
I think... I'll see you soon...
Hey...
Yeah! Go, Straw Hat!
Why are you supporting him?
Can I make you a meal?
which has been making waves.
B-Belo Betty-sama!
Because Straw Hat is one of the candidates.
Luffy!
A meal?
He instantly compelled
the evil army - Germa 66,
Candidates for what?
Stussy... You know about the Worst Generation,
don't you?
the Sun Pirates, and the Firetank
Pirates to submission...
Food!
Th-Thank you very much,
everyone of the Revolutionary Army!
Sanji's cooking!
I'm actually famished!
...through his uncommon personal magnetism
and leadership.
So it got lower.
We can't do anything about it...
I'm starving!
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law.
He has brains which enabled him
to destroy the queen's castle with a well-calculated strategy.
Cheer up, Luffy... I'll help you.
Let's work hard again.
It's safe, free, and delicious!
"Magician" Basil Hawkins.
Sanji's cooking!
Do you want me to make you something?
Did something happen while I was gone?
He is strong enough to take down
the top officers who are worth 800 million and a billion.
"Red Flag" X. Drake.
Hey, what are we meeting up for this time?
Uh-huh...
"Roar of the Sea" Scratchmen Apoo.
We'll pick a fight with
the Celestial Dragons.
It's not too much to say that
Straw Hat Luffy won the battle!"
At the same time, in the East Blue...
NAVY
Oh, that's great! I can't wait!
Capone "Gang" Bege.
Isn't my meal ready yet?!
And this is how the article concluded.
Wait a minute...
Hey, come on!
Oh, and Karasu!
"Glutton" Jewelry Bonney.
BARATIE, THE SEA RESTAURANT
Owner Zeff! Let's kick them out!
Turn on your loudspeaker switch.
"The fifth Emperor of the Sea emerges!"
Why do we have to serve them food?
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
They're our enemies!
Look...
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
I forgot...
I'll cook for them so just clam up!
100 thousand, 1 million, 10 million...
Bring it to me already!
Cut the "fifth Emperor" crap!
It's two days to go until the Reverie.
"Murder Machine" Killer.
100 million...
They're pushing their luck!
Those damn evil pirates
can just mess around...
SAKAZUKI - ADMIRAL OF THE FLEET
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
All the different intentions across the world
start swirling around...
Food! Food! Food! Food!
"Blackbeard" Marshall D. Teach.
Your bounty...
...saying Four Emperors or Five Emperors...
And...
Alright, alright.
Okay, roger.
"Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy.
As long as I am the Admiral of the Fleet,
People always become hungry.
...is 1.5 billion berries!
Clank.
I got a call, Sabo-kun.
I won't let them have their way!
This I know.
Everyone will be here soon.
If they're your enemies or not,
everyone gets hungry.
Whaaat?!
From among those who are called
the Worst Generation...
Okay...
Now, dig in!
Let's go...
The rest of the world is heading
for the Reverie and the Straw Hats
If there's someone who's
hungry, I'll feed them.
a new King of the Pirates will soon be born!
...to drag down the Celestial Dragons.
are on their way to the Land of Wano.
Then we'll talk!
Luffy took on the Emperor
of the Sea - Big Mom.
Jimbei, Germa 66, and Pudding. Each of them tries to
clear the way for the Straw Hats at the risk of their lives.
Hearing that Luffy was titled
the fifth Emperor of the Sea,
The mysterious individuals who appear
when cries echo across the ocean.
His exploits at Impel Down
and during the Paramount War,
the four other Emperors
start moving into gear.
The news instantly spreads across the world
and surprises people in a big way.
have earned Monkey D. Luffy
quite a name in the world!
They're the formidable captains of
the Revolutionary Army that escaped death!
Meanwhile, in a moment of crisis
for the Straw Hats' sworn allies
Inheriting the will of Whitebeard
and his brother Ace,
who are making their way to the Reverie,
As voices echo, singing over the sea of combatants,
the Sunny leaves the battleground of the Whole Cake Island!
Luffy who once wanted to be like Shanks
Luffy has now become a hero of the age and
Luffy’s close friend Koby
who he once adventured
Led by Dragon and Sabo,
they finally start to act to
the Navy's new Admiral of the Fleet, Sakazuki,
finally shows his teeth!
with
and with whom he shares a serious pledge shows up like a hero!
and sailed out to sea now
takes a new title as a pirate!
bring down the Celestial Dragons!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Parting Time! Pudding's Last Wish!"
"The World is Stunned! The Fifth
Emperor of the Sea Emerges!"
"Going into Action!
The Implacable New Admiral of the Fleet - Sakazuki!"
"To the Reverie! The Straw Hats'
Sworn Allies Come Together!"
"Sabo Goes into Action!
All the Captains of the Revolutionary Army Appear!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!