Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
After defeating Katakuri and meeting up with Sanji,
Luffy hurries to escape from the Whole Cake Island!
At Fluffy Island, Big Mom finally comes to her senses
after eating the wedding cake.
It's so delicious... that I could die!
The sweetness is unbelievable!
This is it!
Wedding cake!
Totto Land has been saved!
And the fleeing Sunny was relentlessly attacked
by the Big Mom Pirates.
It was delicious.
Thank you for the cake!
"The Man of Humanity and Justice!
Jimbei, a Desperate Massive Ocean Current"
The end was too easy...
That's how those who rebel against Mama end up...
SWEET CITY, WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Well done, my brothers and sisters...
The Straw Hats have been wiped out!
That's how it should be! This is Mama's territory!
--We won't even let a bug get away!
--That serves you right, Straw Hat!
FLUFFY ISLAND
Mama! Mama!
Perospero-sama...
Get hold of yourself, Mama!
I can't believe this...
She turned back to normal...
Pudding made such an extraordinary cake...
I've never seen her with a look of bliss like that.
Lick.
Mama! You're our captain!
I need to inform you of the situation.
First, Bege should still be around here...
Lick!
I'm happy...
She's not listening at all...
CACAO ISLAND
Is that...?!
Hm? Wait!
Hey, that's not it!
That's not the Straw Hats' ship!
What?!
That's the Sun Pirates' ship!
No way! It must've hit directly!
Did they switch?!
In that case, where did the Straw Hats go?!
Hurry up, Wadatsumi!
Carry it farther!
Are you sure?
This is the legendary ship
that Fisher Tiger made!
--I'm sure!
--Okay!
Hurry up! We don't have time!
Ow, ow, ow!
What?! What?!
He's gonna eat us!
Be patient.
What the?!
Where are we?!
We're in Wadatsumi's mouth!
Let's run!
They're in the water!
I wondered what it was
but that was the Giant Monk's hand!
Chase the Giant Monk!
All ships! Come about 180 degrees!
I won't let you get away! You damn Fish-Man!
Tropical...
...Torpedoes!
It's too hot!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
There it is! Straw Hat's ship!
Wada-kichi!
Shoot! Sink Straw Hat's ship!
Just go, you guys!
Straw Hat! I was a bad boy at the Fish-Man Island...
I'm sorry!
Intimidation Mega Monk!
But Boss Jimbei let me come along with him...
I-I thank him for that!
That bastard...
Outta my way! Sea Bonze!
Ouch!
Wadatsumi!
Since Boss said that he wanted to
join the Straw Hats...
We were determined!
Mama will kill everyone who wants to leave.
So what we can do is...
You want us to serve as Captain Jimbei's shield
and die?!
We can't all die here!
Someone has to survive and tell the story!
Yeah, you're right.
I won't blame you for running away!
Those who follow me, prepare yourselves for anything!
We won't let them get in the way of
Jimbei's new beginning!
We made up our minds!
Get back, Wadatsumi!
Aladdin! You guys!
Go, Jimbei! Straw Hats!
We celebrate your departure!
Let's go, guys!
Shoot!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Those guys...
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat!
Tropical Torment!
I won't let you through!
Water Shot!
Aladdin!
You were affiliated with Mama
but you kept betraying her!
You fools don't deserve to live anymore!
I'm happy to die!
But I'll be damned if I'm getting out of your way!
Fish-Man Karate!
Four Thousand Brick Fist!
That's my husband!
I'll tear those damn Fish-Men limb from limb!
They're trying to fight us
with just those small numbers?
How idiotic!
Keep firing at the water!
Barrage them with bombs!
Don't back down!
Prove that you're a Sun Pirate!
Luffy...
Flooding is a sailing ship's weakness...
Bail the water out quickly!
The ship is getting heavy and slow...
Repair the holes in the sails and catch the wind
at a proper angle,
and advance as fast as you can!
It'll still take several hours
to get out of their territory!
What are you doing, Jimbei?!
What are you trying to say?!
Luffy...
I can't leave them behind!
Okay, I got it!
Then we'll stay too!
I'll bring up the rear to cover you!
If you're chased by that mother ship and the fleet now,
you'll never be able to get away!
Let me bring up...
...the rear!
I'll pull it off and come back alive!
Don't forget, Jimbei!
I'm your captain now!
Genie-uine Rage Split!
I won't stop the ship!
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
Luffy!
Thank you!
Jimbei!
Don't die no matter what!
Is he still alive? That brat - Straw Hat?
Y-Yes, he's sort of alive...
But I just got a call saying
my brothers and sisters are fighting him at Cacao Island.
He has nowhere to go!
If he's not completely dead, I'll go!
Hurry up, Dark-spotted Candy Frog!
Be ready for it, Straw Hat...
I'll take your soul, make vicious Homies out of it
and conquer you!
We escaped death...
Life isn't all bad. Let's get away in peace.
I'm worried about Germa-rero...
Shut up!
What, Chiffon? You, too?
Yes, just a little bit.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
We'll see each other again, right, Nami?!
Burn to death!
Heat Beating!
Are you okay, Aladdin?!
Jimbei! You returned to us?!
No, I'm still a member of the Straw Hats.
In order to save my captain,
I stayed here!
Oh, come on!
You're underestimating us!
If you say so, brother.
All of you must survive
and send me off!
I know how strong you are
more than anyone!
Let's use it to help the Straw Hats run!
Those bastards!
It's a maelstrom!
Brook! Go at full speed
and get as far as you can!
Understood!
When a Fish-Man gets serious,
it'll change the ocean current!
--Oh my!
--The sea is...
The current that the Fish-Men generated
is taking us away!
Jimbei...
Straw Hat Luffy is sailing away with Jimbei in the rear!
Our fleet is tied down completely
and we'll lose their ship soon!
Yeah! Go, Straw Hat!
Why are you supporting him?
Because Straw Hat is one of the candidates.
Candidates for what?
Stussy... You know about the Worst Generation,
don't you?
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law.
"Magician" Basil Hawkins.
"Red Flag" X. Drake.
"Roar of the Sea" Scratchmen Apoo.
Capone "Gang" Bege.
"Glutton" Jewelry Bonney.
"Mad Monk" Urouge.
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
"Murder Machine" Killer.
"Blackbeard" Marshall D. Teach.
And...
"Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy.
This I know.
From among those who are called
the Worst Generation...
a new King of the Pirates will soon be born!
Jimbei, Germa 66, and Pudding. Each of them tries to
clear the way for the Straw Hats at the risk of their lives.
As voices echo, singing over the sea of combatants,
the Sunny leaves the battleground of the Whole Cake Island!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Parting Time! Pudding's Last Wish!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!