Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
"The World is Stunned!
The Fifth Emperor of the Sea Emerges!"
Hey, Luffy! What are you trying to do?!
I'm really serious!
I'm so pissed!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
Oh, it didn't hurt at all!
That's a lie! Don't do such a stupid thing!
I'm not scared of getting hurt!
Take me on your next voyage, Shanks!
I wanna be a pirate, too!
As if you could ever be a pirate!
Why not?!
Luffy. Just being a good swimmer
doesn't mean you'd make a good pirate.
I'm good at fighting, too!
My punches are like pistols!
Oh, really?
What's that supposed to mean?!
He means you're too much of a kid, Luffy!
Seriously, you're as old as my own kid!
I'm not a kid! I'm a grownup!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
Wow! Thanks!
See, you are a kid!
That wasn't fair, Shanks!
Don't laugh!
Pardon us.
We're mountain bandits.
But we ain't here to tear up the place.
Sell us some booze.
20 barrels oughta do.
I'm sorry. I just ran out of alcohol.
Hmm? That's odd.
These pirates seem to be drinking something...
What is it, water?
My apologies.
Looks like we drank the whole place dry.
Sorry! You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
There's an eight million berry
bounty on my head, you know.
One bottle ain't even enough for a bedtime drink!
Don't insult me!
Now the floor's all wet!
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Oh, I'll do that!
Seems you like to clean.
Then maybe you'll find this more fulfilling.
Not worth our time if they're out of booze.
Let's go!
Later, wimps!
Talk about lame, Boss!
He got you good!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
you're not men - or pirates -
if you laugh after something like that!
I can understand how you feel,
but he only spilled some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Whatever!
--Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
--Shut up!
Wait, what're you eating?!
That box! Did you eat what was in that box?!
Y-Yeah...
Spit it out! Right now! Every last bite!
W-What're you doing, Shanks?!
What... was that?
What you ate was the Gum-Gum Fruit!
The Gum-Gum Fruit is known as a Devil Fruit!
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Eh?!
No way!
You dumbass!
Dammit! Apologize!
How dare you make fun of Shanks and his crew!
You're a lost cause, kid...
You can regret all this in the next life!
Luffy!
Please! Let him go!
I was wondering why the bar was empty...
Captain-san!
Looks like it's those mountain
bandits from before.
Shanks!
Luffy! I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols?
Shut up!
I don't know why you're here,
but you'd best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and he'll shoot your head off.
Wimp.
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow your head off!
Put your life on the line.
Huh?!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
What the hell are you talking about?!
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
These bastards fight dirty!
Dirty?
Cut the crap.
You think you're dealing
with saints or something?
You're looking at...
...pirates!
Shut up!
You got nothing to do with this in the first place!
Listen, bandits.
Whether I'm splattered with alcohol
or food or even spit on,
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
But...!
No matter what the reason,
anyone who hurts my friends has to pay!
Shanks...
Has to pay, huh?! Lousy pirates!
Kill them, men!
I'll handle this. Should be easy enough.
Don't get cocky, bandit.
If you wanna fight us,
you better find yourself a warship or something.
So strong!
Dammit!
A smokescreen!
Luffy!
Crap! I let my guard down! Luffy's gone!
Dammit! Let me go, you stupid ape!
I hope you die!
You wish! You're the one who's gonna die!
So long!
Somebody... Help...
Shanks!
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy.
Makino-san told me everything.
You fought for us.
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're alright.
You're leaving, then?
Yeah. It was a long stay,
but now we part ways.
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Well, yeah, but I won't ask
you to take me anymore!
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will, too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the greatest treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be...
...the King of the Pirates!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case, I'll leave...
...this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Come bring it back to me someday.
Once you've become a great pirate.
That's our promise, Luffy!
Alright, I'm going now!
He's finally leaving, mayor.
I'm gonna miss him...
It brings dishonor to the village
to become a pirate.
What a nice day for setting sail!
Here comes...
...our local Sea King!
You don't know who you're messing with.
Look at this technique
I've been training for 10 years!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
That will learn ya, stupid fish!
Let's start with finding a crew!
I want at least 10 of them!
And the black flag!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I wonder what Luffy's doing right now...
Here you are!
Makino!
Mayor-san!
I've been looking for you!
Is something wrong?
That fool is in the newspaper again!
Here! Look!
This is a huge deal!
Luffy!
I'm hungry!
What's this?
Where did you get that?!
Huh? It somehow got in my pocket.
Oh my! Is it real?
What is it?
Don't you remember that
Germa was using this to transform?!
Oh! I remember!
I'm gonna transform with it!
Wait! I go first!
Sanji!
I'm gonna get rid of it!
What?!
Don't throw it away!
If you do, I'll go look
for it on the sea bottom!
That's impossible! You can't swim!
It was in my pocket
so give it to me if you're gonna trash it!
No, let me have it! Please!
No!
But I wonder how it ended
up in Luffy-san's pocket.
It must be Niji!
I guess he did it to annoy me.
I don't wanna become stronger
via scientific technology, with this crap!
Don't jump the gun, Sanji!
Science is human power, too!
Why do you want it so bad?!
If we put the Raid Suit on...
Maybe we can shoot beams!
Are you guys little kids?!
Franky is more than enough of
an unusual crewmember for us!
No! I want it!
What? Did you insult science?
Nami-san!
There's no way I'd insult science!
My Sorcerer's Climate Baton
is created from the science
of weather and Usopp's technology!
Come on!
It's great to be in the baton!
Zeus! You really followed her! I can't believe
you chose appetite over loyalty to Big Mom!
I got myself a powerful servant!
N-Nami-san...
Zeus, just so you know...
I've been serving her since
way before you started!
But I get to live inside the baton
which she keeps with her all the time!
Sanji-san... He's just
a mass of water vapor...
Germa! Let's go!
It's my turn!
All right! Let's go!
Why isn't it working?!
Hey! Stop crying!
I guess it only works when you do it!
Do it for us!
Shut up! I'm not Germa!
Listen! "Germa 66"! "Vinsmoke"!
Don't ever say those names in front of me!
Thank you!
--Please transform!
--L-Let go of me, you fools!
Guys! The newspaper's here!
Is there anything about us?
Let's see...
A closeup of Luffy!
What about Jimbei?
Do they mention what happened after we left?!
Um... Jimbei, Jimbei...
No, it doesn't say what happened after that.
It just says Luffy, Sanji, Jimbei, and Bege
attempted to assassinate Big Mom...
It says Luffy was the mastermind!
Mastermind?!
Oh, a wanted poster!
My bounty has increased
to 330 million berries!
Really?!
Hm? How much was the Moss Head's?
I think Zoro-san's is...
...320 million berries!
Yes!
I beat you, damn Moss Head!
It's just a number...
They changed "only alive"
back to "dead or alive"!
Huh? What's the matter?
My name...
It says "Vinsmoke Sanji"!
I see... My bounty has increased
because of Germa's bad name!
GLOOM...
S-Sanji-san! Are you okay?!
Ugh! I see somebody's in a worse mood there!
DOOM...
L-Luffy!
What's the problem?!
Meanwhile...
Everyone is talking about the Reverie,
the meeting of the world's leaders...
...that takes place in the Holyland of Mariejois
once every four years.
This is the Fish-Man Island
at 10,000 meters below the sea level.
The Ryugu Kingdom.
They did it-jamon!
Jimbei finally joined Luffy-kun's group!
I can't believe they picked a
fight with Big Mom together...
KING NEPTUNE - RYUGU KINGDOM
RYUBOSHI                            MAMBOSHI
I wonder if they got away
on the same ship already.
Jimbei and Straw Hat-fa-so-la-ti-do!
FUKABOSHI
I think they did. It says Big
Mom is angry in the article.
Then this country needs to be protected
by the Straw Hats now-jamon!
Father-sama! Brother-sama!
Shirahoshi!
PRINCESS SHIRAHOSHI
I'll go to the Reverie with you!
If I don't, Luffy-sama
will call me weak again!
I was waiting for you to say that!
Alright, come with us!
Okay!
However, more so than the unstarted council
the news that Luffy, the young pirate,
showed his teeth to Big
Mom, the Emperor of the Sea
who has been reigning for decades,
has excited the world.
This is what the article says.
"One source says that Straw Hat Luffy...
...already took seven powerful pirate groups
under his umbrella,
and has more than 5,000 subordinates
which makes him a great captain.
He is not only a sworn brother of Ace but
also of Sabo, the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army,
which has been making waves.
He instantly compelled
the evil army - Germa 66,
the Sun Pirates, and the Firetank
Pirates to submission...
...through his uncommon personal magnetism
and leadership.
He has brains which enabled him
to destroy the queen's castle with a well-calculated strategy.
He is strong enough to take down
the top officers who are worth 800 million and a billion.
It's not too much to say that
Straw Hat Luffy won the battle!"
NAVY
And this is how the article concluded.
"The fifth Emperor of the Sea emerges!"
Cut the "fifth Emperor" crap!
Those damn evil pirates
can just mess around...
SAKAZUKI - ADMIRAL OF THE FLEET
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
...saying Four Emperors or Five Emperors...
As long as I am the Admiral of the Fleet,
I won't let them have their way!
Hearing that Luffy was titled
the fifth Emperor of the Sea,
the four other Emperors
start moving into gear.
Meanwhile, in a moment of crisis
for the Straw Hats' sworn allies
who are making their way to the Reverie,
Luffy’s close friend Koby
who he once adventured
with
and with whom he shares a serious pledge shows up like a hero!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the Reverie! The Straw Hats'
Sworn Allies Come Together!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!