Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
The Great Pirate Era
a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
is experiencing a groundswell beyond
the World Government's expectation.
is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"In the Dark Recesses of the Holyland!
A Mysterious Giant Straw Hat!"
"One Step Forward for Her Dream!
Shirahoshi Goes Out in the Sun!"
"I Miss Him!
Vivi and Rebecca's Sentiments!"
"The Paramount War!
The Inherited Will of the King of the Pirates!"
"Going into Action!
The Implacable New Admiral of the Fleet - Sakazuki!"
Shirahoshi and the others
who are headed to Mariejois
They say he's the fifth Emperor of the Sea!
where the World Conference
Reverie will take place,
I'm amazed!
are riding the Bondola
which smoothly ascends the Red Line.
This is the Navy Headquarters led by
the new Admiral of the Fleet, Sakazuki.
Hey, Luffy-san ate a lot, didn't he?
Eventually, the Bondola arrives
at the top of the Red Line.
New Marineford.
I told you to get out...
Uh-huh!
He had an unbelievable appetite in Dressrosa!
Two years ago, in the Paramount War between
This is going to be another problem for us.
Thank you for riding with us.
Please watch your step.
the Navy Headquarters and
the Whitebeard Pirates,
He did in the Ryugu Palace, too.
I'll sink every last one of these pirates.
--They're having fun.
--They really are...
the Navy triumphed.
How beautiful she is!
However, Marineford became a battleground
and was devastated.
It's a good thing that those who will lead
Fire! More than I imagined...
My goal hasn't changed a bit after two years!
their countries
in the future get along.
Merfolk!
It was long renowned as
the home of "justice,"
Should we do a feature story on her,
President Morgans?!
You've left the suitable climate for those bubbles
so use these reinforced ones...
Anyway, it's a strange connection.
but to prepare for the
intensifying Pirate Era, the
Yes, we have to thank
Straw Hat and the others.
The public execution of Ace
two years ago...
Thanks!
Princess Shirahoshi!
World Government built an even
greater impregnable fortress.
President Morgans?
Hey! Aren't you Rebecca from Dressrosa?!
That day, from the moment
Straw Hat fell out of the sky,
Wow, it's huge!
Oh, no! He's totally captivated by her!
The new fort of "justice" that's located
at the entrance of the New World...
Guests will climb the large,
long staircase from there
Mermaid Princess-sama!
Oh, I know him!
the times started to change in a big way.
That's New Marineford.
NAVY
until they reach the world's highest and biggest continent
located at the center of the world.
It's me - Sai!
SAI - 13TH LEADER OF THE HAPPOSUI ARMY
Garp, Shirahoshi is very popular-jamon!
I didn't expect to see you again so soon!
Even on land, word is spreading that
The Fish-Man Island's Mermaid Princess...
Fujitora showed up at Mariejois?!
--How've you been?!
--I've been doing fine!
Ace!
Y-Yes, sir!
He's a member of the Happosui Army of Kano...
Somebody, carry me on their back!
From the era of Whitebeard...
I told him that
he can't set foot in any Navy base...
...is as beautiful as
Pirate Empress Hancock!
I heard that Chin Jao
stepped down as leader...
We're almost there, King Stelly.
....to something totally new!
...until he brings Straw Hat and Law's heads!
He is the new leader.
She's so pretty. I'm sure she surpasses
everyone's expectations!
He can't just claim to have forgotten what I said to him
in Dressrosa!
Sai!
And she's huge!
Oh, brother! You're here, too, Leo!
Luffy!!
Oh, I'm scared.
How dare he come back! That fool!
I'm a secret bodyguard!
This is where the descendants of
the creators of the world reside.
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
You're so reliable!
L-Luffy-sama's grandfather-sama!
Y-Yes, we all know what you told him...
We're here for you!
He is, isn't he?
The name of this magnificent place is...
Is he your friend?
Is that what they call a forest on land?!
Then why didn't you send him away?!
Garp! It's your family again!
We exchanged cups of sake
with Luffyland together!
Well... he was perfectly prepared
with theoretical arguments and
The Holyland of Mariejois.
Luffy!
We're both his underlings!
No, that's a tree.
we couldn't combat his wit...
This is where the Celestial Dragons are...
You came here to rescue your brother?
This is not a Navy base...
Hey, Garp the hero!
Well well, Princess Vivi!
I wanna live here!
Yeah.
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
What a beautiful place!
Is that green area a forest?
Wapol!
That's just a quibble!
WAPOL - KING OF THE EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
Is he a witty monk or something?!
You know who I am, don't you?
You fool!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
It's man-made but yes.
KINDERELLA - QUEEN OF THE
EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
So this is... Mariejois!
No, you stupid brat! Get out of my way!
Why are you here?!
Oh?
"Stupid brat"?! I must've heard wrong!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
Isn't it a difficult job?
The castle's still quite far away...
--H-He's competing...
--...With Whitebeard!
It's strange, right?
Yes, I was sent flying!
Yes, Stelly!
Maybe that's not not-it!
Fleet Admiral...
S-Sengoku-san!
Please come this way.
By Straw Hat Luffy, to a far off distant sea!
How rude!
I'm Stelly, king of the Goa
Kingdom where you come from!
Shut up, you semi-retired has-been!
Gum-Gum...
But I'm back!
...Bazooka!
KING STELLY OF THE GOA KINGDOM IN THE EAST BLUE
(SABO'S ADOPTED BROTHER)
Shirahoshi-sama and family,
please use these handles!
Do you wanna know how my darling came back?
Get outta my way!
And since you're a citizen,
you're one of my subjects!
Who else has gone to Mariejois?!
A-Admiral Ryokugyu-san has!
Stay away, Luffy!
Is he Luffy-sama's friend, too?
Remember that!
Ryokugyu, huh?
No, he's our enemy, Shirahoshi!
Is it an earthquake?!
If I'm correct, Stelly is your
adopted brother, right, Sabo?
Contact him immediately!
I beg you, Luffy!
It's started moving!
Yes, sir! What should I tell him?!
I don't want you to share my fate!
Is the humorless King Cobra doing okay?
I'm gonna die! Save me!
It's obvious!
Tell him to turn Fujitora away if he sees him!
Well, I saw him looking not so well earlier
so that's just a bit of sarcasm!
This is all my fault!
This is a Travelator.
It allows the ground to move.
Stelly was adopted by Sabo's noble parents.
All of you, go!
Y-Yes, sir!
I'm...
Father, shall we take a normal walkway?
Shirahoshi, you wanna see the forest, right?
Oh, honey!
...your brother!
With that as his first foothold,
he looked enviously to connect with royalty
You're as entertaining as the universe!
My golddigging self laughs!
What a bunch of idiots!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
Fukaboshi...
and married Princess Isntoinette.
The scenery is beautiful!
Let's take our time!
Why don't you go back to your post, too?
Marco, we can't let that kid die.
Later, the king and prince of the Goa Kingdom
mysteriously died
Wapol!
Oh, that sounds good, Brother-sama!
It's strange, isn't it?
That Straw Hat's bounty...
Cut the crap!
Father-sama, let's do so!
Alright.
and several months ago,
Stelly became the king.
I can't believe you became a king again...
No problem, of course!
DALTON - KING OF THE SAKURA KINGDOM
...went up to 1.5 billion.
We'll escort you!
So there's another poor country.
The Goa Kingdom...
I bet they're afraid of modern conveniences!
Luffy!
The Gray Terminal in that country is
the place we first met, right, Luffy?
The Government must be in decline!
DR. KUREHA - A DOCTOR OF THE SAKURA KINGDOM
That stupid brat...
Stupid fish!
Straw Hat Luffy who dealt an
immense blow to Impel Down,
Why do they wanna affiliate
with this fool again?!
I should've killed him somehow at that time!
Let's procure one for our kingdom!
The Troublator! It's so useful!
came face-to-face with Whitebeard.
GOA KINGDOM
Dalton! The old witch hag!
You're still alive?!
--It's a "Travelator."
--You can call it that, too!
GRAY TERMINAL
--Hm? Indeed - how do I stay so young?
--I didn't ask that!
At that moment, he became an enemy
who we should have never let loose...
What's this?
Dalton-san! Dr. Kureha!
It's nice to see you again!
At once!
I feel something isn't right...
Whoa! You got a lot!
Way more than I did!
Hi, Vivi-chan.
You became even more dignified.
The hell with the Great Pirate Era...
That's a lot of money!
How'd you get that?
Should I be the last voice you hear
before you die?
Move at a nice, slow and comfortable speed!
Are you happy?
On that day two years ago,
it was supposed to end!
I robbed some thugs near the main gate!
If I knew that you were
a princess at that time,
Maintain the same pace, slaves!
I would've charged you a higher medical fee.
Damn! You won again!
We of the Navy thought we ended it!
Don't stop! Keep moving!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
Who are these people?
I met them when I was traveling
with Luffy-san and the others.
It's been five years since we started
to put money in our "pirate savings."
Pops!
Save me... Or just kill me...
Do it!
Just as there are those
who will inherit Roger's will,
I wonder how much we need
to get a pirate ship.
SOME CELESTIAL DRAGON'S PALACE
Nami became ill on our way to Alabasta
so to find her a doctor,
some people will inherit Ace's
sometime in the future!
Don't do it!
F-Father-sama! Father-sama!
I don't know.
10 million or 100 million maybe?
What's wrong, Charlos?
we stopped by at a Winter Island...
Even if you break their blood bond,
you'll never be able to extinguish their flame!
Long way to go.
"A pirate ship"?!
It's a mermaid-eh!
You guys! Are you gonna become pirates?!
A very big one...
Attention, pirates! Leave this place at once!
This instant!
That's how it came down unbroken
throughout the ages!
I'm gonna become one, too!
Hey!
Don't do it!!
At first, Ace and I didn't accept him,
And someday in the future,
Open the gate!
but later, we got close enough to
exchange a cup of sake to become brothers.
carrying hundreds of years of history
on his shoulder,
Vivi!
someone will fling down the gauntlet
in front of the world!
Why, you--!
So from now on,
Aim!
A MINGLING PLAZA INSIDE THE CASTLE
we're brothers!
No! Stop!
Sengoku!
You and the World Government are afraid of...
Yeah!!
Fighting won't help anything!
Seems like royal families and their bodyguards
from across the world are here...
I'm fine! It only grazed my arm!
Ace, Luffy and I did as we liked
...the gigantic war that will embroil
the whole world in one day!
Their bodyguards look very tough.
I guess we'll be safe...
and the old man Garp would beat us.
In that case, we won't land here!
I'm on my way!
We were gonna become pirates...
The food looks fancy, too!
But could we ask for a doctor?
So I forfeited my noble heritage
and I planned to carry on living with the two.
Haki of the Color of the... Supreme King!
If it's joyous like this every day,
during the seven-day conference from tomorrow,
That brat...
Our friend is suffering from a grave illness.
He uses it, too!
Please help! I beg you!
But one day, my father came
and forced me to come back with him.
--Straw Hat will make it!
--Yeah! Keep going!
accompanying family members
won't be bored-fa-mi-re-do!
I'll leave the rest up to you,
pirates.
Do you see it? The tidal wave keeps growing.
Vivi!
If you start a fight here,
what will happen to Nami-san?
We love samba more than anything!
Would you like to dance with us?! Samba!
Of course, mister.
You've already paid us for this.
We will take care of these two
so they won't bother your boy again.
It wasn't this large yet two years ago.
I'd be happy to! King of Samba! Mambo!
Finally... finally...
Please call a doctor!
--Mambo, mambo! Shake, shake!
--Samba, samba! Shake, shake!
Please help our friend!
But now, the tidal wave of the Great Pirate Era
is growing incalculably large...
Wait a minute, Bluejam!
Dad, that's enough! I understand!
I made it!
Father is having a good time, too,
so I'm relieved.
I will show you to the village.
Luffy!
Follow me.
What do you understand?
You're so...!
U-Um...
The Paramount War took place two years ago...
Ace!
Don't do it, Sabo!
E-Everyone?
It all started with the Whitebeard Pirates'
2nd division commander
Oh, Princess from under the sea!
You're breathtakingly beautiful as I heard!
I'll do as you say.
I'll live as you want so...
At that time, the Winter Island was
under the oppressive rule
- Portgas D. Ace getting arrested
You can't get away from me!
of the then king - Wapol,
and sentenced to public execution.
Would you like to meet my son?
He's royalty and single!
...please don't hurt these two!
but one day, when it came
under attack by pirates,
Gum-Gum...
TWO YEARS AGO...
AT THE UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL DOWN
Papan! She's not bad! Not bad!
he abandoned the country instead of fighting.
I'm begging you.
...Giant Balloon!
U-Um...
They're very important to
me, they're my brothers.
Dalton-san who served under him
protected the citizens.
Princess-sama,
we have an only son who is royalty, too!
The battle started in the Navy's special
Underwater Prison Impel Down...
Sabo...
P-Pappy! I like her!
But Wapol, who waited out the invasion
disguised as a pirate,
Then go home right now.
Um... Uh...
You should stop playing pirate -
it's just a waste of time.
No, Mermaid Princess!
Please meet my royal son!
Ace is still alive!
It was an iron-tight stronghold
from which no one had escaped
came back to the island with his underlings.
Fire! Blow them away!
for the past 20 years.
We have three handsome royal princes!
Hey! Don't go!
Detained there
and waiting for his execution was...
Hm?
Be quiet!
Sabo, run!
You don't have to worry about us!
Now, which royal do you like?!
...Ace.
What's that strange flag?
Straw boy!
Oh, um... uh...
You said you wanna live freely with us!
No way!
That's my brother!
The flag...
Ace is my older brother!
Sabo, don't go!
Are you gonna put an end to your dream?!
Um... I...
...belonged to Dr. Hiriluk
who raised Tony-kun with Dr. Kureha
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
Sabo!
None of you are my type!
and loved his country dearly
until the very moment of his death!
What?! Even though they're royal?!
In order to save Ace,
Sabo!
Shirahoshi!
Sabo!!
You've always been like this!
Luffy broke into Impel Down
while the Navy
At that time, all I could do was
turn my back and scream in my mind...
Damn you! You humiliated me!
Luffy!
was distracted by Whitebeard.
"Spread your wings and
fly away freely for me."
This castle is no longer yours!
No, she was saying "I'm not married, either"
in an undersea dialect...
BUGGY THE CLOWN
CHOP-CHOP FRUIT POWER-USER
That's what I don't like
about you and Red-Haired!
You've never even listened to me...
This isn't a place for rotten brats like you!
I'm glad that you're safe,
young master.
I'll change my plan!
Oh, Sabo! You're back.
You got bigger.
Brother Ryuboshi?!
Leave this country!
The Drum Kingdom has already died out!
When this happens,
just say "How lovely" or "Let's have dinner sometime"
...and always done such crazy things!
Now for some chaos!
Mom.
I'm with you!
and turn them down softly, Shirahoshi!
Now Stelly,
say "hi" to your older brother.
Of all the flags, don't fly that quack's flag!
It will ruin the castle!
--Good!
--Oh my!
What?! I can't lie...
Ace!
Nice to meet you, brother!
My name is Stelly and I'm eight.
It's just dodging not lying!
If you hurt someone, it could become
a diplomatic issue-fa-mi-re-do! Let's go!
Ace!!
A fire?!
Yeah. You don't know about it
because you weren't here.
Long time no see-gane, Straw Hat Luffy!
Doctor... tried to save even you!
But they decided it months ago.
Now I'm free thanks to you.
How cute!
MR. 3 / GALDINO
WAX-WAX FRUIT POWER-USER
VIVI - PRINCESS OF THE ALABASTA KINGDOM
(AND KAROO)
They decided to burn down the Gray Terminal.
I always pay back my debts-gane.
You're so cute! You're like a fairy!
Chopper...
Don't hold a grudge against humans.
BON CLAY
CLONE-CLONE FRUIT POWER-USER
LEO - LEADER OF THE TONTA
CORPS, TONTATTA TRIBE
Then this country will be clean!
That's not a compliment to a warrior!
It's been a long time! Straw-chan, it's me!
This country is sick right now.
The king also suffers from a sickness of the heart.
What are you talking about?!
That's impossible!
BIAN     CUB     MANSHERRY
Luffy gained new companions
while he made a dash to save Ace.
Are you okay, Leo?!
Everyone, survive at any cost
and go back to the New World safely!
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't mean it!
They're gonna burn up
all the shame of this country.
However, Warden Magellan stood in his way.
What?!
Then, that's okay!
Why? Doctor, a guy like
him isn't worth saving!
Great! It seems like she's a good person!
What are you doing?!
You have to evacuate!
As soon as you rescue
"Fire Fist" Ace, you run!
Did you want to touch these?!
So you can move rapidly.
I didn't notice until Karoo found you.
Ace! Luffy!
The Whitebeards must be a group of cowards!
Run!
I showed myself because
I heard you said you knew Luffyland.
Well your captain is that guy
so you can't help it, can you?
Hm?
I...
We're Luffyland and his crew's subordinates!
We're pirates!
I won't hit you... so leave this country!
Because after all, Whitebeard is just a...
Pirates?!
What're you saying, Chopper?!
You think he'll just listen to you?!
Don't you wanna give up now?
So cute!
...loser from the old times!
So Luffy-san and his crew have
such a lovely subordinate!
What happened to you, boy?
Nice to meet you, Leo-san!
But... after all...
Take back what you just said!
Nice to meet you, too!
Humph!
I'm gonna rescue Ace
I never thought I'd be able to talk
so much about Lucy at the Reverie.
You were a fake pirate, right?
Whitebeard will die as a loser!
and we're gonna get out of here!
This town smells worse
than the Gray Terminal.
You don't know what this pirate
flag means because you were
It's fitting for a big
fish in a little barrel!
Whitebeard is a great pirate
who shaped this era!
I'm not gonna die without even seeing him!
fake pirates who didn't even risk your lives!
It's no wonder. They're
traveling across the world.
REBECCA - LADY-IN-WAITING OF DRESSROSA
It smells like rotten people!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard"!
Dodge it! Watch out!
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
Did Lucy visit Vivi-san's country...
You can't break this flag!
No, I mean, Luffy?
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
That's right! Luffyland!
He must've been blown away! Such an idiot!
What's that smoke?
He did...
Both Whitebeard and you guys who call him Pops
are the same after all - losers!
My home country Alabasta
still exists today...
I don't wanna lose to you by not touching you
because you're poisonous.
I'm...
...ashamed of being born a noble!
...thanks to them.
See? It didn't break...
I'd rather touch you and...
Princess Vivi of Alabasta,
the sand kingdom in the Grand Line...
They finally made a kid say this!
Goa Kingdom!
You'd better be prepared if you're
Ace...
...give you my arms!
...is the Straw Hats' friend who once
traveled with them on their ship.
gonna meddle with someone else's skull flag!
Gum-Gum...
What a nice day!
It's perfect for setting sail!
I don't want your arms!
Hold on a sec!
I'll give you status and a medal!
Ace's Vivre Card!
But if you want me to have them,
I'll take them!
All right! At any rate, no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm...
I set off.
Gold Roger - the King of the Pirates,
Dragon - the revolutionary.
Doctor...
I left my noble heritage, parents,
and country behind...
The kingdom is...
Gum-Gum...
The Drum Kingdom is...
I was amazed to hear that
sons of those two are step brothers.
...is the sign of our friendship!
...to live as the freest pirate ever!
...Jet Bazooka!
Because of a plot by the
then Warlord of the Sea,
You two have bad blood in your veins.
Sir Crocodile who looked to
take control of the country,
Then... I'll make you vice-king...!
I don't care if the others get away
as long as I get you two!
a civil war broke out between
the royal army and a rebel army...
...about to fall!
...Bazooka!!
Watch what I do.
At last the time has come for the
Alabasta Kingdom to disappear.
How rude is that!
Wait!
While the Straw Hats were trying to
stop the clash between the two armies,
Saint Jalmack!
There is a child on the ship!
Luffy!
When someone flies a black flag,
he's a pirate regardless of who he is-eh.
Thank you. Drum will definitely...
Luffy noticed Vivi was shouldering
everything by herself.
...be reborn...
But most importantly...
Dalton-san helped Luffy-san get rid of Wapol,
A commoner shouldn't cross
the path of my ship!!
And what's wrong with thinking that?
What's wrong with not wanting people to die?!
and by the wish of all the citizens,
People die.
became the king of the renamed
country, Sakura Kingdom.
You seem to have brought me to my knees!
I see.
We never really know what
a cornered rat will do!
Hey, hey, hey!
Dalton! You told me to cut the crap earlier,
even though you're merely my subordinate!
The rebel army, the royal army, and the
people of this kingdom haven't done anything wrong!
Ace...
But now you got enough poison on your hand...
So why do people have to die
when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
That was long ago...
Now...
...to affect your whole body!
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
I'm on even terms with you!
Ace... Luffy...
Hydra!
--Whoa, Luffy! You're going too far!
--Damn it, Luffy!
Honey!
Help me... Somebody...
Dalton-san!
You have the kingly attitude down pat!
Just one look at this kingdom and even I can tell
what most needs to be done!
What? No...
Ace!
Listen, Dalton! You bastard in shining armor!
What is it?!
You can't be naive when running a country!
As if putting your single
life on the line is enough!
Hey, are you all right? Hey.
Then what should I be putting on the line?!
I met Dragon-san there
and it changed my destiny...
I'm living proof since I came back by making
a fortune with my Munch-Munch Fruit power!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
The higher you climb,
the more you'll see how dirty this world is!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
So the damn Celestial Dragons are up there...
Give me...
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
...Ace!
I'll teach you! And pay you back...
Huh?
Aren't we friends?!
Could you tell them...
By the way, did you read
the article on Luffy-kun?
...what I'm about to say now?
Yes, thoroughly.
Say, maybe... Dalton-san...
I'm ready. Let's do it already.
You like Lucy?
This is your punishment.
You like Luffyland, don't you?
Pops!
Chief of Staff.
There is no way to neutralize
the amount of poison you have absorbed!
Yeah!
Everybody!
I like him very much.
And you Luffy.
You will agonize for 24 hours
This is gonna be fun!
Are you guys listening?!
and then pass...
Thank you...
You, old witch hag,
how much longer are you gonna live?!
...to the real hell!
...for loving someone like me
who is good for nothing...
You're way over 150!
The Straw Hats and Vivi headed for Alubarna,
the capital city, to stop the civil war,
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
I'm still a spry 141!
They sank his ship so you must've
thought that Sabo guy was dead.
A... A...
but Crocodile appeared in front of them.
By the way, ladies...
Ace!
Yeah, I thought so at that time.
Did you see that blue-nosed reindeer?
Sables!!
I cried a lot when Pedro died.
Yes, I saw him!
I know how you felt!
...up to today.
In the Ryugu Kingdom, he saved Luffy-sama
who was critically injured as
well as the kingdom itself.
A-Ace... I...
Who do you think I am?
Thank you!
There are any number of rookies like you,
who are nothing but talk,
I wanna become stronger!
I see.
Then I can protect anything or anyone!
I don't have to lose anybody!
Please... teach me to be a doctor!
Straw Hat Luffy,
The poison passed into his system
and he was dying,
here in the Grand Line.
I'll become the all-purpose medicine!
I'll become a doctor who can cure anything!
but Emporio Ivankov, the Horm-Horm Fruit power-user,
saved him.
I beg you!
Taken in by Crocodile's plot,
the rebel army and the
Ace,
I'll cure even a country!
please don't die!
royal army got into a fierce battle.
Cut it out!
Because...
there's no disease in this world that can't be cured!
Worry about yourself first!
Meanwhile, the Straw Hats fought the members
You're far weaker than me!
of Baroque Works, the secret crime
syndicate, on Vivi's behalf.
Miracles only happen to people
who don't give up!
Ace...
Listen carefully, Luffy!
Don't underestimate miracles!
I'll never die!
Take this! Special Attack...
Here it comes! Moletown...
Uh-huh.
Smoke Star!!
Sabo told me to take care of you, too.
What... What?!
I promise that I'll never die!
The rest... is up to you, Chopper!
How can I leave a wimpy
brother like you behind?
Stop! Mr. 4!
Hey, let's be pirates together!
Food!
It's me!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Stop...
Okay?!
I'm not smart so I don't quite know
what really killed Sabo yet.
It's not possible.
Because...
Thus, Luffy recovered.
Ace's death...
Along with Ivankov and his right arm Inazuma,
the Snip-Snip Fruit power-user,
Because I'm a reindeer! I
have antlers and hooves!
And Whitebeard met his end as well...
But it must be something opposed to freedom.
Special Attack: Hammer Shooting Star!!
...with the sudden appearance
of his former subordinate
Luffy tried to reach Ace.
Sabo died before he knew freedom.
I even have a blue nose!
Marshall D. Teech, also known as Blackbeard.
Ace!
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
We exchanged that same cup of sake
and we're alive!
Is this it?!
I can't become your friend! So...!
Ace?!
So listen, Luffy.
Luffy and his allies were cornered
by the Navy's persistent attacks.
Veau Vengeance!!
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
So I just came to say thank you...
Swan Bombardier Dive!!
I do appreciate you guys.
He's not here!
Showing up on the scene in the chaos at Marineford
to end the war was...
Uh-huh.
And there, he met...
Thank you for asking me to join you.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
I'll stay here, but...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
"Red-Haired" Shanks!
Have mercy on me!
one day... if you feel
like it, stop by agai...
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
"Red-Haired"! He is the one who
motivated Luffy to become a pirate!
Uh-huh!
Shut up! Let's go!
That means we'll make enemies of many people.
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
They'll hand over Ace boy
to the Navy Headquarters at any cost!
Everybody.
Even the old man will become our enemy.
You gotta be willing to risk everything.
For now,
I have something to talk with you!
You need to give up on him!
you need to do as I say!
Listen, Doctorine! I'm gonna be a pirate.
I'm going with them!
I mean, you need to trust Whitebeard.
Let's go out to sea at 17!
Take this...
And we will become... pirates!
Tornado Tempo!
He's not gonna give up on one of his own!
He'll definitely do something!
Don't be ridiculous!
Whitebeard, Ace...
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
Let's start with finding a crew!
Let us handle the burial of those two.
I've never heard of a mere reindeer
going out to sea.
I want at least 10 of them.
I'm gonna go to the Navy Headquarters!
And the black flag!
The war was broadcast to the world.
That's right. I'm a reindeer! But...
Don't be stupid!
What?!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm a man, too!
I won't let you dishonor their death
in public any longer!
What?
I'm gonna become...
If I give up now...
...the King of the Pirates!
What do you think someone like you
can do at sea?!
That's ridiculous!
...I'm gonna regret it!
We raise a shout of victory by exposing
their dead bodies to public view!
Straw Hat became the first intruder
in Impel Down's history...
One-Sword Style Iai Draw and
Resheath Technique: Lion Song!
Are you gonna live in a fantasy
just like that quack did?!
So Sabo-san and Ace-san had an
impact on Luffy-san's sailing-out.
I agree!
You're wrong! It wasn't a fantasy!
He snuck in alone
but when he came back out,
Only because it's you, I allow it,
"Red-Haired"!
Atomic Dash!
Doctor's research had
actually been completed!
Isn't that nice?! He sailed out for
a never-ending adventure!
he was surrounded by prisoners.
Thanks.
And your brother Sabo
who you thought was dead
He even allied with
those who he once fought...
is now the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army!
Was it okay to bid farewell like that?
This war is...
The Revolutionary Army's leader
is your father, Dragon.
Let me tell you something...
...over!
NAVY
The other brother, Portgas D. Ace
A pet I was taking care of is being taken in
by someone else. That's all.
You can't save this country.
was the Whitebeard Pirates'
2nd division commander
The terrible thing is whenever he
does something, miracles happen...
I don't like... tears...
Goodbye, Princess...
and the King of the Pirates
- Gol D. Roger's son...
After that war,
The prime example of that is
what happened at the Gates of Justice!
pirates became active again...
What kind of family is that?!
Too many badasses!
Doesn't it make you feel strange
when you think that your sworn
Are you ready, young men?!
Straw Hat Luffy...
Crocodile!!
brother is with your father?
Oh no-gane! We can't open it-gane!
I didn't expect him to play such a big role
in this era!
Hmmm...  I don't know
because I've never met my dad before...
Luffy-san!
Damn! It's a dead end after
coming this far-gane!
On top of that, there were
Whitebeard's last words...
You're talking like me-gane!
But,
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
wherever I am,
it feels like I'm always connected to Sabo.
--What're we gonna do, you shark?!
--Sail through it!
Once my invention is completed,
this country will be saved!
The One Piece...
That's impossible! This is a disaster!
Just in time.
...is real!!
How can you be so relaxed?!
Doctor...! Doctorine...!
It's just a dead man's bullshit!
Vivi...
Keep firing! Sink them...
She tells others not to die...
Damn Whitebeard...
but she's the first to lay down her own life
to save others.
I can't believe everyone's been manipulated!
The Gates of Justice are opening!
They don't know what it means to
rebel against us...
If we don't help her, she'll die.
No way!
You guys will kill her.
I'll teach them!
Why are the Gates opening?!
You're so dense.
The king of the Goa Kingdom?!
I was with him at the entrance a while ago!
That's why I'm telling you
that you can just ditch that burden...!
NAVY
Even though it has been relocated,
He stayed alone at Impel Down?!
The king of the Goa Kingdom, huh?
New Marineford is still guarding the
We don't want her to die!
That's how friends are!
Hey, can you hear me, Bon-chan?!
It's a peaceful rural kingdom
but it's home to a number of outlaws.
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
gate of the Holyland of Mariejois
where the Celestial Dragons reside.
Why are you doing this?!
We were gonna break out together,
weren't we?!
Garp is an exception.
The place where the Paramount War took place
is now Branch G-1.
The leader of the Revolutionary Army - Dragon,
the Chief of Staff - Sabo,
Please... stop fighting!
How many times have I been saved by you?!
and the pirates - "Fire Fist" and Straw Hat.
Please... stop fighting!
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
FORMER MARINEFORD
The two Navy bases are situated
on both sides of the Red Line...
If you are there, say something,
Bon-chan!
How interesting!
Please... stop fighting!
...to protect Mariejois against invasion.
Bon-chan!
Now, kneel at my feet, Garp!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
Ouch!
Bon-chan, the Gates are closing.
Get out of my way. Your face irritates me.
What happened?!
I tried to help Sanji cook
and I cut my finger...
I don't care who you are...
His rudeness leaves me speechless!
I'll surpass you!
Let me see.
We... have to go.
You're fine. It won't take long to heal!
It'll sting a bit.
I'll cut to the chase, Garp.
Gum-Gum...!
Give me some pull with the World Nobles!
Desert...
Chobro, you're great!
Thank you!
I wanna eventually become a Celestial Dragon.
Storm!
What?
Because there's no injury
you can't treat.
La Spada!
You wanna be a scumbag like them?
This is Red Port.
RED PORT
Luffy was all cut up
but now he's totally fine!
Two huge ports like this are
on each side of the Red Line,
What?!
Oh, please! Did anyone hear that?!
That could get us the death penalty!
That's because I was taught
by the greatest doctor in the world!
Brother Bon, thank you!
and it's the Government's official means
of getting to the other side of the wall.
Oh! I shouldn't say that. I take it back.
--Thank you!
Bondola 1, now departing.
He scares me!
It's a nice day.
Oh, Dad! It's going up!
Leo.
Straw-chan!
I've been working for the Kano
Kingdom, but I'll cut ties
Bondolas, bubble-based gondolas,
make their way up to the Holyland of Mariejois.
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan!
Are you okay-jamon, young man?
with them after this bodyguard duty.
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
What?
He moved?! I thought he was a building!
This will be my last service for them.
Is he a Giant? I heard they eat humans
and can melt rocks with their saliva...
I'm deeply indebted to Straw Hat and the others
for saving us in Dressrosa.
Luffy-san...
Look! Ships are arriving one after another!
I know that you can save
your brother for sure!
Yeah!
Please stop fighting!
We're seven representatives of the Straw Hat Fleet
with over 5,600 troops in total.
Bon-chan!
No, wait. Who are they?!
Fangs?!
Please don't fight... any more...!!
We have to be ready to help him at all times.
Scales?!
Look at the colors of their skin.
Uh-huh.
Are they Fish-Men who are
half-human and half-fish?!
Clear the way for the royals!
I heard the other members
started preparing, too.
They're classified as fish and you'll
get a rare disease by touching them...
To take down Whitebeard
by luring him out with Ace's public execution,
Since our nightmares are... all over...
Oh! Beer VI of the Roshwan Kingdom!
Don't touch me!
There are the Matryoshesses!
Crocodile's plot was thwarted
by Luffy and the others and
the Navy summoned the best
and was prepared to fight.
How cute!
What did you say?!
the Alabasta Kingdom was saved.
RESIGNATION
You're suddenly leaving
the Standing Kingdom?!
Queen Morollon of the Tajine Kingdom!
She's so beautiful!
NAVY
However, the Straw Hats
didn't get credit for it,
Bondola 2, now departing.
Give me a reason!
Cheers to all the lovely eyes in the world!
because the Government reported that
it was the Navy's achievement.
I have to pay back a great debt!
Barrier!
It's better to die standing
than live on your knees!
Barrier Crush!
Say, everyone...
All right, take care of yourself!
King Taco of the Kingdom of the Dead!
What... should I do...?
Luffy-sama's grandfather-sama,
thank you very much.
Just by crossing fingers,
anyone can put up a barrier!
King Ham Burger of the Ballywood Kingdom
has arrived as well!
We'll draw the ship near the eastern harbor
just once at exactly noon tomorrow.
I have something to tell you all.
Even children know that!
It was fun to travel with you.
W-We surrender!
Portgas D. Ace...
Why does he walk so slowly?
We lose! We'll serve under you
so give us a break!
If you want to continue traveling with us,
that moment is the
It's about the great significance of
his death today.
only chance to come aboard.
Well then...
If that happens, we'll welcome you...
though you'll become a pirate.
I may walk slowly, but...
Put this on.
A year and three months
after the father's death,
Wh-What is it?
Come, Vivi! Definitely come! Come now!
I'll never turn around!
the child was born with the blood of
the world's most heinous man in his veins.
Let's support the Straw Hats together!
If I go, you'll go too, right?
Let's!
Say... Karoo...
That was you!
What would you like to do?
Two unidentified ships are approaching!
Your father is...
That ship is...
Are they remnants of Doflamingo's troops?
...Vice Admiral Garp's Navy ship!
...the King of the Pirates -
Everyone!
Cavendish.
It's so high...
Gold Roger!
As you may know,
Vivi!
Unbelievable...
Karoo!
I was formerly the prince of
the Bourgeois Kingdom.
Vivi-chan!
Let's go back! Better hurry!
The Navy is right there, too!
What's the matter-jamon, Shirahoshi?
Cavendish-sama!
Oh, that's...
But all the women in the country
were crazy about me
I came to say goodbye!
...the Great Knight of
the Sea - King Neptune!
What did she just...?
Father-sama... It's the sun...
and not one of them was
willing to marry other men...
And the three strongest of the Neptune Army!
I can't... go with you!
I was expelled from the country
for being too popular.
The Ryugu Kingdom is attending the Reverie!
Brother-sama! The sun is shining so brightly!
Here comes Moby Dick!
Thank you so much for everything!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Yeah...
Moonfish! Moonfish!
I wanna have fun on land!
So...
I'd like to go on more adventures,
The sky goes on forever!
It's not necessary to attack them
since they're not our enemies.
but there's no ignoring...
that I love this country!
The sea is also endless
and sparkling in the sun!
It's so bright on land-do-re-mi-fa-so!
So I can't go!
Let's go, guys.
Moonfish!
I know that Straw Hat
will face those who are
Yeah, it's really amazing! Mambo!
I see!
I...
more dangerous than Doflamingo hereafter.
Garp-sama!
I...
I thought I was gonna die in the deep sea!
I didn't know that the
surface was so dazzling!
I...
We have to become stronger.
Yes! I'm training myself with my crew, too!
If we ever meet again someday...
What a beautiful world!
RYUGU PALACE
Hey, Princess-san! Come out!
will you call me your friend again?!
It's been a while, Sengoku.
Mm-hm.
I hope we can fight for
Luffyland together again!
The Sun Tree that lights up the sea floor
can't compare-jamon.
Okay, Shirahoshi.
Whitebeard.
Yep!
You better tell me that my beloved son...
Let's go to Mariejois!
...is all right.
Yes...
Father-sama, I...
The Underwater Prison Impel Down...
THE UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL DOWN
If possible, I want to live on land!
So this is the surface!
I want to show this world in the sun
to the people of our kingdom!
All right! At any rate, no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm...
It's Mermaid Princess-sama!
The lowest level...
Level 6 holds the criminals
who are considered extremely dangerous.
...is the sign of our friendship!
It has been 200 years
Now it's coming!
The seaquake that he set up before!
I'll ask them.
That's what the Reverie is all about-jamon.
since the Ryugu Kingdom began
affiliating with the World Government,
The Infinite Hell.
They don't like to be seen as heroes...
but they have attended the Reverie
only once before.
Coming in the form of tsunami!
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
And because of their bounties and people's talk,
they keep gaining notoriety,
Since you're fighting against the
World Government for the Fish-Men,
So this is indeed a big deal.
What's this solitary cell?
Don't think that our superior forces
will guarantee us victory.
but I'm sure they haven't changed.
Am I all alone here? I feel so lonely.
do you have mixed feelings, Koala?
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
When I read about Dressrosa,
We could well fail.
Because that man has...
Don't tell me you're trying
to protect me, Magellan!
About the Ryugu Kingdom
attending the Reverie?
I knew that Luffy-san and the others decided to
save somebody again!
Clank.
No, I don't, Betty-san.
...the power to destroy the world!
Sakazuki-san told me to find you
and kick you out...
Did an assassin from on high come to kill me?
It's not the World Government
that we really wanna bring down.
That's right!
To us, Luffy is...
In order to prevent me from telling someone
about the secret of Mariejois,
It's the Celestial Dragons who rule it.
The Straw Hats are very special!
You wanna fight me?
RED LINE
did they send an assassin to silence me?!
Give me a break! I don't want to!
--Mount a counter-offensive!
--Yes!
It's really high! I'm scared!
It's not like you wanna destroy
the conference, right?
I miss him... Lucy...
It's very windy! And it's shaking!
Why does it matter if it's revealed now?
Power doesn't last long.
Um...
No, I don't...
Were you talking about Luffy-sama just now?
What I want to destroy is...
It'll rot faster than anyone thinks!
...the system.
Oh, the Mermaid Princess!
Be quiet.
Shirahoshi!
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious!
MARIEJOIS
D-D-Did you just see that?!
Talking about him doesn't always mean
they know him!
What did you see?
You had a long journey.
How is the old man Vegapunk doing?
Luffy-kun is a pirate!
If someone finds out you're his friend-ti-do!
There was a G-Giant in the wall,
staring at us!
Well, of course I couldn't lay eyes on it
but he has completed something incredible.
H-H-He had a trident!
The Mermaid Princess knows Luffy-san?
You must be hallucinating...
Hey, did you just say Luffy-sama?
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
Can't you see how high we're at now?
Oh, what is it like?
Wait, Rebecca! If we heard wrong...
It was really there!
Yes!
I did say so! Do you know him?!
We no longer need the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
--Look over there! They're crows!
--They don't usually come up this high.
Stop! Everyone knows his name!
I'm indebted to Luffy-sama...
You're crazy! Really!
Great Eruption!
Those are the birds that
everyone was talking about?
By the way, the food here is delicious,
just as I thought!
They're flying!
So are we!
If they peck at the bubble, we're gonna fall!
Why don't you eat something?
Are you still fasting?
Your voice is heard by us.
It was a back-and-forth battle
and it became very intense.
RYOKUGYU - AN ADMIRAL
OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Hey, guard! Pull out your gun!
Shoot down the crows!
They're gonna pop the bubble!
And then...
If some young lady helps me, I would eat!
Let's go for a walk!
He came...
Ace!
I'm so lazy. I haven't eaten
anything for three years!
Don't worry.
I bet you're happy, Rebecca,
to see your dad!
You'll be fine. King Stelly.
We're here for you!
The Revolutionary Army led by Sabo commences
In front of Vivi and the others,
the Sakura Kingdom's Dalton, Dr. Kureha,
The threat of a Celestial Dragon who
suddenly strikes falls on Shirahoshi.
While the world surges
powerfully around Luffy,
Vivi from Alabasta. Rebecca from Dressrosa.
And Shirahoshi from the Fish-Man Island.
their operation to infiltrate Mariejois for
the purpose of changing history forever!
Fujitora and a new Navy
Admiral turn up at Mariejois!
and their arch-enemy Wapol appear
and tensions rise in the Holyland!
He has Rob Lucci from Cipher Pol on his side
and no one can stop him
Meanwhile, the dazzling view of
the beautiful surface world brings
The three heroines who once stood up
Meanwhile, a lone figure goes deep inside
the Pangaea Castle
nevertheless Neptune moves to make
an attack much to his chagrin!
to save their countries
from crises along with the Straw Hats,
Meanwhile, from under the sea,
with a flood of emotions,
tears to Shirahoshi's eyes
and gives her a wish that marks a new chapter
in the Fish-Men's history!
However, it comes to a stunning end!
meet each other with memories
of Luffy in their mind!
and a great hidden secret is unveiled!
Shirahoshi surfaces!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Miss Him! Vivi and Rebecca's Sentiments!"
"The Paramount War! The Inherited
Will of the King of the Pirates!"
"One Step Forward for Her Dream!
Shirahoshi Goes Out in the Sun!"
"In the Dark Recesses of the Holyland!
A Mysterious Giant Straw Hat!"
"The Holyland in Tumult! The
Targeted Princess Shirahoshi!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!