Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"Going into Action!
The Implacable New Admiral of the Fleet - Sakazuki!"
This is the Navy Headquarters led by
the new Admiral of the Fleet, Sakazuki.
New Marineford.
Two years ago, in the Paramount War between
the Navy Headquarters and
the Whitebeard Pirates,
the Navy triumphed.
However, Marineford became a battleground
and was devastated.
It was long renowned as
the home of "justice,"
but to prepare for the
intensifying Pirate Era, the
World Government built an even
greater impregnable fortress.
The new fort of "justice" that's located
at the entrance of the New World...
That's New Marineford.
NAVY
Fujitora showed up at Mariejois?!
Y-Yes, sir!
I told him that
he can't set foot in any Navy base...
...until he brings Straw Hat and Law's heads!
He can't just claim to have forgotten what I said to him
in Dressrosa!
Oh, I'm scared.
How dare he come back! That fool!
Y-Yes, we all know what you told him...
Then why didn't you send him away?!
Well... he was perfectly prepared
with theoretical arguments and
we couldn't combat his wit...
This is not a Navy base...
That's just a quibble!
Is he a witty monk or something?!
Oh?
Isn't it a difficult job?
Fleet Admiral...
S-Sengoku-san!
Shut up, you semi-retired has-been!
Who else has gone to Mariejois?!
A-Admiral Ryokugyu-san has!
Ryokugyu, huh?
Contact him immediately!
Yes, sir! What should I tell him?!
It's obvious!
Tell him to turn Fujitora away if he sees him!
All of you, go!
Y-Yes, sir!
What a bunch of idiots!
Why don't you go back to your post, too?
It's strange, isn't it?
That Straw Hat's bounty...
...went up to 1.5 billion.
That stupid brat...
I should've killed him somehow at that time!
The hell with the Great Pirate Era...
On that day two years ago,
it was supposed to end!
We of the Navy thought we ended it!
Just as there are those
who will inherit Roger's will,
some people will inherit Ace's
sometime in the future!
Even if you break their blood bond,
you'll never be able to extinguish their flame!
That's how it came down unbroken
throughout the ages!
And someday in the future,
carrying hundreds of years of history
on his shoulder,
someone will fling down the gauntlet
in front of the world!
Sengoku!
You and the World Government are afraid of...
...the gigantic war that will embroil
the whole world in one day!
Do you see it? The tidal wave keeps growing.
It wasn't this large yet two years ago.
But now, the tidal wave of the Great Pirate Era
is growing incalculably large...
The Paramount War took place two years ago...
It all started with the Whitebeard Pirates'
2nd division commander
- Portgas D. Ace getting arrested
and sentenced to public execution.
TWO YEARS AGO...
AT THE UNDERWATER PRISON IMPEL DOWN
The battle started in the Navy's special
Underwater Prison Impel Down...
It was an iron-tight stronghold
from which no one had escaped
for the past 20 years.
Detained there
and waiting for his execution was...
...Ace.
That's my brother!
Ace is my older brother!
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
In order to save Ace,
Luffy broke into Impel Down
while the Navy
was distracted by Whitebeard.
BUGGY THE CLOWN
CHOP-CHOP FRUIT POWER-USER
That's what I don't like
about you and Red-Haired!
I'll change my plan!
Now for some chaos!
I'm with you!
Long time no see-gane, Straw Hat Luffy!
Now I'm free thanks to you.
MR. 3 / GALDINO
WAX-WAX FRUIT POWER-USER
I always pay back my debts-gane.
BON CLAY
CLONE-CLONE FRUIT POWER-USER
It's been a long time! Straw-chan, it's me!
Luffy gained new companions
while he made a dash to save Ace.
However, Warden Magellan stood in his way.
Did you want to touch these?!
Don't you wanna give up now?
I'm gonna rescue Ace
and we're gonna get out of here!
I'm not gonna die without even seeing him!
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
What's that smoke?
I don't wanna lose to you by not touching you
because you're poisonous.
I'd rather touch you and...
...give you my arms!
I don't want your arms!
But if you want me to have them,
I'll take them!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
You seem to have brought me to my knees!
We never really know what
a cornered rat will do!
But now you got enough poison on your hand...
...to affect your whole body!
Hydra!
Give me...
...Ace!
This is your punishment.
There is no way to neutralize
the amount of poison you have absorbed!
You will agonize for 24 hours
and then pass...
...to the real hell!
A... A...
Ace!
The poison passed into his system
and he was dying,
but Emporio Ivankov, the Horm-Horm Fruit power-user,
saved him.
Miracles only happen to people
who don't give up!
Don't underestimate miracles!
What... What?!
Food!
Thus, Luffy recovered.
Along with Ivankov and his right arm Inazuma,
the Snip-Snip Fruit power-user,
Luffy tried to reach Ace.
Ace!
Is this it?!
Ace?!
He's not here!
And there, he met...
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Have mercy on me!
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
They'll hand over Ace boy
to the Navy Headquarters at any cost!
You need to give up on him!
I mean, you need to trust Whitebeard.
He's not gonna give up on one of his own!
He'll definitely do something!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
I'm gonna go to the Navy Headquarters!
Don't be stupid!
What?
If I give up now...
...I'm gonna regret it!
Straw Hat became the first intruder
in Impel Down's history...
He snuck in alone
but when he came back out,
he was surrounded by prisoners.
He even allied with
those who he once fought...
NAVY
The terrible thing is whenever he
does something, miracles happen...
The prime example of that is
what happened at the Gates of Justice!
Oh no-gane! We can't open it-gane!
Damn! It's a dead end after
coming this far-gane!
You're talking like me-gane!
--What're we gonna do, you shark?!
--Sail through it!
That's impossible! This is a disaster!
How can you be so relaxed?!
Keep firing! Sink them...
The Gates of Justice are opening!
No way!
Why are the Gates opening?!
I was with him at the entrance a while ago!
He stayed alone at Impel Down?!
Hey, can you hear me, Bon-chan?!
Why are you doing this?!
We were gonna break out together,
weren't we?!
How many times have I been saved by you?!
If you are there, say something,
Bon-chan!
Bon-chan, the Gates are closing.
We... have to go.
Thank you!
Brother Bon, thank you!
--Thank you!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
I know that you can save
your brother for sure!
Bon-chan!
To take down Whitebeard
by luring him out with Ace's public execution,
the Navy summoned the best
and was prepared to fight.
NAVY
I have something to tell you all.
Portgas D. Ace...
It's about the great significance of
his death today.
A year and three months
after the father's death,
the child was born with the blood of
the world's most heinous man in his veins.
That was you!
Your father is...
...the King of the Pirates -
Gold Roger!
Here comes Moby Dick!
It's been a while, Sengoku.
Whitebeard.
You better tell me that my beloved son...
...is all right.
Now it's coming!
The seaquake that he set up before!
Coming in the form of tsunami!
Don't think that our superior forces
will guarantee us victory.
We could well fail.
Because that man has...
...the power to destroy the world!
--Mount a counter-offensive!
--Yes!
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
Great Eruption!
It was a back-and-forth battle
and it became very intense.
And then...
He came...
Ace!
We're here for you!
While the world surges
powerfully around Luffy,
Fujitora and a new Navy
Admiral turn up at Mariejois!
Meanwhile, from under the sea,
with a flood of emotions,
Shirahoshi surfaces!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Paramount War! The Inherited
Will of the King of the Pirates!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!