Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on which is written "Go to Hell"
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's covered in cuts and bruises
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku tachi no sekai terasu yo
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
The Great Pirate Era
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
In order to cope with the turbulent Great Pirate Era,
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"The Holyland in Tumult!
The Targeted Princess Shirahoshi!"
"Finally, It Starts!
The Conspiracy-filled Reverie!"
"An Explosive Situation!
Two Emperors of the Sea Going After Luffy!"
"Sabo Enraged!
The Tragedy of the Revolutionary Army Officer Kuma!"
"Marco!
The Keeper of Whitebeard's Last Memento!"
PANGAEA CASTLE
The Pangaea Castle has...
There is something that I've
wanted since I was a kid.
Ring, ring, ring...
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
On this day, King Neptune
of the Ryugu Kingdom...
...three gates outside of its main gate
and all of them are guarded.
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
...arrived at the Holyland of Mariejois,
site of the Reverie.
One of those gates is the
Celestial Dragon Gate
This was the fervent wish
of the late Queen Otohime.
which leads to the Land of the Gods
where the Celestial Dragons live...
NEW WORLD
Okay, let's go home-eh.
We shall live under the sun!
The day that humans and we
understand each other will come!
Kaido-sama!
--I came at the request for reinforcements.
--Yes, we're aware.
This place looks terrible, too.
There are traces of robberies across the city.
Otohime...
What is it?!
Are you trying to disturb me while I'm drinking?!
I wish I could bring you with me here!
Open the gate!
No! I'd never do that!
The thing is...
What happened here?
PANGAEA CASTLE
King Stelly of the Goa Kingdom, come in.
MINK TRIBE GUARDIANS
Master Cat Viper's navigation
skill was quite formidable!
They left.
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
Let's start a strategy meeting.
That's what I'd expected from a man
who sailed on the ship of the King of the Pirates!
We understand the geography of Mariejois
and the structure of the castle.
Now, how much longer should we wait
in these ruins?
What do you want?!
But the problem is their security...
I heard even the Navy Admirals are here.
It's about Straw Hat.
Until Master Cat Viper brings Marco here!
He's on his way to you...
I wonder if he'll show...
That's what we expected!
So what?
No matter who gets in our way,
we'll save Kuma!
If Marco comes along with us to the Land of Wano,
he'll make for a strong ally.
Listen, keep your hands off of him!
Of course, we will.
That's what we're here for...
I'll come to the Land of Wano
to chop Straw Hat's head off myself.
So that is the center of the world!
Marco is the former 1st division commander of
the infamous Whitebeard Pirates!
Your brother and his crew were saved by him, too,
right?
Is that some kind of joke?! I refuse!
Yeah, while I was suffering memory loss
and couldn't do anything...
People call him Marco the Phoenix!
It has nothing to do with you.
I was surprised to know
that he's Master's friend!
I must cut off his head
or I'll keep losing face!
At the Sabaody Archipelago,
All right!
I'm gonna go take a look at that man, too.
he helped my brother and his crew
escape Admiral Kizaru!
There's something I want
to take back from him, too!
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait!
--Now, make a pledge...
--What?
I don't care!
Master told you to wait here
because you-gara got a scary face!
Can I sit on it?!
I think you owe me quite a favor.
Everyone focus on escaping!
Don't even joke about such things!
Hmph! Is he the kind of guy
who'll get frightened by my face?!
A favor?
Tsk!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
No one's allowed to sit on the throne.
You do remember it, don't you?
That was a long time ago.
Listen!
It's the Empty Throne.
He said there is a peaceful village
on the other side of a cave at the back of that waterfall...
But that's a lifetime debt.
It symbolizes the pledge that
royals of all countries are
equal and no one desires a dictatorship.
A group of warriors like us
will scare its residents.
You're right.
The 20 weapons that protect the throne...
I have greater resentment
towards that brat - Straw Hat!
But Master Cat Viper's
face is scarier than mine!
...represent the 800-year-old
pledge that was made by the
Yes, when he gets mad.
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing there?!
--But he's cute when he smiles.
--Certainly!
First Twenty who created the world system.
Kaido used to buy tons of SMILEs,
those artificial Devil Fruits Doflamingo was manufacturing,
Run! Run!
It's located at the center of the world
Put your hands up and turn around slowly!
Damn you!
and its vacancy is a visible
demonstration of peace...
in order to form the ultimate pirate group
made of all Devil Fruit eaters.
Stop! Sanji!
Just as the most powerful in the world
divide their power amongst five,
However...
as the Five Elders,
the highest-ranking Celestial Dragons,
No!
This damn factory that gave
you Tontattas a hard time!
no one rules the world single-handedly.
There!
Hey, wait!
Luffy... Help m--
Nami!
Destroy it!!
Now, make a pledge, King Stelly.
If I can sit there, I'll
be the king of the world!
Stop it! That's enough!
The SMILE manufacturing factory in Dressrosa
was destroyed by the Straw Hats.
King Stelly?
I wanna sit there!
MINGLING PLAZA IN THE PANGAEA CASTLE
Robin!
Straw Hat Luffy! Trafalgar Law!
Luffy!
MINGLING PLAZA, PANGAEA CASTLE
Okay.
A lot of people are gone...
His treatment is finished.
He can go now-yoi.
Come on!
It's to be expected
after something like that happened.
I know! They're from the generation, right?!
He said you can go now.
Tama, can you stand?
What are you...?!
No one wants to get involved
in unwanted trouble.
Please stop!
Those brats think they're something
just because they brought down a Warlord!
I found one-eh! I found a giant Mermaid-eh!
SAINT CHARLOS - A WORLD
NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
They must realize they messed up my business!
Don't push yourself.
Wow...
The Flames of Restoration only
have a limited effect on others.
Shirahoshi!
What is this? What is this?!
How's that, Shirahoshi-san?
I'm...!
The bruise is completely gone!
MARCO
FORMER 1ST DIVISION COMMANDER (SHIP'S DOCTOR)
OF THE WHITEBEARD PIRATES
You've been treated and I know
it'll be restored faster.
Father-sama...
Screw them!
Should that unruly behavior be forgiven,
Father-sama?!
Thank you very much, Mansherry-chan-sama!
You'll be jumping around by tomorrow.
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
That's a great ability!
Come on! Stop fighting!
Wow! Marco's magic!
Hey, you!
Tell those idiots from your generation!
What are you doing?! Please stop!
Good for you, Tama!
I think you two are both the biggest princess
and the smallest princess in the world!
Yeah! Chain her up!
We will never meet again.
"You'd better run!
What we were doing was just playing at being pirates!"
I'm sorry that I was
afraid of you at first...
Shirahoshi!
Wait! What are you trying to do,
Princess of Alabasta?!
I don't mind at all, Mansherry-chan-sama!
Great! Great!
Shirahoshi-chan!
Stop, Rebecca! He's a Celestial Dragon!
So you're okay now, Tama!
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
Farewell...
All countries have both
good people and bad people.
So what?! Let go of me!
They have no moral qualms!
If you make them mad, they'll destroy Dressrosa!
The Fish-Men are not an exception-jamon!
I said, "By tomorrow."
Don't jump yet!
Thanks to you,
I could keep my promise with Otohime.
I'll be who kills that brat!
Thanks, Marco!
I love you!
They've developed their skills quite a bit
during the two years they were away.
If you come, I'll kill you, Linlin!
No need to thank me, Neptune.
That bastard...!
I want to return the favor
for saving me 10 years ago.
Don't do it, Leo!
The 1st division commander of the
Whitebeard Pirates, Marco the Phoenix.
Try it. I didn't call to ask your opinion.
I just called to warn you.
I met some of them in Dressrosa.
They were very strong.
Shirahoshi...!
During the seven days of the conference,
I'll look after Princess Shirahoshi.
NAVY
I guess they had to become stronger.
He's Whitebeard's right-hand man
who fought at the front lines...
If I can use my status to help anyone,
it'd make me so happy.
Okay? I'll chop his head off!
...in the Paramount War
against the Navy two years ago.
Let's be friends... just like we used to be!
I've been told that I should keep my hands off of
the Celestial Dragons,
Whoa, come on!
but can I kick their butts
and say that it was on your orders?
No one interfere!
It's even rarer than Logia.
Come on!
Y-Yeah! If it's necessary to protect
the princess and the others,
Mythical Zoan Type.
I'll take full responsibility!
Big Mom is on the move!
Go, Slave-3!
I can't believe there is
an odd man like him...
Damn!
NAVY HEADQUARTERS, NEW MARINEFORD
It seems like she's going to meet Kaido!
I'm too weak!
I can't save anybody!
I'll make her my pet-eh!
They're using an unsecured channel.
Vivi-sama!
So he's the 1st division commander...
Damn! Damn!
They don't care about being wiretapped!
Are they trying to provoke us?
No matter what kind of attack he absorbs,
he recovers by flames...
Damn! Damn!
I can't hold myself back!
How dare he do that to our Boss's friend!
I'm sorry, Vivi-sama. I
heard there was trouble...
Damn! Damn!
Let's be friends...
Marco the Phoenix!
I should've stayed with you.
Dammit!!
Those Emperors of the Sea, Big Mom and Kaido,
can only be stopped...
Don't worry, Pell. I'm alright.
Leo!
The members of the Whitebeard Pirates
called their leader, Whitebeard, "pops"
Damn! I have no choice!
Anyway, how's my dad?
...by the Admirals or the Seven Warlords.
Cobra-sama is talking to...
I'm coming for you, Mermaid Princess!
Luffy-kun.
...Navy Admiral Fujitora
who wrote him a letter
and Whitebeard called them his "sons."
--Don't do it, soldier of Kano!
--Somebody, stop him!
Go away!
Do you want me to go handle it, Sakazuki?
Leave me alone!
as I told you and King Riku from Dressrosa.
They had incomparable cohesion.
I can't!
Wait, Borsalino...
I see...
I can't just watch you hurt yourself anymore.
Let me go!
The Land of Wano has mighty,
mysterious warriors.
Squard!
It's my own body!
It's none of your business!
Leo!
The samurai, huh?
Who are you bastards?!
Why did you do that?!
Answer me, Squard!
ROB LUCCI - CIPHER POL "AIGIS" 0
RED PORT
You should be thanking me.
Gee! Garp-chan?!
Squard once had all of his pirate
crew killed by Gold Roger.
Can't you see things clearly now?!
Kaido and Big Mom are going
after your grandson...
Cipher Pol 0...
You believed that you could overcome anything!
And Navy Admiral Akainu artfully manipulated
his deep grudge.
Yes, since we stopped you,
...Straw Hat Luffy!
And you've never doubted your strength!
several countries have been saved.
KAKU
Don't stand against the Celestial Dragons.
That's funny!
He told him the truth
that Ace was actually Roger's son
But all those formidable enemies
took away your confidence!
Even children know that.
That's not funny at all!
and lied that Whitebeard sold
the Whitebeard Pirates' lives to the Navy...
STUSSY
I heard there was a notice from above...
And your brother was your guide on the sea!
I know that you have lost a lot!
Are you gonna allow two of
the Four Emperors to team up?
GION (MOMOUSAGI)
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Yeah, since there was a ruckus
at the Mingling Plaza earlier,
Cipher Pol is a secret organization
under the direct control of the World Government.
...in exchange for Ace's life.
Well, whether we like it or not,
it's the time of the Reverie now.
And the toughest enemies in the world
blocked your way time after time!
they wanna tighten security.
Among them, "Aigis" 0 is the greatest
and the most powerful unit.
Well, I don't think even
a mouse can get in here...
All of our soldiers who could stop them
are escorting royalties!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
But if nothing is done...
And when this man, Rob Lucci...
You can't get back what you've lost!
Pardon me, young lady!
Oops...
What is it that you still have?!
and Kaku were members of CP9,
another unit of Cipher Pol,
I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
Intruder!
We're talking about Big Mom...
Stop!
She knew that the Navy
is short on soldiers...
TOKIKAKE (CHATON)
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
they got in trouble with the Straw Hats.
...because of the Reverie!
He's not outside!
You're right but...
Gee! Where did he go?!
I know how much you hate Roger...
What did Boss Sakazuki say?
CP9 caught Nico Robin
who they considered a threat and were pursuing,
He said, "The Land of Wano is a non-affiliated country
so it's outside our jurisdiction."
...so much so that I can feel your pain.
and took her to Enies Lobby,
the Island of Justice.
That's what I thought!
But, Squard, it's ridiculous to lay the blame on a child
for the sins of his father.
We'd better not get involved now!
Did Ace do something to you?
Let's go the Land of the Gods next!
I still have...
But Garp-kun...
I still have my friends!
I don't give a damn who Ace's father is.
It's a pain in the butt.
Let's get out here.
If Big Mom and Kaido are up to something,
Look at that symbol, you damn pirates!
Zoro! Nami! Usopp! Sanji!
HINA - A REAR ADMIRAL
OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
we can't just sit here and do nothing.
We all met each other on
this wide sea by chance!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
Because those two are...
Here is the core.
...the reason that you've been
called the hero of the Navy...
Not only the two of you
but all of you, I take as my sons!
That logo indicates the unity
of over 170 member countries
They are my friends!
Dragon Claw Fist!
spanning the four seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world!
"Rox," huh?
I wanna see them now...
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any other.
Dragon Breath!
I wanna see them!!
Do you now realize how completely
powerless you guys are to fight against it?!
Hina, you're young.
How do you know that?
What's the matter with you,
Usopp'n?
You are all family to me!
Before Roger,
it was definitely their time!
Do you realize how huge of an organization
this woman has been pursued by?!
You went reckless again...
I...
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
Do you wanna screw up the whole plan?
But that was 40 years ago.
The past is the past...
...have no time to waste here now!
It's fine! We'll get in a big fight with them
later anyway!
...with all your strength!
Even after they lost their captain,
they're growing in power.
I now understand well the
identity of Robin's enemy.
Luffy lost his brother in the war!
Hina's worried.
CELESTIAL DRAGON GATE
Sogeking.
Hm?
With the Whitebeard Pirates' support,
Luffy successfully freed Ace.
No need to be worried!
Shoot through that flag.
They may become a threat if they come back,
but things always defy our expectations...
He must be having a very hard time now!
Roger.
Huh?
Stop! Who are you?!
This is my new weapon,
a Giant Slingshot... named Kabuto!
And Whitebeard...
CONNEY - QUEEN DOWAGER OF THE SORBET KINGDOM
What is "Rox"?
Have a good look at its power!
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
Without a doubt, it's deeply linked to
the two of the Four Emperors - Kaido and Big Mom.
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Why it's Queen Dowager Conney
of the Sorbet Kingdom!
And its comeback is feared...
When your friend is having a hard time,
I'm gonna give you an order from the Captain
one last time!
you should be there for him!
The Land of the Gods is beyond this point.
Why are you smiling? Hina can't understand.
Oh, no...!
Pops!
You can't get by and it's dangerous
so please go back to the castle...
All of you and I will split up from here!
Robin!
Remember the Paramount War in Marineford?
We still haven't heard you say it!
It hurts-eh! It's unforgivable-eh!
Damn Mjosgard!
Everyone, survive at any cost
and go back to the New World safely!
Luffy! I know that you're okay!
What?
I'm sorry!
You've always supported us!
Say you want to live!
Saint Charlos! Please be calm!
At that time, unbelievable things
happened one after another, too...
It's our chance to return the favor!
It's bad for your wounds!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
He can't get away with this-eh...
It was your grandson who
stirred up things the most.
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
There is no ship that can bear me
in the new era!
Open the gate!
I can't believe that Straw Hat
became such a big figure...
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
What?! What's going on?!
I want to live!
Hina's surprised.
Saint Charlos is hurt!
I got it, Luffy!
Take me to the sea with you!
He needs to be treated urgently!
Go, you guys!!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Right away!
The meeting will be two years later
instead of three days later.
Not big enough...
In order to save Robin,
the Straw Hats picked a fight with CP9.
And everything else was done
just to get all the publicity.
In fact, Luffy kept up with
the shocking incidents
This is a message exclusively to us.
Luffy made a decision.
right after the Paramount
War in Marineford as well.
KAKU - CP9
A ZOAN-TYPE DEVIL FRUIT - COW-COW FRUIT
MODEL: GIRAFFE
I'll use my strongest
Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
Hurry up! To the doctor!
the one that slashed this tower...
Along with "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
Even if we rush now,
we're not good enough to get far in the New World.
and "Dark King" Rayleigh, he
boldly invaded the Navy HQ
Oh, Charlos! Are you okay?!
...and end this battle by
splitting you into two!
SAINT ROSWALD - A WORLD
NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
We have to stop once and get stronger.
and rang the bell to honor the memories of
Ace and Whitebeard.
So give it up. You have nowhere to escape.
And meet again no matter what!
I heard what happened
and I was on my way to pick you up-eh!
That encouraged the rookies with bounties of
over 100 million.
Luffy-san has made up his mind.
Well, then I have to do something, too.
Just tell me one thing, Ace.
You're the one who has to give up.
Saint Roswald!
F-Father-sama!
He always does ridiculous things.
So maybe he did it to announce
the end and the beginning of the era.
Are you happy to have me as your father?
Oh, look at you!
If I left him alone...
Demon Aura... Nine-Sword Style...
He wants to say,
My dearest son!
STRAW HAT LUFFY APPEARS IN MARINEFORD
"Whitebeard's era is over.
I'll shape the new era"?
If I left him alone,
he'd probably end up dead.
Of course I am!
...Asura!
In fact, after the war, he took the lead
among the rookies with a bounty of over 100 million.
He's not-so-bright
and high-maintenance!
Oh?
Where did Queen Dowager-sama go?
Uh-huh.
That's why I wanna help him.
Splendid! But it's too late!
Damn Mjosgard! I'll make him pay for this!
But I won't let him do whatever he wants.
You're the one who's too late.
He's a strange man who doesn't have a
Like he helped me.
Wait until you dodge this
Tempest Kick to make such a boast.
single slave even though
he's a Celestial Dragon!
However, Luffy had a
totally different motive.
I never thought that I'd want to get stronger...
Just like Homing who descended
to the lower world 30 years ago,
"3D2Y."
Sky Slicer!
...for somebody else.
Long time no see!
I'm glad that I'm present at your death!
It was a message to his far-flung friends.
the Donquixote Family are crazy-eh!
The Straw Hats swore to meet up at the
Sabaody Archipelago two years later
Pops!
Father-sama, he's...
You're the only one that I
refuse to call my son, Teech!
and started to train themselves separately.
BARTHOLOMEW KUMA - A CURRENT WARLORD OF THE SEA
(A FORMER TOP OFFICER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY)
(AND FORMER KING OF THE SORBET KINGDOM)
...the invincible slave Kuma!
My slash attack...
See you at the Sabaody Archipelago
in two years!
You broke the one and
only iron rule on my ship
...was turned into mist?!
That's right!
My turn to rent him finally came-eh!
See you at the Sabaody Archipelago
in two years!
Hardships are fine by me!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
and you killed your mate!
Bartholomew Kuma was once a pirate
They must've had unimaginably hard training days...
I will avenge the 4th division
commander - Thatch...
who was called Tyrant and feared by everyone,
...by taking this fool's life
thereby ending the matter!
And two years later,
but no one's ever had as
checkered a life as his.
Well then, Rayleigh...
they reappeared in the limelight.
Asura... Silver Mist!
Thanks again for everything!
Kuma is one of the Seven Warlords
I'm going now!
and was assigned a special mission by the
Kill him, guys!
Rise to the top!
World Government
to eliminate the Straw Hats.
Thus he suddenly emerged in front
of Luffy and the others right
Alright...
After finishing their individual training,
Let's go!
after the hard battle in Thriller Bark.
Whoa, I'm out of bullets!
Hey, give me another gun!
the Straw Hats met up at the Sabaody Archipelago
and headed to the Fish-Man Island.
Waiting for someone?
He must be a wimp who'll apologize in tears
once he hears Captain Luffy's name anyway!
It's not you!
You're still alive?!
That was the last promise
we made with Mother-sama.
So come here now!
36-Pound Phoenix!
The man that Roger is waiting for...
I'll only say it once!
She told us that
no matter who did it to her,
...is not you, Teech, at any rate!
You're no match for me
so I'm not gonna drink with you!
Is that your ability?
we should not get angry or hate anybody!
I'm sorry but I no longer belong to the weak trio
with you and Chopper.
I have the power to repel various things.
You know, Shirahoshi, what you did
is what we would call pretty stupid in this world!
Forgive me, my sons.
I am a Paw Pad Human,
having eaten the Paw-Paw Fruit.
I became a warrior
who isn't fazed by anything!
During this battle against CP9,
Luffy's power evolved drastically.
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
Did I shake them off?
Are you truly willing to die for that man?
You'll now...
At the Fish-Man Island, they rescued
Shirahoshi and the others who were captured,
You guys gave me everything.
Brook's concert?
no longer be
able to keep up with me.
Right now, it's the only way
to save my crewmates!
URGENT CREW NEEDED
and stopped the coup by
the New Fish-Man Pirates.
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
What?
All my techniques will
evolve one step further.
This is it for me.
They saved the Ryugu Kingdom from the crisis.
My ambition means nothing if
I can't protect my own captain.
What is going on?
Gear... Two!
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Robin!
Luffy will become the King of the Pirates!
Gum-Gum...
I've been traveling a very long time.
We finally see each other
but you're acting weird!
--Shave!
--...Jet Pistol!
...Elephant Gatling!
Zoro and Sanji,
you guys got along in these two years.
ROB LUCCI - CP9
A ZOAN-TYPE DEVIL FRUIT - CAT-CAT FRUIT
MODEL: LEOPARD
He has good companions.
Oh, you're being shy, you bastards!
Let's sail out!
I should have expected no less
from your son, Dragon.
Women! Real ones!
Jet Whip!
Ah, there's no doubt!
There are actual ladies in front of me!
Even though Kuma is a Warlord,
he disobeyed the Government's order
In addition...
The sweets are gone!
and for some unknown reason,
spared the Straw Hats' lives.
It was a great voyage!
I ate them all!
Did you forget, Straw Hat Luffy?
I ate 10 tons of them!
These are the real ladies that I've longed for
every single day, on this island!
You went down with a single
thrust I gave you in this form.
That's odd! What kind of pirate
doesn't have interest in treasures?
Monkey D. Luffy...
Then, Kuma reappeared in front of the Straw Hats
in the Sabaody Archipelago.
I know your name now.
What is it that you want?
Viva Sabaody!
Come! To the New World!
Oh, that... I got better after I ate meat.
At that time, his body had undergone
a tremendous change.
Hey, Newgate!
Sure, wait for me there.
Shave!
What an attractive woman before me!
Finger Pistol!
There's some business I want
to settle with you, too.
There is something that I've
wanted since I was a kid.
You're our super archaeologist -
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
--What is this?!
--He can do this, too?!
I can't leave it in your hands -
that's too dangerous!
Oh, you have something?
Why don't you tell us?
...Jet Bazooka!
Robin, aren't you?!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
Gear Three!
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
A family.
"A family?"
What is he talking about?!
I can't believe he picked a fight with
one of the Four Emperors at the Fish-Man Island.
Bone Balloon!
Gum-Gum...
I have deep appreciation.
Iron Body!
I got on...
That's funny!
...Giant Pistol!
Goodbye, my sons!
...the wrong ship.
The Straw Hats entered the New World
People think Straw Hat Luffy is dead?
and arrived at Punk Hazard,
the mysterious island where fire and snow coexist.
That's nonsense!
Tell this to the whole world!
The Kuma-looking man
who appeared in front of the Straw Hats...
In the midst of the deadly fight against Lucci,
Luffy's power evolved even more.
All right!
...was actually one of the Pacifistas,
the human weapons.
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy is alive!
Let's go, recon team!
Gear Two to Gear Three.
However, the evolution was associated
with a great risk.
While Luffy was exploring the island,
Kuma became a guinea pig for
Dr. Vegapunk, the Government's genius scientist,
He will become the King of the Pirates someday!
he met Trafalgar Law again.
Whitebeard died!
and by replicating him,
these human weapons were developed.
There are only two ways to survive
in the New World.
His departure shouldn't be a quiet one!
Oh baby!
You guys won't be able to
get past Enies Lobby after all!
The feud with Blackbeard
seemed to have ended by Whitebeard's death.
Either by living under the Four Emperors
or going against them.
That's just reality!
Wait, PX-1.
Gum-Gum... Jet Axe!
However, his true motive
was revealed thereafter.
Even if this island gets
destroyed in the process...
And I guess you're not the kind of person
who wants to work under someone.
Everybody!
Now there's another one!
Yeah, I want to stay as a captain.
I brought them!
...I'll pursue that woman who
threatens the World Government's plans...
What in the world's going on?!
Hey!
I've had enough!
Just how many of these guys are there?!
Then, we have to form an alliance!
...to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
...in the name of dark justice!
Luffy-san! I missed you so much!
An alliance?
We came to take Robin away from all that!
If you and I join forces, maybe we can do it.
You guys sure do look stronger!
Alright, let's begin!
Jet Stamp!
I have a plan...
We all got together again!
This one's...
Six King Gun!
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
...the real deal!
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
You guys!
I'm gonna put on a show!
The Emperor's name is...
I've got a lot of things that I want to share with you
but in any case,
It's a show that will shake the whole world!
Gum-Gum...
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
...Kaido, the King of the Beasts!
...Jet Gatling!
thank you for going along with
my selfish decision for two years!
As long as Shanks is not the first one to fight,
I have no problem.
That wasn't the first time.
Because...
He's right!
You've always been selfish!
Black Hole!
...I plan to beat all of the Four Emperors!
Kuma gradually lost his personality
in the process of the modifications.
That's my Dark-Dark Fruit power!
"Beat all of the Four Emperors"?
Set sail!!
However, with his own remaining free will,
We share a mutual interest
but you're underestimating them.
Yeah!
And now...
he saved the Straw Hats by sending them
away to different parts of the world.
They are the emperors of the sea who have
skirmished over territories
...this is...!
We will never meet again.
even against Whitebeard himself.
That pose is...!
And above all, they say Kaido, the King of the Beasts
is the strongest creature in the world.
We'll ally with each other
until we kill Kaido.
Farewell...
And our chances of success are...
And now, the Straw Hats...
Well, I'll just say they're really low.
The gravity of darkness brings
total annihilation!
Okay, let's do it!
And the power of tremor
destroys everything!
...have become the most prominent pirate group
in the sea world...
Later, when Kuma was deployed
in the Paramount War,
Thus, the Straw Hats and the
Heart Pirates led by Law...
I possess them both!
No one can compete with me now!
It's over...
he had already received
his final modifications.
They're a huge success.
We'll be okay now.
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
...formed the pirate alliance
to take down one of the Four Emperors - Kaido.
Yeah, if it weren't for Kuma,
they would've never made it.
I'm the strongest man in the world!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
And, with Kin'emon, the samurai
from the Land of Wano,
But as a consequence, he became...
We're gonna go back together!
Thus, Teech who ripped off the power
from Whitebeard...
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight back
although I'm a gentle person!
He's our special comrade.
they saved the captured Momonosuke...
...would later be known to the world
as one of the Four Emperors.
Robin!
I have to return the favor
for what he did for my brother!
I don't know how you know him
but you may as well give up!
...who was a son of Kozuki Oden,
the great daimyo of the Land of Wano.
Then they took down Caesar Clown,
the mad scientist and the
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
a top officer of the Revolutionary Army!
Let's save Kuma-chan - our dear friend!
--Marco...
--Marco-san...
former colleague of Dr. Vegapunk,
...I got bad stiff shoulders...
CAT VIPER - MINK TRIBE GUARDIANS
You...! What do you mean?!
What's wrong with him?!
and released the children
who were being treated as guinea pigs.
Marco, at the mountain...
After being defeated by Luffy,
Rob Lucci disappeared once,
Marco, the vegetables in my field...
You're a friend of
Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
Marco, my back hurts again!
Gum-Gum...
but he returned to Cipher Pol at some point
--Marco-chan, my knees...
--Marco, help me study...
He was once called Tyrant Kuma
and now he is...
...Grizzly Magnum!
and became a member of
their greatest unit - "Aigis" 0.
Marco, my little brother is mean to me!
All right-yoi.
I'm gonna listen to you all in order-yoi.
...dead.
Why are you laughing?
What are you talking...
The wanted poster?
In fact, he volunteered to be a guinea pig for
a study to build a human weapon...
Next, they infiltrated Dressrosa
where the Warlord - Doflamingo reigned.
Sai!
Well, his bounty tripled,
from 500 million to 1.5 billion...
...run by the Government.
The Celestial Dragons are gods
who created this world.
That's the bounty of a great pirate.
Stop lying! Kuma hates the Government!
And all we have here are
merely royals of the lower world.
We made it! Dressrosa!
Oh, it's News Coo.
Of course, you have to give a god
whatever he wants.
He wouldn't sacrifice his life for them.
After learning that the country was
unjustly governed by Doflamingo's plot,
WORLD CONFERENCE CONVENES TODAY
It finally starts.
This is the village Pops built-yoi...
I know that he wouldn't do that!
He's right-eh, you idiots!
What does?
That's not fair and it
doesn't make any sense!
The good old man Whitebeard?
What do you mean by that?
The Reverie.
And...
Luffy clashed with Doflamingo who used
the Haki of the Color of the Supreme King
But now, he doesn't even
A god doesn't need to make sense.
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
...it's finally time for the Reverie!
remember that he was born human
so he is no better than dead.
Vivi-chan-sama...
and activated his new technique - Gear Four.
Because of their extreme poverty,
PANGAEA CASTLE
they can't pay their Heavenly Tribute
and affiliate themselves with the World Government...
The sea world is divided in four...
He is a monster who fights
as the Government tells him.
Do your worst, brat!
Otohime...
...by the high wall - the Red Line...
The world that you dreamed
to live in side-by-side with humans is...
That's how it goes with
the non-affiliated countries.
Spiderweb!
He is Pacifista PX-0!
and the dangerous sea - the Grand Line...
Pirates and kidnappers do as they like
and those islands become lawless.
The world under the sun is...
EAST BLUE          NORTH BLUE
MARIEJOIS                       NEW WORLD
SOUTH BLUE         WEST BLUE
So you better forget about the past!
King Kong...
...in which Luffy and the others are traveling.
Give me back Shirahoshi! She's my friend!
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
The countries go to ruin
and tons of children become orphans...
And the World Government
is a huge organization...
God Thread!
Pops was one of those children-yoi.
...Gun!
...which is affiliated with 170 countries,
the majority of the world.
Wait, Princess of Alabasta!
He set out to sea at an early age.
King Neptune!
And two years later,
the Straw Hats got back together...
Among them, 50 representative kings and queens
assemble at this Holyland every four years.
Thank you! I won't forget your kindness!
There's something that I have to
tell you all about.
I'm afraid I must let it go now-jamon!
Even after he became a pirate,
he cared about this island
What?!
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
By heroically taking down Doflamingo,
and continued sending dirty money and resources
without revealing his identity...
I'll kick their butts
and go back to the sea bottom-jamon!
W-Where's my seat?!
Luffy freed the citizens who were suffering
from the tyranny, and the former king.
...for the rest of his life.
The news and the video that were broadcasted
to the neighboring countries spread instantly
I've been expecting you.
Even though he didn't have a family from the start
and all his friends were gone,
No! Don't hit him!
What are you doing here?!
If this is how life on the surface would be,
I can't bring my people anyway!
and shook up the world.
--Finally.
--Yeah.
this was his home.
Mission accomplished.
How's your country been?
You said it was ravaged by pirates four years ago...
Freedom... Freedom...
That's what Luffy-senpai wants...
No! This isn't how it'd be!
In this corrupt world,
there's no such a thing as clean money!
King Neptune! They don't represent humans!
Thanks to Fleet Admiral Sakazuki,
they've been sent to Impel Down.
In that case, I admire you
even more, Luffy-senpai!
I'm sorry, Otohime...
Speaking of pirates, I often hear one name lately.
I think it's...
Thank you-yoi...
There isn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
Let's face them together!
After the Paramount War,
Straw Hat Luffy, right?
And Rayleigh told me later...
In addition, the tough ones who Luffy
Then maybe we can make a difference
for the future of the children on this island,
we at least tried to defend
the things that Pops was protecting
met in Dressrosa and fought alongside
to bring down Doflamingo...
He attempted to kill Big Mom and rumor has it that
he's going after Kaido next.
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
...rallied around Luffy, and
the Straw Hat Fleet with over
Since I have a connection with them,
I wanna let them get away from here.
so we started the Grudge War against Blackbeard
who came to invade our territory...
Kaido?! Does that mean the Land of Wano
will be in turmoil next?
I think you guys half expected that.
5,600 troops total was formed.
even just a small one!
He saved our lives!
The Land of Wano is not affiliated with the World Government
so it's lawless.
Even if we give them our
love, humans won't change!
Then, Luffy and the others arrived at
the traveling country Zou
Just remember that.
Bartholomew Kuma turned out to be
one of our greatest allies.
We don't know if it's even proper
to call it a country.
I have to save Shirahoshi... Forgive me!
and learned that the Land of Wano had been
suppressed by Kaido and its shogun...
Do you dare to defy me?
Kill him, Cipher Pol 0!
Is there anything we can do?!
Why did he help Luffy and the
others get out of trouble
Yes, sir.
Let's join hands!
Get out of my way!
But we were no match for Teech
since he even got Pops' fruit-power.
Sending the Navy costs money.
Stop, Neptune the Great Night!
Don't jump the gun!
and give them chances to escape?
We're allies!
He can't explain his motive now...
Let me have Kaido's head though!
Father-sama... no!
We should not hate anyone!
How could he cause problem after problem,
that Straw Hat Luffy.
Thank you! Thank you!
Can't believe it, huh?
What's so funny, Prodence?
Our objective is...
Kuma!
He took everything away...
Luffy-kun...
Ugh...
The chairman is chosen in turn.
This is exciting-eh! Father-sama finally got to rent
the invincible slave Kuma!
Who punched a Celestial Dragon?!
...to kick Emperor Kaido's butt!
Who is it this time?
It's me!
I-I have nothing to do with this!
Okay, you fools?!
I wanted to beat the hell
out of that ingrate...
Thank you very much.
It's convenient to have
a Warlord as a slave-eh!
It's Ballywood.
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
Sounds good.
It feels good to hit him!
I think you'll run everything efficiently.
I'm sorry...
As a fellow Celestial Dragon, I feel ashamed!
Even if we have a full seven days,
we have so many things to discuss.
It feels good to stab him!
Pops was...
However, to take back Sanji
who was involved in a political marriage,
Please forgive us!
The big conference where they decide
the direction of the world.
He was actually stingy, wasn't he?
Is he a Celestial Dragon?!
the crew temporarily split up
It is called...
Let go of the Princess, you idiot!
He doesn't even scream.
He's a top-class slave-eh!
and Luffy infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
ruled by the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
All right. Let's have a good debate as always.
My apologies to everyone!
This fool brought panic to a place meant for socializing!
Nice, Father-sama! I want one, too-eh!
At last, Luffy and the others
clashed with Big Mom!
He often wanted other people's drinks
For the sake of this beautiful world!
Kings and queens of various countries!
Ow, ow, ow... I'm gonna die-eh...
and never bought us drinks!
I assume you don't remember me, Neptune...
The furious Big Mom Pirates came after them,
Keep quiet, Charlos-sama!
but they brought down the formidable Katakuri
whose bounty was over a billion.
But I was indebted to the Ryugu Kingdom
and have been waiting for this day!
That's because he was passing
all of his share of treasure to this village...
...The Reverie!
It seems like the conference has begun...
The day that you all would come here...
Buzz Cut Mochi!
During this congress, Cobra, the king of Alabasta,
is requesting to see us, too.
All of us knew it!
Don't tell me you're...
King Cobra!
Karasu!
I see...
I'm a silly Celestial Dragon...
The Nefeltari Family...
You can't get away now!
So this village is the last memento
that he left behind.
...was the only family of the First Twenty,
who stayed in the lower world 800 years ago.
...who drifted down to the
Ryugu Kingdom a decade ago...
Go!
Ow, ow, ow... I really
had a terrible time-eh...
Hurry up and save my life, you fools!
Yeah...
Oh, poor Charlos!
In a sense, they're betrayers.
Has he noticed something?
And...
Let's get the world's greatest
doctor to look at you-eh!
...Red-Haired buried him nearby...
Let's hope things don't become complicated.
Don't do it, fools! Know your place!
Who do you think I am?!
You can say the same about
Big Mom and Kaido's problem.
By the way,
--Kill him!
--Make him suffer!
a Warlord named Weevil
is proclaiming he's Pops' biological son
I didn't expect to see him this soon...
It's been two years since the Paramount War...
The swell is unstoppable now.
Show him no mercy!
Don't do it!
You stupid fish!
and attacking people connected to Whitebeard.
The balance of the world can't be maintained forever.
Mommy! Mommy!
The news about Luffy and the others
devastating Big Mom's troops and getting away safely...
I'm Whitebeard's son, right?!
We need to clean it up thoroughly soon.
JEWELRY BONNEY
A PIRATE FROM THE WORST GENERATION
CAPTAIN OF THE BONNEY PIRATES
My beard's white as well!
...spread across the world in no time.
That's right, dear!
The infiltration is successful.
You're the only biological son of
the world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard!
I think... I'll see you soon...
Queen Otohime!!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
INSIDE PANGAEA CASTLE
CHAMBER OF FLOWERS
I'll never forgive them!
And I'm...
The Queen has been shot!
Luffy!
...the woman who Whitebeard loved!
Imu-sama.
They are all here.
Ever!
Oh, is that true?!
What a pain in the neck!
And your grandson's bounty...
It's a man-loves-woman thing
so I don't know for sure,
Damn!
but I guess they're after his fortune.
...jumped to 1.5 billion berries
because of the things he has done!
Queen Otohime...
Don't get mad, Sabo...
BENEATH THE LAND OF THE GODS,
HOME TO THE CELESTIAL DRAGONS
Everybody, drop your gun!
They won't take our word for
it that there isn't any.
Gee, boys scare me!
Both this place and I will become their target
sooner or later-yoi.
It's hard not to get mad!
He's still just a fledgling!
Children are watching!
Our friend is going through hell like that!
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
I see.
Now, even at the Holyland of Mariejois,
Our gentle Kuma!
Then you can't leave-meow.
PANGAEA CASTLE
the unexpected was about to happen...
Otohime-sama...
It's unforgivable...
Weevil's mother Buckin used to be a pirate.
It's just a scratch.
ROOM OF AUTHORITY
Calm down.
Why do you protect him?
I know 30-something years or nearly 40 years ago,
she was on the same ship with Pops.
We got you. We all feel the same.
You don't know what he did to us in the past!
We won't leave Kuma-san like that!
I can feel your anguish - it's very painful.
FIVE ELDERS
HIGHEST AUTHORITIES OF THE WORLD GOVERNMENT
That's what we came here for...
Then, maybe he's also a memento
that should be protected.
I know it's hard but...
What did you come all the way here for?
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
toward humans in children's mind!
Having said that, even if we set him free,
he'll never return to his old self...
It's the time of the Reverie now...
His behavior tells me otherwise-yoi!
Considering your status, you
should stay away from politics.
You're right!
But Kuma-chan is a prime example of
the World Government's oppression!
They need a chance to meet humans
and figure them out on their own.
Since it's you, we made time.
If you're going to see Straw Hat Luffy,
I want you to pass on a message, Cat Viper.
Yes... I appreciate that.
Kuma-san is formerly a king
of an affiliated nation.
SAINT DONQUIXOTE MJOSGARD
A WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
Let's hear it.
Guys, would you excuse us?
I was admonished by the late Queen Otohime
That's why they used him as a warning.
Yeah, no problem.
and became a decent human!
Yes, sir!
Have you decided which "light"
needs to be extinguished...
--You said you're gonna go to the Land of Wano?
--Yeah.
To say that no matter how tough you are,
this is how you end up if you disobey the gods!
I would do anything to help your people!
What are you planning to do there?
...From history this time?
King Neptune! It's my honor to see you again!
The Celestial Dragons have CP-0
and the Navy Headquarters on their side.
Cipher Pol! Retreat from here!
We'll take down Kaido!
If so, share the name with us!
If we blunder and get caught...
The Emperor of the Sea - Kaido?!
Blundering is not an option.
It's either success...
Luffy, that fool...
Is he gonna pick a fight with Kaido this time?!
...or death!
I want to talk to you
about a certain pirate...
The Straw Hats enter an unknown sea area!
The Reverie has finally begun!
Cat Viper and his clan meet Marco at Whitebeard's homeland.
Will Marco stand up again?!
Meanwhile the Five Elders, the highest
authorities of the world, are secretly on the move!
Will they be able to reach the Land of
Wano that is shut to all outsiders?!
Sabo and the Revolutionary Army start
their mission to sneak into Mariejois.
Kaido and Big Mom talk to each other about going after Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Marco! The Keeper of Whitebeard's Last Memento!"
"Finally, It Starts! The Conspiracy-filled Reverie!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
The two angry Emperors of
the Sea are on the move!
After overcoming various
obstacles, Sabo finally reaches
"Climbing Up a Waterfall!
A Great Journey Through the Land of Wano's Sea Zone!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
While the Navy raises the level of caution
to deal with the unprecedented situation,
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
the Land of the Gods where
the Celestial Dragons live,
an even more unimaginable thing is about
to happen in Mariejois!
but there, he is shocked
at the appearance of the
I'm gonna kick the Emperor of the Sea, Kaido's butt!
I'm gonna kick the Emperor
of the Sea, Kaido's butt!
Revolutionary Army's
warrior Bartholomew Kuma!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Tough enemies are waiting for him!
Samurai, shogun, and ninja!
"An Explosive Situation! Two Emperors
of the Sea Going After Luffy!"
"Sabo Enraged!
The Tragedy of the Revolutionary Army Officer Kuma!"
One Piece! The Land of Wano
Arc will finally begin!
One Piece! The Land of Wano Arc will finally begin!
One Piece! The Land of Wano
Arc will finally begin!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
LAND OF WANO ARC STARTS
SUNDAY, JULY 7TH! (JST)
LAND OF WANO ARC STARTS SUNDAY, JULY 7TH! (JST)
LAND OF WANO ARC STARTS
SUNDAY, JULY 7TH! (JST)