Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era
is experiencing a groundswell
beyond the World Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"An Explosive Situation!
Two Emperors of the Sea Going After Luffy!"
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Kaido-sama!
What is it?!
Are you trying to disturb me while I'm drinking?!
No! I'd never do that!
The thing is...
WHOLE CAKE ISLAND
What do you want?!
It's about Straw Hat.
He's on his way to you...
So what?
Listen, keep your hands off of him!
I'll come to the Land of Wano
to chop Straw Hat's head off myself.
Is that some kind of joke?! I refuse!
It has nothing to do with you.
I must cut off his head
or I'll keep losing face!
There's something I want
to take back from him, too!
I don't care!
I think you owe me quite a favor.
A favor?
You do remember it, don't you?
That was a long time ago.
But that's a lifetime debt.
I have greater resentment
towards that brat - Straw Hat!
Kaido used to buy tons of SMILEs,
those artificial Devil Fruits Doflamingo was manufacturing,
in order to form the ultimate pirate group
made of all Devil Fruit eaters.
However...
This damn factory that gave
you Tontattas a hard time!
Destroy it!!
The SMILE manufacturing factory in Dressrosa
was destroyed by the Straw Hats.
Straw Hat Luffy! Trafalgar Law!
I know! They're from the generation, right?!
Those brats think they're something
just because they brought down a Warlord!
They must realize they messed up my business!
Screw them!
Hey, you!
Tell those idiots from your generation!
"You'd better run!
What we were doing was just playing at being pirates!"
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
I'll be who kills that brat!
If you come, I'll kill you, Linlin!
Try it. I didn't call to ask your opinion.
I just called to warn you.
Okay? I'll chop his head off!
Let's be friends... just like we used to be!
Big Mom is on the move!
NAVY HEADQUARTERS, NEW MARINEFORD
It seems like she's going to meet Kaido!
They're using an unsecured channel.
They don't care about being wiretapped!
Are they trying to provoke us?
Let's be friends...
Those Emperors of the Sea, Big Mom and Kaido,
can only be stopped...
...by the Admirals or the Seven Warlords.
Do you want me to go handle it, Sakazuki?
Wait, Borsalino...
The Land of Wano has mighty,
mysterious warriors.
The samurai, huh?
RED PORT
Gee! Garp-chan?!
Kaido and Big Mom are going
after your grandson...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
That's funny!
That's not funny at all!
Are you gonna allow two of
the Four Emperors to team up?
GION (MOMOUSAGI)
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Well, whether we like it or not,
it's the time of the Reverie now.
All of our soldiers who could stop them
are escorting royalties!
But if nothing is done...
Pardon me, young lady!
We're talking about Big Mom...
She knew that the Navy
is short on soldiers...
TOKIKAKE (CHATON)
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
...because of the Reverie!
You're right but...
What did Boss Sakazuki say?
He said, "The Land of Wano is a non-affiliated country
so it's outside our jurisdiction."
That's what I thought!
We'd better not get involved now!
But Garp-kun...
If Big Mom and Kaido are up to something,
HINA - A REAR ADMIRAL
OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
we can't just sit here and do nothing.
Because those two are...
...the reason that you've been
called the hero of the Navy...
"Rox," huh?
Hina, you're young.
How do you know that?
Before Roger,
it was definitely their time!
But that was 40 years ago.
The past is the past...
Even after they lost their captain,
they're growing in power.
Hina's worried.
No need to be worried!
They may become a threat if they come back,
but things always defy our expectations...
What is "Rox"?
Without a doubt, it's deeply linked to
the two of the Four Emperors - Kaido and Big Mom.
And its comeback is feared...
Why are you smiling? Hina can't understand.
Remember the Paramount War in Marineford?
What?
At that time, unbelievable things
happened one after another, too...
It was your grandson who
stirred up things the most.
I can't believe that Straw Hat
became such a big figure...
Hina's surprised.
Not big enough...
In fact, Luffy kept up with
the shocking incidents
right after the Paramount
War in Marineford as well.
Along with "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
and "Dark King" Rayleigh, he
boldly invaded the Navy HQ
and rang the bell to honor the memories of
Ace and Whitebeard.
That encouraged the rookies with bounties of
over 100 million.
So maybe he did it to announce
the end and the beginning of the era.
He wants to say,
STRAW HAT LUFFY APPEARS IN MARINEFORD
"Whitebeard's era is over.
I'll shape the new era"?
In fact, after the war, he took the lead
among the rookies with a bounty of over 100 million.
But I won't let him do whatever he wants.
However, Luffy had a
totally different motive.
"3D2Y."
It was a message to his far-flung friends.
The Straw Hats swore to meet up at the
Sabaody Archipelago two years later
and started to train themselves separately.
See you at the Sabaody Archipelago
in two years!
Well then, Rayleigh...
Thanks again for everything!
I'm going now!
Rise to the top!
After finishing their individual training,
the Straw Hats met up at the Sabaody Archipelago
and headed to the Fish-Man Island.
That was the last promise
we made with Mother-sama.
She told us that
no matter who did it to her,
we should not get angry or hate anybody!
You know, Shirahoshi, what you did
is what we would call pretty stupid in this world!
Father-sama! Brothers-sama!
At the Fish-Man Island, they rescued
Shirahoshi and the others who were captured,
and stopped the coup by
the New Fish-Man Pirates.
They saved the Ryugu Kingdom from the crisis.
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gatling!
In addition...
The sweets are gone!
I ate them all!
I ate 10 tons of them!
Monkey D. Luffy...
I know your name now.
Come! To the New World!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business I want
to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your hands -
that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
I can't believe he picked a fight with
one of the Four Emperors at the Fish-Man Island.
That's funny!
The Straw Hats entered the New World
and arrived at Punk Hazard,
the mysterious island where fire and snow coexist.
All right!
Let's go, recon team!
While Luffy was exploring the island,
he met Trafalgar Law again.
There are only two ways to survive
in the New World.
Either by living under the Four Emperors
or going against them.
And I guess you're not the kind of person
who wants to work under someone.
Yeah, I want to stay as a captain.
Then, we have to form an alliance!
An alliance?
If you and I join forces, maybe we can do it.
I have a plan...
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
The Emperor's name is...
...Kaido, the King of the Beasts!
As long as Shanks is not the first one to fight,
I have no problem.
Because...
...I plan to beat all of the Four Emperors!
"Beat all of the Four Emperors"?
We share a mutual interest
but you're underestimating them.
They are the emperors of the sea who have
skirmished over territories
even against Whitebeard himself.
And above all, they say Kaido, the King of the Beasts
is the strongest creature in the world.
We'll ally with each other
until we kill Kaido.
And our chances of success are...
Well, I'll just say they're really low.
Okay, let's do it!
Thus, the Straw Hats and the
Heart Pirates led by Law...
...formed the pirate alliance
to take down one of the Four Emperors - Kaido.
And, with Kin'emon, the samurai
from the Land of Wano,
they saved the captured Momonosuke...
...who was a son of Kozuki Oden,
the great daimyo of the Land of Wano.
Then they took down Caesar Clown,
the mad scientist and the
former colleague of Dr. Vegapunk,
and released the children
who were being treated as guinea pigs.
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Next, they infiltrated Dressrosa
where the Warlord - Doflamingo reigned.
We made it! Dressrosa!
After learning that the country was
unjustly governed by Doflamingo's plot,
Luffy clashed with Doflamingo who used
the Haki of the Color of the Supreme King
and activated his new technique - Gear Four.
Do your worst, brat!
Spiderweb!
King Kong...
Sixteen Holy Bullets!
God Thread!
...Gun!
By heroically taking down Doflamingo,
Luffy freed the citizens who were suffering
from the tyranny, and the former king.
The news and the video that were broadcasted
to the neighboring countries spread instantly
and shook up the world.
Freedom... Freedom...
That's what Luffy-senpai wants...
In that case, I admire you
even more, Luffy-senpai!
In addition, the tough ones who Luffy
met in Dressrosa and fought alongside
to bring down Doflamingo...
...rallied around Luffy, and
the Straw Hat Fleet with over
5,600 troops total was formed.
Then, Luffy and the others arrived at
the traveling country Zou
and learned that the Land of Wano had been
suppressed by Kaido and its shogun...
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
Thank you! Thank you!
Our objective is...
...to kick Emperor Kaido's butt!
We're the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance!
However, to take back Sanji
who was involved in a political marriage,
the crew temporarily split up
and Luffy infiltrated the Whole Cake Island
ruled by the Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom.
At last, Luffy and the others
clashed with Big Mom!
The furious Big Mom Pirates came after them,
but they brought down the formidable Katakuri
whose bounty was over a billion.
Buzz Cut Mochi!
King Cobra!
You can't get away now!
Go!
The news about Luffy and the others
devastating Big Mom's troops and getting away safely...
...spread across the world in no time.
I think... I'll see you soon...
Luffy!
What a pain in the neck!
And your grandson's bounty...
...jumped to 1.5 billion berries
because of the things he has done!
He's still just a fledgling!
HOLYLAND OF MARIEJOIS
Now, even at the Holyland of Mariejois,
PANGAEA CASTLE
the unexpected was about to happen...
ROOM OF AUTHORITY
FIVE ELDERS
HIGHEST AUTHORITIES OF THE WORLD GOVERNMENT
What did you come all the way here for?
It's the time of the Reverie now...
Considering your status, you
should stay away from politics.
Since it's you, we made time.
Yes... I appreciate that.
Let's hear it.
Guys, would you excuse us?
Yes, sir!
I want to talk to you
about a certain pirate...
Sabo and the Revolutionary Army start
their mission to sneak into Mariejois.
After overcoming various
obstacles, Sabo finally reaches
the Land of the Gods where
the Celestial Dragons live,
but there, he is shocked
at the appearance of the
Revolutionary Army's
warrior Bartholomew Kuma!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sabo Enraged!
The Tragedy of the Revolutionary Army Officer Kuma!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!