Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"Sabo Enraged!
The Tragedy of the Revolutionary Army Officer Kuma!"
PANGAEA CASTLE
The Pangaea Castle has...
...three gates outside of its main gate
and all of them are guarded.
One of those gates is the
Celestial Dragon Gate
which leads to the Land of the Gods
where the Celestial Dragons live...
--I came at the request for reinforcements.
--Yes, we're aware.
Open the gate!
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing there?!
Put your hands up and turn around slowly!
MINGLING PLAZA IN THE PANGAEA CASTLE
A lot of people are gone...
It's to be expected
after something like that happened.
No one wants to get involved
in unwanted trouble.
Wow...
How's that, Shirahoshi-san?
The bruise is completely gone!
Thank you very much, Mansherry-chan-sama!
That's a great ability!
I think you two are both the biggest princess
and the smallest princess in the world!
I'm sorry that I was
afraid of you at first...
I don't mind at all, Mansherry-chan-sama!
All countries have both
good people and bad people.
The Fish-Men are not an exception-jamon!
Thanks to you,
I could keep my promise with Otohime.
No need to thank me, Neptune.
I want to return the favor
for saving me 10 years ago.
During the seven days of the conference,
I'll look after Princess Shirahoshi.
If I can use my status to help anyone,
it'd make me so happy.
I've been told that I should keep my hands off of
the Celestial Dragons,
but can I kick their butts
and say that it was on your orders?
Y-Yeah! If it's necessary to protect
the princess and the others,
I'll take full responsibility!
I can't believe there is
an odd man like him...
Vivi-sama!
I'm sorry, Vivi-sama. I
heard there was trouble...
I should've stayed with you.
Don't worry, Pell. I'm alright.
Anyway, how's my dad?
Cobra-sama is talking to...
...Navy Admiral Fujitora
who wrote him a letter
as I told you and King Riku from Dressrosa.
I see...
I heard there was a notice from above...
Yeah, since there was a ruckus
at the Mingling Plaza earlier,
they wanna tighten security.
Well, I don't think even
a mouse can get in here...
Oops...
Intruder!
Stop!
He's not outside!
Gee! Where did he go?!
Let's go the Land of the Gods next!
It's a pain in the butt.
Let's get out here.
Here is the core.
Dragon Claw Fist!
Dragon Breath!
You went reckless again...
Do you wanna screw up the whole plan?
It's fine! We'll get in a big fight with them
later anyway!
CELESTIAL DRAGON GATE
Stop! Who are you?!
CONNEY - QUEEN DOWAGER OF THE SORBET KINGDOM
Why it's Queen Dowager Conney
of the Sorbet Kingdom!
The Land of the Gods is beyond this point.
You can't get by and it's dangerous
so please go back to the castle...
It hurts-eh! It's unforgivable-eh!
Damn Mjosgard!
Saint Charlos! Please be calm!
It's bad for your wounds!
He can't get away with this-eh...
Open the gate!
What?! What's going on?!
Saint Charlos is hurt!
He needs to be treated urgently!
Right away!
Hurry up! To the doctor!
Oh, Charlos! Are you okay?!
SAINT ROSWALD - A WORLD
NOBLE (CELESTIAL DRAGON)
I heard what happened
and I was on my way to pick you up-eh!
Saint Roswald!
F-Father-sama!
Oh, look at you!
My dearest son!
Oh?
Where did Queen Dowager-sama go?
Damn Mjosgard! I'll make him pay for this!
He's a strange man who doesn't have a
single slave even though
he's a Celestial Dragon!
Just like Homing who descended
to the lower world 30 years ago,
the Donquixote Family are crazy-eh!
Father-sama, he's...
BARTHOLOMEW KUMA - A CURRENT WARLORD OF THE SEA
(A FORMER TOP OFFICER OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY)
(AND FORMER KING OF THE SORBET KINGDOM)
...the invincible slave Kuma!
That's right!
My turn to rent him finally came-eh!
Bartholomew Kuma was once a pirate
who was called Tyrant and feared by everyone,
but no one's ever had as
checkered a life as his.
Kuma is one of the Seven Warlords
and was assigned a special mission by the
World Government
to eliminate the Straw Hats.
Thus he suddenly emerged in front
of Luffy and the others right
after the hard battle in Thriller Bark.
36-Pound Phoenix!
Is that your ability?
I have the power to repel various things.
I am a Paw Pad Human,
having eaten the Paw-Paw Fruit.
Are you truly willing to die for that man?
Right now, it's the only way
to save my crewmates!
My ambition means nothing if
I can't protect my own captain.
Luffy will become the King of the Pirates!
He has good companions.
I should have expected no less
from your son, Dragon.
Even though Kuma is a Warlord,
he disobeyed the Government's order
and for some unknown reason,
spared the Straw Hats' lives.
Then, Kuma reappeared in front of the Straw Hats
in the Sabaody Archipelago.
At that time, his body had undergone
a tremendous change.
--What is this?!
--He can do this, too?!
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
The Kuma-looking man
who appeared in front of the Straw Hats...
...was actually one of the Pacifistas,
the human weapons.
Kuma became a guinea pig for
Dr. Vegapunk, the Government's genius scientist,
and by replicating him,
these human weapons were developed.
Wait, PX-1.
Now there's another one!
What in the world's going on?!
I've had enough!
Just how many of these guys are there?!
This one's...
...the real deal!
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
Kuma gradually lost his personality
in the process of the modifications.
However, with his own remaining free will,
he saved the Straw Hats by sending them
away to different parts of the world.
We will never meet again.
Farewell...
Later, when Kuma was deployed
in the Paramount War,
he had already received
his final modifications.
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight back
although I'm a gentle person!
I don't know how you know him
but you may as well give up!
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
a top officer of the Revolutionary Army!
You...! What do you mean?!
What's wrong with him?!
You're a friend of
Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
He was once called Tyrant Kuma
and now he is...
...dead.
What are you talking...
In fact, he volunteered to be a guinea pig for
a study to build a human weapon...
...run by the Government.
Stop lying! Kuma hates the Government!
He wouldn't sacrifice his life for them.
I know that he wouldn't do that!
But now, he doesn't even
remember that he was born human
so he is no better than dead.
He is a monster who fights
as the Government tells him.
He is Pacifista PX-0!
So you better forget about the past!
And two years later,
the Straw Hats got back together...
There's something that I have to
tell you all about.
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
I've been expecting you.
What are you doing here?!
Mission accomplished.
There isn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
And Rayleigh told me later...
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
Since I have a connection with them,
I wanna let them get away from here.
I think you guys half expected that.
He saved our lives!
Just remember that.
Bartholomew Kuma turned out to be
one of our greatest allies.
Why did he help Luffy and the
others get out of trouble
and give them chances to escape?
He can't explain his motive now...
Kuma!
This is exciting-eh! Father-sama finally got to rent
the invincible slave Kuma!
It's convenient to have
a Warlord as a slave-eh!
It feels good to hit him!
It feels good to stab him!
He doesn't even scream.
He's a top-class slave-eh!
Nice, Father-sama! I want one, too-eh!
Ow, ow, ow... I'm gonna die-eh...
Keep quiet, Charlos-sama!
Karasu!
Ow, ow, ow... I really
had a terrible time-eh...
Oh, poor Charlos!
Let's get the world's greatest
doctor to look at you-eh!
I didn't expect to see him this soon...
JEWELRY BONNEY
A PIRATE FROM THE WORST GENERATION
CAPTAIN OF THE BONNEY PIRATES
The infiltration is successful.
I'll never forgive them!
Ever!
Damn!
Don't get mad, Sabo...
BENEATH THE LAND OF THE GODS,
HOME TO THE CELESTIAL DRAGONS
Gee, boys scare me!
It's hard not to get mad!
Our friend is going through hell like that!
Our gentle Kuma!
It's unforgivable...
Calm down.
We got you. We all feel the same.
We won't leave Kuma-san like that!
That's what we came here for...
Having said that, even if we set him free,
he'll never return to his old self...
But Kuma-chan is a prime example of
the World Government's oppression!
Kuma-san is formerly a king
of an affiliated nation.
That's why they used him as a warning.
To say that no matter how tough you are,
this is how you end up if you disobey the gods!
The Celestial Dragons have CP-0
and the Navy Headquarters on their side.
If we blunder and get caught...
Blundering is not an option.
It's either success...
...or death!
The Reverie has finally begun!
Meanwhile the Five Elders, the highest
authorities of the world, are secretly on the move!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally, It Starts! The Conspiracy-filled Reverie!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna kick the Emperor
of the Sea, Kaido's butt!
Tough enemies are waiting for him!
Samurai, shogun, and ninja!
One Piece! The Land of Wano
Arc will finally begin!
LAND OF WANO ARC STARTS
SUNDAY, JULY 7TH! (JST)