Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
saikou no yume shinjiau
Believing a great dream together
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
The Great Pirate Era is experiencing
a groundswell beyond the World
Government's expectation.
Being at the center of the unstoppable swell
and drawing the most attention is...
Monkey D. Luffy!
And the Straw Hats!
In order to cope with the
turbulent Great Pirate Era,
50 leaders hold the World Conference
every four years.
Known as the Reverie, it is about to start.
The times are changing drastically now.
"Marco!
The Keeper of Whitebeard's Last Memento!"
There is something that I've
wanted since I was a kid.
NEW WORLD
This place looks terrible, too.
There are traces of robberies across the city.
What happened here?
MINK TRIBE GUARDIANS
Master Cat Viper's navigation
skill was quite formidable!
That's what I'd expected from a man
who sailed on the ship of the King of the Pirates!
Now, how much longer should we wait
in these ruins?
Until Master Cat Viper brings Marco here!
I wonder if he'll show...
If Marco comes along with us to the Land of Wano,
he'll make for a strong ally.
Marco is the former 1st division commander of
the infamous Whitebeard Pirates!
People call him Marco the Phoenix!
I was surprised to know
that he's Master's friend!
All right!
I'm gonna go take a look at that man, too.
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait!
Master told you to wait here
because you-gara got a scary face!
Hmph! Is he the kind of guy
who'll get frightened by my face?!
Listen!
He said there is a peaceful village
on the other side of a cave at the back of that waterfall...
A group of warriors like us
will scare its residents.
You're right.
But Master Cat Viper's
face is scarier than mine!
Yes, when he gets mad.
--But he's cute when he smiles.
--Certainly!
There!
Hey, wait!
Okay.
His treatment is finished.
He can go now-yoi.
He said you can go now.
Tama, can you stand?
Don't push yourself.
The Flames of Restoration only
have a limited effect on others.
MARCO
FORMER 1ST DIVISION COMMANDER (SHIP'S DOCTOR)
OF THE WHITEBEARD PIRATES
You've been treated and I know
it'll be restored faster.
You'll be jumping around by tomorrow.
Wow! Marco's magic!
Good for you, Tama!
Great! Great!
So you're okay now, Tama!
I said, "By tomorrow."
Don't jump yet!
Thanks, Marco!
I love you!
The 1st division commander of the
Whitebeard Pirates, Marco the Phoenix.
NAVY
He's Whitebeard's right-hand man
who fought at the front lines...
...in the Paramount War
against the Navy two years ago.
It's even rarer than Logia.
Mythical Zoan Type.
So he's the 1st division commander...
No matter what kind of attack he absorbs,
he recovers by flames...
Marco the Phoenix!
The members of the Whitebeard Pirates
called their leader, Whitebeard, "pops"
and Whitebeard called them his "sons."
They had incomparable cohesion.
Squard!
Why did you do that?!
Answer me, Squard!
Squard once had all of his pirate
crew killed by Gold Roger.
And Navy Admiral Akainu artfully manipulated
his deep grudge.
He told him the truth
that Ace was actually Roger's son
and lied that Whitebeard sold
the Whitebeard Pirates' lives to the Navy...
...in exchange for Ace's life.
I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
I know how much you hate Roger...
...so much so that I can feel your pain.
But, Squard, it's ridiculous to lay the blame on a child
for the sins of his father.
Did Ace do something to you?
I don't give a damn who Ace's father is.
We all met each other on
this wide sea by chance!
Not only the two of you
but all of you, I take as my sons!
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any other.
You are all family to me!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
...with all your strength!
With the Whitebeard Pirates' support,
Luffy successfully freed Ace.
And Whitebeard...
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm gonna give you an order from the Captain
one last time!
Pops!
All of you and I will split up from here!
Everyone, survive at any cost
and go back to the New World safely!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
There is no ship that can bear me
in the new era!
Go, you guys!!
Just tell me one thing, Ace.
Are you happy to have me as your father?
Of course I am!
Long time no see!
I'm glad that I'm present at your death!
Pops!
You're the only one that I
refuse to call my son, Teech!
You broke the one and
only iron rule on my ship
and you killed your mate!
I will avenge the 4th division
commander - Thatch...
...by taking this fool's life
thereby ending the matter!
Kill him, guys!
Whoa, I'm out of bullets!
Hey, give me another gun!
It's not you!
You're still alive?!
The man that Roger is waiting for...
...is not you, Teech, at any rate!
Forgive me, my sons.
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
You guys gave me everything.
This is it for me.
I've been traveling a very long time.
Let's sail out!
It was a great voyage!
That's odd! What kind of pirate
doesn't have interest in treasures?
What is it that you want?
Hey, Newgate!
There is something that I've
wanted since I was a kid.
Oh, you have something?
Why don't you tell us?
A family.
"A family?"
What is he talking about?!
I have deep appreciation.
Goodbye, my sons!
Whitebeard died!
The feud with Blackbeard
seemed to have ended by Whitebeard's death.
However, his true motive
was revealed thereafter.
Alright, let's begin!
I'm gonna put on a show!
It's a show that will shake the whole world!
Black Hole!
That's my Dark-Dark Fruit power!
And now...
...this is...!
That pose is...!
The gravity of darkness brings
total annihilation!
And the power of tremor
destroys everything!
I possess them both!
No one can compete with me now!
I'm the strongest man in the world!
Thus, Teech who ripped off the power
from Whitebeard...
...would later be known to the world
as one of the Four Emperors.
--Marco...
--Marco-san...
...I got bad stiff shoulders...
CAT VIPER - MINK TRIBE GUARDIANS
Marco, at the mountain...
Marco, the vegetables in my field...
Marco, my back hurts again!
--Marco-chan, my knees...
--Marco, help me study...
Marco, my little brother is mean to me!
All right-yoi.
I'm gonna listen to you all in order-yoi.
This is the village Pops built-yoi...
The good old man Whitebeard?
What do you mean by that?
Because of their extreme poverty,
they can't pay their Heavenly Tribute
and affiliate themselves with the World Government...
That's how it goes with
the non-affiliated countries.
Pirates and kidnappers do as they like
and those islands become lawless.
The countries go to ruin
and tons of children become orphans...
Pops was one of those children-yoi.
He set out to sea at an early age.
Even after he became a pirate,
he cared about this island
and continued sending dirty money and resources
without revealing his identity...
...for the rest of his life.
Even though he didn't have a family from the start
and all his friends were gone,
this was his home.
In this corrupt world,
there's no such a thing as clean money!
Thank you-yoi...
After the Paramount War,
we at least tried to defend
the things that Pops was protecting
so we started the Grudge War against Blackbeard
who came to invade our territory...
But we were no match for Teech
since he even got Pops' fruit-power.
He took everything away...
I wanted to beat the hell
out of that ingrate...
Pops was...
He was actually stingy, wasn't he?
He often wanted other people's drinks
and never bought us drinks!
That's because he was passing
all of his share of treasure to this village...
All of us knew it!
I see...
So this village is the last memento
that he left behind.
Yeah...
And...
...Red-Haired buried him nearby...
By the way,
a Warlord named Weevil
is proclaiming he's Pops' biological son
and attacking people connected to Whitebeard.
Mommy! Mommy!
I'm Whitebeard's son, right?!
My beard's white as well!
That's right, dear!
You're the only biological son of
the world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
And I'm...
...the woman who Whitebeard loved!
Oh, is that true?!
It's a man-loves-woman thing
so I don't know for sure,
but I guess they're after his fortune.
They won't take our word for
it that there isn't any.
Both this place and I will become their target
sooner or later-yoi.
I see.
Then you can't leave-meow.
Weevil's mother Buckin used to be a pirate.
I know 30-something years or nearly 40 years ago,
she was on the same ship with Pops.
Then, maybe he's also a memento
that should be protected.
His behavior tells me otherwise-yoi!
You're right!
If you're going to see Straw Hat Luffy,
I want you to pass on a message, Cat Viper.
Yeah, no problem.
--You said you're gonna go to the Land of Wano?
--Yeah.
What are you planning to do there?
We'll take down Kaido!
The Emperor of the Sea - Kaido?!
Luffy, that fool...
Is he gonna pick a fight with Kaido this time?!
The Straw Hats enter an unknown sea area!
Will they be able to reach the Land of
Wano that is shut to all outsiders?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Climbing Up a Waterfall!
A Great Journey Through the Land of Wano's Sea Zone!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna kick the Emperor
of the Sea, Kaido's butt!
Tough enemies are waiting for him!
Samurai, shogun, and ninja!
One Piece! The Land of Wano
Arc will finally begin!
LAND OF WANO ARC STARTS
SUNDAY, JULY 7TH! (JST)