One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
Yes! We've got Super Powers
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
Yes! We've got Super Powers
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
Yes! We've got Super Powers
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
Always and forever...
eien ni...
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
One Dream One Wish
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
Over The Top
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Ring, ring, ring...
Separated from Sanji and the others,
Luffy arrived on the Land of Wano alone
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Ring, ring, ring...
and saved Otama from Kaido's soldiers.
Led by Luffy, the Straw Hats entered
the sea around the Land of Wano.
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Ring, ring, ring...
Listen, guys. You're in the Land of Wano.
I'll kill you!
Ring, ring, ring...
The Shogun's name is...
Yes! We're the Super Powers
Ring, ring, ring...
There's no turning back!
...Kurozumi Orochi!
It's a strong wind!
Carrot, furl the sail!
Ring, ring, ring...
Yes! We're the Super Powers
--Okay!
--I'll help!
Clank.
Until all of our allies get here
and we're ready to fight,
Now...
I need to know if this is
the Land of Wano or not.
Oh no! It's coming!
Why are carp in the sea?!
How's business, Cidre-kun?!
we can't let them know who we are!
Yes! We're the Super Powers
This country?
Oh! Look at that!
The best bounty hunter of this generation!
So pretend that you're citizens for now
Yes, this is the Land of Wano!
Climbing up the large waterfall
that was in their way,
What do you want,
Festa, Master of Festivities?!
and quietly and peacefully,
You're in a region called Kuri
in the Land of Wano!
they thought that
they had finally reached the Land of Wano...
"Climbing Up a Waterfall!
A Great Journey Through the Land of Wano's Sea Zone!"
I'm hunting pirates now!
Call me later!
play your roles!
Big Bro!
ON THE SEA IN THE NEW WORLD
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
Luffy! Let go of those carp!
No! They're my dinner!
Big Bro! Big Bro! Big Bro!
Big Bro! Big Bro!
So you're in the middle of
making money as we speak!
Big Bro? Why do you call me "Big Bro"?
With Luffy and the others on board,
They have been drawn into a massive whirlpool
along with the Sunny.
the Sunny is on its way to
their next destination - the Land of Wano.
Well...!
Where did they go?
Because you saved my life,
you're my Big Bro!
"Side Story!
The World's Greatest Bounty Hunter, Cidre!"
Luffy! It says the Reverie has begun!
Kings and queens from all over the world
are attending the conference at Mariejois!
Oh, I see!
"The Land of Wano!
To the Samurai Country where Cherry Blossoms Flutter!"
Hmmm...
This time, all eyes are on the Ryugu Kingdom
Ya-hoo!
since they're joining for the
first time in two centuries!
Neptune-san and the brothers are there...
Hey!
"He'll Come!
The Legend of Ace in the Land of Wano!"
And it says there was great applause
for Shirahoshi at Red Port!
Dammit!
Chopper! Put out the fire now!
Hey, you! Don't break our ship!
Now...
So she came up to the surface!
She became much stronger, that Yowahoshi!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Why were you being chased?
It's a giant dog!
Gust Sword!
Well...
Is it a dog or boar?
STRAW HAT LUFFY - CAPTAIN OF THE STRAW HAT PIRATES
BOUNTY: 1.5 BILLION BERRIES
It seems like your grandpa was their escort.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Oh...
I went to the town for shopping...
They took a big step towards their dream
to relocate the Fish-Men to the surface!
But on my way home,
that evil one's men with the baboon found me.
Poele a Frire Spectre!
Vivi-chan!
To protect me, Komachiyo
attacked the baboon...
You became an even more beautiful princess!
Three-Pace Hum...
Uh, that's why you guys were in a fight.
Who could it be for?
...Notch Slash!
Me?! Hey, is it for me?!
Meanwhile...
A BABOON
How annoying!
They stole everything I bought!
Out of anger,
I said something that goes against the law.
Vivi!
Go down! Go down!
It's Vivi!
Tres Fleurs!
It's been a while! I haven't
seen her for a long time!
Clutch!
A sword-using animal?
She's become a graceful and regal princess!
So I guess this is the Land of Wano!
Oh, so this is Vivi-san.
When the Kozuki Clan comes back,
they'll teach you a lesson!
When I get to see her someday,
I'd like to see her panties...
"Otama Appears!
Luffy vs. Kaido's Army!"
No way!
What?!
They keep coming in one after the other!
Let go of me!
Oh, these are photos of the Mingling Plaza...
Look at all the royals
and bodyguards who came along.
I thought I'd never be able to go home again,
Cidre-kun!
I-If Dressrosa is participating...
He's coming to the Pirates Fest!
There she is! Viola-chan!
but thanks to you, I got away!
The Demon Heir...
Douglas Bullet!
So let me return the favor!
LAND OF WANO
Ugh! It's Wapol!
I don't know what kind of wild animals you are
but the first thing I see here is a fight?
Oh, that'll help me out.
The acorn pops is there, too!
I just arrived here so I
have a lot of questions.
What? Wapol?! Did he come back?!
Want some freshwater clams?!
Rebecca! Sai! So many faces I know!
Move outta my way!
Of course. Royals across the world gather
at the Reverie and discuss things!
Okay! You need to eat!
Bullet's coming, huh?!
UDON
Come in! Come in!
Try our special Flower Udon!
I finally get to kick his ass!
Oh, maybe at the Reverie...
--Is this okay?
--Yes.
At the Reverie, the princesses that I know...
The enemy won't find it here.
That worst pirate in the world!
...are getting excited talking about me!
Not just Bullet!
Damn! As I thought,
there's nothing to eat!
I'm gonna kill all the pirates
coming to the festival!
Wouldn't that be special?
Hey, guys! You can fight all you want
but don't crash into the ship!
Big Bro!
Let's go now!
Yeah, do it!
Hey, look at this, Chopper!
At the Pirates Fest, pirates whose bounties
would add up to over 10 billion will gather!
What?
Right here!
I'd like to invite you over for a treat!
What is it, Chobro?
Oh yeah...
If you make a spectacle,
KOMACHIYO - A LION-DOG
Big Bro! Hihimaru! This way!
that's reason alone to invite
you as a special guest!
What was I doing?
HIHIMARU - A NEW FRIEND
Doctorine!
Bullet isn't the only attraction!
His name is Hihimaru?
We're short-handed here.
Could you help me a little bit?
Oh, is she still alive?
I think...
I just came up with it!
The rookie that everyone's talking about,
Hey!
I see. I'm counting on you, Hihimaru!
Straw Hat Luffy whose bounty rose up to 1.5 billion
will be invited, too!
Hey! Carry the other end!
--Come on. Carry that end.
--We don't have enough joists!
He can't make it!
Doctorine...
Because I'm driving them to the wall!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! What are you doing, Chopper?!
New guy!
--Don't cut it out!
--What? Whoa!
There are pirates that I like
and that I don't like!
Whoa-whoa-whoa! Do it at the festival!
Oh yeah! I remember!
--Give me back my princesses!
--What are you doing?!
Is it you who did this part?!
Straw Hat Luffy is one of the main draws!
That makes no difference to me.
Yes, Boss!
No way!
All the pirates who step in front of me...
When we climbed up the waterfall,
we saw land...
Is there something wrong?
Hey! I haven't read the back side yet!
It's full of holes!
It's more than just something wrong,
you fool!
...will be destroyed!
But we were drawn into a whirlpool
before getting there...
What kind of idiot are you?!
Oh? Is this an article about Kaido?
What's this?!
We'll finish them off
with Fizzy Torpedoes-ger!
Hey, the tide is running in reverse!
It's perr-fect!
We'll get a big payout!
I can't believe this!
After we climbed up the waterfall,
You're strong and kind.
Big Mom... What?! It's unreadable!
Good job!
we're drawn into a whirlpool!
You damn fool!
Sanji-kun! Chopper!
Give these back to me!
Of course, it's perfect because I...
Nope!
Hang tough, Sunny!
That is your role!
I'm happy to see everyone doing well!
Nami-san, hold onto me!
My house is over there.
Once we finish sailing around the world,
let's go see them!
Thank you, Sanji-kun!
Oh...
You're most welcome, Nami-san!
Yes! That's the right order!
There's a village in the mountains?
That's good... Thank you, sir!
Sanji!
Anyway, Luffy-san, the Transponder Snail
still won't connect?
No, it's gone, now!
Yeah, hold onto me!
Franky! Prepare for the Coup de Burst!
Okay, I'm gonna jump to land!
Now, my Master-sama and I live by ourselves.
You asshole!
Roger! Sunny, I know you can do it!
Oh, I forgot.
FRANOSUKE - A CARPENTER
--Ready?!
--Wait, Sanji!
Hey! This is Luffy! Come in!
In the future, I'm gonna be a bewitching...
Everyone!
Take me with you!
Gather 'round! Gather 'round!
Well, no response.
...female ninja!
Chobro!
That's enough. Let's push on!
Those of you who are not in rush,
please stop and listen!
I can't! Too heavy!
Is it okay?
No! Don't leave me behind!
The plan was once we get near the Land of Wano,
we'd call Kin'emon, right?
"Bewitching"?
Yes, "bewitching"!
I'm sorry but you need to let go.
That's "bewitching"!
Forget it! Let's just go!
To the Land of Wano!
How could you...?!
This is a noted sword...
Just kidding. Hold on tightly!
...which Sandai Kitetsu
gave ample time to forging.
Go for it, Sunny!
The Land of Wano...
Sanji!
It's a mystery-filled country
where samurai swagger about,
It's totally different from blunt swords...
Now, allow me to join.
Coup de Burst!
...that have tips and middle parts that can be
easily cut themselves but can't cut anything!
that's completely isolated
from other nations.
I love you all!
Squeeze!
On the massive moving island, Zou,
I feel some hard bones!
Gather 'round!
the Straws Hats learned the truth about
the Land of Wano samurai.
Hi-yah! Once you draw it,
Hey! Bones... Bones are gross!
it won't be sheathed
until first slicing something!
That's disgusting! Don't squeeze me!
This man right here is the heir to...
I thought you could run on the water!
...Kozuki Oden-sama, great daimyo
of Kuri in the Land of Wano!
Here's a sheet of paper
- no gimmicks or setup!
What the hell was that?!
You're terrible!
I can't run on such a stormy sea!
Our bounties are getting away!
One sheet becomes two!
His name is Kozuki Momonosuke-sama!
Baron Corpse!
Two sheets become four!
Now, Sanji-san! Let's jump in a snap!
Just like a bone!
Four sheets become eight!
Oden (stew) wouldn't be
"oden" if it wasn't boiled!
Eight to sixteen,
then thirty-two to sixty-four!
Hey!
Use my belly, Sanji!
Hi-yah! Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
I give you the fluttering dance of...
Okay!
Oden-sama was...
...a springtime cherry blossom shower...
...executed!
and the snowfall of Wano's early evening!
See you later!
Thank you, Sunny!
Yeah! I'll come right after you!
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
You saved us!
It's dirty, small, and stinky here.
But it's taken so much damage...
Okay, I'm gonna take off!
What?!
Big Bro, that's a little impolite.
Sunny! I promise I'll find you later!
To save all of us retainers,
They were spouting something
just like the Sunny.
Oh, smells delicious!
he met his fate!
Now you see how sharp this great sword is.
Yeah, I think carbonation
was their energy source.
It's gonna be ready soon!
Here I go!
By Kaido?!
Just by grazing it a bit...
Their aerial attacks were quite annoying...
See how easily you get cut.
Isn't it ready yet, Tama?!
There's no doubt that they have
a superior scientific technology.
The octopus?!
What do you still want from me?!
And...
If they come back, we'll be in trouble.
You damn octopus!
...Emperor of the Sea Kaido's
Beast Pirates are...
That means we have to stay alert.
But, watch this!
Let's repair while we can.
What I have here is toad oil!
...still in the Land of Wano!
It's ready!
If you apply it to the wound...!
Everyone! There's an island!
What we have to do now is
to put our lives on the line and avenge our master!
Here you go.
Go ahead and dig in!
Ta-dah!
Big Bro!
Look! You see?!
We need to kill the shogun
who stole the Land of Wano
Then, I was here when I woke up.
It works like this!
Freshly-cooked rice!
and open the closed country to the world!
So am I above the waterfall?
Or did I fall?
The blood's stopped, too!
Thank you for the food!
That's our wish!
The East Blue's special toad oil!
Come and get some!
Am I in the Land of Wano?
Now, we have a favor to ask, Luffy-dono!
--I'll have some!
--Me too!
You folks have a good eye!
And you too, Law-dono!
It's delicious!
Now, gather 'round! Gather 'round!
Since we are fated to share the same purpose,
Oh? The Vivre Card is gone!
USOHACHI - A TOAD OIL SALESMAN
will you help us fight to kill
the shogun of the Land of Wano
I lost it! Is it in the sea?!
Damn!
and Emperor Kaido?!
Aren't you gonna eat?
Pop, pop, pop, pop...
There is carbonated water everywhere.
No, not now.
I want to bring down Kaido!
Oh, what the hell! Forget it.
You're doing great! That's it! That's it!
So irresistible!
What an interesting island!
I can't become a ninja if I'm not agile!
Magistrate-sama!
You committed a high crime! Zorojuro!
I'm begging you!
We're running out of cola?!
Your hand is too low!
Please...
Seconds, please!
Lower your hips more!
How quick!
We used it all up
with the last Coup de Burst!
But that was all I cooked.
Yes, ma'am...
I got it!
What should we do?!
If they come back, we won't be able to get away!
What you're trying to achieve is nigh on impossible!
So push yourself!
--You damn slasher!
--You're not gonna admit your guilt?!
What?
There are no more pickles, either...
Hey, it seems like there is carbonated water on this island.
Maybe we can get cola.
You're not gonna be called by the Shogun
in a short time like that!
Let's join hands!
Okay.
Yeah? That's great!
I was just joking when I asked for seconds.
It must be cola!
At least a barrelful of it!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
All right! I'll go buy it!
Give me money, Nami!
Keep it up, baby!
What?!
I know what you're doing!
You just wanna explore this weird island!
You're bad at lying!
Now, Luffy and the others are
heading towards the Land of Wano.
Yes, ma'am...
--Three swords?!
--What?!
OROBI - A GEISHA
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Oh, young man, that's not good.
All right! Take the helm, Brook!
Come on! Don't be daunted! Attack!
Wait, Luffy!
You shouldn't be out of soda on this island!
What's wrong?
The wind...
Here! It's 150 berries!
What the?!
Old lady, do you have cola?
I need a barrelful of it.
Dragon Twister!
It's delicious sake.
You can't get a barrelful of it
unless you go to the factory.
ZOROJURO - A RONIN
--I'll come back soon.
--Thank you very much!
Oh! It's over there?!
Thanks! I'm gonna go now!
Be careful!
This cold wind... and these waves
that I've never seen before...
All the men were taken to that factory
and they never come back...
The moon's beautiful...
I haven't had enough yet
but she's kind enough to cook for me.
I have nothing but bad feelings about this!
I should drink and take in the view later.
She's so nice! Tama...
That factory is owned by
a dangerous group called the Cidre Guild.
You're better off being satisfied
with a bottle of cola!
Who the hell are you?!
So this is the sea area
around the Land of Wano!
Hmm...
What?! Usopp...
No, it's not!
If nothing else, the weather is pretty nice
in this country.
Why are you lying down here?!
Stop!
Let me go!
I didn't say anything like that!
No!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Give me back my rice, too!
GINGER - LEADER OF THE CARBONATE FIREARMS SQUAD
CIDRE GUILD
Don't tell me you ate the rice.
The torpedo guy from earlier!
No, I'm sure you said it!
We kill all pirates!
Move!
When the Kozuki Clan comes back,
they'll teach you a lesson!
That's the Cidre Guild's rule-ger!
The wind is getting stronger as we draw close
and the waves are running high!
I did. Who are you...
The smell of blood...
You fool!
You traitor...
Wait!
You're an ally of that evil
family, the Kozuki Clan!
It doesn't look like a normal wind-drift current.
The way it swells...
You smell pretty good, buddy.
It's a serious crime!
It's like a blood-scented perfume...
Cidre Guild?!
So it was you guys who attacked the Sunny!
On top of the unusual flow...
We'll either sell you to a brothel
or send you to prison.
Look at the bad weather over there!
There'll be no mercy!
--But...
--Could you shut up for a minute?
Stop making noise, stomach!
It's quite pungent...
This isn't becoming of a samurai!
We're on duty now!
And it makes me sick.
Look! There's a ship on the beach!
We wanna avoid a storm...
Shall we wait a little more?
Just one survivor?
Wait!
The baboon's having trouble
with the lion-dog!
Who are you?!
You're charging at us like a fool!
Take this!
Hey! What are you talking about Brook?!
Let's go now to the Land of Wano!
I'm just here because Tama cooked for me.
I thought he was a more
dependable guard than that.
Super Strong Tornado Soda!
Luffy-san, why do you wanna put
your crew in such obvious danger?
Oh! Komachiyo?!
Why did she cook for you?
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
Guys, that's enough...
My eyes!
But, Brook...
How many days do you think it's been
since she ate?!
Boss! It was there, just as the report said!
The trespassing ship!
ARREST
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
Kin'emon actually warned me about this...
Yeah, the slasher went that way.
What?
Do you see its crew?
I'll explain it to you on the snail thing,
Even if she busily weaves hats every day
and sells them,
We saw one.
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
One, huh?
but the whole sea area around the Land of Wano
is always subject to bad weather.
We'll knock him out and take him with us!
He'll at least become our laborer!
--You slasher!
--Don't resist!
we can only earn barely enough for
one person to live!
The sea is rough
and the current is strong,
Just hold still!
so it's difficult to enter the country!
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
Good boy. Sleep well!
What?! The weather is always bad?!
Then we should just go?!
When you wake up,
we'll treat you well... as our slave!
That's my thinking. Let's go!
I have to defend myself...
Not only does it have strong samurai
but it's also perilous to enter...
...from the trouble that I'm getting into!
It's truly an isolated country!
That is your role!
Let me think a little bit...
There must be a way to get through safely...
Listen, guys. You're in the Land of Wano.
Sometimes we get to eat barnyard grass
and that's it.
The Shogun's name is...
But at least, twice a year,
...Kurozumi Orochi!
on her birthday and New Year's,
I want her to eat rice!
Officials who follow him are
all under the control of Kaido.
RICE
So I gave her money today
--What's that thing?!
--It's an octopus!
and sent her to the town
to buy rice for her eighth birthday!
Good boy. Sleep well!
That's why those officials
are so high-handed.
A giant one!
Why's an octopus here?!
When you wake up,
we'll treat you well... as our slave!
--It's here because we're on the sea!
--I know that, but...
But if you touch them,
Kaido will hear about it!
When did it come on board?!
How could you eat that?!
Until all of our allies get here
and we're ready to fight,
Hey! We're going farther into
the waters around the Land of Wano!
What?!
we can't let them know who we are!
Master-sama!
It doesn't matter! Go on, Sunny!
He dodged?!
Please stop!
So pretend that you're citizens for now
To the Land of Wano!
Forgive me for cooking it
without asking!
and quietly and peacefully,
But...!
play your roles!
He saved my life!
I can't believe it!
Don't bring disgrace on me!
Luffy!
I guess I have no choice...
I got it-de-gozaru...
I'll weave many hats!
What the?!
Hey, tie him up!
Please forgive me!
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
Let me return the favor to
Big Bro Luffy properly...
Who's attacking me suddenly?!
Hancock!
Bastard!
Please...
There's no turning back!
I can't hit him!
That's amazing!
Wait, you octopus!
Otama!
Hey, what's going on?
Swords become stronger
by absorbing human blood...
Tama!
Well, it's nothing...
It's the same no matter
how many straw dummies you cut.
What do you want?
Hey, Tama!
We caught the slasher!
She must've done a foolish thing!
Oh...
I suppose she drank the river water
to ease her hunger.
Hey! Something's coming towards us!
Water?
This beach is so noisy.
Oh...
The Pirate Empress is here on this island?
River waters in this country...
Yes, sir! It seems like she met Straw Hat.
GUARANA - LEADER OF THE CARBONATE SWORD SQUAD
CIDRE GUILD
...are polluted by liquid wastes
from Kaido's factory!
That arch-villain who was
stoking fear in the town recently!
What?! What is it?!
Dammit...
It looks like a giant fish!
Hey, baboon!
Don't just stand there and watch!
Magistrate-sama has finally,
finally caught him!
--Is it a shark?!
--A shark?!
How lucky!
CIDRE - COMMANDER OF THE CARBONATE ASSAULT
CIDRE GUILD
That's favorable for us!
Oh no! It's coming!
The criminal will be sentenced to seppuku!
For a small girl like her,
it's like drinking poison.
Forget the dog now! Catch that guy!
This is our chance to get rid of
that annoying Warlord of the Sea!
More details are in here!
I hate him! He sliced up my husband, too!
Huh? What do you mean?
Then, why are you living here?!
No, I give you permission! Kill him!
C-Carp...
What a relief! Just this month, as many as three people
were slashed on the streets at night...
Kill them both!
Oh my, oh my!
There are places that would be
a bit better.
If we do that,
we'll have trouble with the Navy!
It's a massive carp!
But she's waiting here.
Hey, can I have one, too?!
We can just tell them that
Straw Hat killed the Pirate Empress!
Thank you!
For someone who promised to come back...
Excuse me.
It's a school of carp?!
Luffy! Did you hear that I was here...
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
Z-Zorojuro...
He is a pirate named Ace!
...and come for me?!
Why are carp in the sea?!
I knew he would do something like this.
What? I just came here to buy cola!
They're freshwater fish!
How can they live here?!
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
It doesn't matter!
They're monster carp anyway!
What?!
Ace?!
Hey, Sanji? Are they delicious?!
We bumped into each other by chance...
What do you want?
Forget about those monsters!
It's truly...
...meant to be!
Well, alternating it in baths of
hot and cold water firms it up
resulting in a delicious dish called arai.
You can simmer it in miso, too.
--Hey!
--You should just eat cultivated ones!
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
That's not the issue now!
Tempura and sweet-boiled ones are
also good.
Tama...
You fools!
All right!
Do you know who's taking a bath now?!
We'll have a banquet with this
once we see Zoro and the others again!
The Ace that you're waiting for is...
--Don't, Luffy!
--Carp have so many tiny bones!
"Who's taking a bath"?!
...Portgas D. Ace, right?
Of course, we know-ger!
Who cares?!
That's not important now!
Do you know him?
Good!
Big Bro...
Don't fight so much, guys!
Uh-huh.
Don't fight back!
Of course, it fights back!
Why are you like that?!
Why are you getting intimidated?!
Sanji-kun! You're responsible, too!
Bring back Luffy!
There's just one pirate!
You're alive as I thought, Straw Hat!
So your name is Zorojuro...
Don't worry, Nami-san.
He'll be fine.
Ace died.
What?!
Everyone was afraid of the slasher...
Instead, let's protect our ship!
If you slash your belly,
the town will become peaceful again.
Look what you did, you squirt!
I can't believe you're...
I'll kill you!
...also a grave-robber.
Damn brat, stop!
F-Forgive me!
23 years ago...
Luffy! You...!
Amid the confusion of
the pirate trouble,
You don't want them to see
that thing on your back, do you?
The wind is strong!
Carrot, furl the sail!
the legendary swordsman
Ryuma's corpse and...
Leave the rest to me!
--Okay!
--I'll help!
You're nothing!
......his great sword, Shusui, went missing!
Don't act all cool
because you're in front of a woman!
I surrender!
Legend has it that Ryuma chopped off
a giant savage dragon's head...
I surrender!
Luffy!
What are you doing?
That's a lie...
...with this sword, Shusui.
Thank you for protecting me.
That's a lie!
I said I surrender! I surrender!
But it's rude to enter
while someone's bathing...
That's a lie!!
But now, you slasher...
I should teach them a lesson!
OTAMA
Look how clear the water is!
It's like water in a mountain river!
That grave-robbery took place 23 years ago.
I'm not gonna do anything to you!
Big Bro, you're a liar!
Y-You mean it?
I'd prefer it wasn't so clear!
The giant fish in the water scare me!
You don't look that old.
Yeah!
Did you steal it from the robber?
U-Um...
What? Then, is this a river?!
I'm sorry but while you're here,
may I have some of your time?
Oh, well...
Where are those carp heading?!
The famous Shusui is now in my hands!
Guys! Pull yourselves together!
They're pirates-ger!
Th-This is my chance!
Hang on tight!
We're going with the flow!
Chance? What do you mean?
"No mercy for pirates"!
That's what Commander Cidre always says-ger!
Tama!
--All right. Let's do it.
--Huh? What are you gonna do?
Is Luffy still around here?!
Otama!
Pull yourself together, Tama!
Kibi Dango!
Yes, sir.
Shoot-ger!
Now, Zorojuro, it's time.
She fainted.
Here it is!
What?!
What?! Your cheek came off!
Hey.
Gum-Gum...
Whoa-whoa, what is that?!
This blade has no grip...
So Ace visited the Land of Wano, too...
...Gatling!
The river's flowing to the bottom of the waterfall!
How's that possible?!
...de-gozaru.
Are you a devil or something?!
A seppuku blade is usually short
and has no grip.
You can eat this!
How could you tell Otama
that Ace died so casually?!
You won't fight with it
so it doesn't matter.
But it's true.
Do you know the proper etiquette of seppuku?
Even if it's true,
that wasn't the right time!
Slave...
The slasher cut Magistrate-sama?!
...Arrow!
But no matter how long she waits,
Ace won't come back!
If you call yourself a samurai,
admit your guilt and kill yourself honorably!
Yeah, he hasn't been caught yet!
How scary!
But still...
Oh yeah!
What?!
Before you start suffering...
you should've considered
when and how to say it!
If this waterfall is the
reason that it's fresh water,
Three-Sword Style?!
a massive water source should be up there!
I'll assist you in dying!
You have no delicacy!
Yeah, it says so on the
wanted poster right there!
Could it be that the Land
of Wano is up there?!
That's serious!
You bastards!
Who are you?!
Not only Magistrate-sama
but he also sliced up
Up there...
What?! Whaaat?! How is it possible?!
I'm Luffy.
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!
all the samurai there with a massive twister!
Snake Princess!
But Three-Sword Style
takes three swords, right?
What?! You're a pirate?!
One in the right hand
and another one in the left hand.
I generally don't like pirates!
Who are you?!
How does he hold the third one?
Big Sis-sama! Catch this!
Well, of course...
I'm Hitetsu.
Oh, thanks!
Like this!
Well then...
TENGUYAMA HITETSU - A SWORDSMITH
I'm a swordsmith.
Farewell.
--No way!
--You're so funny, Franosuke!
TENGUYAMA HITETSU - A SWORDSMITH
(A BEAUTIFUL GIRL KOKESHI DOLL COLLECTOR)
Don't cry like a baby...
Ace is now gone!
Thanks, thanks!
Oh! Look at that!
Take Tama and move to a better place!
A proper death is a samurai's honor.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
--The carp are climbing up the waterfall!
--Why?!
Enough fooling around!
It's gonna get dark, you idiots!
I truly want to do so.
We have witnesses! And enough evidence!
But I've been waiting...
It's an honorable death
that you don't deserve!
I-I'm sorry!
...for someone here for a long time myself.
What did he do?! Dammit, Zoro!
Thanks for waiting!
Oh, carp! Oh, carp!
Be happy that you can perform seppuku.
I'm all ready!
A sailing ship can't do that!
We'll sink under the waterfall!
Okay, hurry up! By performing in front of customers,
you can improve yourself!
There are only the two of us here now,
Damn you! I have no options left!
but there was a village
called Amigasa before.
Of course, we will!
Yes, ma'am!
Luffy!
But around a year ago,
Wow, those carp are so strong!
a man who joined Kaido's army as a Headliner
came here.
Oh? What is it?
--This is no time for that!
--Luffy! She says this ship's gonna sink!
I'll go and look.
Okay, count on me!
He was a pirate named X. Drake.
What?!
Z-Zoro!
Take this! Super Highly-concentrated...
ZOROJURO - A SERIOUS CRIMINAL
MURDERING THE MAGISTRATE
Hang on tight!
...Deluxe CO2 Gas-ger!
You can't take your eyes off of the poster?
Is that someone you know?
--N-No.
--Oh, okay. Then, let's go!
The village's five key samurai
were taken down
You can do it, carp!
You've got to be kidding!
Yes, ma'am.
and everything was destroyed.
I'm gonna kill you all-ger!
It has nothing to do with us.
Go!
Zoro... What did you do?!
In the Land of Wano,
there is only one place that's thriving now
I can't breathe...
Hm? A placard?!
and that is the Flower Capital
where the Shogun Orochi lives.
Oh, no!
Man, he went on a rampage this time!
Let's retreat!
The other places...
Hey!
...were turned into lawless wilderness areas
by Kaido and his clan.
Seems like you know that person!
Hancock!
I smell blood.
Huh?!
Are you okay?
No way, Officer-sama!
Please catch that ruffian as soon as possible!
That man came here four years ago.
You...
Your face was very close!
This village was always poor
L-Luffy's very close...
Look, Chobro!
We're climbing the waterfall!
...are the slasher!
Otherwise, I can't help being scared!
W-What should I do?
and no one had enough to live on
so people often died of hunger.
I have ten kids
and the oldest is still seven!
Hancock!
It's dangerous here with the gas!
When I think that they might get hurt,
I can't even let them walk outside!
--Let's escape for now!
--Oh, yes!
Just when we thought that
the village was doomed...
Nooo!!
Commander Cidre! I have a report.
I'm begging you! Officer-sama!
The targets are heading
towards the cola factory.
Ace was tossed up on the beach.
Okay! Count on me, brother!
What should we do?
I'm gonna catch him at any cost!
The villagers stole all the food and water...
All right!
Don't do anything! I'll come myself!
...from those weak pirates
Hey! Get outta my way!
It's our first hunt of big-time
pirates in a long time!
Up we go!
then ate it up and stayed alive.
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
Damn it all, Zoro!
Catch him no matter what!
Yeah!
Ace watched them finish everything,
Gee, they need to keep it down...
then, surprisingly,
he easily untied himself.
What?
This is the Cidre Guild's stronghold...
Everyone thought he was gonna retaliate
and prepared themselves.
Mm-hm. Looks like
they gave up the chase for now.
They've already got my face up.
What's wrong with the sea area
around the Land of Wano?!
You think your sisters are okay?
It's so chaotic!
It really is difficult to enter...
You can eat this!
Are you worrying about them?
You're so kind.
Did you eat enough?
It was fun, wasn't it, Chobro?!
Ouch!
I'm sorry that I got you involved
in this mess...
What?
I thought I was gonna die!
Uh... Uh-huh.
Don't mention it. I'm happy!
Hey! There's the shore!
I didn't think I'd be able to see you
until the Pirates Fest...
Then you want something sweet now!
W-What are you doing?
The Pirates Fest?
What?!
Oh! Is that the Land of Wano?!
Where can I find something for dessert?
You don't know it?
We're finally... finally
here at the Land of Wano...
It's a festival exclusively for pirates
Okay, I'm gonna go pick it!
that randomly takes place about
once every several years.
Everyone was stunned.
Chobro, it's the Land of Wano...
From across the Grand Line,
pirates whose bounties
Ace stayed at the village
for several weeks.
Is this... the Land of Wano?
Shake hands!
would easily add up to over
10 billion will gather
and it's also a dark festival
during which lawlessness reigns.
Otama was especially attached to him.
What?! That beast is tamed!
I did it!
Oh, that sounds interesting!
The Pirates Fest!
I finally befriended the savage wild baboon
of the mountain!
Wow! Look at that massive whirl!
I wanna go and see it for myself!
A whirlpool!
Yay!
I did it!
You can come with me!
You're a power-user!
That's a very handy power!
I'm getting excited!
I'll get cola and go to the festival!
Where did they go?
Luffy! Let go of those carp!
Let's see...
No! They're my dinner!
What happened to us?
Enough already!
Okay, okay. You're our friend now!
Brook! Take the helm!
Okay!
Good boy.
Is that your dog?
Everyone! Fight him!
Yes, he is! His name is Komachiyo!
I can't believe our lives were saved
by the shipwrecked pirates.
That's the power of carbonation!
Oh, Komachiyo!
If you release the gas pressure
which is increased to its limit all at once,
Good to see you! I'm Luffy!
It's no good! The current is too strong!
you can cause a big blast
that'll make a hole in the ground!
Yeah...
And my name is Otama.
What's your problem?!
Damn! We're almost there!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Okay, Otama! Good to see you, too!
We're not gonna make it this time!
--Nice to meet you!
--Now...
We'll have your heads!
Doctorine!
I need to know if this is
the Land of Wano or not.
This country?
I see.
We, the Cidre Guild, will!
Oh? Where are my carp?
Yes, this is the Land of Wano!
--That's not important now!
--What?
You're in a region called Kuri
in the Land of Wano!
Big Bro!
The communication was
probably cut at Kuri Beach.
I see! This is the Land of Wano!
Are they bounty hunters?
It's possible that they
were beaten by someone.
I just want cola!
As I thought, I've arrived
at the Land of Wano!
We don't know how many there are.
Oh no! We're gonna be
caught in the whirlpool!
We have no cola to sell to pirates!
Wait for me, Kaido!
And there is no ship, but it's definite
that they came from the outside world.
Wait, did you call me "Big Bro"?!
Hey! When did I become your big brother?!
What should we do, Boss?
I'm Commander Cidre!
A big brother is a big brother!
One of you two will be the
100th head that I hunt!
What do you mean by that?
Well, whatever.
Okay, Big Bro!
Prepare yourselves!
Don't tell Kaido-san.
What the?!
I'll handle it!
Luffy and Hancock get in
a fierce fight against
Cidre finally turns into
his ultimate true form!
Transcending time and space, the bond between
the army of the world's
strongest bounty hunter!
Surrounded by samurai, Zoro
is in a desperate situation!
I'll kick the Emperor of the Sea Kaido's ass
and open up the Land of Wano!
Ace and Luffy is reconnected
in the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Will he be able to use his
technique without his swords?!
Facing his furious consecutive
attacks, Luffy and Hancock
"Side Story! The World's
Greatest Bounty Hunter, Cidre!"
What did Ace promise Otama
after he saved her village?
The Straw Hats finally gather
together at the Land of Wano!
Meanwhile, Luffy meets a mysterious
girl Otama and clashes
display their powerful techniques!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Another legend of Ace is revealed!
Formidable enemies are waiting for them
Luffy or Cidre, who will
survive in this final battle?!
with the Emperor of the Sea Kaido's army!
in the country of the
strong which even the Navy can't touch!
It's the Pirates Fest!
And with the appearance
of a rookie with a bounty
The battle in the Land
of Wano finally begins!
An unprecedented battle begins now!
of over 100 million,
another crisis closes in!
The King of the Pirates challenges you!
TO GET THE KING OF THE PIRATES' TREASURE
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Side Story! Clash! Luffy vs. the King of Carbonation!"
"Otama Appears! Luffy vs. Kaido's Army!"
Come on and seize the treasure!
"He'll Come! The Legend of
Ace in the Land of Wano!"
"The Land of Wano!
To the Samurai Country where Cherry Blossoms Flutter!"
ALL THE PIRATES AND MARINES COME TOGETHER!
The movie ONE PIECE STAMPEDE!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
AND... A DARK PLOT IS LAUNCHED
Your ambition...
...is ignited!