Yes! We've got Super Powers
Your dream is like a monster
kimi no yume wa monsutaa kyuu de
Every time it breaks the cage in your heart
mune no ori bukkowashitewa
Jump into the paradise on
which is written "Go to Hell"
tobikomu yo "Go to Hell" to kaita paradaisu
It's always, Dangerous! Dangerous!
itsudatte Dangerous! Dangerous!
"We like it!"
Serious! Serious!
"Oh!"
Someday, the dream that's
covered in cuts and bruises
kizu darake ni natta yume wa itsuka
will become your one and only treasure
daiji na takaramono ni naru sa
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing in a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
To that planet where love combines with tears
ai ga namida to mazaru hoshi ni
The future gently brings a morning
sotto mirai wa asa wo hakobi
It shines on our silly but dear world
oroka de itoshii boku
tachi no sekai terasu yo
Fight! The most formidable enemy is yourself
tatakae! saikyou no teki wa jibun sa
Always and forever...
eien ni...
Magical excitement connects friends
fushigi na koufun ga nakama wo tsunagu
Living your life to the fullest
kenmei ni ikiru koto
Shall we call it an adventure?
bouken to yobou ka
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Believing a great dream together
saikou no yume shinjiau
The bond with your rival
raibaru tono kizuna
Even failure is strangely charming
shippai mo myou ni chaamingu
Yes! We've got Super Powers
Yes! We're the Super Powers
"Climbing Up a Waterfall!
A Great Journey Through the Land of Wano's Sea Zone!"
ON THE SEA IN THE NEW WORLD
With Luffy and the others on board,
the Sunny is on its way to
their next destination - the Land of Wano.
Luffy! It says the Reverie has begun!
Kings and queens from all over the world
are attending the conference at Mariejois!
Hmmm...
This time, all eyes are on the Ryugu Kingdom
since they're joining for the
first time in two centuries!
Neptune-san and the brothers are there...
And it says there was great applause
for Shirahoshi at Red Port!
So she came up to the surface!
She became much stronger, that Yowahoshi!
STRAW HAT LUFFY - CAPTAIN OF THE STRAW HAT PIRATES
BOUNTY: 1.5 BILLION BERRIES
It seems like your grandpa was their escort.
Oh...
They took a big step towards their dream
to relocate the Fish-Men to the surface!
Vivi-chan!
You became an even more beautiful princess!
Who could it be for?
Me?! Hey, is it for me?!
How annoying!
Vivi!
It's Vivi!
It's been a while! I haven't
seen her for a long time!
She's become a graceful and regal princess!
Oh, so this is Vivi-san.
When I get to see her someday,
I'd like to see her panties...
No way!
Oh, these are photos of the Mingling Plaza...
Look at all the royals
and bodyguards who came along.
I-If Dressrosa is participating...
There she is! Viola-chan!
Ugh! It's Wapol!
The acorn pops is there, too!
What? Wapol?! Did he come back?!
Rebecca! Sai! So many faces I know!
Of course. Royals across the world gather
at the Reverie and discuss things!
Oh, maybe at the Reverie...
At the Reverie, the princesses that I know...
...are getting excited talking about me!
Wouldn't that be special?
Hey, look at this, Chopper!
Right here!
What is it, Chobro?
Doctorine!
Oh, is she still alive?
Hey!
Doctorine...
Hey! What are you doing, Chopper?!
--Don't cut it out!
--What? Whoa!
--Give me back my princesses!
--What are you doing?!
Hey! I haven't read the back side yet!
It's full of holes!
Oh? Is this an article about Kaido?
Big Mom... What?! It's unreadable!
Sanji-kun! Chopper!
Give these back to me!
Nope!
I'm happy to see everyone doing well!
Once we finish sailing around the world,
let's go see them!
Yes! That's the right order!
Anyway, Luffy-san, the Transponder Snail
still won't connect?
Oh, I forgot.
Hey! This is Luffy! Come in!
Well, no response.
That's enough. Let's push on!
Is it okay?
The plan was once we get near the Land of Wano,
we'd call Kin'emon, right?
Forget it! Let's just go!
To the Land of Wano!
The Land of Wano...
It's a mystery-filled country
where samurai swagger about,
that's completely isolated
from other nations.
On the massive moving island, Zou,
the Straws Hats learned the truth about
the Land of Wano samurai.
This man right here is the heir to...
...Kozuki Oden-sama, great daimyo
of Kuri in the Land of Wano!
His name is Kozuki Momonosuke-sama!
Oden (stew) wouldn't be
"oden" if it wasn't boiled!
Oden-sama was...
...executed!
By the shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
What?!
To save all of us retainers,
he met his fate!
By Kaido?!
And...
...Emperor of the Sea Kaido's
Beast Pirates are...
...still in the Land of Wano!
What we have to do now is
to put our lives on the line and avenge our master!
We need to kill the shogun
who stole the Land of Wano
and open the closed country to the world!
That's our wish!
Now, we have a favor to ask, Luffy-dono!
And you too, Law-dono!
Since we are fated to share the same purpose,
will you help us fight to kill
the shogun of the Land of Wano
and Emperor Kaido?!
I want to bring down Kaido!
I'm begging you!
Please...
I got it!
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
Now, Luffy and the others are
heading towards the Land of Wano.
All right! Take the helm, Brook!
Wait, Luffy!
What's wrong?
The wind...
This cold wind... and these waves
that I've never seen before...
I have nothing but bad feelings about this!
So this is the sea area
around the Land of Wano!
The wind is getting stronger as we draw close
and the waves are running high!
It doesn't look like a normal wind-drift current.
The way it swells...
On top of the unusual flow...
Look at the bad weather over there!
We wanna avoid a storm...
Shall we wait a little more?
Hey! What are you talking about Brook?!
Let's go now to the Land of Wano!
Luffy-san, why do you wanna put
your crew in such obvious danger?
But, Brook...
Kin'emon actually warned me about this...
I'll explain it to you on the snail thing,
but the whole sea area around the Land of Wano
is always subject to bad weather.
The sea is rough
and the current is strong,
so it's difficult to enter the country!
What?! The weather is always bad?!
Then we should just go?!
That's my thinking. Let's go!
Not only does it have strong samurai
but it's also perilous to enter...
It's truly an isolated country!
Let me think a little bit...
There must be a way to get through safely...
--What's that thing?!
--It's an octopus!
A giant one!
Why's an octopus here?!
--It's here because we're on the sea!
--I know that, but...
When did it come on board?!
Hey! We're going farther into
the waters around the Land of Wano!
What?!
It doesn't matter! Go on, Sunny!
To the Land of Wano!
There's no turning back!
Wait, you octopus!
Hey! Something's coming towards us!
What?! What is it?!
It looks like a giant fish!
--Is it a shark?!
--A shark?!
Oh no! It's coming!
C-Carp...
Oh my, oh my!
It's a massive carp!
It's a school of carp?!
Why are carp in the sea?!
They're freshwater fish!
How can they live here?!
It doesn't matter!
They're monster carp anyway!
Hey, Sanji? Are they delicious?!
Forget about those monsters!
Well, alternating it in baths of
hot and cold water firms it up
resulting in a delicious dish called arai.
You can simmer it in miso, too.
--Hey!
--You should just eat cultivated ones!
That's not the issue now!
Tempura and sweet-boiled ones are
also good.
All right!
We'll have a banquet with this
once we see Zoro and the others again!
--Don't, Luffy!
--Carp have so many tiny bones!
Who cares?!
That's not important now!
Don't fight back!
Of course, it fights back!
Why are you like that?!
Sanji-kun! You're responsible, too!
Bring back Luffy!
Don't worry, Nami-san.
He'll be fine.
What?!
Instead, let's protect our ship!
The wind is strong!
Carrot, furl the sail!
--Okay!
--I'll help!
Look how clear the water is!
It's like water in a mountain river!
I'd prefer it wasn't so clear!
The giant fish in the water scare me!
What? Then, is this a river?!
Where are those carp heading?!
Hang on tight!
We're going with the flow!
Is Luffy still around here?!
What?!
Whoa-whoa, what is that?!
The river's flowing to the bottom of the waterfall!
How's that possible?!
Oh yeah!
If this waterfall is the
reason that it's fresh water,
a massive water source should be up there!
Could it be that the Land
of Wano is up there?!
Up there...
What?! Whaaat?! How is it possible?!
Oh! Look at that!
--The carp are climbing up the waterfall!
--Why?!
Oh, carp! Oh, carp!
A sailing ship can't do that!
We'll sink under the waterfall!
Of course, we will!
Luffy!
Wow, those carp are so strong!
--This is no time for that!
--Luffy! She says this ship's gonna sink!
Okay, count on me!
What?!
Hang on tight!
You can do it, carp!
You've got to be kidding!
Go!
Look, Chobro!
We're climbing the waterfall!
Nooo!!
All right!
Up we go!
What's wrong with the sea area
around the Land of Wano?!
It's so chaotic!
It really is difficult to enter...
It was fun, wasn't it, Chobro?!
I thought I was gonna die!
Hey! There's the shore!
Oh! Is that the Land of Wano?!
We're finally... finally
here at the Land of Wano...
Chobro, it's the Land of Wano...
Wow! Look at that massive whirl!
A whirlpool!
Luffy! Let go of those carp!
No! They're my dinner!
Enough already!
Brook! Take the helm!
Okay!
It's no good! The current is too strong!
Damn! We're almost there!
We're not gonna make it this time!
Doctorine!
Oh? Where are my carp?
--That's not important now!
--What?
Oh no! We're gonna be
caught in the whirlpool!
I'll kick the Emperor of the Sea Kaido's ass
and open up the Land of Wano!
The Straw Hats finally gather
together at the Land of Wano!
Formidable enemies are waiting for them
in the country of the
strong which even the Navy can't touch!
An unprecedented battle begins now!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Land of Wano!
To the Samurai Country where Cherry Blossoms Flutter!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!