One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Listen, guys. You're in the Land of Wano.
The Shogun's name is...
...Kurozumi Orochi!
Until all of our allies get here
and we're ready to fight,
we can't let them know who we are!
So pretend that you're citizens for now
and quietly and peacefully,
play your roles!
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
Where did they go?
Hey!
Hey, you! Don't break our ship!
It's a giant dog!
Is it a dog or boar?
A BABOON
A sword-using animal?
So I guess this is the Land of Wano!
"Otama Appears!
Luffy vs. Kaido's Army!"
I don't know what kind of wild animals you are
but the first thing I see here is a fight?
Hey, guys! You can fight all you want
but don't crash into the ship!
Oh yeah...
What was I doing?
I think...
Oh yeah! I remember!
When we climbed up the waterfall,
we saw land...
But we were drawn into a whirlpool
before getting there...
What's this?!
Hey, the tide is running in reverse!
I can't believe this!
After we climbed up the waterfall,
we're drawn into a whirlpool!
Hang tough, Sunny!
Nami-san, hold onto me!
Thank you, Sanji-kun!
You're most welcome, Nami-san!
Sanji!
Yeah, hold onto me!
Okay, I'm gonna jump to land!
--Ready?!
--Wait, Sanji!
Take me with you!
Chobro!
I can't! Too heavy!
No! Don't leave me behind!
I'm sorry but you need to let go.
How could you...?!
Just kidding. Hold on tightly!
Sanji!
Now, allow me to join.
I love you all!
Squeeze!
I feel some hard bones!
Hey! Bones... Bones are gross!
That's disgusting! Don't squeeze me!
I thought you could run on the water!
You're terrible!
I can't run on such a stormy sea!
Baron Corpse!
Now, Sanji-san! Let's jump in a snap!
Just like a bone!
Hey!
Use my belly, Sanji!
Okay!
See you later!
Yeah! I'll come right after you!
Okay, I'm gonna take off!
Sunny! I promise I'll find you later!
Here I go!
The octopus?!
What do you still want from me?!
You damn octopus!
Then, I was here when I woke up.
So am I above the waterfall?
Or did I fall?
Am I in the Land of Wano?
Oh? The Vivre Card is gone!
I lost it! Is it in the sea?!
Damn!
Oh, what the hell! Forget it.
Magistrate-sama!
You committed a high crime! Zorojuro!
--You damn slasher!
--You're not gonna admit your guilt?!
--Three swords?!
--What?!
Come on! Don't be daunted! Attack!
What the?!
Dragon Twister!
If nothing else, the weather is pretty nice
in this country.
Stop!
Let me go!
I didn't say anything like that!
Give me back my rice, too!
No, I'm sure you said it!
When the Kozuki Clan comes back,
they'll teach you a lesson!
You traitor...
You're an ally of that evil
family, the Kozuki Clan!
It's a serious crime!
We'll either sell you to a brothel
or send you to prison.
There'll be no mercy!
--But...
--Could you shut up for a minute?
We're on duty now!
Look! There's a ship on the beach!
Just one survivor?
The baboon's having trouble
with the lion-dog!
I thought he was a more
dependable guard than that.
Oh! Komachiyo?!
Guys, that's enough...
Boss! It was there, just as the report said!
The trespassing ship!
Do you see its crew?
We saw one.
One, huh?
We'll knock him out and take him with us!
He'll at least become our laborer!
Good boy. Sleep well!
When you wake up,
we'll treat you well... as our slave!
Good boy. Sleep well!
When you wake up,
we'll treat you well... as our slave!
He dodged?!
What the?!
Who's attacking me suddenly?!
Bastard!
I can't hit him!
Hey, what's going on?
Well, it's nothing...
This beach is so noisy.
Dammit...
Hey, baboon!
Don't just stand there and watch!
Forget the dog now! Catch that guy!
No, I give you permission! Kill him!
What do you want?
Good!
Don't fight so much, guys!
Why are you getting intimidated?!
There's just one pirate!
Look what you did, you squirt!
I'll kill you!
Damn brat, stop!
F-Forgive me!
I surrender!
What are you doing?
I said I surrender! I surrender!
OTAMA
I'm not gonna do anything to you!
Y-You mean it?
Yeah!
U-Um...
I'm sorry but while you're here,
may I have some of your time?
Th-This is my chance!
Chance? What do you mean?
--All right. Let's do it.
--Huh? What are you gonna do?
Kibi Dango!
Here it is!
What?! Your cheek came off!
You can eat this!
The slasher cut Magistrate-sama?!
Yeah, he hasn't been caught yet!
How scary!
What?!
Three-Sword Style?!
Yeah, it says so on the
wanted poster right there!
That's serious!
Not only Magistrate-sama
but he also sliced up
all the samurai there with a massive twister!
But Three-Sword Style
takes three swords, right?
One in the right hand
and another one in the left hand.
How does he hold the third one?
Well, of course...
Like this!
--No way!
--You're so funny, Franosuke!
Thanks, thanks!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Enough fooling around!
It's gonna get dark, you idiots!
I-I'm sorry!
What did he do?! Dammit, Zoro!
Okay, hurry up! By performing in front of customers,
you can improve yourself!
Yes, ma'am!
Oh? What is it?
I'll go and look.
Z-Zoro!
ZOROJURO - A SERIOUS CRIMINAL
MURDERING THE MAGISTRATE
You can't take your eyes off of the poster?
Is that someone you know?
--N-No.
--Oh, okay. Then, let's go!
Yes, ma'am.
It has nothing to do with us.
Zoro... What did you do?!
Hm? A placard?!
Oh, no!
Man, he went on a rampage this time!
Hey!
Seems like you know that person!
Huh?!
No way, Officer-sama!
Please catch that ruffian as soon as possible!
Otherwise, I can't help being scared!
I have ten kids
and the oldest is still seven!
When I think that they might get hurt,
I can't even let them walk outside!
I'm begging you! Officer-sama!
Okay! Count on me, brother!
I'm gonna catch him at any cost!
Hey! Get outta my way!
Damn it all, Zoro!
Catch him no matter what!
Yeah!
Gee, they need to keep it down...
What?
They've already got my face up.
You can eat this!
W-What are you doing?
Shake hands!
What?! That beast is tamed!
I did it!
I finally befriended the savage wild baboon
of the mountain!
Yay!
I did it!
You're a power-user!
That's a very handy power!
Okay, okay. You're our friend now!
Good boy.
Is that your dog?
Yes, he is! His name is Komachiyo!
Oh, Komachiyo!
Good to see you! I'm Luffy!
And my name is Otama.
Okay, Otama! Good to see you, too!
--Nice to meet you!
--Now...
I need to know if this is
the Land of Wano or not.
This country?
Yes, this is the Land of Wano!
You're in a region called Kuri
in the Land of Wano!
Big Bro!
I see! This is the Land of Wano!
As I thought, I've arrived
at the Land of Wano!
Wait for me, Kaido!
Wait, did you call me "Big Bro"?!
Hey! When did I become your big brother?!
A big brother is a big brother!
What do you mean by that?
Well, whatever.
Okay, Big Bro!
Transcending time and space, the bond between
Ace and Luffy is reconnected
in the Land of Wano!
What did Ace promise Otama
after he saved her village?
Another legend of Ace is revealed!
And with the appearance
of a rookie with a bounty
of over 100 million,
another crisis closes in!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"He'll Come! The Legend of
Ace in the Land of Wano!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!