One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
How's business, Cidre-kun?!
The best bounty hunter of this generation!
What do you want,
Festa, Master of Festivities?!
I'm hunting pirates now!
Call me later!
So you're in the middle of
making money as we speak!
"Side Story!
The World's Greatest Bounty Hunter, Cidre!"
Ya-hoo!
Dammit!
Chopper! Put out the fire now!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Gust Sword!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Poele a Frire Spectre!
Three-Pace Hum...
...Notch Slash!
Go down! Go down!
Tres Fleurs!
Clutch!
They keep coming in one after the other!
Cidre-kun!
He's coming to the Pirates Fest!
The Demon Heir...
Douglas Bullet!
Bullet's coming, huh?!
I finally get to kick his ass!
That worst pirate in the world!
Not just Bullet!
I'm gonna kill all the pirates
coming to the festival!
Yeah, do it!
At the Pirates Fest, pirates whose bounties
would add up to over 10 billion will gather!
If you make a spectacle,
that's reason alone to invite
you as a special guest!
Bullet isn't the only attraction!
The rookie that everyone's talking about,
Straw Hat Luffy whose bounty rose up to 1.5 billion
will be invited, too!
He can't make it!
Because I'm driving them to the wall!
Whoa-whoa-whoa! Do it at the festival!
Straw Hat Luffy is one of the main draws!
No way!
All the pirates who step in front of me...
...will be destroyed!
We'll finish them off
with Fizzy Torpedoes-ger!
We'll get a big payout!
Franky! Prepare for the Coup de Burst!
Roger! Sunny, I know you can do it!
Go for it, Sunny!
Coup de Burst!
What the hell was that?!
Our bounties are getting away!
Thank you, Sunny!
You saved us!
But it's taken so much damage...
They were spouting something
just like the Sunny.
Yeah, I think carbonation
was their energy source.
Their aerial attacks were quite annoying...
There's no doubt that they have
a superior scientific technology.
If they come back, we'll be in trouble.
That means we have to stay alert.
Let's repair while we can.
Everyone! There's an island!
Pop, pop, pop, pop...
There is carbonated water everywhere.
What an interesting island!
We're running out of cola?!
We used it all up
with the last Coup de Burst!
What should we do?!
If they come back, we won't be able to get away!
Hey, it seems like there is carbonated water on this island.
Maybe we can get cola.
Yeah? That's great!
It must be cola!
At least a barrelful of it!
All right! I'll go buy it!
Give me money, Nami!
I know what you're doing!
You just wanna explore this weird island!
Oh, young man, that's not good.
You shouldn't be out of soda on this island!
Here! It's 150 berries!
Old lady, do you have cola?
I need a barrelful of it.
You can't get a barrelful of it
unless you go to the factory.
Oh! It's over there?!
Thanks! I'm gonna go now!
Be careful!
All the men were taken to that factory
and they never come back...
That factory is owned by
a dangerous group called the Cidre Guild.
You're better off being satisfied
with a bottle of cola!
Hmm...
Straw Hat Luffy!
GINGER - LEADER OF THE CARBONATE FIREARMS SQUAD
CIDRE GUILD
The torpedo guy from earlier!
We kill all pirates!
That's the Cidre Guild's rule-ger!
Cidre Guild?!
So it was you guys who attacked the Sunny!
You're charging at us like a fool!
Take this!
Super Strong Tornado Soda!
My eyes!
I can't believe it!
Luffy!
Hancock!
Oh...
The Pirate Empress is here on this island?
Yes, sir! It seems like she met Straw Hat.
GUARANA - LEADER OF THE CARBONATE SWORD SQUAD
CIDRE GUILD
How lucky!
CIDRE - COMMANDER OF THE CARBONATE ASSAULT
CIDRE GUILD
That's favorable for us!
This is our chance to get rid of
that annoying Warlord of the Sea!
Huh? What do you mean?
Kill them both!
If we do that,
we'll have trouble with the Navy!
We can just tell them that
Straw Hat killed the Pirate Empress!
Luffy! Did you hear that I was here...
...and come for me?!
What? I just came here to buy cola!
What?!
We bumped into each other by chance...
It's truly...
...meant to be!
You fools!
Do you know who's taking a bath now?!
"Who's taking a bath"?!
Of course, we know-ger!
You're alive as I thought, Straw Hat!
Luffy! You...!
You don't want them to see
that thing on your back, do you?
Leave the rest to me!
You're nothing!
Don't act all cool
because you're in front of a woman!
Luffy!
Thank you for protecting me.
But it's rude to enter
while someone's bathing...
I should teach them a lesson!
Guys! Pull yourselves together!
They're pirates-ger!
"No mercy for pirates"!
That's what Commander Cidre always says-ger!
Shoot-ger!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Slave...
...Arrow!
You bastards!
Snake Princess!
Big Sis-sama! Catch this!
Oh, thanks!
Thanks for waiting!
I'm all ready!
Damn you! I have no options left!
Take this! Super Highly-concentrated...
...Deluxe CO2 Gas-ger!
I'm gonna kill you all-ger!
I can't breathe...
Let's retreat!
Hancock!
Are you okay?
Your face was very close!
L-Luffy's very close...
W-What should I do?
Hancock!
It's dangerous here with the gas!
--Let's escape for now!
--Oh, yes!
Commander Cidre! I have a report.
The targets are heading
towards the cola factory.
What should we do?
Don't do anything! I'll come myself!
It's our first hunt of big-time
pirates in a long time!
This is the Cidre Guild's stronghold...
Mm-hm. Looks like
they gave up the chase for now.
You think your sisters are okay?
Are you worrying about them?
You're so kind.
I'm sorry that I got you involved
in this mess...
Don't mention it. I'm happy!
I didn't think I'd be able to see you
until the Pirates Fest...
The Pirates Fest?
You don't know it?
It's a festival exclusively for pirates
that randomly takes place about
once every several years.
From across the Grand Line,
pirates whose bounties
would easily add up to over
10 billion will gather
and it's also a dark festival
during which lawlessness reigns.
Oh, that sounds interesting!
The Pirates Fest!
I wanna go and see it for myself!
You can come with me!
I'm getting excited!
I'll get cola and go to the festival!
That's the power of carbonation!
If you release the gas pressure
which is increased to its limit all at once,
you can cause a big blast
that'll make a hole in the ground!
What's your problem?!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
We'll have your heads!
We, the Cidre Guild, will!
Are they bounty hunters?
I just want cola!
We have no cola to sell to pirates!
I'm Commander Cidre!
One of you two will be the
100th head that I hunt!
Prepare yourselves!
Cidre finally turns into
his ultimate true form!
Facing his furious consecutive
attacks, Luffy and Hancock
display their powerful techniques!
Luffy or Cidre, who will
survive in this final battle?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Side Story! Clash! Luffy vs. the King of Carbonation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!