One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
In order to take Otama to a doctor,
Luffy left Amigasa Village and ran into Zoro on the way.
Luffy arrived at the Land of Wano
and met Otama.
Here you go.
After being attacked
by an unknown army, the Cidre Guild,
Go ahead and dig in!
Let me borrow this sword, too!
It's very samurai-ish!
Big Bro!
Why did she cook for you?
Luffy rescued a girl named Otama
from Kaido's subordinates,
the Straw Hats evacuated to a small island
filled with CO2 gas and started repairing the Sunny.
However, Hawkins who became Kaido's subordinate
stood in their way!
You fool! You can't take that!
It's a well-known sword!
It's a sin to handle it so casually!
and was treated to freshly-cooked rice
in return.
How could you eat that?!
My ancestor, Kotetsu,
forged that world-famous sword!
But they ran out of cola
for the Coup de Burst so Luffy...
Don't bring disgrace on me!
Nigiri...
It's called Kitetsu II!
It must be cola!
At least a barrelful of it!
Tower Climb...
Otama!
Tama!
All right! I'll go buy it!
In order to take Otama to a doctor,
Luffy learned that Otama is waiting to
see Ace again in her village but...
...Ripple!
Stop making noise, stomach!
Luffy borrowed Hitetsu's sword
and left Amigasa Village.
Give me money, Nami!
This isn't becoming of a samurai!
However, this island is
actually the Cidre Guild's stronghold
She must've done a foolish thing!
After losing Hawkins, Luffy and the others
headed for a teahouse following Otsuru's directions.
Ace died.
I suppose she drank the river water
to ease her hunger.
That's Zoro!
and they have a monopoly on cola.
Hey, Zoro! It's me, it's me!
Water?
Big Bro, you're a liar!
Take this!
Super Strong Tornado Soda!
At the teahouse, the waitress, Okiku, was hit on
by Urashima, the No.1 wrestler in the Land of Wano...
Luffy bounds through the wasteland
to save Otama.
Hey!
Luffy!
However, Hawkins stands in his way!
My eyes!
You were here after all!
Hey... I'm sorry but your fat-ass is in my way.
I finally got to see you!
Along with Hancock who
was visiting the island,
The communication was
probably cut at Kuri Beach.
Now, let's play a game.
Thus, Luffy met Zoro again.
Move aside.
What should we do, Boss?
Luffy reached the Cidre Guild's cola factory.
However, there came...
A game?!
That's right... With these Strawman Cards...
Just then, their leader Cidre
launched his attack!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Meanwhile, a group spies on
Luffy and the others' movements.
In this Land of Wano, you either follow the strong
or become their prey...
Don't tell Kaido-san.
We'll have your heads!
I'll handle it!
I just want cola!
You have no other option!
"The Greatest Day of My Life!
Otama and Her Sweet Red-bean Soup!"
"The Headliner!
Hawkins the Magician Appears!"
One of you two will be the
100th head that I hunt!
Otama!
Ace!
"Defeat is Inevitable!
The Strawman's Fierce Attack!"
"Side Story!
Clash! Luffy vs. the King of Carbonation!"
The probability of you two living another month...
"Save Otama!
Straw Hat, Bounding through the Wasteland!"
Prepare yourselves!
I drew a good card.
The Reversed Hierophant...
19 percent...
The card of pursuit!
Tama! Stay with us!
If you're here for sightseeing,
get lost.
That must be Luffy...
Tama!
Do you know who reigns over this country
behind the scenes?
He's showing off...
Now, you guys are next.
I don't know!
It's Kaido, right?!
We're here to...
W-Wait!
This is a decoction of Evil-Purging Herbs.
...beat the Emperor of the Sea!
Please wait!
Hey!
We're not members of the Cidre Guild!
Hey, Luffy!
Kin'emon said
we shouldn't say things like that, either...
It's bitter but it works well.
Let her drink it.
Where can I get water and food?
We were threatened
and forced to fight as their soldiers!
Stay with us, Tama!
Uh, that was a lie!
I don't know!
Uh-huh.
Tama. Here's the medicine.
Save us... and the island!
And is there a doctor around here?
Drink it!
Don't tell me...
I'm gonna take Tama!
Yww!
In return for giving me food!
Bear with it and drink!
Gum-Gum...
If you cross the wasteland to the north,
you'll find a town with a doctor...
...Pistol!
By the way, where did you get that sword?
Drink!
Okay.
Wait!
It's a famous sword, isn't it?
Drink!
Kaido's subordinates could be on patrol
along the way!
Well, it really seems like a famous sword to me.
Besides, carrying Otama there is too much...
Don't worry! I'm quite strong!
Let me see it for a sec.
We're bounty hunters
who target pirates!
No way!
We can make money
and the world of the sea becomes peaceful!
Hey, Luffy!
You're bleeding from your arm...
I can't risk Otama's life for my cause...
Come on! Let me just hold it!
Protect the brat!
So it's a win-win!
Oh, it's just a scratch.
--No-de-gozaru!
--Just let me see it!
Isn't this a golden opportunity?
--It's gotta be treated now...
--It'll heal on its own.
--I said no-de-gozaru!
--Why?!
--No-de-gozaru!
--Hey, cut it out!
I'll...
No!
A sword is a samurai's soul-de-gozaru!
Wait, you fool!
Your outlandish outfit is too conspicuous!
Put this on!
Pirate Empress!
Here...
...handle...
I won't let you get in Cidre-sama's way!
...that one!
No, I won't let you hurt Luffy!
Oh, it's a kimono!
You're a pirate!
Is it okay for you to have a samurai's soul?!
--Stay still!
--I like samurai armor, too!
I couldn't ask for more!
Let's fight!
Oh, are you awake?!
You can't use a sword anyway
so just give it to me!
No one wears that every day!
Big Bro! Ma'am!
No, no, no!
I'm gonna cut them up-de-gozaru!
You're good to go!
Slave Arrow!
Where am I?
This is my teahouse.
There's a reason I can't go to the town...
Zorojuro, handle those in the back-de-gozaru!
Take care of Otama!
Okay... But listen!
I'll reimburse the doctor's fee later!
Komachiyo!
Once we take care of them,
let me see your "soul"!
You're as agile as a rat.
Sorry to make you worry.
If I can meet my friends before that,
we'll get food and medical care for free!
Charge.
Otama-chan!
If you can't hit me,
your special ability doesn't scare me.
They'll help us!
How's your stomach?
Does it hurt, Otama-chan?
We, the Cidre Guild, are a team of
This is a sword fight-de-gozaru!
strong warriors who are looking
to succeed as bounty hunters.
Look what you got there!
Don't throw the scabbard!
We're good at chopping off
power-users' heads!
Let me borrow this sword, too!
It's very samurai-ish!
Gum-Gum...
Okay, see you!
...Pistol!
Tama! I'll take you to a doctor now!
You're not priced at 1.5 billion for nothing!
No, wait!
That's not a sword technique!
You fool! You can't take that!
I feel better!
It's a well-known sword!
It's a sin to handle it so casually!
It worked so fast!
My ancestor, Kotetsu,
forged that world-famous sword!
Gatling!
The Evil-Purging Herb is
an incredible wonder drug.
Thank you all!
It's one of only 21 Excellent Grade Swords!
It's called Kitetsu II!
Nin-nin!
But...
Listen!
Out of the numerous swords in the world,
...the poison in your body
can't be removed completely.
the ones that were made by the great swordsmiths
are called Grade Swords.
So don't ever drink the river water again,
Otama-chan.
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Dog! Hang on just a bit!
Okay, I got it!
And the finest among them are called...
This is my chance!
50 FINE GRADE SWORDS
...the 50 Fine Grade Swords,
21 EXCELLENT GRADE SWORDS
the 21 Excellent Grade Swords,
You're not using it the right way!
Stop making noise, stomach!
This isn't becoming of a samurai!
12 SUPREME GRADE SWORDS
and the 12 Supreme Grade Swords.
Water!
There's a story behind Kitetsu in particular...
River!
Otama-chan! Stop!
Huh?!
He's gone!
Pistol Kiss!
You're quite tough.
I'm a samurai!
I'm gonna dice it up more and more-de-gozaru!
The river water...!
See you! I'm gonna take the sword!
Huh?
What?!
Hey! Listen to me!
The river water...
Don't ever drink it!
Wait! Wait!
One Gorilla!
I said no!
There, it's done.
This is only a field dressing though...
That sword is made of
carbonated water, too?
Two Gorilla!
Then, let me borrow your sword instead!
It's the Carbonated Stream Sword.
Yeah. Thank you.
This one is a famous sword, too!
The one you took is cursed!
You're so huge.
It's quite scary.
I don't wanna carry it!
You're gonna become cursed!
But Big Mom was an even huger woman.
Thank you for saving me earlier
when the sumo wrestler was hitting on me.
As I thought, you pirates...
...especially power-users...
I'm leaving now, Grandpa Nose!
Ace...
I didn't do anything.
...are the vermin of the world!
We made a promise...
I forgot to introduce myself.
I won't forgive you
if anything happens to Otama!
I (sessha) am Okiku.
Yeah, I'll save her at any cost!
And don't forget to return the sword!
Sessha?!
Answer me!
What?!
Why aren't you responding?!
I can't... I can't... No, no!
Once you go out to sea,
wherever you go,
power-user pirates are making a mess!
You shouldn't do that!
Someone has to do it...
If no one else is gonna do it,
Go ahead and eat.
I'll hunt down those pirates!
Dammit!
Please! Take it away! Ma'am!
Oh, Dog! Are you gonna carry us?!
Boss!
I know... Don't worry.
The real fight starts now!
I don't even have money for the herbs!
How could I pay for
some sweet red-bean soup?!
This is much easier!
Please make a beeline to the town!
How are you doing with the Empress?
Just what you'd expect
from a Warlord of the sea.
You don't have to pay for it.
Big Sis-sama!
No!
Oh, you two!
I can't have it!
Oh, you guys are okay!
What?!
How dare you attack our Big Sis!
We'll make you regret it!
I know both you and Okiku-san
haven't eaten much!
Oh, Tama! You're up!
Big Bro, where are we going
riding Komachiyo?
Get ready!
That's okay. Don't be shy.
To the doctor.
You get ready.
You've already saved my life
and now you're trying to give me food!
Does this dog know the way?
How can I accept this?!
That's okay.
No!
Ace died.
I said that's okay!
Here I come! I won't just disappear
after getting beaten like that!
I'll pay you back for the herbs
no matter what...
Ginger!
Nails?!
Okay, bring it on!
We'll make a ruckus!
That's enough!
Don't drop your guard!
Whoa-whoa, stop! You're gonna fall!
Kill them all!
What?!
Once a woman serves food...
Ginger, stay out of this!
You're a liar!
"I don't want it."
"Okay."
Do you think she'll just put it away so easily?!
Well, let's retreat for now.
Back to the factory!
Gum-Gum...
Ace can't come back!
That means you're gonna use that killer rig?!
If you're not gonna eat it...
Everyone knows about the Paramount War!
I'll spill it in the street!
Yeah, that's right.
I'm gonna show them a thing or two!
...Battle-Axe!
No!
Otama-chan, eat it!
Those bastards!
Otsuru-san won't take no for an answer.
Wait!
Luffy! Let's go, girls!
But...
...we made a promise.
Commander, until you get fully geared up,
we'll stall them.
Ace will come back!
Mm-hm. It won't take long!
Luffy, you chase Cidre!
There must be cola there!
Ace! Take me to the sea with you!
Got it!
I'm old enough!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Two-Sword Style...
How long will you sit like that?
Hawkins-san! We're no match for them!
But you're only five.
You should be happy!
Today's your birthday!
Damn Straw Hat!
I'm already five!
Nigiri...
Boss! Please fight for us!
--You're good at that.
--Yeah, I am!
Where are you looking?
Is that true?
Boss!
Tower Climb...
You're gonna leave here soon, right?
That's what I heard.
Yeah! I have to finish this before that...
You guys have committed
quite a lot of atrocities...
Then, take it as a birthday present from me
...Ripple!
and eat up.
...for your own benefit...
I... don't wanna say goodbye to...
Ace and everyone else...
What?! You guys came to steal cola
for your own benefit, too!
Tama...
We'll come back!
After we become a greater pirate group!
No matter what I do, I'll be forgiven...
Then, will you let me join your crew?
Because...
Gum-Gum...
...I'm beautiful.
...Pistol!
I wanna go on an adventures with you!
You're nothing but a pirate...
Should we go after them, Hawkins-san?!
Ace! Let me join your crew!
Even the lizard's attacking me!
To be a pirate, you must be strong!
Damn you!
This is a good warm-up
before going to kick Bullet's ass...
When I come back,
if you become a bewitching female ninja or something,
I'll take you along!
The Hierophant.
Ace! Is it the "bewitching" thing required?!
It's the card of help.
Straw Sword.
He's a perfect opponent to test this...
Someone will show them the way
and they'll escape safely...
Ace!
Straw Hat!
I got it! That's a promise, okay?!
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
We were very close...
What?
Is this your first time having it?!
He said he'd come back...
Yes!
Cidre! Where are you?!
How many days do you think it's been
since she ate?!
You don't know how nice he is!
That's why you don't understand my pain!
What kind of sword is that?!
Give me cola!
Even if she busily weaves hats every day
and sells them,
I feel bad for the lizard!
Stop hitting me...
Although it doesn't hurt...
we can only earn barely enough for
one person to live!
Cidre!
How could you say he died that casually?!
Are you in here?!
Hawkins...
You... dummy!
That guy has an annoying ability...
Help us!
We were forced to fight like this by Cidre!
There are some rice cakes in it!
We had no choice
because he took our families hostage!
What a sumptuous treat!
Oh! So you guys are...
That was fast!
You can make them out of your cheek.
...the men of the island that the
soda-pop old lady was talking about!
We're almost out of the bamboo forest!
You can't fill your stomach with those.
He's a little pesky...
Yum-yum!
Thanks for waiting!
It took time for me to prepare for
taking you out...
Now, how's the brat doing?
Ma'am! Thank you very much!
Instead of an apology,
let me tell you something.
Ouch!
I don't think I could top
a wonderful birthday like this!
The Grandpa Nose was right...
The real power and terror of
carbonated water...
Her temperature's rising...
Dog!
Run faster!
...are materialized into this form!
I feel bad for Master-sama though!
It's really a wasteland!
In order to destroy you damn power-users
and bring down history's greatest evil,
Bullet the Demon Heir,
Otsuru-san...
That's impressive.
this, the Cidre Guild's most
powerful rig, was made!
This is the greatest day of my life!
What just happened?!
Why's he still alive?!
THE SLASHER
They still haven't caught the slasher yet?!
It's dangerous...
Oh? What's the problem?
Children like her are not uncommon...
Straw Hat, do you like the power of this rig?
...in the Land of Wano...
Such a small child not being able to get enough food
is unbelievable!
Don't tell me...
The rotation that's generated
by the force of CO2 gas...
Are you lost?!
Minus One Life.
Well, if you're a grown-up,
you can eat poison.
I can't sleep at night!
What are the authorities doing?!
...beats everything in its path!
No, you can't!
As long as we have the sea, mountains, and forests,
getting food shouldn't be a problem.
That bastard! Where did he go?!
Dog! You're the only one who knows the way!
Please!
These Strawmen represent my subordinates.
But it's quite weak...
Right.
Shut up!
If we humans hadn't ruined them ourselves...
We've got no time to waste...
I can store them within my body
with my Straw-Straw Fruit power,
Damn Kaido!
Let's just... go right.
Yeah...
This place is great!
I can eat as much meat and fish as I want!
so I won't be harmed.
Go left.
If I store ten of them,
I can die ten times.
You're such sweet young men.
You samurai-sama are so strong.
Oh, yeah! What are your names?
If I could just get sake, it'd be perfect...
My name is Zorojuro.
Who are you?!
Fly away, Pirate Empress!
I'm a ronin.
Hey! Woman, stop!
I can't believe you repelled Hawkins...
I'm Monkey D...
You're...
Now, let's play a game.
I was saved by you, green
gentleman, earlier...
Come on! Take this!
A game?!
His name is...
It's a tiger!
My name is Tsuru.
Perfume Femur!
And a boar!
OTSURU - A TEAHOUSE OWNER
Luffytaro.
What?!
R-Right...
That's right... With these Strawman Cards...
What is that?!
--Th-That's a Sharkodile!
--It's pretty wild!
Were you hiding in that tail all this time?!
I'm Luffytaro!
...Gozaru.
If you're ever hungry,
you can just eat them!
Yes, I was.
That's impossible.
Thank you for saving me.
You're from overseas, right?
N-No way... How could I...
Those samurai who were strong enough to catch them have
--It must've been hard to enter the country.
--How could you tell?
either been arrested or became bandits...
--You talk weird.
--What?!
That's our Big Sis-sama.
Oh, no!
Besides...
Don't worry. I won't tell anybody.
That was great.
Here!
Seems like your fight is over,
Snake Princess.
Could you at least wipe the sweat off of her?
Animals drink the polluted river water, too...
I'm new to this town, too.
Oh! Thanks!
So they are poisonous for humans to eat...
And Okiku-chan has only been working here
for a month.
If Luffy can get rid of Cidre,
this'll be over.
I hope this doesn't sound too forward,
But they look so delicious!
That's unforgivable!
but could I take care of
that child, Otama-chan?
I heard this town is called Okobore (Leftovers).
What kind of name is that?
--Do you know her?
--Yes.
Is that the factory where the smoke is coming from?!
Just like the name implies,
Oh, good! Please!
those who live here
get leftovers from the town of officials.
Yes!
They have a mine and a weapon factory...
She drank the polluted river water
to ease her hunger.
So there are a lot of
Kaido's subordinates there.
Tama said there is
non-poisonous food somewhere.
Gear Two!
I thought so...
Look over there.
What do they eat?
That's not good.
Gum-Gum...
You see the mountain without chimneys?
The Shogun and Kaido have an untainted farm...
...Jet Gatling!
On the top of it,
there used to be a castle called Oden.
...just for themselves.
It's already been 20 years.
Instead of seeking a doctor,
That's why they have clean water and rice...
Oden... I've heard that word before.
What was it?
come to my teahouse.
Tea?!
...and fish...
This is no time for tea!
Until some 20 years ago,
If we don't hurry up,
she's gonna die!
...and meat... lots of them...
a clan called Kozuki had governed this Land of Wano
for a very long time.
I don't know who the brat is
so I guess it's not my concern but...
Man! So it's not like
there isn't any on this island!
That vast farm that expands
to the bottom of the mountain...
Hey! Tama! Are you alright?!
No, no...
Pirates...
We have a medical herb
that works very well against the poison of the river.
Ouch!
...was made by the late Oden-sama,
I think your temperature is rising!
...only exist for me to get rich!
in order to feed everyone in Kuri
delicious food.
That'll be the best to treat
Otama-chan's condition.
Hang on!
It wasn't meant for Orochi and the others
to monopolize the country's food supplies.
I'll get you to a doctor soon!
If the enemy has water and food,
that serves my interest just fine!
I see... Then, help us!
Hurry up, Dog!
I don't need dreams or the One Piece
That Paradise Farm...
Thank you!
because they don't really exist!
Okay, I'll show you the way.
I heard that!
I'll even destroy Bullet the Demon Heir,
at the Pirate Fest...
If you go left, you can get to the town.
Please forgive me!
Dog! Go!
Wait, woman!
...to get my revenge
and seize a huge sum of money!
Leave everything you have!
To return the favor I owe you,
Help! Somebody!
let me treat you, too,
green gentleman...
You can't take down any pirate.
It wasn't meant for Orochi and the others
to monopolize the country's food supplies.
You have no conviction...
That Paradise Farm...
...and I won't lose to you.
I heard that!
I'm not a straightforward person
who'd fight two pirates from the Worst Generation squarely.
Is there non-poisonous food at the farm?
Damn! I'll make you pay for this!
There is.
Lady, step back...
Gear Three!
Safe delicious food,
clean water and clothes...
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI, LAND OF WANO
They all belong to...
...the Shogun Orochi!
ZOROJURO - A SERIOUS CRIMINAL
MURDERING THE MAGISTRATE
You're that serious criminal, Zorojuro!
Here you go.
Gum-Gum...
Oh! These dango dumplings
that I eat on rare occasions in this teahouse...
He's a bigger pain in the ass than I thought...
You fool.
On the other side of the shrine gate,
there is a town where the officials live.
That sake...
...Elephant Gun!
What else would you expect?
...are the only things...
Give it to me!
We beg them to sell us things that they no longer use
and nearly spoiled food to maintain our lives.
....that keep me going.
You're exaggerating...
That's why it's called Okobore Town...
Soon, you'll be able to eat as many as you want
just like you used to.
But we're fine...
At least, we can live.
Let's begin.
I hope so...
OKIKU - THE TEAHOUSE WAITRESS
Hey, old man, the place is closing now!
Go away!
Now, Okiku.
You can't pay the street tax, right-pe?
I'm just saying I'll help you.
Samurai-sama!
The Reversed Fool!
If you become my wife,
Cidre has been brought down?!
you won't have to work!
He talked so big like that
but he's that weak?
You can eat delicious food from the farm
as much as you want every day-pe!
Oops... It signifies an internal discord.
I don't know who you are,
but thank you for saving my life!
Now I can't wait to see Straw Hat Luffy!
Our social standings are too different.
What do you think you're doing?!
Don't get in my way!
If you won't order anything,
Straw Hat Luffy and Bullet...
please leave...
I heard you, woman!
Oh, don't mention it.
I don't wanna eat anything from this place!
If those two really clash with one another,
I just wanted their sake...
You were speaking ill about the Shogun!
These dango and tea are made from
someone's leftovers!
it's gonna be very exciting!
...de-gozaru.
I can hear six times better
than normal humans!
BAT-MAN - A GIFTER WITH THE BAT SMILE FRUIT
But I wanna return you a favor.
Hey, you don't know me well, do you-pe?
I won't miss a foul word spoken
about the Shogun!
Then, sake, please!
Sorry... I'll draw a better card next...
Oh, I don't have any.
I'm a famous yokozuna at the capital.
I understand that you heard it,
but is that a good reason
to take someone's life?
You must take the risks,
because there are cards that will grant you power
which exceeds your limits.
She would've died if it hit her.
This is good cola.
The No.1 sumo wrestler in the Land of Wano!
Is it really okay to take that much?
As long as you live quietly,
I'll rarely have cause to hurt you!
That's Zoro!
Urashima!
It's free!
We don't have to buy it for a while!
Hey, Zoro! It's me, it's me!
But Orochi-sama...
Quit this seedy teahouse!
Hey!
...will never allow people to harbor
a rebellious spirit!
We changed back...
Stop living pathetically
on someone's leftovers
Luffy!
...all the men of the island
who were turned into stone.
You were here after all!
I assume they're meeting their families
by now.
and why don't you and I... huh?
I finally get to see you!
Zoro!
Okiku-chan!
Thank you, Hancock.
You helped me a lot!
Ya-hoo!
It's been a long...
Please don't mention it.
I'm happy to support you any time...
Otsuru-san!
It's been a long time-de-gozaru!
By the way, Luffy,
about the Pirate Fest...
Otama-chan drank the poison of the river!
Oh, don't worry.
Oh! That's serious!
Is everyone with you?
Tsk! How about this?!
Yeah, I lost them, but...
See? I got an invitation.
Please! Do something to save her!
...I guess they're okay!
What?
Okiku-chan!
Alright, I'm leaving now!
See you at the Pirate Fest!
Brew the Evil-Purging Herbs!
Yes, right away!
Oh, Luffy...
Hey!
He went away...
Who are you fools-pe?!
Just like a whirlwind...
You have meat! Gimme some!
Okiku and I were talking-pe!
Well, that's okay.
I can see him again soon...
There are a bunch of fish and animals to hunt
in this area, Luffy!
Hey! What are you doing, Dog?!
This means I'll have a date with him!
Hey... I'm sorry but your
fat-ass is in my way.
Hawkins-san!
You'll never be short of food!
Fear not.
Move aside.
No, be careful!
The water around here is poisonous!
Ta-dah!
I'm asking you...
Look what I found!
So I heard the meat and fish
are poisonous, too!
Why would I have to do that...
That's an invitation to the Pirate Fest!
I see.
That's why I have a stomachache.
Hm? What is the Pirate Fest?!
Tama! Stay with me, Tama!
Okiku! I'll have a match
in Bakura Town later-pe!
It's a pirate-only festival.
She's burning up!
A festival?! And we get to go?!
That's why this dog is rushing.
I'll show you how strong I am
so come see if you're interested!
It's a very fun, but terrifying, festival.
Anyway, Zoro, come with us!
I got this!
--You bastards!
--We won't let you get away!
What?! W-What do you mean it's terrifying?
One thing led to another,
and I'm on my way to take her to a doctor.
A bunch of pirates will gather,
Chase them!
so there'll be fishy business and dealings,
and some friction.
A sick brat!
You shouldn't be stopping to eat!
Even so, festivals always
attract beautiful ladies.
Don't worry! I'll eat fast!
Stop!
I bet there'll be rare kinds of sake, too.
Samurai-sama!
Where'll that festival take place?
I'll treat you, too, so come here!
--Just eat already!
--Okay!
It says this one will take place
at Delta Island.
And there'll be a competition to
find Roger's treasure.
Hey, Shachi! They're...
What?!
Yeah...
We gotta hurry up!
B-By Roger, you mean
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates?!
Are you...
Yeah, I'm gonna finish them off!
Arrows!
Hawkins-san! They're getting away!
...the ronin who is wanted
across the country, Zorojuro,
He blocked all of them!
I wonder if it's true...
Who are you?!
Boss!
That's them, right?! The Straw Hats!
We'll see once we go there.
For several weeks,
there have been robberies at the farm.
and members of his clan?
Racing against other pirates
to find Roger's treasure...
I hope they won't mess up our plan...
I drew a good card.
We're looking for the robber now!
Should I go tell them
before they make any trouble?!
That sounds like fun!
Don't tell me it's you guys!
Oh?! He's...
Let's go! Set sail for Delta Island!
The Reversed Hierophant...
You'd better not!
That's right...
You'll draw people's attention!
Seems like he's working for Kaido.
Yeah!
The card of pursuit!
They'll go "Why is a bear here?!"
and get panicky!
A one-eyed ronin?!
Straw Hat!
Now, gather...
I was on my way to Kuri Beach...
I'm sorry...
ZOROJURO THE SLASHER
I saw him on the wanted poster!
Anyway, let's just report it to the Captain.
Damn pirates with bounties
of over 100 million...
But you're the one who caused the trouble there, aren't you?
Two of my subordinates
and one baboon went missing...
Hey, Roger... I wish I could let you see it.
BASIL HAWKINS
ONE OF THE BEAST PIRATES' HEADLINERS
The possibility that you guys have something to do with it...
...is 98 percent.
It's gonna be the greatest thing in history!
The whole ocean and world...
But...
...that doesn't matter.
...will finally change by my hands!
In this Land of Wano, you either follow the strong
or become their prey...
Let go of me!
Dear world, enjoy it!
This festival... The exciting...
You have no other option!
Who are you?!
...Pirate Fest!
I'm a great runner!
I can run at 200 kilometers per hour!
ONIGASHIMA
Big Bro!
One of the Four Emperors,
Kaido, King of the Beasts!
This is the warning Kin'emon gave us, Luffy!
Tama!
He is the strongest creature in the world!
"Don't make a scene!"
Otama-chan!
For now, he is just sitting down
and calmly biding his time.
It's gonna start, Roger!
Help!
Only the strongest one will survive!
Big Bro!!
Well, then I'll have to just...
Just one!
...apologize to him later!
Tama!!
Luffy and Zoro demonstrate their intense
When Otama and Luffy end up in a deadly crisis,
Zoro's avenging slash howls!
sword skills!
Will they be able to defeat the invincible Hawkins?!
While traveling across a wasteland with Otama,
Luffy finally sees Zoro again!
Otama is taken away to Bakura Town where officials and pirates
under the control of Orochi's subordinates thrive!
Polluted soil! People in tears!
Otsuru reveals the cruel reality of the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Headliner! Hawkins the Magician Appears!"
"Defeat is Inevitable! The Strawman's Fierce Attack!"
However, Hawkins, one of the enemy's Headliners,
stands in their way!
As danger descends on Otama moment by moment,
will Luffy and his clan be able to reach the enemy's territory?!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
When the taste of tears
becomes sweet red-bean soup,
In the land where the
law of the jungle rules,
the rookies from the Worst Generation clash!
Everybody! Let's go!
Let's go!
the promise between Luffy and
UNEXPECTED ALLIANCE
It finally begins!
THEATERS ARE PACKED!!
Otama opens the future
for the Land of Wano!
I'm gonna kill
all the marines and pirates!
BIGGEST OPENING DAY OF 2019
On the next episode of One Piece! "Charging into the
Enemy's Territory! Bakura Town - Where Officials Thrive!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
You need friends because you're weak!
"Save Otama! Straw Hat, Bounding
through the Wasteland!"
Pave the way for Luffy!
"The Greatest Day of My Life!
Otama and Her Sweet Red-bean Soup!"
--Luffy!
--Straw Hat-ya!
In this sea world, no one lives alone!!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The movie ONE PIECE STAMPEDE!
A BLOCKBUSTER NOW PLAYING!
THEATERS GET ALL HEAT UP!!