One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
After being attacked
by an unknown army, the Cidre Guild,
the Straw Hats evacuated to a small island
filled with CO2 gas and started repairing the Sunny.
But they ran out of cola
for the Coup de Burst so Luffy...
It must be cola!
At least a barrelful of it!
All right! I'll go buy it!
Give me money, Nami!
However, this island is
actually the Cidre Guild's stronghold
and they have a monopoly on cola.
Take this!
Super Strong Tornado Soda!
My eyes!
Along with Hancock who
was visiting the island,
Luffy reached the Cidre Guild's cola factory.
Just then, their leader Cidre
launched his attack!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
We'll have your heads!
I just want cola!
One of you two will be the
100th head that I hunt!
"Side Story!
Clash! Luffy vs. the King of Carbonation!"
Prepare yourselves!
That must be Luffy...
He's showing off...
Now, you guys are next.
W-Wait!
Please wait!
We're not members of the Cidre Guild!
We were threatened
and forced to fight as their soldiers!
Save us... and the island!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
We're bounty hunters
who target pirates!
We can make money
and the world of the sea becomes peaceful!
So it's a win-win!
Pirate Empress!
I won't let you get in Cidre-sama's way!
No, I won't let you hurt Luffy!
I couldn't ask for more!
Let's fight!
Slave Arrow!
You're as agile as a rat.
If you can't hit me,
your special ability doesn't scare me.
We, the Cidre Guild, are a team of
strong warriors who are looking
to succeed as bounty hunters.
We're good at chopping off
power-users' heads!
You're not priced at 1.5 billion for nothing!
Gatling!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Pistol Kiss!
That sword is made of
carbonated water, too?
It's the Carbonated Stream Sword.
As I thought, you pirates...
...especially power-users...
...are the vermin of the world!
Once you go out to sea,
wherever you go,
power-user pirates are making a mess!
Someone has to do it...
If no one else is gonna do it,
I'll hunt down those pirates!
The real fight starts now!
How are you doing with the Empress?
Just what you'd expect
from a Warlord of the sea.
Big Sis-sama!
Oh, you two!
Oh, you guys are okay!
How dare you attack our Big Sis!
We'll make you regret it!
Get ready!
You get ready.
Here I come! I won't just disappear
after getting beaten like that!
Ginger!
Okay, bring it on!
We'll make a ruckus!
Don't drop your guard!
Kill them all!
Ginger, stay out of this!
Well, let's retreat for now.
Back to the factory!
That means you're gonna use that killer rig?!
Yeah, that's right.
I'm gonna show them a thing or two!
Those bastards!
Wait!
Luffy! Let's go, girls!
Commander, until you get fully geared up,
we'll stall them.
Mm-hm. It won't take long!
Luffy, you chase Cidre!
There must be cola there!
Got it!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Damn Straw Hat!
Where are you looking?
You guys have committed
quite a lot of atrocities...
...for your own benefit...
What?! You guys came to steal cola
for your own benefit, too!
No matter what I do, I'll be forgiven...
Because...
...I'm beautiful.
You're nothing but a pirate...
This is a good warm-up
before going to kick Bullet's ass...
He's a perfect opponent to test this...
Straw Hat!
Cidre! Where are you?!
Give me cola!
Cidre!
Are you in here?!
Help us!
We were forced to fight like this by Cidre!
We had no choice
because he took our families hostage!
Oh! So you guys are...
...the men of the island that the
soda-pop old lady was talking about!
Thanks for waiting!
It took time for me to prepare for
taking you out...
Instead of an apology,
let me tell you something.
The real power and terror of
carbonated water...
...are materialized into this form!
In order to destroy you damn power-users
and bring down history's greatest evil,
Bullet the Demon Heir,
this, the Cidre Guild's most
powerful rig, was made!
Straw Hat, do you like the power of this rig?
The rotation that's generated
by the force of CO2 gas...
...beats everything in its path!
But it's quite weak...
Shut up!
Fly away, Pirate Empress!
Come on! Take this!
Perfume Femur!
N-No way... How could I...
That's our Big Sis-sama.
That was great.
Seems like your fight is over,
Snake Princess.
If Luffy can get rid of Cidre,
this'll be over.
Gear Two!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Pirates...
...only exist for me to get rich!
I don't need dreams or the One Piece
because they don't really exist!
I'll even destroy Bullet the Demon Heir,
at the Pirate Fest...
...to get my revenge
and seize a huge sum of money!
You can't take down any pirate.
You have no conviction...
...and I won't lose to you.
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Cidre has been brought down?!
He talked so big like that
but he's that weak?
Now I can't wait to see Straw Hat Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy and Bullet...
If those two really clash with one another,
it's gonna be very exciting!
This is good cola.
Is it really okay to take that much?
It's free!
We don't have to buy it for a while!
We changed back...
...all the men of the island
who were turned into stone.
I assume they're meeting their families
by now.
Thank you, Hancock.
You helped me a lot!
Please don't mention it.
I'm happy to support you any time...
By the way, Luffy,
about the Pirate Fest...
Oh, don't worry.
See? I got an invitation.
What?
Alright, I'm leaving now!
See you at the Pirate Fest!
Oh, Luffy...
He went away...
Just like a whirlwind...
Well, that's okay.
I can see him again soon...
This means I'll have a date with him!
Ta-dah!
Look what I found!
That's an invitation to the Pirate Fest!
Hm? What is the Pirate Fest?!
It's a pirate-only festival.
A festival?! And we get to go?!
It's a very fun, but terrifying, festival.
What?! W-What do you mean it's terrifying?
A bunch of pirates will gather,
so there'll be fishy business and dealings,
and some friction.
Even so, festivals always
attract beautiful ladies.
I bet there'll be rare kinds of sake, too.
Where'll that festival take place?
It says this one will take place
at Delta Island.
And there'll be a competition to
find Roger's treasure.
What?!
B-By Roger, you mean
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates?!
I wonder if it's true...
We'll see once we go there.
Racing against other pirates
to find Roger's treasure...
That sounds like fun!
Let's go! Set sail for Delta Island!
Yeah!
Now, gather...
Damn pirates with bounties
of over 100 million...
Hey, Roger... I wish I could let you see it.
It's gonna be the greatest thing in history!
The whole ocean and world...
...will finally change by my hands!
Dear world, enjoy it!
This festival... The exciting...
...Pirate Fest!
It's gonna start, Roger!
Only the strongest one will survive!
Just one!
While traveling across a wasteland with Otama,
Luffy finally sees Zoro again!
However, Hawkins, one of the enemy's Headliners,
stands in their way!
In the land where the
law of the jungle rules,
the rookies from the Worst Generation clash!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save Otama! Straw Hat, Bounding
through the Wasteland!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!