One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Here you go.
Go ahead and dig in!
Big Bro!
Luffy rescued a girl named Otama
from Kaido's subordinates,
and was treated to freshly-cooked rice
in return.
Stop making noise, stomach!
This isn't becoming of a samurai!
She must've done a foolish thing!
I suppose she drank the river water
to ease her hunger.
Water?
Luffy bounds through the wasteland
to save Otama.
However, Hawkins stands in his way!
Now, let's play a game.
A game?!
That's right... With these Strawman Cards...
"Defeat is Inevitable!
The Strawman's Fierce Attack!"
I drew a good card.
The Reversed Hierophant...
The card of pursuit!
Stay with us, Tama!
Hey, Luffy!
Protect the brat!
I'll...
...handle...
...that one!
Dog! Hang on just a bit!
You're quite tough.
One Gorilla!
Two Gorilla!
Dammit!
Boss!
I know... Don't worry.
Nails?!
Two-Sword Style...
Nigiri...
Tower Climb...
...Ripple!
Should we go after them, Hawkins-san?!
The Hierophant.
It's the card of help.
Someone will show them the way
and they'll escape safely...
Hawkins...
That guy has an annoying ability...
He's a little pesky...
Now, how's the brat doing?
Ouch!
Her temperature's rising...
Dog!
Run faster!
Oh? What's the problem?
Don't tell me...
Are you lost?!
Dog! You're the only one who knows the way!
Please!
We've got no time to waste...
Let's just... go right.
Go left.
You samurai-sama are so strong.
Who are you?!
I can't believe you repelled Hawkins...
You're...
I was saved by you, green
gentleman, earlier...
My name is Tsuru.
OTSURU - A TEAHOUSE OWNER
Were you hiding in that tail all this time?!
Yes, I was.
Thank you for saving me.
Oh, no!
Here!
Could you at least wipe the sweat off of her?
Oh! Thanks!
I hope this doesn't sound too forward,
but could I take care of
that child, Otama-chan?
--Do you know her?
--Yes.
Oh, good! Please!
She drank the polluted river water
to ease her hunger.
I thought so...
That's not good.
Instead of seeking a doctor,
come to my teahouse.
Tea?!
This is no time for tea!
If we don't hurry up,
she's gonna die!
I don't know who the brat is
so I guess it's not my concern but...
No, no...
We have a medical herb
that works very well against the poison of the river.
That'll be the best to treat
Otama-chan's condition.
I see... Then, help us!
Thank you!
Okay, I'll show you the way.
If you go left, you can get to the town.
Dog! Go!
To return the favor I owe you,
let me treat you, too,
green gentleman...
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI, LAND OF WANO
Here you go.
Oh! These dango dumplings
that I eat on rare occasions in this teahouse...
...are the only things...
....that keep me going.
You're exaggerating...
Soon, you'll be able to eat as many as you want
just like you used to.
I hope so...
OKIKU - THE TEAHOUSE WAITRESS
Hey, old man, the place is closing now!
Go away!
Now, Okiku.
You can't pay the street tax, right-pe?
I'm just saying I'll help you.
If you become my wife,
you won't have to work!
You can eat delicious food from the farm
as much as you want every day-pe!
Our social standings are too different.
If you won't order anything,
please leave...
I don't wanna eat anything from this place!
These dango and tea are made from
someone's leftovers!
Hey, you don't know me well, do you-pe?
I'm a famous yokozuna at the capital.
The No.1 sumo wrestler in the Land of Wano!
Urashima!
Quit this seedy teahouse!
Stop living pathetically
on someone's leftovers
and why don't you and I... huh?
Okiku-chan!
Otsuru-san!
Otama-chan drank the poison of the river!
Oh! That's serious!
Please! Do something to save her!
Okiku-chan!
Brew the Evil-Purging Herbs!
Yes, right away!
Hey!
Who are you fools-pe?!
Okiku and I were talking-pe!
Hey... I'm sorry but your
fat-ass is in my way.
Move aside.
I'm asking you...
Why would I have to do that...
Okiku! I'll have a match
in Bakura Town later-pe!
I'll show you how strong I am
so come see if you're interested!
Samurai-sama!
I'll treat you, too, so come here!
Hey, Shachi! They're...
Yeah...
That's them, right?! The Straw Hats!
I hope they won't mess up our plan...
Should I go tell them
before they make any trouble?!
You'd better not!
You'll draw people's attention!
They'll go "Why is a bear here?!"
and get panicky!
I'm sorry...
Anyway, let's just report it to the Captain.
ONIGASHIMA
One of the Four Emperors,
Kaido, King of the Beasts!
He is the strongest creature in the world!
For now, he is just sitting down
and calmly biding his time.
Polluted soil! People in tears!
Otsuru reveals the cruel reality of the Land of Wano!
When the taste of tears
becomes sweet red-bean soup,
the promise between Luffy and
Otama opens the future
for the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Greatest Day of My Life!
Otama and Her Sweet Red-bean Soup!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!