Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Hiriluk's Cherry Blossoms!
Miracle in the Drum Rockies."
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
I'll save this country as a doctor one day.
Humph!
Didn't you mean to say
"destroy the country"?
This is a winter island where
it's bitter cold year around.
Cherry blossoms won't bloom here.
They will!
I was a hopeless thug and dying,
but I lived on after seeing
those cherry blossoms.
I was able to have
a profound change of heart.
Every human in this world can be saved!
There's no disease in this
world that can't be cured.
I raised this skull towards
all the diseases!
This is a symbol of the belief
that nothing is impossible!
By raising this,
I'll fight just like pirates do!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
If you do, you'll understand very
well how small your problems are.
Doctor... I...
Hm?
I found you!
Hey, monster! Come with us!
Hm?
Ah!
Are you all right, Dalton-san?!
Yeah, I'm fine. I just felt
a little drained. That's all.
I'll be fine if I get some rest.
Hey, you guys!
Hm?
Ah! D-Dr. Kureha!
Are you happy, brats?
Take that injured guy
to the medical ward.
Ahh! You're that damn old hag!
And anyone else injured, too!
Y-Yes, Ma'am!
Don't dilly-dally!
Do you want the same
experience as this man?!
Nami-san, you should have your
sickness treated all the way.
Quiet! If I don't escape from here now,
our departure for Alabasta
will be delayed by two days!
Do you wanna see Vivi keep suffering?!
Stop grumbling, you two...
and get back to the medical ward!
Ahhhh!
I'm Usopp! Captain Usopp!
As I thought, his injuries have gotten
worse... since he overexerted himself.
Now... Dalton...
Where's the key to this arsenal?
You know where it is, right?
Key to the arsenal...
Why do you need such a thing?
It's none of your business.
That key was... always carried
by Wapol from long ago.
So if it's still the case, it flew
off with Wapol into the sky...
What?! Is that right?! Oh darn...
Doctorine...
Hm?
About the treatment fee for our crew...
would you make it all free?
Also, would you discharge me right away?
Did you ask just for the heck of
it knowing it's all impossible?
As my fee, I'll take the entire
cargo and money on your ship.
And you'll stay here and rest
at least for two more days!
Nami-san, she's right!
You should be treated all the way!
I'll be fine since I don't feel like I'll die!
That can't be a reason!
Ah...
You need the key to the arsenal, right?
What?! Why do you have that key?!
Is that the real one? How'd you get it?!
I stole it.
What?!
You've got guts dictating
terms to me like that.
You are really an unbelievable girl.
Okay then... You don't have
to pay my fee. But that's all.
I can't accept the other term as a doctor.
Wait a sec! If that's the case, I can't
give the key to you! Give it back!
Listen, girl.
I have to leave this room
now to take care of things.
There's a drawer chest with
my coat in the back room.
And it's not like I'm posting guards...
Also, that young man's backbone
treatment is already complete.
But listen, don't you dare escape!
You guys, come with me.
I need you for heavy lifting.
Yes, Ma'am!
She told me to wear her coat, take
Sanji-kun and escape using this chance.
Yeah... that's how it sounded to me, too.
Hmmm...
I sure ran around a lot.
Night came before I even knew...
I don't hear voices any more...
Looks like they're gone...
This is for the best...
I can't leave this place...
It's a full moon tonight...
--Hey! Reindeer!
--Hm?
--Let's be pirates together!
--No way! They're still looking for me!
Hey, Luffy. Just give it up.
He hasn't shown up even after
all our efforts to find him.
He doesn't wanna be a pirate.
That's not true.
I wanna take him with us!
Like I said, that's what you want, right?!
It's not that I don't wanna go...
Reindeer!
Come out, reindeer!
But I won't go. I can't go!
I'm not like those guys!
Hm?
Reindeer!
Tony-kun!
Hey, let's be pirates together! Okay?!
It's not possible.
Yes, it is since it's fun!
Hey, you don't make sense.
But...
But I'm a reindeer!
I have antlers and hooves!
I even have a blue nose!
Can you guys heal the scar in his heart?
It's true... that I wanna be a pirate, but...
I'm not even a human! I'm a monster!
I can't become your friend! So...!
So I just came to say thank you...
I do appreciate you guys.
Thank you for asking me to join you.
I'll stay here, but...
one day... if you feel like it,
stop by agai...
Shut up! Let's go!
You don't ask people to join you
by telling them to "shut up."
Hey, Nami! Are you really okay?
I'm fine! I'm feeling great!
--Hey, let's go to say good-bye
--There! To commemorate our reaching here,
--to that old lady doctor and acorn pops, too.
--I built Snow Queen V!
--Don't be silly.
--Hey, how dare you kick
--Let him be alone with Doctorine.
--Snow Queen V! How disrespectful!
--He lived with her alone for 6 years.
It'll sure be a tearful farewell...
Doctorine acts like that in front of us,
but she is actually a kind person.
Hmmm... Really?
Then, we're really leaving here
without saying anything to her, huh?
Of course. Once Chopper comes,
we'll go down the mountain
and set sail immediately... to Alabasta!
You're fine with that too, right, Vivi?
Yeah, if a doctor comes with us...
A doctor?
Okay then, I'll get the ropeway ready.
Hey, Luffy! Give me a hand.
I didn't realize there was
a ropeway... That's amazing!
Now, hurry up and take them out!
Once they're outside
the gate, line them up!
Dr. Kureha!
Hm?
What are we taking so many
cannons out of the arsenal for?
Just hurry up and take them out!
Hm?
Oh? It seems there are
some patients missing.
They escaped...
disobeying your order...
I see... What am I going
to do with them...?
Doctorine!
I have something to talk about with you!
Chopper, where have you been?
Go downstairs and help
them take the cannons out.
Listen, Doctorine!
I'm gonna be a pirate.
I'm going with them!
What?!
I'm going out to sea.
I'll join them as a ship's doctor
and travel around the world!
Don't be ridiculous!
Now listen. You're my only assistant!
Who do you think taught you medicine?!
Or are you saying you don't
feel any gratitude towards me?!
Th-That's not true!
I do appreciate you, Doctorine!
I also love this land
where I met Doctor and you!
Humph! Then you can stay here.
You can't live in a fine castle
like this no matter where you go.
Pirates are good for nothing!
You'll end up dead in no time.
That's okay!
Don't talk so cocky!
I've never heard of a mere
reindeer going out to sea.
That's right. I'm a reindeer!
But I'm a man, too!
You sure talk big...
In any case, I won't allow it.
If you wanna leave that bad,
you have to get through me first!
Doctorine...
A crybaby like you is a man?!
Don't make me laugh!
Doctorine... But they...
Shut up! Let's go!
understand...
Shut up!
I won't allow you to have your way!
Come back, Chopper!
Wait!
Hm? It seems noisy...
Well, no matter what's going on,
we'd better take the cannons in
this arsenal outside the castle,
or Dr. Kureha will throw a
spear or something at us.
Don't be silly...
Wait!
Hm?
I won't let you escape!
Chopper!
Come back!
What's going on?
It's noisy inside the castle.
Gee, how thoughtless...
Why can't they be quiet when
others are saying farewell?
I'm sorry, Doctorine!
But I wanna see the world!
What do you think someone
like you can do at sea?!
Are you gonna live in a fantasy
just like that quack did?!
You're wrong! It wasn't a fantasy!
Doctor's research had
actually been completed!
Hey, he's coming...?! Hm?!
What?!
What's going on?! He's being chased!
Hey! The ropeway is rea... Hm?
Everyone! Get on the sleigh!
We'll go down the mountain!
What?!
Hey, look...
What the heck is that?
Ah! That's the witch's sleigh!
What was that?!
It was Dr. Kureha's reindeer.
The ones on the sleigh
were those pirates!
What happened up there?!
What the heck happened to Wapol?
Is Dalton-san okay?!
That felt good! Hey, do it again!
You idiot! We're setting sail right away!
I-I thought I'd die...
Hm? Where am I?!
Ah, Sanji-san! You came to?
Was it okay to bid farewell like that?
A pet I was taking care of is being
taken in by someone else. That's all.
I don't like... tears...
--Come with me!
--Ow!
We have to prepare a flashy send off!
Ouch...
I finally did it... This is it...
I've waited for this reaction for 30 years...
Doctor! It wasn't just a fantasy, right?!
Your research was completed then, right?!
Or, was that a lie, too?
I did it, Chopper! My research succeeded!
Did you lie because I'd be sad
if you died without saying so?
"Nothing is impossible for the man
who raised a flag with a skull!"
Please say it again, Doctor!
Are you ready, young men?!
Yes, Ma'am!
Fire!
Listen, Kureha. This dust is...
Dr. Kureha! What in the world...?
Just shut up and watch.
The noises are coming from the castle!
Hm? Has Wapol started
fireworks or something?
Idiot! They're cannon noises!
What's happening?!
Watch out for the cannonballs!
Dammit! We can't see
anything since it's night!
Dr. Kureha! We shot all of them!
Light them up!
Amazing...
Yeah...
It's so beautiful...
This is the answer that
I found spending 30 years.
What a fantastic sight this is...
I can't understand what
that idiot was thinking...
I will make cherry blossoms bloom.
Once my invention is complete,
this country will be saved!
Get out of here, quack!
Dammit! I thought lizard
eyeballs would work...
Listen. This red dust isn't ordinary dust.
This will attach to the
white snow in the air
and make vivid pink snow fall.
Doctor...! Doctorine...!
I will never shoot you!
My name is Dr. Hiriluk! I'm a doctor!
Tony Tony Chopper.
That's a cool name, isn't it?
That's what I'll call you.
Chopper, you'll be able to become
a good doctor. I'll guarantee it.
Even if I disappear,
my dream will come true.
I had... such a good life!
Thank you, Chopper!
Now, have a safe trip, my stupid son...
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Hey, Chopper! What's the matter?
How long are you gonna be in a daze?
Come here and dance! Sing!
Shhhh! Leave him alone for now!
He's experiencing what it's like
to set out on a journey as a man.
Okay, then! Let's toast to our new friend!
Yeah!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Goodbye Drum Island!
I'm Going Out to Sea!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!