One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Move out of my way!
Let go of me!
Bring the boss of this town!
Luffy and Zoro were rushing towards a town to save Otama.
From the town of leftovers,
Otama has been kidnapped by Shogun Orochi's men.
Don't do it...!
I have to tear Okiku into bits...
With the help of medicine brewed by Otsuru,
If you don't want me to, show your ability!
We're here to take back Tama!
Otherwise I'll lose face!
the teahouse owner they met along their way,
Big Bro!!
Otama made a full recovery.
Tama!
Tama!!
Luffy learned that the people of Wano
have been forced to live hard lives.
To save Otama,
Luffy and the others infiltrated Bakura Town.
In order to take back Otama
who has been kidnapped,
Luffy, Zoro, and Okiku go into action.
A notebook?
On their way,
they stumbled across a sumo event
Okay! No problem!
There are three Headliners in that town.
Tama said there is
non-poisonous food somewhere.
Well then...!
and Urashima, the yokozuna
who was pursuing Okiku, was there.
Hawkins.
Dosukoi!
Don't keep us waiting!
There is.
Holdem.
Ball-de-boo! Give us back Tama!
Dosukoi!
Safe delicious food,
clean water and clothes...
You guys!
Speed.
We're looking for someone!
How could you tame the savage baboon?!
They all belong to...
If you can beat me!
She's a little girl named Tama!
...the Shogun Orochi!
My men saw you do it!
Tell me where this town's boss is!
What?!
In order to protect Okiku, Luffy confronted Urashima,
a yokozuna of the Land of Wano's grand sumo.
I heard that!
However, Urashima and his clan didn't listen
and came to take Okiku away.
Don't try to pretend that you don't know!
I'm right here, boy!
Don't get in our way!
Meanwhile, captured by Holdem, a Headliner of
the Beast Pirates, Otama was in danger.
It must be none other than
a real Devil Fruit power.
You were speaking ill about the Shogun!
So you're this town's boss...
That's unforgivable!
...Ball-de-boo! Am I right?!
Shut up, you commoners!
Come on...
Stop chasing after ghosts forever...
Spit it out!
Luffy and the others
suddenly came under attack.
My name is Holdem!
To save Otama,
Luffy and the others go into action.
The Kozuki were an evil clan...
To us samurai-class, you fools are all
the same, vulgar, lowly bastards-pe!
However, the Gifter's true purpose was...
You finally showed yourself!
...that tried to destroy the Land of Wano
two decades ago!
I had no option!
I believe they said you tore
part of your cheek off.
How could you destroy my house
with a sumo wrestler?!
I (sessha) don't know anyone
who is called...
Although his opponent was the
undefeated monster, Urashima,
...a lowly bastard!
Luffy didn't give in an inch
and the bout heated up.
Let go of me!
Big Bro!
I'll save you now, Tama!
And then...
Who are you?!
I won't give her back to you!
Otama-chan!
If you're not gonna tell me...
Help!
Idiot!
Gum-Gum...
Meanwhile, noticing that there was trouble,
Hawkins and Law...
Big Bro!!
Let's give that a try.
Hey, bring me some pincers!
...were simultaneously heading
to Bakura Town.
Tama!
Yes, sir!
Tama!!
So cool!
Those fools...
GAZELLE-MAN - A GIFTER WITH THE GAZELLE SMILE FRUIT
Not that one! The bigger one!
Mission accomplished!
Kiku is so daring!
"Taking Back Otama!
A Fierce Fight Against Holdem!"
"Charging into the Enemy's Territory!
Bakura Town - Where Officials Thrive!"
Okiku!
Big Bro Luffy...
...Giant...
I knew you were the kind of man
who would hit a woman...
...Sumo Slap!
Help!
Don't do it...!
--Otama-chan!
--Damn!
If you don't want me to, show your ability!
Die!
Give us back Tama!
Urashima's deadly slap
is about to be unleased on Okiku!
Big Bro!
Tama! I'll save you right now!
"A Climactic Sumo Battle!
Straw Hat vs. the Strongest Ever Yokozuna!"
Save her?!
Tama!
How would you save her?! Hmm?!
I won't let you go!
Dosukoi!
Don't get in my way!
"The Yokozuna Appears!
The Invincible Urashima Goes After Okiku!"
Don't move!
If you resist,
this brat's body will be chewed up by...
"Luffy Rages!
Rescue Otama from Danger!"
Okiku-chan!
...Kamijiro the lion in my stomach!
Gum-Gum...
Tama!
FRONT ENTRANCE OF BAKURA TOWN
KURI, LAND OF WANO
We're here to save you!
Hey!
KAMIJIRO - HOLDEM'S STOMACH
...Sumo Slap!
Bring the boss of this town!
A sword?!
No!
Luffytaro-san!
He runs so fast!
You can't do that!
Let go of me!
Otama-chan! We'll save you now!
Shut up, you little shit!
Let go of Tama, Ball-de-boo!
Or I'm gonna kick your ass!
Give me a lift, Lion-dog-kun!
Hey!
Stop right there!
Like I said, my name is Holdem!
Say it right already!
Don't start a fuss!
We're here to take back Tama!
Dog!
Why?!
There's no record of them
leaving the town.
He's...
Big Bro!
Hey, take a good look!
Hey, who are you guys?!
Okiku-chan!
--That woman's holding a sword!
--She said she knew how to use it...
Komachiyo!
Everyone in this town is in league with
Otama-chan's kidnappers.
It's no mistake.
He's...
Just say whatever you like, fool!
I've never seen her using it though...
I'm not gonna give her back to you!
Why do you want this stupid brat back
so bad?!
Dog!
They're rebels!
Take me with you!
If we make a bigger scene,
it might put Otama-chan in danger.
I guess that you know about her ability!
Boss!
We have a group of lowlife rebels here!
Look at his arm!
The magistrate killer,
Zorojuro, is with them!
Wait!
Fear not.
I'll come, too!
I'm on my way.
Okay!
I see.
One of them has a straw
hat on his neck, right?
Those fools!
Y-Yes, sir!
Don't fight them.
You guys are no match for them!
Luffytaro-san! Zorojuro-san!
How could you do that to the yokozuna?!
I'll hold you guys hostage,
What do they want from that brat?!
--You're just a lowly bastard!
--I'll teach you a lesson!
and catch Shutenmaru, too!
I don't know!
But we have to get her back now!
Who's that?
Tama!!
Is Tama the brat who
Holdem-sama has captive?!
What?!
Did you do something?!
I'm gonna save you right now!
You want her back?! Bring it on!
That was Haki!
Shutenmaru...
Big Bro!!
Haki?
Don't play dumb!
I just had a sumo match
and now it's a sword fight?!
Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
Oops, oops, oops, oops...
Oh no, oh no... No, no, no...!
He's the head of your thieves brigade!
Fight them!
Not if I have my say!
The robberies at the farm these days...
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
No, no, no, no, no...!
Dog! Dodge!
Give us back Tama!
...are the work of you Atamayama Thieves Brigade,
aren't they?!
That's a huge lion-dog!
Oh no, whoa-whoa-whoa, no, no...!
He threw it again!
Who owns it?
Even if it was by sheer dumb luck,
you took down Urashima.
Whoa! Oh no, oh no!
How do we find the brat named Otama?
Gazelle-man! Just go!
So I bet you're one of his
important subordinates!
Oh no, oh no...!
Whoa-whoa-whoa...
All right!
The people of the town won't tell us
even if we ask them.
Hang on, Luffytaro-san!
What are you talking about?
They're all under Orochi's influence.
Oh! Oh no, no, no... Whoa-whoa...
Luffytaro-san...
Please try to not make him mad.
Oh no, no, no!
But there are ordinary people
who don't seem likely to fight.
No, no, no!
He's quite angry already!
Tama!
Oh no, oh no!
The townspeople have always been here.
That's why you shouldn't provoke him anymore!
Until 20 years ago,
this was a vibrant castle town.
What should I do?!
He's strong, too, but...
Don't play innocent.
But one day, Orochi's subordinates
came and seized the houses they liked.
...who the townspeople are really afraid of
isn't Holdem himself...
I'm not gonna help you!
You can't catch up to him anymore!
Then everyone except for
the merchants deemed essential...
I don't know anyone
who is called...
...but a person who has his back.
...was kicked out of the town...
Dammit!
...a lowly-bastard!
The Beast Pirates...
How pathetic!
...Kaido's right-hand man...
Damn!
I'm sure they've been planning this!
What did you do to my slap?!
Jack the Drought...
Some Headliner must've ordered this!
...is the true ruler of Kuri!
That's the truth behind this Bakura Town.
And there is only one place to go
in that direction...
Damn you...
Who are you to Okiku-pe?!
Should I... c-cut people, too?
Isn't he the one who destroyed Zou?
Move out of my way!
It's definitely the town of officials.
Cut them!
What? Oh, that guy!
If you wanna save the brat!
I have to tear Okiku into bits...
He used poison against that Cat and Dog...
That's the town where those who sell
their leftovers to you guys live.
Otherwise I'll lose face!
Right...
In the end,
the elephant sent him flying, right?
Otama-chan...
A notebook?
Who are you, really?
There are three Headliners in that town.
I want to save her!
Hawkins.
Okay! No problem!
Holdem.
Well then...!
Speed.
A sumo wrestler? How did he...?
Dosukoi!
In addition...
there are about 30 soldiers who've gotten special abilities from strange artificial fruits.
Dosukoi!
Something's going on inside the town.
A sumo wrestler came flying out...
Jack sank into the sea along with his ship!
If you can beat me!
So I suppose it's a sumo match.
Didn't he die?
Give us back Tama!
What?!
As expected, is there no one
who can take down Urashima?!
Cat? Dog? Elephant?
If you don't bring her here soon...
Are you talking about animals?
You're not just an ordinary girl.
You'll all be dead!
So you know Jack was involved
in a marine accident!
I'm...
Who are you?
He's most certainly not dead!
...good at sumo!
Get out of my way!
He showed up here in Bakura Town
several days ago.
LUFFY-NO-UMI - SUMO-WANNABE PIRATE
RECORD: UNDEFEATED VS. USOPP
What?!
If you make Holdem mad now
If you can fit into the ring,
I don't care how many there are...
I (sessha) am...
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI
and Jack who is known as a Disaster
comes to retaliate,
...a samurai.
Let's have a sumo match!
I'm gonna fight you all at once!
this town will be in ruins.
Today, we're having
a special exhibition match!
We can't let that happen!
That's not fair!
If anyone can take down Urashima,
he'll win the unbelievable sum of 500 Gold coins!
PEACE REIGNS OVER THE LAND
It's like they're holding
the whole town hostage!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ready...
Clank.
There's a commotion in the other town...
Holdem-sama! This is Gazelle-man!
I'm hungry!
I caught the brat who they said
tamed the baboon!
Move...
Hey!
Stop! You're embarrassing yourself!
...out of my way!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Go!
--Those two men at once may pull it off!
--I'll bet on the challengers this time!
What are you guys talking about
over there?!
Go! Go! Whoa!
A man from the Land of Wano must not whine!
Let me go!
Me, too!
Well done...
What's wrong?
I'm hungry!
Urashima-sama!
Why don't you try to take back
this little brat?!
She'll be of use...
Good luck!
Time is up! Hands down...
Bring her here.
But if you move even an inch...
Yes, sir!
Don't cry, don't cry.
Ready...
This is what will happen!
Otsuru-san!
Go!
--Otsuru-san, do you have any Evil-Purging Herbs?!
--What?
It hurts!
Bodhisattva Slap!
He's immovable!
My child drank the river water
purely out of hunger!
You guys are so weak!
Big Bro Luffy!!
Stop it! You bastard!
Oh my!
Come on in!
This is the flourishing town in Kuri, Land of Wano, called Bakura Town.
Ah, the sweet, anguished cries of the lowly!
He's dodging Urashima's slaps!
He's so agile!
--Keep it up, little guy!
--You can't win if you're just running around!
The match's over!
Don't forget that you tossed that yokozuna
Urashima!
and destroyed my house!
Once again, is there no one
who can take down...
RESTAURANT
Damn!
Oh no!
...the yokozuna of the
Flower Capital, Urashima!
That annoying ronin!
URASHIMA
A YOKOZUNA OF THE LAND OF WANO'S GRAND SUMO
I backed away because of
his strangely strong spirit,
TREASURE
but I wanna take Okiku as my wife
at any cost-pe!
PARADISE FARM AT THE FAR END OF BAKURA TOWN
Another bunch of weaklings-pe.
I have high social status, a good name,
and safe food supplies...
What's going on, Holdem?!
It's time to collect!
She'd be crazy to reject me-pe!
It's Speed-sama's food treasure ship!
It's our grub for today!
Put your harvest on the pallet!
Again...
I'm starving!
Stop worrying over nothing, you idiot!
Sumo, huh? It should be fun!
That's a lot of food!
That's food from the Paradise Farm...
She's a girl from Okobore Town, right?
They're so low-class that Orochi-sama
wouldn't even bother to rule over them...
It was grown with clean water
so it's non-poisonous.
The number of wrestlers
who fought against Urashima...
S-Sir...
Oh, you want this?
...is 19 now.
F-Five Silver coins?!
But the number of bones that have been
broken is...
Whether she loves you or not
doesn't matter at all.
When you're done, go out the back way!
And slink home to Okobore Town!
You can force her to marry you...
Please!
This isn't enough to feed my family for a week!
10 arm bones.
...or burn her house down...
Why do they get to keep it all?!
15 leg bones.
...or kill all of her relatives
so she'll have no place to go.
We can't even buy water!
52 ribs.
Shut up! Don't complain!
4 skulls and...
...7 backbones!
Take away all her options
and make her dependent on you!
It's 88 bones in total
and 4 wrestlers are missing!
You're of the samurai class!
Overwhelming!!
MOUSE-MAN
A GIFTER WITH THE MOUSE SMILE FRUIT
In the Land of Wano, we have a clear status system.
Zoro! Could you handle that?!
His strength is unhuman!
Okay...
You little shit...
What?
The undefeated monster!
You're like a rat!
I'll save Tama!
The Yokozuna Urashima!!
What? What?!
You're a star of our national sport
so if you give a damn about a lowly person like that,
Kiku! I'm sorry but
we've decided to steal it and run.
Ear-Splitter!
Take down Urashima!
you're not setting a good example
for others!
What? When did you...?
Hey!
I'll bet on you guys!
Eye-Splitter!
You can do it, guys!
I'm sure it'll piss him off
but it's better than kicking his ass, right?
We have the perfect plan!
We'll get the prize!
You're right!
What's the name of your boss?!
Bo... Ho... H-Holdem...
Yeah! I can do whatever I want with Okiku!
--Beat that jerk!
--Urashima-sama!
Ho... Ho... Holdem...
Hey! Those are all illegal moves!
Shut up!
Yokozuna...
Didn't you like the food?
"Ball-de-boo"?
I'm...
Get the firefighters!
Oh! Look at this!
...a yokozuna!!
Fire! A fire broke out!
That's a raccoon dog, right?
Yes, it's a pet that we've had
for a long time...
Ready...
Go!
--Cook it!
--What?!
Show yourself! Ball-de-boo!
Well, whatever!
Raccoon dogs are my favorite food!
If you harm Tama,
I won't forgive you!
Hawkins-san!
Okiku!
They're out of our league!
I knew you were gonna come!
Where's Holdem?
He's in a mess at the
plaza in the 4th district!
So you've decided to be my wife, right?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
BUDO
Holdem-sama! We have a problem!
He's not picking up. Holdem.
Excuse me.
Huh? The yokozuna got his topknot
chopped off by a woman?
There's no way you can hide behind me.
I can't believe it!
Everyone's upset!
And we don't know what to do!
You're finally here...
There is a woman who is engaged
to be married to Urashima!
I need you to stop here, Basil Hawkins!
I don't care!
What do you want me to do?!
How lucky!
She's loved by a yokozuna!
This is big news!
I see it!
I'm busy tearing her cheek off!
Who are you?
We'll charge in there!
Luffytaro-san and Zorojuro-san!
He's strong...
Beyond that point is Bakura Town!
The town of officials and pirates!
Have mercy on me!
You can have your baboon back!
We're in this isolated Land of Wano
cut off from the outer world,
There's no guarantee of our safety!
Please stop!
but he knows our faces...
Hey!
Okiku!
I won't!
So I'd better make him disappear!
Are you ready?!
My wife!
I heard that you mentioned the name "Kozuki."
What?! Urashima-zeki's wife?!
Yeah!
That woman is his wife?!
I wish I were her!
When the Kozuki Clan comes back,
they'll teach you a lesson!
His wife?
No...
As you saw earlier,
it's just his belief I'm going to marry him.
I bet you know...
...that saying the name "Kozuki"...
Who is it?! Who is
responsible for this mess?!
Okiku! I'll have a match
in Bakura Town later-pe!
...is a serious offense!
So this is also a punishment
for your crime...
I'll show you how strong I am
so come see if you're interested!
What's this smoke?
Holdem-sama, are you okay?!
Stop chasing after ghosts forever...
Yokozuna?!
The Kozuki were an evil clan...
The one who sent him flying
was the magistrate-killer Zorojuro's ally.
I have a mind of my own.
Now...
...it was fun talking to you but it's over!
...that tried to destroy the Land of Wano
two decades ago!
What?!
Where are you, Ball-de-boo?!
I see.
From here,
Is this her?
Show yourself, Ball-de-boo!
You guys!
the real fun starts!
We're looking for someone!
Poor girl...
Just come out already!
She's a little girl named Tama!
She's about to cry.
Big Bro!
So that's him!
I don't care if you happen to
kill one or two of them in the process!
Tell me where this town's boss is!
He's acting like he owns the place
and it's pissing me off!
Catch them right now!
She should be there!
I'm not gonna cry!
That woman! How frustrating!
She gets to marry a man of wealth!
Hey, woman!
Don't try to act strong!
A CERTAIN RESIDENCE, BAKURA TOWN
She's huge but just right for Urashima!
You remember that
we have this brat as a hostage, right?!
Get out of my way, you little shit!
It's unforgivable!
I'd be a better match!
What Okiku did is irreparable-pe!
They're not listening...
Okiku came to see me.
Guys, bring her to me!
Big Bro!
She turned down the honor of marrying
and serving the samurai-class me,
Ouch...
Yes, sir!
Big Bro!
I didn't know you were good with girls!
Luffytaro-san... Zorojuro-san...
and even muddied my good name!
I wanna be like you!
No wonder she fell for you!
--Why...
--Look what you've done!
I'll smash her brains in
and set an example!
Oh, I see now!
You don't need the brat back, right?!
Okiku!
Okay, we're gonna look for her ourselves!
Let's go!
Then, I'll have her chewed up as you wish!
Lady! Big Bro Urashima wants you!
Come with us!
Go ahead, Kamijiro!
I have a pain in my side!
Show yourself! Ball-de-boo!
Who are you fools?! Out of our way!
Just shut up!
Kick their asses!
Shut up! Gazelle-man!
Bring Tama here!
Like I said, do as you like once you beat me!
Don't get in our way!
Ball-de-boo!
It's...
...Holdem!
You can go now!
Your heavy breathing annoys me!
Ball-de-boo!
What?!
The brat's gone!
You can't beat me though!
What do you mean?!
Huh?! When did he get her?!
Build up your stamina!
What?!
I'm...
You idiot!
Nice charge!
Open the gate!
Kamijiro! What the hell are you doing?!
I'm...
Open the gate!
...the greatest yokozuna in the Land of Wano!
I guess the winning technique was
a frontal thrust out...
I wasn't talking to you!
B-Big Bro?!
Come with me, lady!
Stop staring at my face like that!
Far Bank Slap!
Big Bro...
No... Please stop!
As usual, we have so many kinds of
delicious-looking food today!
Big Bro!
Are you gonna cut up an unarmed naked man?
He's coming this way!
That's right, Speed-sama.
Why don't you look it all over?
Don't tell me he...
The food is behind you!
Ya-hoo!
What's this?
--I can see it!
--What?
Stop him!
I don't know... What is it?
HOLDEM - A HEADLINER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
WITH THE LION SMILE FRUIT
I'm so scared!
Because...
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
...my range of vision...
He has a lion in his stomach!
...is 350 degrees!
--You're like a horse!
--You think so?
Kiku!
KAMIJIRO - HOLDEM'S STOMACH
You smile like a horse, too!
Outta my way!
What is that hostile look?!
SPEED - A HEADLINER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
WITH THE HORSE SMILE FRUIT
You're a yokozuna...
Hey, Zoro!
How could you let them take her away?!
And I'm...
The fire bell?
Fire! Fire!
--Clear the way!
--Move! Move!
...the man who's gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
I'm sorry...
We, of the group one I-gumi, claim this fire!
I thought that it wasn't right to...
...slash a naked man.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Protect the treasure ship at any cost!
And...
This place...
...she's not just a teahouse waitress.
What happened?
Please stop!
There it goes! The lion's blow to the balls!
Let go of me!
Let's get out of here, Tama!
Big Bro...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Help me...
Put out the fire!
Big Bro Luffy!
This is Holdem's house...
Komachiyo!
I (sessha) am...
Gum-Gum...
You bastard!
But...
Why has it been destroyed like this?!
...a samurai.
...since they share the same body,
that groin also belongs to the lion!
It's behind you, Speed-sama!
Kamijiro!
I can see it.
I'll chop you up with a flaming sword!
I have a wide range of vision like a horse.
Come into my arms-pe!
I thought there was a sumo event today...
Why doesn't he learn?
What's going on?
Why do some people repeat the same mistake?
Hey! She's a girl from the teahouse
in the other town!
Don't keep us waiting!
No one's ever gotten away
from my Trick Mechanism Sword!
Ball-de-boo! Give us back Tama!
With her rank,
it's presumptuous of her to even enter this town!
...Giant...
Holdem-sama.
What should we do with this brat?
...Sumo Slap!
Hell Fire Edge!
Is that so?!
Then you gotta kick her out!
Holdem-sama!
She's a vulgar tramp!
My balls (tama)...
I got you! Come on!
You're gonna be our hostage, too!
So your name is Otama.
Ball-de-boo!
How could a weak little shit like you...
Shut up, you commoners!
I'm right here, boy!
...tame the savage baboon?!
My men saw you do it!
To us samurai-class,
you fools are all the same, vulgar, lowly bastards-pe!
So you're this town's boss...
...Ball-de-boo! Am I right?!
Dosukoi!
My name is Holdem!
Your worthless lives...
Whether to spare them or take them...
...is my choosing!
Don't push your luck!
Holdem-sama!
Kick his ass!
Is it okay if your friend gets killed?!
Don't try to pretend that you don't know!
It must be none other than
a real Devil Fruit power.
You finally showed yourself!
I had no option!
Drop your swords now!
How could you destroy my house
with a sumo wrestler?!
No...!
Come on...
Spit it out!
What the...?
Giant...
Otama!
Yeah, that's it!
So, Okiku!
Your ability is enticing even to your enemies.
...Sumo Slap!
Zorojuro-san...
You stay right there!
I'm gonna beat you to death!
Why don't you...
Don't ever use it in front of others!
...be...
Dosukoi!
...mine?!
Hey...
I (sessha) don't know anyone
who is called...
I'm not gonna help you.
I-It's just...
...a lowly bastard!
...animals...
Don't you care about her?!
...tend to love me...
Oh!
I won't let you get away!
I see!
A-Am I safe now?
That's what it's all about!
Urashima crashed into my house
and it's in ruins!
Pardon me.
Yes, it is.
Who are you bastards?!
Do you think I'm a fool?!
What should I do?
Take care of your side!
Okay!
You damn brat!
Th-The yokozuna...
Stop your joking.
The only vulgar thing here is your heart.
He was sent flying!
I believe they said you tore
part of your cheek off.
Yokozuna!
No way!
He can't be beaten by a little guy like him!
Big Bro!
Tama!
Otama-chan!
The yokozuna's topknot!
I'm a yokozuna!
If you're not gonna tell me...
You guys stand against us...
I don't care who you are,
just bring it on!
So cool!
...because you work under
Shutenmaru the thief?!
Kiku is so daring!
Let's give that a try.
It's getting exciting!
Hey, bring me some pincers!
I guess we did enough to
get the attention of their boss.
You shouldn't have messed
around in Bakura Town!
Yes, sir!
I think so!
The yokozuna...
Th-That guy...
Shutenmaru?
What are you talking about?
Not that one! The bigger one!
Urashima...
Dog! This way!
I remember!
He killed the magistrate!
He got rejected by a woman...
WANTED - ZOROJURO
...and had his topknot chopped off!
Shutenmaru...
Big Bro Luffy...
You fools!
Zorojuro?!
Seems like you want this brat back...
Thank you!
Now we don't have to look for the brat...
But first, don't move!
He can chew her up anytime!
So what?
This is a quick way to bring their boss!
Get us out of town!
Help! Big Bro Luffy!
Don't tell me he's that guy's ally!
Big Bro...
Tama!
Alright! Let's go now, guys!
Tama...
What happened to your cheek?
What's the matter, Bepo?
Stop! Stop! Don't you wanna live?!
Invaders!
Okiku!
It's nothing.
Bepo, you...
Bakura Town is just past them!
It was just pulled by some pincers.
Luffy! We don't have time
to fight those weaklings!
You...
Kibi Dango...
...betrayed me!
Room!
You won't be able to pull it out like that...
I know!
Charge, dog!
Why did I do that...
...in front of others?!
He has a lion in his stomach...
Scan!
What?!
He's looking like a fierce god!
Captain!
Pincers?!
I knew it.
We have a problem!
Sorry.... I couldn't control myself
and...
Holdem-sama is talking to
the straw-hat guy now!
Give me a minute!
Stop running!
Okiku!
A-Am I gonna die, Captain?
Captain!
A battle could break out at any minute!
--Oh, no! That pose is...!
--His Far Bank Slap that sends opponents flying!
What? Why are you so upset?
No way! You've just got the runs.
Boss! What are your orders?!
Big Bro! I'm fine now!
Because you already saved me!
It's Straw Hat and Roronoa!
That's why I told you
not to eat fish from the river.
I'll be there soon!
Please forgive me, Urashima-sama.
I'm in front of Bakura Town!
Straw Hat-ya is in the Land of Wano?!
So he's finally here...
Boy, the timing couldn't be any worse!
I-I'm sorry...
Hm?! Is he coming to attack?!
Captain, Hawkins is at the entrance!
Straw Hat and Roronoa plunged themselves
into Bakura Town!
Roar! Lion Fire!
But...
And there was a fire in the town.
The cause of the fire is...
Hey, wait!
All we can expect from this is trouble!
I knew you were the kind of man
who would hit a woman...
Stop acting cute!
That's right...
Captain, don't abandon me...
Big Bro!
Man! Why's everyone causing trouble?
Captain?
Take a look at my Trick Mechanism
Sword's additional force!
Don't tell me it's him.
Die!
Yeah, I see Straw Hat...
I hope they're laying low...
Captain?!
Those fools...
Huh?!
You vulgar, lowly tramp!
Let's go stop those idiots!
Gum-Gum...
Aye-aye, Captain!
Big Bro!
I'll save you now, Tama!
...Red Hawk!
I won't give her back to you!
Hey!
Idiot!
Bring the boss of this town!
Don't do it...!
Gum-Gum...
Those fools...
If you don't want me to, show your ability!
...Sumo Slap!
We're here to take back Tama!
Tama!
When Holdem takes a flaming blow,
Otama sees the shadow of the man who she misses!
Law and Hawkins finally clash!
A sumo match between Urashima,
the yokozuna from the Land of Wano, and Luffy.
Luffy, Zoro, and Okiku's swords swing
and cut up Kaido's men one after another!
It's a battle of the brains!
Which one of them will win?!
As the undefeated yokozuna, Urashima,
doggedly makes advances on her,
The enraged Urashima's continuous
slaps rush at Luffy!
the samurai, Okiku, says something which will lead to further turmoil!
On the next episode of One Piece!
Then, Bakura Town's boss and a Headliner
"Taking Back Otama! A Fierce
Fight Against Holdem!"
"Duel! The Magician and
the Surgeon of Death!"
But then, Luffy's killer technique
blasts in the heated ring!
who has a lion head
in his stomach, Holdem springs into action!
Seeing Okiku in danger, Luffy finally goes into action!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The big sword fight in Bakura Town heats up!
Will he be able to help Okiku, targeted by Urashima,
out from the tight spot?!
In the hard bout that draws
everyone's attention,
which of them will be declared the winner?!
Get ready for the origin of One Piece,
written by Eiichiro Oda!
Will Luffy and the others
be able to rescue Otama?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Rages! Rescue Otama from Danger!"
The One Piece 20th anniversary special program!
"Romance Dawn"
"The Yokozuna Appears! The Invincible Urashima Goes After Okiku!"
"A Climactic Sumo Battle!
Straw Hat vs. the Strongest Ever Yokozuna!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!