One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
After rescuing Otama,
Luffy stole a treasure ship with a store of food
Big Bro!
Luffy came to the ruins of Oden Castle
along with Law,
Romance Dawn means the dawn of an adventure.
After invading Bakura Town,
Luffy was furious at Holdem, a Headliner,
who was holding Otama hostage, but...
Luffy took down Holdem, a
Headliner of the Beast Pirates,
and found the graves of
Kin'emon and the others.
This is the story of a Luffy slightly different from the one
in One Piece...
and took it to Okobore Town.
and successfully rescued the kidnapped Otama.
If you make Holdem mad now
Why are their graves here?!
It's water!
and Jack who is known as a Disaster
comes to retaliate,
It's non-poisonous! Help yourself!
Alright! Let's run!
Luffy-dono!
this town will be in ruins.
What?
I'll make it your everyday life!
That's not fair!
Kin!
Kibi Dango!
It's like they're holding
the whole town hostage!
He was reunited with
Kin'emon and Momonosuke...
By the time we leave this country,
Get off, you little...
TREASURE
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
While Luffy and the others were at it,
another Headliner, Speed,
...who he parted with at Zou.
I had a good sleep! I feel great!
This is Kibi Dango. It's delicious.
Also...
And Law is now taking Luffy and the others
to the ruins of Oden Castle.
showed up leading a treasure ship
filled with provisions.
Hey!
Screw that!
I'm not gonna eat a
suspicious dango like that!
Luffy, you're here!
What's going on, Holdem?!
We'll go meet the ghosts of the Land of Wano.
Then, through the power
of Otama's Kibi Dango,
Luffy!
It's Speed-sama's food treasure ship!
It's our grub for today!
Luffy and the others tamed
another Headliner, Speed,
Garchu!
Ghosts?
You'll be surprised...
Luffy!
You're dressed like a samurai! It's cool!
and tried to get out of Bakura Town
along with a treasure ship with a store of food.
That's a lot of food!
Yeah, I was stunned, too...
Then Luffy and the others were told
a surprising truth by Kin'emon.
That's food from the Paradise Farm...
What was that noise?
Is my boat broken?!
There, you'll learn...
After seeing the excess amount of food,
Luffy asked...
That ability...
...an unbelievable truth!
Chambres!
The thing is we came from
the Land of Wano of 20 years ago...
It's fine. Weird!
Zoro! Could you handle that?!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
"Mysterious Grave Markers!
A Reunion at the Ruins of Oden Castle!"
Okay...
--I'll save Tama!
--What?
...crossing through time
to the present Land of Wano!
What? W-What? What is it?!
Meanwhile, around the
entrance of Bakura Town,
Kiku! I'm sorry but
we've decided to steal it and run.
Trafalgar Law and Basil Hawkins
were fighting fiercely.
What are you talking about?!
What? When did you...?
Is it true?
I assume you're not here for vacation
since your allies are also here...
Is this a bird? An ostrich?
No, a panda?
20 years ago?! What do you mean?!
How did you get here?!
Hey, tell me! What do you mean by "ghosts"?!
Look what you've done!
Oh, I wasn't even born yet!
Oh, I see now!
You don't need the brat back, right?!
You didn't expect that I knew?
Zoro!
There!
--You'll see once you get there.
--What?!
I ran across Straw Hat
and the others earlier.
No way!
Stay right there!
Who can do a time leap?
Go ahead, Kamijiro!
Tra-guy! Don't leave me hanging!
I'm filling the hole with your butt!
If I don't, the boat'll sink!
I bet you wanted to silence me
before it's too late...
In any event,
That doesn't make sense! Explain it again!
Ring, ring, ring...
we'll talk once we get to the top of this mountain
where the ruins of Oden Castle are.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
A wound?!
Then the gunshot earlier was...
She's right! Tell us in detail!
Clank.
Tsk! You're so mean!
Balloon!
Holdem-sama was taken down by thieves
and they're on the run now!
Balloon!
Everything that I'm going
to tell you is true!
Kamijiro! What the hell are you doing?!
N-No!
We've already reported to Jack-sama!
Stay still! M-My boat... Oh, no!
It's the truth...
They crushed Holdem
and now Jack has been notified?!
...about the Land of Wano!
As you just heard,
all your effort was for nothing.
There's someone strong.
Yeah.
Maybe it's Orochi's assassin.
That's a huge ship!
And of course, Kaido-san will know
what you and Straw Hat's group are doing.
Luffy, you go ahead.
Balloon! Fly away as far as you can!
I'll catch up to you after I take care of this.
Get us out of town!
Thanks.
Those fools...
Because of them, we have
the worst possible outcome!
"A Legendary Samurai!
The Man Who Roger Admired!"
What happened to your cheek?
It's nothing.
Hey, you guys! Clear the way!
Young man with a straw hat.
Could you bring that bird up to this ship?
It was just pulled by some pincers.
Roronoa-ya!
Kibi Dango...
You think you're hiding well?
Okay.
You won't be able to pull it out like that...
Here is where Oden Castle used to stand...
"The Coming of the Treasure Ship!
Luffytaro Returns the Favor!"
I can really feel your thirst for blood.
Pincers?!
But it's just a nickname...
Give me a minute!
How dare you?!
Why did you bring Balloon?!
It's actually called Kuri Castle!
What's your problem, Tra-guy?
The people of Kuri truly loved Oden-sama.
That's why they nicknamed it.
Damn you!
Red Hawk!
He got caught because of you!
What?! Who is that?!
Is that Momo's dad?!
NAME: ANNE
TREASURE
FLOWER CAPITAL
That's right!
Alright, everyone, let's start the class.
Is Balloon that panda?
Our lord, Oden-sama, was
a very daring person.
He's not a panda!
Today, you'll learn the history of
the Land of Wano!
Give us back our food!
He was shot.
Yes, Six Hones Spiel shot him.
He was a son of Kozuki Sukiyaki-sama,
a Shogun of the Land of Wano at the time,
Horselina-chan!
Yes, ma'am!
Who's that?
Thank you for running!
The captain of this pirate ship...
Oh, is this a pirate ship?
Here you go!
but he was free-spirited
and hot-blooded.
Neigh-neigh!
That's right. Spiel is
an infamous and cruel sorcerer.
Now, everyone...
What is sakoku?
When my village was raided,
everyone tried to fight back with their weapons,
Roronoa-ya!
I know!
On top of becoming a wanted person,
you drew Jack's attention!
It means closing a country's doors
to maintain the peace of that country!
but they couldn't even get near him.
He caused violent incidents again and again
--That's correct!
--It's easy!
You promised that
you weren't gonna cause trouble!
"Duel!
The Magician and the Surgeon of Death!"
and he was eventually banished
from the Flower Capital.
Hmmm, a pirate who attacks villages, huh?
Next...
KUROZUMI OROCHI
what is kaikoku?
The Captain's here!
Sorry...
--What?!
--Banished?!
--Me!
--Here!
First of all,
--Pick me!
--Me, me!
Well... For the young Oden-sama,
why are you in Kuri?!
--You there.
--Yes.
You were supposed to be
a ronin in the Flower Capital!
the Flower Capital was
too small and too boring.
It's a very bad action that will let evil people and ideas into a country!
They know each other?
There! That's him!
Is everything okay?
No, it's not!
The countries outside want various things
from the Land of Wano.
I'm sorry!
Look at that.
I had no choice!
--Damn you!
--Go to hell!
Even his crewmembers are afraid of him!
That's exactly correct!
Because I ran into Luffy.
He destroyed my village and stole our treasure!
But, a long time ago,
There was a so-called "lawless area"
in the Land of Wano at that time...
Big Bro!
Straw Hat-ya! It's him again!
there were some fools who tried to do just that.
Holdem-sama!
All who defy him will be killed!
KOZUKI ODEN
Holdem-sama!
There, criminals and ronin who were
expelled from their hometowns formed groups.
Horselina-chan!
Do you wanna eat another one?
It was Oden and the Akazaya Nine!
Well done. So you managed to catch
a Ruku - monster bird.
They stole from and mutilated each other
and there was bloodshed every day...
Yes!
Wait, I didn't ask for your answer!
Good. And you're the kid
who helped us catch it, right?
It's delicious!
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle!
The place was so wild
that even the Shogun family gave up on it.
Why is even the enemy's Headliner here?
There it is! Her stretchy neck!
Come down!
What do you want for a reward?
I guess Luffy won her over
while rescuing that brat.
That was Kuri.
You answered without my permission!
What bad kids!
Why couldn't we answer?
This seems exciting!
He's doing as he likes...
Because the Akazaya Nine...
What's the matter, boy?
I'm asking what you want.
Hey, where's Straw Hat-ya?
I thought he was with you!
The young Oden-sama stepped into that infamous Kuri
of all places!
...is a name I don't even wanna hear.
Tama!
Your head's weird.
He said he'd be back soon!
But it's been two decades now.
Big Bro!
FELICITATIONS
And...!
Seems like he forgot something!
Hold on tight!
Hey, kid! Give us all your belongings!
Okay!
M-M... M-My head's weird?
There it is!
There was a hero who took down those evil samurai.
NICKNAME: SIX HONES SPIEL
So some people have it!
Alright! Let's run!
You fool! Were you listening to me?!
This will make Tama and the others happy!
It was the Shogun - Kurozumi Orochi!
Well, look at his head! It's weird!
Stop it! This water...
That's correct!
...is tribute for Shogun Orochi!
Orochi Two-Sword Style!
Watch out, Akazaya Nine!
I'll bring you down!
Help!
Lock these idiots up!
Okay, thank you for this!
All right. Keep quiet.
What a horrible education!
What are you doing?!
Holdem-sama!
It's all falsehoods!
What a view! Big ships sure are nice!
Shogun Orochi saved the Land of Wano
from the bad guys!
He's flying!
You're a Headliner
but you got knocked out by a single blow?!
Oh! Whoa!
That's right.
Oden-sama was cool!
20 years ago,
Who did it?!
I really wish I could kill you...
all of those bad people died.
Then Kuri's most dangerous man who was
Don't.
And the Land of Wano became...
leading the ruffians of the region showed up.
Hey, is that ostrich yours?
...the peaceful country it is now!
He's not an ostrich either!
He's a so-called Ruku, a type of monster bird!
His name is Balloon!
Zorojuro-san!
We're leaving town!
Luffy, that fool!
He shouldn't have done that...
His name was Ashura Doji
and they clashed almost immediately!
Orochi-sama is a coward!
Alright...
Luffytaro-san!
We've been together for
as long as I can remember...
Empty it at Okobore Town!
Otama-chan!
K-K-Kyoshiro-dono! What are you saying?!
Don't worry!
Leave the brat to Luffytaro!
We've played and napped together,
and never left each other's side even for a moment
You're too loud!
Don't stop!
Keep making for the entrance of the town!
I wonder if they're doing okay...
Shut up! Idiot!
He may look like just a bird to others...
Mom! I'm hungry!
But to me, he's a more trustworthy,
important friend than anybody else.
Don't be scared!
Just a while longer.
Win back the treasure ship!
Or we'll lose our food!
Even if anyone hears it,
I only spoke the truth.
I'm starving...
KOROZUMI CLAN'S MONEY CHANGER
I see...
Then why have you been kidnapped?
NAPPING KYOSHIRO
A good question!
That's because...
Hold on tight!
...I'm cute!
Yes, Big Bro!
I'm not gonna let go of you!
Y-Yeah? You sure?
What were you doing in that small boat
in the middle of the sea?
Booze! Bring me more booze!
You can't go any farther!
What is it?
I was seeking out the Peace-mains
so we can become friends.
Does he have something to do with Orochi?
Peace-mains?
He brought Ashura Doji down beautifully.
They're a type of pirates.
Napping Kyoshiro...
The pirates who just lawlessly plunder
like the ones on this ship are Morganeers.
That wasn't all...
Maybe I can get some serious information.
He became the leader of the ruffians.
Th-That's...
And the Peace-mains go on adventures
ripping them off.
...a treasure ship!
20 years ago...
in front of the burning Oden Castle,
There are so many fish!
Oden's wife uttered these words
before she passed away.
I wanna become a Peace-main!
--Oh, he was quite something.
--He saved Kuri!
Food! Food!
My grandpa was a Peace-main pirate!
On top of that, Oden-sama brought change
to the town!
How could you do that to Holdem-sama?!
Grandpa!
First, he taught the ruffians to work.
You bastard...
Don't think you can get away!
YOU ARE THE MOON UNAWARE OF THE DAWN
"You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
Hey, Luffy! It's good to be a pirate!
He developed the town, built the castle,
May your purpose be fulfilled
MAY YOUR PURPOSE BE FULFILLED
A treasure ship is here!
We'll be saved!
and cast nine shadows on the night woven of 20 years
If you're a man, set out to the sea!
B-Big Bro...
20 YEARS
and made the Paradise Farm for everybody.
THE NIGHT
Chop him up!
Grandpa...
NINE SHADOWS
It's great!
and you shall know the brilliance of the dawn"!
I'm not gonna become a pirate!
Guys, hurry up!
Kuri became a free and vibrant region
full of laughter
Let's divide the spoils we gained this time!
I'll take this!
and Oden-sama was finally given
the title of "daimyo of Kuri"
Oh, Captain! That's not fair!
She just said it out of desperation,
but Orochi-sama interpreted in a very specific way!
by the Shogun, Sukiyaki-sama.
Cut it out! Thank me for not losing our way
on that island!
That's what Oden-sama accomplished
at only 20 years old.
But...
Shut up! If I can have this one,
it's enough for me this time!
Hey, Luffy! Come here!
Big Bro!
Here! Take a look!
It's the best part of our haul.
He made a river...
Big Bro!!
How did he interpret it?
...and built docks.
He connected regions...
Orochi-sama...
It's a mystic fruit, a Gum-Gum Fruit!
...and people.
Go on!
An enemy ship had it by chance
and we stripped them of it thanks to me!
And then, I...
We can sell it for 5 billion berries...
It's food!
Right. And...
Can we eat it?!
Yuck!
--Thank goodness!
--We'll be able to survive!
You fool!
That's a diabolical fruit!
Get out of my way!
It's delicious!
He was a daimyo who was loved by
the people of Kuri...
If you eat it,
you'll never be able to swim again!
Um...
There are tons and tons of food!
But Oden-sama was a freewheeler...
What?! No way!
How did he interpret it?!
It's true!
We won't go hungry! It's great!
I'll never be able to swim again?
Oh, right. Like this.
Having so many vassals didn't suit his style.
What a relief...
Yeah...
No...
"I lay a curse on you"!
Like a ghost?!
I've got to catch up to Zoro and the others
or they'll eat all the delicious stuff!
W-Well, but that's okay.
I wasn't gonna become a pirate anyway...
"20 years later, on a moonlit night,
in order to settle this grudge,
This is what he kept saying.
Everyone's so happy!
O-Okay... So you don't mind.
nine samurai will appear as ghosts...
--Great! Let's hitch a ride! I'm gonna jump!
--What?
Yeah...
Whoa-whoa-whoa, wait!
It could've been worse
if you wanted to become a pirate!
You fools!
...to kill you."
Which means "to kill Orochi-sama"!
Those aren't leftovers yet!
Who is it?!
It's all right!
Stay away from the treasure ship!
Who's holding me in his arms?!
There are tons of people
who enjoy their lives without being involved with water!
"And they'll open up the Land of Wano"!
Oh! It's so restrictive!
Giddy up, horse!
You lowly bastards!
This marks the 20th year!
Okay!
You shouldn't be touching that food!
Wait, what're you doing?!
What?! She's a human?!
Grandpa... I was lying...
You idiots forgot your place!
Neigh-neigh!
That's why Shogun Orochi is in fear!
No, she's a horse!
--How dare you get on Speed-sama like that?!
--Yank them down!
Because I wasn't sure if I could become one...
But the truth is...
You can't go any farther!
Thinking "the ghosts of the Kozuki Clan
might come to kill him"!
The Land of Wano was a little too small
for Oden-sama...
You're taking the lowly people's side!
Get off of me, you rude bastards!
You fools will have to pay for this!
I wanna become a pirate like you
and travel to all kinds of places!
DUKE DOGSTORM
KING OF THE DAY, MOKOMO DUKEDOM
I want to fight them!
Hey, Tama, bring out the dango!
The good old days...
I can't stand the fact
that I won't be able to swim again!
--What?!
--Just do it!
Hey!
Yes, that was this beach!
Kibi Dango!
Luffy, you...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
We were washed ashore here
and everyone called us "the talking dog and cat"
Now, tame the horse!
I see. So you wanna become a pirate...
What? That's impossible!
It won't work on humans!
and they were afraid of us...
You don't know until you try!
But what can the dead do?
Don't underestimate the sea!
Get off, you little...
But Oden-sama was different!
Listen! The sea is nothing like ponds or rivers!
It's a monster!
It's water!
This is Kibi Dango. It's delicious.
The samurai of the Kozuki Clan...
You monsters!
Screw that!
What would you do if your ship sank
in the middle of the sea?!
It's non-poisonous! Help yourself!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
I'm not gonna eat a
suspicious dango like that!
20 years ago, we cornered them in the castle...
Stop!
A man shouldn't cry over such a little thing...
What did they do to you?!
I'm not gonna...
You brutal geezer!
You fear those who are different
due to your stupidity!
I'm not gonna...
...and burned them all alive!
I'm... not...
Damn you!
How could you kick your grandfather?!
Shame on you all!
Neigh-neigh! It looks delicious!
You started it!
What did you say?!
I'm sorry...
No violence!
It's your fault, Grandpa!
--Stop it! Ouch!
--You'll become a good-for-nothing...
It's been years since we've had
this much drinking water!
--Oh, so you can't swim.
--For the rest of my life.
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
S-Speed-sama?
That brutal geezer wore this hat all the time.
I'm Luffytaro!
Tell them that in case someone asks you!
There is no castle!
--I said "ruins."
--Oh, yeah.
RUINS OF ODEN CASTLE -
KURI, LAND OF WANO
As I thought, it won't work on humans...
It's this way. Follow me.
This is my treasure.
He was our savior...!
Neigh-neigh! Where should I take you,
Master-sama?!
Your treasure, huh?!
Yep...
The samurai from the Land of Wano,
What's your treasure?
who mesmerized Whitebeard
and was admired by Roger!
Luffytaro-san, thank you!
In that case, Balloon is mine!
Yay!
It worked!
Big Bro!
But why?
What? Hey, Kiku!
He was a true hero!
Tama!
I guess it's because she's half horse.
Look at that! A pod of whales!
Did you get to eat something good?
He was our master!
What's wrong with her?
Oh! Come to think of it,
Zoro hasn't returned yet, either.
I'm talking!
Not yet!
Gee!
I was waiting for you!
S-Speed-sama...
I can't just stay here like this!
I'm gonna get out of here!
I see. Then...
Let's go after her!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
Oden-sama was funny, dynamic, and merry!
Don't be silly. That's impossible!
Oh?
Tra-guy!
She's too fast!
It's been a while!
GRAVE OF ODEN
His spirit and good nature...
Alright, Horselina! Chase the treasure ship!
You're right. My boat was wrecked.
Straw Hat-ya...
I'm not your servant!
...turned Kuri into a great region.
No, I mean you won't be able to
get out of here.
My name is Speed!
Don't call me Horselina as if I'm your friend!
What you're doing is
a rebellion against the Land of Wano...
I thought it was an assassin
but it's a tiger!
A rebellion? That's not what this is about!
You're driving me crazy...
I want you to do as he says,
Horselina-chan.
Here!
You'd better stop being ridiculous
and save your energy, too.
Certainly, Master-sama!
Great! Do you wanna fight?
But now, because of Kaido,
it has become...
Alright!
I can't believe the Headliner Speed-sama
became obedient like that!
It's an apple!
How did you get out?!
The key was hanging there.
Tama...
Do they have something on her?
What I'm asking is how you could get it
from behind bars!
I'm paying you back for feeding me.
Here we go!
This is just the start of it!
--Can you use sorcery or something?
--No.
It's unforgivable!
But it's kinda close.
Hey, help me with rescuing Balloon.
Momonosuke-sama!
This place is creepy.
No. I'm gonna look for a boat.
It's been abandoned for 20 years.
--Help me!
--No. It's a pain.
Look at this meat!
Father!
Okay, you jerk!
Hey! Guys!
Damn Kaido!
Give me some meat, too!
Meat! Meat, meat!
Kaido and Kurozumi Orochi...
Big Bro...
What are those?
Meat, meat, meat, meat!
Red Hawk!
...secretly joined forces!
Balloon! I'll get you out of there now!
Meat!
And they set Oden-sama up!
"Kozuki Oden..."?
Fire Fist!
I'm so lucky! Everyone's having a nap!
Look at the other graves, too.
The Land of Wano fell to pieces...
"Kozuki..."
Holdem-sama!
MO
The fire is spreading!
NO
When did you get here?!
SUKE
...and Oden-sama...
Where are the firefighters?!
Momonosuke is...
Hey, girl!
...was labeled a criminal!
It's showtime!
Have a one-on-one fight with him!
That grave belongs to that brat you know.
Holdem-sama! Stay with us!
KOZUKI ODEN
What?! What are you talking about, Tra-guy?!
Please wake up!
If you win, I'll release the Ruku.
It's not just him.
Big Bro, you were like...
Do you promise?!
Yes, I keep my word.
...Ace earlier...
Only the lion woke up! It's scary!
"Raizo"?!
A good haul!
I found food while looking for a ship!
"Kanjuro"?!
"Kin'emon"?!
That's right...
There it is! That boat looks good!
Hm? What?
Monkey D. Luffy, Roronoa Zoro.
Did you say something?
Why are their graves here?!
And Trafalgar Law.
I don't want to give a
poor account of myself,
No!
Okay, let's go back...
Never mind.
but when there are three troublesome guys,
it's too much even for me...
Where did they go?
Wait a minute, when we were on our way
to the Land of Wano,
Clank.
Did you underestimate me
because I am a woman?
I couldn't get in touch with Kin'emon...
Now, release Balloon as promised!
It's a dock.
KIN'EMON
AT THE ENTRANCE OF BAKURA TOWN
Wait! Oh, don't do it, Captain!
D-Don't tell me...
What a piece of crap...
How could he lose to a little girl like her...
Oden-sama who was loved by everyone...
...he's dead!
You won.
You can let it out.
TREASURE
Great!
Tell us! What happened to Oden?!
Balloon! I'll get you out of there!
He died... as a criminal...
at the Flower Capital!
They're dead?
What?!
Momo.
Raizo.
Who are you?
How naive.
Pirates don't keep their promises.
Kanjuro.
You've got to be kidding!
Kin'emon.
What a sneaky piece of shit! Orochi!
No way...
I can't believe it!
They can't be dead!
I won't release it.
I took a lot of trouble to catch it!
GRAVE OF KIN'EMON
I thought Kin'emon was waiting here...
That's awful!
He's been gone for quite a while.
The horrific death of Oden-sama...
Idiot!
Gone?!
...happened 20 years ago...
Maybe he'll come out at night.
He appeared repeatedly last night, too.
I'm gonna take your life.
...but for us...
...it was only a few months ago...
That sounds like he's a ghost or something!
Kozuki Oden was a brave samurai...
What's the meaning of these graves?!
Spit it out, Tra-guy!
Is there something you don't wanna say?!
His final moment...
Hi.
...still vividly replays in my memory!
I'm not the one who should be telling you about it.
It's a lovely day, isn't it?
Where are you going?
What a hero!
I'm gonna take your life.
What did you say?!
It's amazing that you guys made it out of
such a situation.
It's so delicious!
Damn you!
Don't mess around with us!
Good for you, Tama!
Yeah...
We no longer had allies,
Your friend is in a mess.
What are you gonna do?
Y-Yes!
--Let's take him out!
--Yeah!
I don't think I could top
a wonderful birthday like this!
so from there, we just ran for our lives!
Your hair looks like a water bug.
Tama!
Room!
Don't set the bar too low!
We left the execution ground
I'll make it your everyday life!
and ran straight to Oden Castle!
Is he a fool?!
That ability...
He shouldn't say that!
By the time we leave this country,
That tattoo...
Hey!
Is he...?!
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
Why are you lying down bleeding?
On our way, Dogstorm and Cat Viper
quarreled with each other
Isn't it obvious?!
I got shot and collapsed!
and were caught by Orochi's underlings
so we gave up on them!
It missed my vital organs
so I was waiting for the right moment.
That's possible!
They formed an alliance!
Oh, okay.
Even if any of us might have died,
You insolent brat...
someone had to get to Oden Castle!
Why don't you show more concern?!
So you're fine, right?
Roronoa-ya is with them
and he knows our plan.
Luffy-dono!
Orochi who was looking to bring down the Kozuki Clan
was taking aim at...
What?
Even as reckless as they are,
they wouldn't do a foolish thing like taking down Holdem.
Know your place!
Kin!
...Momonosuke-sama who was at the castle!
I'm glad that you're alive!
I'm sorry that I couldn't come to get you...
When we come back to this country,
Holdem-sama!
It's so great that you arrived safely.
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
Oh no!
We've got to report this to Jack-sama now!
I'm afraid I've got the runs pretty bad
and I thought I wouldn't be able to...
Th-The castle is...!
If they do something to him,
Oh, that was surprising!
Why did you do that all of a sudden?!
...come out from the bathroom tonight again.
our plan will...
But Kaido had already made a move
and the castle was on fire.
What just happened?
But I'm starting to feel a little better.
...no longer...
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON - A VASSAL OF THE KOZUKI CLAN
Well, well, well, it was painful.
Come on, Hammer!
Go away, Hawkins!
He's alive, Tra-guy!
Damn! You bastards!
Go to hell!
When did I say he wasn't?
I won't forgive you!
Chambres!
--I meant he'd appear from the bathroom at night.
--You misguided me!
Idiot! He shouldn't have pushed his luck!
Catch them!
Hm? You don't want that?
What?!
Kin-sama!
What? What? Whaaat?!
Kiku!
N-No...
O-Of course...
You were back!
Of course, I'm happy!
Flower Shuriken!
I really missed you!
And it made my body tremble!
It's just... I'm surprised...!
Oh, okay...
Why do you keep attacking me?!
Don't make me mad!
Honestly! If you were back,
why didn't you tell me?!
Help me!
Momonosuke-sama, his younger
sister Hiyori-sama,
What?! I'm alive?!
No way!
I see!
Hey, guys! Don't just stand there!
Your Captain is in trouble!
I was worried about you!
Don't be a stranger!
and their mother Kozuki Toki-sama
were left behind in the castle.
What the hell?!
His lower body's moving by itself!
I-I'm sorry!
Momonosuke-sama is okay, too?
Y-Yes, sir!
Mother...
Yes.
Momo's alive, too, huh?
Oh? Do Kiku and Kin know each other?
Injection!
Man! You did such a reckless thing!
Shot!
Momonosuke-sama! Hiyori-sama!
--Seems like they're very close.
--What?
Now, they'll really come after us!
Get ready for it!
Kiku, why are you with Luffy-dono's group?
Toki-sama!
Yeah, we can't cause any trouble!
Okay, guys?!
I just saw your limbs stretch!
What's wrong with you?!
Come on! Hurry up!
What?! Don't tell me they're...
You're the troublemaker here!
It's a riot, right?
We shouldn't stay here too long.
Let's move on!
Remember when I told you
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit?
Who wants to hear the story
and where should I start?
It's no use...
Follow me!
And...
Now... What kind of ability was that?
You're right, Kiku!
We'll go to the ruins of Oden Castle
at the top of the mountain!
Momonosuke-sama!
They are our strong allies
to help us bring down Orochi!
...my entire body turned to rubber
in exchange for my swimming ability!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Luffy-dono and Law-dono!
Hiyori-sama! Toki-sama!
So that was a true story!
Whoa!
H-He's a monster...
Straw Sword!
Hey, Luffy!
Only you can beat him, Captain!
Take off your mask!
You arrived safely!
I'm sorry!
You don't have to call me Captain!
Trafalgar Law!
Even though we were there...
we let Oden-sama be...
Momonosuke-sama?!
Luffy, I was just practicing my swordsmanship!
Okay, I'll get going!
This pirate group is breaking up!
It was not your fault at all.
Yeah!
--Good!
--Watch this!
Because I got what I wanted!
But...
Lift your head up.
Balloon!
Thank you!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Rubber Man, just keep expanding
and contracting right there forever!
Toki-sama, it's dangerous here!
Let's get out!
Alright, take good care of her, Horselina!
Mm-hm. Kiku. It's been a while.
I will stay.
Is Dog Pops here in the Land of Wano, too, Momo?
Goodbye!
I'm Speed, Headliner of the Beast Pirates!
Balloon!
You cannot!
What? Momo?!
Let's get out of here!
I don't take orders from you, fool!
It's rude to speak to Momonosuke-sama
without an honorific!
Toki-sama!
Servants naturally protect their masters!
Oh, that's fine, Kiku.
What? Okay.
Then we will share the
same fate with you here!
Of course, Dogstorm is here, too.
Why are you doing this to us?!
Yeah. I'm counting on you!
--Balloon!
--He turned his back on his crew!
I see.
Leave... to the future!
Why is the Headliner at the brat's mercy?
Then, it's just them left now.
There it is! The treasure ship!
The future?
Oh, no!
I'm gonna drown!
People can never go back to the past...
Are we there yet? We walked a lot.
Hey!
Zoro!
But you can go forward into the future.
I wonder if Kin'emon and the others are there.
Big Bro...
Luffy!
Hm? What is it?
Me, too.
Horselina, jump!
He said to look for castle ruins,
so this mountain's got to be it.
I'll never forget...
I'm not your servant!
I traveled farther and
farther into the future
Please! Horselina-chan!
by the power of the strange Time-Time Fruit
I'm glad that we got in touch with him!
and finally arrived at the place
where this journey ends.
I'm still alive!
I'll never forget the taste
of the sweet red-bean soup
Th-Thank you! Thank you so much!
Whoa! It looks delicious!
and the apple that I had today
for the rest of my life!
Hey!
It was hard to believe,
You saved my life!
There is so much food!
I've never seen this much at once before!
Okay!
Luffy, you're here!
but rumor had it that Toki-sama was born
way back in the past...
When I return to Amigasa Village,
I'm gonna give this apple to Master-sama!
Luffy!
Hey...
Guys! Get over here!
Balloon...! Balloon...!
Say hi to Grandpa Nose for me!
I promise I'll bring back the dog!
It's unbelievable!
Luffy!
You mean...
I'm glad that you're okay!
...you met Oden-sama.
Balloon is said to be the last Ruku...
Okay!
Yes. That is why I will stay here.
Komachiyo!
Garchu!
I want you to help Big Bro!
They believe there is magical power in Ruku's blood...
Luffy!
You're dressed like a samurai! It's cool!
Oh yeah!
What took you guys so long?!
That's why I got kidnapped.
Let me borrow this sword for a little longer!
Without it, I can't call myself a samurai!
We were looking for you! Even on the sea bottom!
Big Bro, are you okay?!
You are determined...
As long as they have me here,
Balloon will come back again and again...
We found your Vivre Card
so we at least knew you were alive.
No one can stop you!
You're not using it at all!
Let me see it for a moment... Really!
Onami!
I wish he wasn't so rare
and didn't have magical power!
Momo-chan!
Kin'emon-san, how are you now?
Oh, yeah! The most important
thing isn't here!
I'll tell Master-sama so!
Even if he wasn't special,
he'd still be my most important friend for me!
I'm getting by.
--What?
--I'll be back!
Yeah, thanks!
Momonosuke-san, you look good.
We must get going, Master-sama!
If we really go into the future...
I thought so, you dirty brat!
Oh, thank you!
So you've returned to the group, Sanji-dono.
Big Bro, where are you going?!
Be careful on the way!
Gum-Gum...
We will surely fulfill Oden-sama's dream
Yeah, sorry to make you worry.
Okay! Well then...!
...Rocket!
Not yet!
Kin-san!
See you again!
Don't give up!
He's your best friend, right?!
and take down Orochi and Kaido!
Are these people Luffytaro-san's friends?
What is the most important thing?
Don't worry!
Leave it to a Peace-main!
What a lovely lady!
See you!
Crush, crush, crush...
And we will certainly...
Tama!
Hey!
...open up this country!
That's enough! Get off of her!
You're rude, Bonekichi!
What are you gonna do?!
Leave him alone, Brook!
Please look after Momonosuke.
I'm gonna fly!
Right, Momo-chan?
I knew it wasn't gonna be that easy,
Basil Hawkins!
--Onami...
--Momo!
Alright...
Mother?
Momo!
Luffy!
But...
They are all Luffy-dono's friends!
We gotta get going, too!
No, I don't want that!
I will stay here with you!
Stop talking!
I'm gonna shut you up!
The reliable people who will help us!
Luffytaro-san!
Attack!
Mother, please don't do that!
I'm proud of myself.
I know when to quit!
Luffytaro-san!
Wait!
I've never seen this much food before!
Mother! Mother!
Momonosuke-sama,
I'm glad that he lightened up like that.
Even if I fight that monster,
I would've earned nothing.
My grandfather became well!
I lived to see my dream come true!
Amputation!
All I need is this bird's blood.
Our child has his energy back!
Captain!
Oh, you guys.
I can form another pirate group anytime.
I've never eaten this much before!
How's Bepo doing?
He hasn't come out of the bush yet
because of the runs.
Takt!
What's wrong with everyone?
Hey, Ruku!
Don't try to escape death now.
Straw Hat-ya.
Just give up!
Let's have a talk inside.
Ouch...
That's good!
Okay.
What?!
Chambres!
We stole safe food from the farm.
Hi! I wish I could fly like you!
So you're the one who did it!
How the hell did you get here?!
Huh?! What the...?!
Alright then!
Hey, you fool! Don't get on!
This broomstick is for one person!
Thank you for the treasure ship!
This ruined castle will be our headquarters.
Am I dreaming?! Where am I?!
Get off!
Thank you!
Hey!
--Come visit again!
--Thank you!
Where is the castle?! And the fire?!
Don't touch my hat!
Toki-sama! Hiyori-sama!
Pirates shouldn't do such a good deed!
Ouch!
O-O-Okay!
It makes me sick!
Oh, no! The Ruku!
Oh, we did a good thing!
Where are you, Mother?!
The Ruku...
What a messy room!
Don't worry! It'll be here any minute!
Please stop! Momonosuke-sama!
You stole it.
You cut up all my proxies...
I'm sorry, everyone...
Mother!
What will?!
You catch on to things quickly.
My right hand.
It's just a threat though.
Guys!
Look after yourselves!
Kin'emon!
I'd rather not kill anyone
seeing as how I'm a doctor.
Welcome to the Land of Wano.
It's been a while since the fateful Sabaody.
Luffy-dono! Everyone!
No... Don't... Don't... Don't...
Thank you for coming to the Land of Wano!
I assume you're not here for vacation
since your allies are also here...
Are these our graves?!
Don't do it!
Once again, thank you very much!
And they are old graves!
So you didn't become her servant
by eating that dango.
--Don't mention it!
--Yeah!
It was real... Toki-sama's power!
You didn't expect that I knew?
I ran across Straw Hat
and the others earlier.
And...
First, aside from Momonosuke-sama's identity,
...why are you coming with us?
I bet you wanted to silence me
before it's too late...
there is another thing that I haven't told you guys.
I-I'm sorry!
I've always wanted to visit Oden Castle!
Ring, ring, ring...
Is that the town in Kuri?
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
I can go home after we get there
so I won't give you trouble!
You guys have so many secrets!
Clank.
Just tell us everything!
We're not strangers!
Holdem-sama was taken down by thieves
and they're on the run now!
Is this...
the Land of Wano in the future?!
Is it gonna be okay?
--He's right.
--We're friends!
Look, I know you saved me...
We've already reported to Jack-sama!
Yeah!
Kiku is a good person and she's strong
so it's gonna be fine!
You're totally right... I'm sorry!
They crushed Holdem
and now Jack has been notified?!
Since we came from the past,
But isn't there a better way to carry me?
But you're not going to believe
what I'm about to say.
this world after 20 years
was literally unknown.
Forget it. Let's go back!
As you just heard,
all your effort was for nothing.
No...
What is it? Just say it!
She's hiding something!
To learn about the country that had been
And of course, Kaido-san will know
what you and Straw Hat's group are doing.
completely changed by Orochi
and the others' evil doing,
By the way, Tra-guy,
why are we going to the castle?
Hey, Luffy.
Remember! Real treasure is not
a huge diamond, gold, silver, pearls, nor coral.
It's not a castle now...
You know Kanjuro and Raizo.
we walked around.
Only the deserted ruins remain.
We saw a row of factories...
And the three of us here.
Those fools...
Because of them, we have the worst possible outcome!
And so many smokestacks
that vent black smoke...
Why does he wanna go to Oden Castle?
It's not all the things that only sparkle.
The five of us altogether!
Undrinkable water...
Food under strict control...
Oh, it's not?
As a matter of fact,
Luffytaro-san and the
others are good people...
Right, you'll see
once you set out to the sea!
But I can't drop my guard yet.
we came from the past!
Daimyo and regions that are destroyed!
Hey, you guys! Clear the way!
Huh?
After we separated from you guys,
What?
Sterile lands!
The past?
Roronoa-ya?!
we made a plan
and were taking action accordingly...
Kozuki's name is despised
because of all their lies.
Excuse us! Let us pass through!
We're in a hurry!
What do you mean by that?
The sea is great, Luffy!
You'll see once you get there.
This is no longer...
Uh-huh!
First,
...the Land of Wano that we know!
we'll go meet the ghosts of the Land of Wano.
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
Ghosts?
KIN'EMON
There!
Chase! They stole our food!
KANJURO
You'll be surprised...
I hope you can become a Peace-main!
RAIZO
MOMONOSUKE
I thought no one would
fight together with us.
Yeah, I was stunned, too...
I'll become one at any cost!
But that was not true.
Roronoa-ya!
The thing is we came from
the Land of Wano of 20 years ago...
See you again!
Hey, Tra-guy!
There, you'll learn...
Yeah, see you!
Even after 20 years,
You idiot!
...crossing through time
to the present Land of Wano!
VASSAL KANJURO
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
there are still people who admire Oden-sama
and want to help the Kozuki Clan!
VASSAL RAIZO
VASSAL KIN'EMON
All right!
This is the beginning of a new journey!
MOMONOSUKE
...an unbelievable truth!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
Huh?!
Several years later, a pirate named Straw Hat Luffy
makes his name in the world of the sea!
Huuuuuuh?!
ODEN
The name, Kozuki Oden, marking
the old grave tells of
Momonosuke's father, Kozuki Oden, was a man who
mesmerized even Whitebeard!
The Reversed Crescent Moon lights up the sky!
The treasure ship filled with food gives a rays of hope
to the people of Okobore Town!
Guided by two birds and a pit viper, light shines on their way
to take down Kaido!
This is the origin of One Piece,
written by Eiichiro Oda!
a heartbreaking event that happened
in the Land of Wano two decades ago!
He was aggressive and daring!
A grand romantic adventure! A
mighty dream across the sea!
Samurai! Ninja! The joining of new allies raises
the fighting spirit of Luffy and the others!
The Kozuki Family's name was tarnished
and the
"I will make the country a place where
everyone can eat as much as they want!"
The man got out of the Land of Wano
true story of what happened
has been distorted.
and saw the ends of the world along with the King of the Pirates!
The freest man in the sea world!
Otama sees in Luffy, as he looks to the future,
the shadow of Ace who she misses!
When the shocking truth is revealed,
He is the King of the Pirates!
The beginning of another Luffy's epic journey!
Together with their friends
who had dreadful experiences,
His horrific final moments make Luffy and the others wail!
a secret operation to bring down
Kaido is finally put into action!
Luffy and the others are
overwhelmed and surprised!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Legendary Samurai! The Man Who Roger Admired!"
One Piece 20th anniversary special program!
"Romance Dawn"
"The Coming of the Treasure Ship! Luffytaro Returns the Favor!"
"Bringing Down
the Emperor of the Sea! A Secret Raid Operation Begins!"
"Mysterious Grave Markers! A Reunion
at the Ruins of Oden Castle!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!