Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba"              "Nanohana"   "Katorea"
Have a safe trip...
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
my stupid son...
in the kingdom of oases.
"Alabasta's Hero and
a Ballerina on the Ship!"
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
Well, we're finally here.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
I'd tell you not to be too eager,
but I guess that's asking too much.
"Goodbye Drum Island!
I'm Going Out to Sea!"
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
But do you have a plan
for stopping the rebellion?
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
I do have a plan, but there's no
guarantee it will make things stop.
Out of our way! Out of our way!
and a mighty swell.
Whoa!
After arriving in Alabasta,
Luffy and the others
It's beautiful...
Having returned to the
Alabasta Kingdom at long last,
Yeah...
encountered Navy Captain Smoker.
Cherry blossoms, huh?
So hungry...
So hot...
Princess Vivi and Luffy's party
landed at the port town of Nanohana.
Please! Don't make a hasty decision!
There to save Luffy
in the nick of time
Hey... is Chopper okay?
was the man who controls fire:
Fire Fist Ace.
While hiding from
Baroque Works' assassins,
Let's leave him alone for now.
Ace turned out to be
Luffy's older brother.
the group prepares for a trek across
the desert to stop the rebel army.
He's experiencing what it's like
to set out on a journey as a man.
"Nanohana, Alabasta Kingdom"
However, Luffy had rushed
ahead of everyone else
Yeah, he is about to leave the
island he's spent his entire life in.
"Ace and Luffy!
Hot Emotions and Brotherly Bonds"
and found himself
lost outside of town.
"Off to the Desert Kingdom! The Rain-
Summoning Powder and the Rebel Army"
Yeah...
I'm leaving, Doctor... Doctorine...
My adventure... is finally starting.
"The Heroes' Reunion!
His Name is Fire Fist Ace!"
Crocodile-sama...
Crocodile-sama!
Crocodile!
Move.
I'm afraid that's a no-can-do.
So this is an Alabasta city?
Huh?
Food!
Ahh... Crocodile-sama!
Listen, guys! Use self-control and
try not to act on instinct too much!
As always, he came for us!
Crocodile?!
This is a joyous day!
Don't tell me it's the Crocodile,
one of the Seven Warlords...
Yes, Nami-san!
The moon is out and the
cherry blossoms have bloomed.
Fire Fist Ace...
Shut up, ignorant people!
The guy who needs to hear
that the most is already gone.
Chopper! Hey, Chopper!
You son of a gun!
To think you're Straw Hat's brother...
I just came to get that pirate's head.
How long are you gonna
be in a daze like that?
Food place!
He's so wonderful...
Get back here!
Drink!
What?
He's all-instinct.
That's what you always say,
but you always save us.
Come here and sing!
What?
What should we do?
Here, stick these
chopsticks up your nose!
Don't worry.
Hurray for Crocodile!
What?
Find where the most commotion is,
and he'll be there.
Really, what a grand nighttime
view of cherry blossoms...
How could we not have a
party at a time like this?!
You got that right.
Alabasta's Guardian Angel!
White...
Ugh! I wish he'd at least realize
he has a bounty on his head!
Crocodile!
Spark!
Are you surprised?
Crocodile!
King of the desert! Crocodile!
You made friends with
some really crazy guys, huh?
Especially in a big country like this!
Oh, youngster!
I haven't seen you before!
Forget about him.
Let him do whatever.
Is this your first time in Alabasta?
Friends...
Let's just eat first.
We can think after that.
Wh-What is that?!
Well, call me what you will.
That's right. They're over the top,
but since you're one of us now,
Whadya say? Check out
this solid-gold apple!
--Is a house on fire?!
--No, it's no ordinary fire!
Anyway, pirates, don't cause
a ruckus in this country.
They're all the same...
Hold on!
you'll have to get used to it.
Don't tell anyone,
Karoo and I can't go with you.
What in the world is happening?
but this is an incredible treasure
I found in some ancient ruins!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Aren't you underestimating us?
It's a fight between flame and smoke?!
--Eh?
--Huh? Are you not feeling good?
Karoo! What were you doing
frozen in the river?
He did say he ate
the Flame-Flame Fruit.
It's said one bite of this magic gold
apple will let you live 1000 years!
Are you planning to take
on all of us by yourself?!
I'm too recognizable here...
That's for sure.
You're the government's dog,
one who sold his soul to authority!
Don't worry! I'll go shopping
for you too, Vivi-chan!
Sorry. I'm not interested
in living a thousand years.
But Luffy! Is it true
that guy's your brother?!
He probably slipped or something.
He's a clumsy one!
Who do you think you are,
acting like a hero?!
Quiet, Mr. Bushido!
Yeah! His name's Ace!
I just need to live today.
Those who don't wanna die,
lay down on the ground.
Yeah... yeah...
What is it?
You having a brother
isn't that surprising,
He says that the guy named Zoro was
swimming in the river and disappeared.
Is he an idiot or what?!
He's a perfect target for us!
Mr. 3's ship!
but what's he doing
in the Grand Line?!
He thought Zoro was in trouble so he
jumped into the river and got frozen.
Get him! The money and
valuables in this town are ours!
Ace is a pirate!
That creep didn't kick
the bucket after all?!
He left the island three years
before me to find the One Piece!
--A solid-gold apple?!
--1000 years of life?!
So it was your fault!
There's no doubt about it!
Yeah!
His ship runs on the power
of his Wax-Wax Fruit!
Ow...
For real?! For real?! You found
it in some ancient ruins?!
Tony-kun, you can understand
what Karoo is saying?
The bastard's here?
Yep, sure did! It's a legendary
artifact of an ancient civilization!
Yes. I'm an animal by nature,
so I can talk with animals.
This is bad. He's seen our faces.
A-Anyways, let's hurry back to the ship!
One bite and we can live 1000 years?!
So this is what the famous
Seven Warlords are like?!
It's alright! I have an idea!
You can talk with animals?
Let's escape before
anyone comes after us!
Yep! It's the truth! I give you my word!
That's incredible, Chopper!
Yes, Nami-san!
To be able to do that along
with your medical skills!
Awesome!
I see you have very sharp eyes!
There's no telling where he is,
so we hafta move without standing out.
Dummy! Praising me like that wouldn't
make me feel happy! You jerk!
In that case, I'll part with it for
the one-time price of 1000 Berries!
Still, I never thought I'd
see Ace in a place like this!
I think we're standing out quite a bit...
He sure looks happy.
1000 Berries?! You got yourself a deal!
By the way, Nami, what do
you mean by "medical skills"?
Alright! You can come out, guys!
Chopper is a doctor... a first-class one
Honestly, now! What are you thinking?!
The path splits into two!
We've been long out.
Usopp, left! Hear me, guys?!
Looks like nobody noticed us!
with all the medical skills
hammered into him by Dr. Kureha.
Yes, Nami-san! I'll follow
you wherever you go!
I wouldn't take him seriously if I were you.
If so, it's a miracle.
Enough, pervy cook!
What?!
Vivi-chan. We're safe from
view for a little while now.
Chopper! You're a doctor?!
Cool! The fireball's gone even higher!
Hey! Let go!
I was just about to live 1000
years for only 1000 Berries!
Incredible!
No way!
Quit wasting time and look for Luffy!
Vivi-chan?
It seems there really is no end to
a fight between flame and smoke.
Good Lord! What did you think Chopper
was when you asked him to join us?!
Yes?! Yes? You were saying?
We're done shopping,
so we leave for the next town
What's wrong?
the minute we find him!
A seven-form transforming
interesting reindeer.
Though it was already obvious enough.
Where did Luffy run off to, anyway?
Emergency food.
I'm sorry. I just felt
a little relieved, so...
Where did Straw Hat's crew go?
What?!
Ah...! Darn it! I forgot to bring my
medical tools since I left in a hurry!
Th-They're gone!
Shut up, you two!
At the very least,
So is Ace! We've lost sight of him!
from what I've seen of this town,
things still seem all right...
I caught Straw Hat for the
first time in the Grand Line...
Can't be... Then what is this?
What?
I probably can't rest easy...
But Portgas D. Ace.
You simply had to get in the way.
He's...
My bag!
It was in the sleigh.
Just a quick question.
Have you seen this guy?
...but I think I'll make it in time.
How come...?
Huh?
How come? Didn't you prepare
for the trip by yourself?
Hurry and load the stuff!
We're leaving right away!
Monkey D. Luffy?
Yeah. It does seem like a peaceful town.
Hurry!
Humph...
Set the sails!
Ah...
He might be here in town. I've been
looking for him for a while now.
I'm a pirate on a
different level, you pig.
Hey, Vivi.
You said you had a plan for
stopping the rebel army, right?
S-Say. Are we leaving again just
after we finally reached the island?
Hmm. Never seen him.
What will you do now?
Ah!
Yes. We only stopped by this town
to get what we're going to need.
Oh, but if you're looking for someone,
ask at the restaurant up ahead.
What should we do?
Eh?
If you think you're gonna make it in
time, it'd be better to act quick.
Now we're going to head up the
river into the interior of Alabasta.
Crocodile!
The owner there knows a lot of people.
Th-That's true, but the agreement
was only to bring me to Alabasta--
Much appreciated.
The restaurant, huh? I was
just feeling hungry, anyways.
Our next destination is Erumalu,
the City of Green.
Come on, now!
Are you still saying that?
Crocodile! Crocodile!
Erumalu?
Nami-san?!
Hurry!
We traveled this far together.
We can't just leave you now.
Pick up the pace!
Who's that? He looks incredibly strong.
All set!
Okay! Let's set sail!
Why's he looking for Luffy?
Yeah, Vivi! Don't act so distant!
Maybe he's a bounty hunter?
Plus, I'm interested in this
Warlord of the Sea!
No. He's not.
After all... she knew
everything you were thinking...
You don't have to mention that!
Y'know...
Huh?
Anyways, stop thinking that way!
Not to mention people are
out to kill all of us but me.
I get the feeling we're
missing someone...
That mark...
Sanji-san...
What a wonderful person she is...
So do I...
As a former pirate-hunter,
there's no way I wouldn't recognize it.
So there you have it!
--Ah! I got snot on the chopsticks!
Yeah. We're missing
approximately one person.
And besides, if this
country gets destroyed,
--Yeah...
--Ah! I got snot on the chopsticks!
we won't get our reward
for bringing you here.
That moron!
Crocodile again...
--Understand?
--Y-Yes.
"Alubarna Palace, Alabasta Kingdom"
Hey, Chopper, you try it too!
Very good, then!
Huh?!
He was one step ahead again?
Go to hell.
No... It couldn't be!
Thank you, Zoro! I haven't forgotten
about your debt to me, either!
Geez... When you're reminiscing...
Right, Chopper?
That's weird.
By the time we got to Nanohana,
it was already...
It's wrong!
Wh-Why, you--!
Selling a sword like this for 200,000
Berries is as good as swindling!
Even if I'm a ghost I'll
still come for my money!
Why am I the only one here?
I see...
Chopper?
You lousy--!
Don't!
Either way, it's fine as long
as the citizens are okay.
You'd better pay the
400,000 Berries you owe!
Do you even have a permit?!
It's gone up!
Where did they go?
"King of Alabasta, Nefertari Cobra"
Okay... guys!
He does a lot for us.
It'll go even higher if
you're not quick to repay!
It is her!
I didn't realize you were
Roronoa Zoro, and a pirate.
Sheesh! I guess my letting you
escape was pretty much pointless.
--Hey, Usopp! Say something!
--Thank you.
--Attention!
--Forget it!
--Nami-san is in the right!
--You bastard!
--Attention!
--Well, I'd like to introduce
There's no mistake.
This ship is heading to Alabasta.
Say what?!
You... You lied to me!
Yo!
our new friend to you!
Ace!
Northwest of this city
is an oasis called Yuba.
--Sanji! Go!
--Tony Tony Chopper!
Haven't seen you in a while, Luffy!
A rogue like you can't be
allowed to own a renowned sword!
--He'll be our ship's doctor.
--I...
--To celebrate his coming on board...
You too, Ace!
That's where the rebel army is based.
I'll be there soon...
Hey! Listen to me, you jerks!
I'd like to go there
first to stop the uprising.
I'll collect your sword,
the legendary Wado Ichimonji!
Luffy! Don't lie!
I...
How many years has it been?
But to get to Yuba,
we'll have to cross the desert.
Tell me what you know.
Good question.
What is that woman doing here?!
But, Luffy. It looks like you
still go at your own pace,
Hey, why are you looking away?
Look me in the eyes!
For that, we'll need to stock up on
the necessary food and water here...
just like you did
since you were a kid.
Never try this again!
Do you understand?!
I've never had this much fun before.
You too, Ace! I was surprised
you ate a Devil Fruit,
Well, seriously... I don't know anything.
Yeah!
...but if Mr. 3 is in town...
Let's toast to our new friend!
but besides that, you're the same!
What're you doing, Zoro?
Oh. In that case, it's no problem.
Then let me ask you something.
Like when you'd sneak into the fields,
eat 100 watermelons,
Why're you hiding?
How did enough food for 8 people,
Yeah!
which I carefully divided so that
it'd last until we get to Alabasta,
He hasn't seen my face.
That woman spells nothing
but trouble! Dammit!
and then spit the seeds
out like a gun and run!
Cheers!
That's right! You've met
almost none of them so far!
That wasn't me! That was you!
disappear during the night?
Hey. Tashigi.
And one other!
Stop fighting, it's pointless!
You've got a horrible poker face.
And then you got big bumps right here!
Oh, yeah! Chopper, too!
I wonder if they've left the island by now.
That'll be perfect. We'll have a
lot to carry. I'm counting on you!
That was you, too!
I watched and laughed!
Captain Smoker!
Burp...
A reindeer with a first-rate heart
and first-rate skills as a doctor...
Right! Got it!
Small fry pirates.
Hey, now. You gonna be okay?
They thought they could act
like big-shots around me,
Hey, you have something
around your mouth.
I'll be okay! I wanna do what I can!
If the cherry blossoms that Hiriluk put
his life into really did lead to a miracle,
so I took care of 'em.
Ah! Shoot! Food crumbs?!
I guess we're both the same!
Even in such a distant land, your
distaste for pirates is unfaltering!
There's no problem like this, right?
Yeah!
Alright! Now that's a human reindeer!
See, it was you!
it'd have to be just that clumsy
reindeer going out to sea.
This brings back memories!
If you got time for pointless chit-chat,
have the royal army take 'em!
In that case, your help is appreciated.
Say, weren't your friends
looking for you?
Leave it to us!
That kid... acting like he's all grown up...
I've listed everything we need.
Oh, and we'll need some clothes, too.
Y-Yes, sir!
Yeah.
Geez...
But, Ace. What are you
doing in this country?
There doesn't seem to be any word yet
Clothes?
Ahhh, Nami-san...
You saw it, right?
Ordinary clothes so we won't stand out.
Huh? You mean you didn't get
the message I sent to Drum?
of Straw Hat Luffy having
come to this country.
He'll be a fine ship's doctor.
--Ah.
--And perfume!
The large rat trap
is no longer good enough.
Yes, Nami-san!
But don't let your guard down.
They will show up. I'm sure of it.
So, what're you gonna do from here on?
--Food and water!
--Tabasco!
Drum?
Please buy a lockable refrigerator.
Who cares about you!
--Food and water!
--Tabasco!
Yeah. It's no big deal
or anything, though.
Well...
Still...
Smoker? That's the Navy
captain from Loguetown!
I was... working as the Captain
of the Security Guard under Wapol.
...where could that idiot be,
and what is he doing?!
I'll think about it... since it
can be a life or death issue...
I'm just in these waters
on minor business,
Are you saying he followed us
all the way here from Loguetown?!
I will have to atone for that sin.
so I thought I might look you up.
Hm?
Minor business?
It would seem so.
I was thinking about leaving this land
Well...! We'd better catch
something for Sanji-kun...
Hmm... It doesn't look like there'd
be a food place here at all...
And then there's that man...
Things could get ugly quick.
and entrusting this new
country to the citizens...
I'm a member of the
Whitebeard Pirates now.
Hey, any luck fishing?
Whitebeard Pirates?
Where is that idiot?!
But, actually...
Are you... going to do that then?
This is the mark of the
Whitebeard Pirates. It's my pride.
...where am I?!
W-Well...
No... I've come to realize that
leaving isn't the only way of atoning.
Oh?
"Nanohana"
No choice. I'll just have
to go back the way I came.
Luffy. Won't you join
the Whitebeard Pirates?
I feel good...
I'm hungry...
This country is breaking
the shackles of monarchy,
Seriously, I can't take my eyes
off these guys for a moment...
Your friends can come too, of course.
and a new country made by the
citizens' hands is about to be born.
No.
Oh! Thanks for this lunch, old guy!
Smoke?
There may be something I can do for
the birth of this country by staying.
If there's smoke, that means...
I figured not. Just thought I'd ask.
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
Food place!
Ahh... I'm starving...
The fish aren't biting at all...
That wasn't enough at all one bit...
I feel that that is indeed
a way for me to atone.
I wanna help him to be
King of the Pirates...
Luffy! It's your fault!
It's because you even ate the bait!
Humph, you youngster...
If we don't have bait,
the fish won't bite!
And not you, Luffy.
Where's the town?!
You do have a heart
to care for the country.
That's fine!
Then we'll just have to fight!
You ate it, too!
Where in the world is the food place?!
Well... I only ate the
stuff on the bait box cover.
Says it's deer meat!
A heart to care for the country, huh...?
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
Luffy-san. Usopp-san.
Have you caught anything?
That's what's great
about historical lands!
I once learned it from
a girl who was only ten.
Got all kinds of ingredients!
Hey! Don't drink it all, Luffy!
Ahh!
Karoo! Oh no!
"The Holy Land of Marie Jois"
Ahh... World Summit?
What is it, Chopper?
There's something strange mixed
in with the smell of the food...
I wonder if we can
catch a shark or something...
Such a tiresome, worthless event.
I wanna catch a Sea King.
Strange?
It is, indeed.
Something must've happened in town.
Oh! That's the scent of perfume!
What're you two... doing to Karoo?!
Food!
Smoker and all the
marines left the ship...
I wonder if the Drum Kingdom
will be okay like this...
Perfume?
Yeah. That shop there sells some.
Food!
I don't really like this smell... Hey!
The rift between the king
and citizens keeps growing...
But...
This is perfect! I'll use this
chance to escape somehow!
That's a wonderful outfit, Miss!
What's that?
Ah...
It's the king of the Alabasta Kingdom...
But it and your exotic fragrance
are put to shame by your raw charm!
Mr. 11.
It's Nefertari Cobra-sama!
You must be members of Baroque
Works if you know my codename!
Hey! What's going on? What happened?
What do you say?
Would you like to have some tea--?
Oh. It seems someone suddenly
died in the restaurant.
So that's the king of Alabasta,
famed for his benevolence and wisdom.
What was that, Chopper?!
That was just getting good!
What the heck is that?
Are you Millions?! Hurry and untie me!
I wonder if it's cotton candy...
What are you doing?
Shopping comes first!
I'll go get Nami-san!
Suddenly died?!
Yeah, we are members of Baroque Works.
Yeah, I know!
Revolutionist Dragon...
This man's ideologies are dangerous.
He supposedly died in the middle
of a conversation with the owner!
Oh, it's too much!
This smell is making me sick...
But we're Billions. Meaning we're
candidates to be Number Agents.
It's very clear that he'll become a
big enemy to us, the World Government,
Oh, that's okay. Don't push yourself.
He's a traveler.
Hm?
Mr. 11. You're barely an agent.
You're not much stronger than us.
Nami-san, there's a problem!
Come right away!
We think he unwittingly ate a
Desert Strawberry while traveling...
I'll do the shopping.
You go wait over there.
in 5-6 years and stand in our way.
Later!
A Desert Strawberry?
Miss!
O-Oh! I see!
Ahh... don't worry.
It's nothing. It's just steam.
They're poisonous spiders that
look like red strawberries.
Ahh... How ridiculous.
Sorry about that, Billions.
But could you hurry and untie me?
Is he really gonna be okay?
Eat one by accident, and you'll
suddenly keel over a few days later.
Steam is coming up from the sea?
That has nothing to do with my country.
Yeah. It's a hot spot.
I govern my country so that my people
won't be led astray by a revolutionist.
Don't be silly!
What the heck is that?
Contagious poison spreads through
your corpse a few hours after that,
It's an area where magma is produced.
With you gone, one of us can
be promoted to a Number Agent.
This is bad. I'm starting to
have symptoms of heat stroke.
There's an undersea volcano
underneath that area.
If you guys wanna capture him,
go ahead and do it on your own.
so nobody can get close.
Wapol!
I see...
You're too selfish!
A volcano even though it's undersea?
In the desert, what you
don't know can kill ya.
I need to go somewhere where it's cool...
What do you think the World Summit is?!
That's right. There're more undersea
volcanoes than above ground ones.
So let's empty one of the Agents' seats!
Just look! The way he's
still stuck holding the meat
Act more responsibly!
W-Wait!
Woah...
Damn Nefertari Cobra!
I don't really care...
since it's not food.
is proof of just how powerful
the Desert Strawberry's poison is!
Humph! What an unpleasant
conference that was.
With the volcano like this,
Hm? That's...
a new island will be born here over
thousands or tens of thousands of years.
Ah! That feels nice!
Hey!
That's the daughter of
that detestable Cobra!
I think I'll take a nap until
Sanji comes back.
You're so cool, Nami-san!
Fire Fist Ace is in this town!
Tens of thousands of years...
I wonder if I can live that long...
Is that okay? Is it? I guess it is...
What?! Fire Fist Ace?!
Oops! My hand slipped.
Well, you're a human. So you should
try dying sometime before that...
He came back to life!
The Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates?
Wapol-sama!
Vivi-sama!
Is it closed?
Have you caught anything?
If we can take down Ace,
we're guaranteed to be Number Agents!
Oh, excuse me. If I'm not mistaken,
you're the princess of Lord Alabasta.
Yeah. Let's go.
Oh hey, Sanji. I'm hungry.
Cook something.
We don't want anyone finding it.
What a poor child, to be the
daughter of that hopeless king.
You guys're hopeless...
Anyways, let's look for your friends.
I'll go search the storage thoroughly
to see if there's anything left.
You bastard! What're you doing?!
Stop, Igaram! I'm fine!
Getting spotted by the
Navy's always a pain.
A-Are you all right?
They might've gone back to the ship.
I'm sorry, too, for bumping into you.
Whoa!
Now where'd he go?
Which harbor is your ship in?
Oh, whoops.
What a child!
Actually, I can't remember at all.
"Katorea"
I fell asleep.
Nanohana is famous for its perfume,
In the World Summit where kings gather,
You were asleep?!
Oh, geez.
even a minor argument can trigger a war.
but the perfume is actually
made at an oasis called Katorea.
Th-That's absurd! You were in the
middle of a conversation and a meal!
Ahh! It smells of sulfur!
Pirate ship captains usually
remember where they leave their ship.
We can't see anything!
There's steam everywhere!
It's a city west of here.
She tolerates this situation knowing that?
And now he's eating again!
Bear with it. We should
be through it soon.
Already at this young age...
Don't worry about it!
I dunno, this doesn't seem like
a food place at all, but...
What's all this commotion, anyway?
You are the same as ever.
We were worried about you!
Humph! What an annoying brat.
Let's go, Dalton.
Anyone here?!
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Say, what kind of crew do you have?
Does this restaurant do
comedy skits or something?
What is it?!
Sorry.
There's smoke at 12 o'clock!
No, it's not like that.
But it's good you're alright.
A swordsman who wants to be the
world's greatest sword master.
Huh? No one's even here?
It doesn't matter! Cut through it!
He's always wearing a haramaki.
It hurts!
Oh! Water!
At any rate, unless we take care
of Mr. 3, I'll be in danger!
Hey, now! Don't sleep again!
A navigator who likes maps
and tangerines and money!
You were magnificent, Vivi-sama.
Then there's a cook who
makes really yummy food...
Come on! Just a little would be good!
Yes sir! We're going in!
Aw, so he wasn't dead after all?
The princess' heart to care for the country...
Oh, and there's a liar, too!
Just a false alarm...
What is this foggy thing?
And then a reindeer!
Her nobility hasn't changed one bit.
We can't see ahead!
What're these?
Ah!
That's quite the variety you got there.
How magnificent she turned out to be...
We also have a princess and a duck now!
That hit the spot!
We got through!
Oh?
Dalton-kun...
They're all so interesting!
Say, Mister.
Ahh! Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama is gone!
Yeah?!
The heart to care for the
country still remains in us.
I'd say you're probably the
most interesting of all, though.
Has this guy been in town?
Look for him in the cabins!
We can't find him!
Let us do something...
to help this new country...
He's a pirate who wears a straw hat...
Can't be!
Still, only a handful of people for a
pirate crew... That's just like you.
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
I'm impressed you're bold
enough to eat out in public...
What's this green powder?
Is it food? It doesn't look very tasty...
Whoa...!
I also want a musician!
...Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates...
Stop right there, Fire Fist Ace!
Hiriluk...
...Portgas D. Ace.
This country will surely be reborn...
Yuck! Yuck! What is this stuff?! Blech, yuck!
Shoot!
As you can see,
there's no place to run now!
just like your son, Chopper...
Why did I jump on the duck
that I suddenly came across?!
Wh-Whitebeard?! The Whitebeard Pirates?!
Oh! Perfect!
Fire Fist Ace! Your head is mine!
Dalton-san! This is serious!
That dimwit is one of the
Whitebeard Pirates?!
--Is he a human?
--Dunno...
This stuff is obviously poison!
Prepare yourself!
I just remembered something serious!
Come to think of it, I have seen
the mark on his back before!
Oh?! Ahh!
Now you burn!
What is it?
That's the mark of
the Whitebeard Pirates!
Look at this.
What a waste of time that was.
Now to find me a food place...
Help me! Please!
What's he doing here?!
It's him! The Straw Hat
pirate who beat Wapol!
What is a famous, big-shot
pirate doing in this country?
I can't swim--!
There's no doubt about it!
A 30 million-berry bounty is
on his head... They are...?
What is that?!
Oh? They're quite the rogues, aren't they...
I'm searching...
Rain...
Where did you find this?
Well... I completely forgot
to report it to you, but...
I-Is it really okay to
set sail without Luffy?
Oh! This is perfect! Water!
for my little brother!
Food place!
about a week ago, a man who
appeared to be a traveler
The Navy will be all over the harbors.
Wh-What is this?!
Aah! All the bags are gone!
We need to hide the ship first.
suddenly appeared in Robelle Town.
There should be a cove ahead
that's hidden from view!
What the hell did you do?!
It was an unusual day where no snow fell.
--Who are you?
--Shut up!
So we'll wait for things to
cool down, then look for Luffy.
What is that?! There's a
weird smell in the way!
I'm asking what you did with that powder!
I thought I'd die...
We don't know where he landed.
Oh! There's one! There's a food place!
Powder?
Yeesh! He's always, always
causing trouble like this!
Well... I'm really swanny.
I burned it all!
Anyway, this guy said that
he was after Blackbeard,
You burned it?!
To think that I was saved by
pirates who are total strangers...
My Dance Powder! My treasure!
He's a real reliable captain...
the pirate that attacked this country.
I will never forget your
kindness for the rest of my life!
What's with you, old guy?
Why're you so sad?
But once he realized that
Blackbeard was long gone, he said,
Also, may I have a cup of warm soup?
Shut up! How dare you
waste my prized powder!
Then let me ask you one more question.
Do you know how much I spent for it?!
We don't have it!
Has a pirate wearing
a straw hat come here?
We're the ones who're hungry!
I don't care! Why would you
want that poison anyway?!
Fire Fist Ace! Your bad luck ends here!
So? What do you want from me?
When we said we didn't know,
he showed the wanted poster and said,
That's none of your business, you bastard!
Oh, hey you! What a cutie!
Give me my dream back!
To let me capture you quietly.
If this guy comes here...
You're my type!
I wanna eat you! Smooch!
That stuff was your dream?!
Nope. I think I'll pass.
Hey! Isn't that Straw Hat Luffy?!
That's right! It was a step
toward achieving my big ambition!
Such a weirdo...
If he does...?
Yeah, I figured.
So you can't swim, huh?
tell him that I'll wait for him
in Alabasta for just 10 days.
N-Now that you mention it--!
I'm very sorry!
That's right. I ate a devil fruit.
Apologizing won't fix things!
Pay me for it!
H-He's worth 30 million Berries!
I'm busy trying to find
another pirate at the moment.
I can't. I don't have money.
Okay?
Really? What kind of fruit?
Talk about lucky! Fire Fist Ace
and Straw Hat Luffy!
Don't say that proudly!
To be honest, I have no
interest in taking you in.
Well... since there's no need to rush
until my ship comes to pick me up...
I even built a cabin out here and
finally managed to get this far...
Hey! Wait! What's your name?
Once I have your heads, our promotion
is a hop, skip, and jump away!
Then just look the other way.
Oh yeah... I forgot...
Can't.
C'mon, don't be so down!
You can just buy some more!
In lieu of entertainment,
I'll show you...
Anyway, let's find your ship.
Let's go to the shore.
This is my power!
It's not that easy to buy!
My name is Ace.
Yeah.
The World Government outlawed
it from being made or sold!
If you tell him that when he comes,
he'll know who I am.
Hey, you!
Hold it right there!
Not as long as I'm a marine...
Come again?
Bastards!
What're you...
and you're a pirate.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Hey, old man.
Are you a really bad guy?
Get them!
Hey, please catch him!
He just ate and skipped on the bill!
That's a bland reason.
I just told you that
this is entertainment!
You found me out?
Take this!
Ahh! Well then,
tell him, okay? Thanks!
What?!
Then die!
Let's have some fun.
What the--?! What the--?!
Gimme a break!
Ah?!
He'll wait for 10 days in Alabasta... huh...?
That's me!
So sorry!
Surprised?! Surprised?! Surprised?!
Gum-Gum...
Hold the bastard down!
Rocket!
Hm? Dr. Kureha, what's the matter?
If I touch my face with my left hand...
See?! I'm back to myself!
You look out of it.
Wh-What the--?! His arms stretched!
This is the power of the
Clone Clone Fruit I ate!
Do you know Gol D. Roger?
Huh?! Where am I?!
He has Devil Fruit powers?!
The voice, too...
D? Are you talking about Gold Roger?
The body was also the same...
Don't scare me like that, you jerks!
A... Amazing!
Is that what he's called these days?
There...!
Well, for that matter,
I don't have to knock you down...
Huh? Huh? Who're they? Where am I?
It looks like...
A food place! I finally found one!
my reindeer went with
an extraordinary guy...
Now, look!
Now I can eat! I'm starving!
Rifles!
All I have to do is...
Old guy! Food! Food! Food!
On the double!
touch faces with my right hand.
So... the will of D... was still alive...
What's wrong?
As you can see, I can...
Thought I heard a voice. It's nothing.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Food! Food! Food!
mimic anyone!
Gum-Gum...
I dunno what's going on,
but they seem dangerous!
Bodies, too!
Ahh!
I should probably get out of here, quick!
Oww! Hot!
Ouch!
Oww!
Stop it!
...Bazooka!
Hey, are you all right?
--Good work. That took a while.
--Yeah.
Ow, ow, ow...
Well... sorry, but I can't
show any more of my power...
The weapon store guy really raised
his prices, that greedy bastard...
It can't be helped. They're in huge
trouble if they get found out, too.
You're amazing! Do it more!
Yum! This is such a yum food place!
Amazing!
Ahhh... Well... if you insist...
I guess I'll show more...
--Where's Koza?
--Inside.
Y-Yeah. Thanks. But...
The sea is huge!
We got a bit of food, too.
It's in the back.
--Yeah! Show it! Show it!
--Gee, he's actually into it!
Of course! And the ones who go on
adventures on that huge sea are pirates.
Got it.
D-Don't let 'em scare you!
--Gee, he's actually into it!
--We wanna see! We wanna see!
--Well then, I guess I'll show...
The rank of Number Agent
is riding on this!
Uhh, you should probably
run away while you can...
Furthermore, I'm equipped
with a memory feature!
I see! Pirates are
incredible after all. Hm?
After them!
How come?
Oh! The ocean!
Huh?
That guy that got sent flying
just now... Do you know who he is?
See your ship?
Here we go!
Whoa! What's that?!
What is this?
Whoa!
It's a seagull.
There's no escape!
Huh? Who sent someone flying?
There isn't a seagull that big.
They went and bought a whole deer?
You did!
You guys just never learn.
Hey! Seagull!
I did? Who went flying?
Koza. We got some weapons.
Just a few, anyway...
Oh! There it is!
Ahhh! It's coming!
Ah!
Yeah. Sorry for giving you
such a dangerous job.
See? I was right. It is a seagull.
Hey! Over here! Guys!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
What's with these holes?
Now's not the time to discuss that!
It's coming because you called it!
It's nothing at all.
How stupid!
Hey, Luffy. Go on--
What a weird shop!
Is this your hobby, old guy?
Amazing! It's a great adventure!
Spin! Spin!
Never mind.
Why're you in such a daze?
You caused it!
So how was my secret talent?!
I did? When?
Oh! There he is! It's Luffy!
This country is screwed...
--I found Luffy!
--You did?
I usually never show it to others.
Why, you--!
Hey, where's Luffy?
It'll either collapse from the inside, or...
Yeah. That stupid face is definitely his.
Hm?
Yoo-hoo!
Who the hell did this?!
Huh?!
Cool!
Hey! Don't become bird food!
Whatever the case, it won't stay at peace.
--Gimme a break! Gimme a break!
--Amazing! Amazing! He's amazing!
What the hell?!
Ahh! It's terrible! A bird ate Luffy!
We have enough men now after
300,000 of the Royal Army
I'm back!
What's the big idea?!
Oh whatever!
That's my ship!
This is no time for playing around!
Luffy's in trouble!
Sanji-san! Tony-kun!
switched to our side, but we
don't have enough weapons...
Amazing! Amazing! He's...
Whoosh!
Did he say he wanted our help?
Or food.
Oh, come on!
Oh! Sorry for disturbing your meal!
No, he didn't.
Then there's no problem.
Don't worry about it.
Not again...
And our strength is at its limit.
It's already time to say goodbye...?
What a shame...
But...
There's no point in shedding
any more unnecessary blood.
Sorry 'bout that, Sanji, Chopper!
Gum-Gum...!
What?!
Do you not know how to learn your
lesson?! I oughta gut you whole!
Please don't go!
We're going to finish everything
for good with our next attack!
Propeller!
What idiot would do
something this crazy?!
Don't be sad!
We, the rebel army,
must change this country!
Yeah! Do you have any idea how
much trouble you've caused?!
Journeys are always
accompanied by farewells..
Amazing...
But don't ever forget this.
Try to act somewhat like a captain!
Ahhh!
Friendship... has nothing to do with
how long we've known each other.
Hey! Wasn't there deer meat here?
Sorry.
Oh, that's right! Ace!
Hey, Sanji! I've got some meat! Huh?
Huh? Are you sure someone
didn't haul it out already?
Lu--!
--Ace?
--Your brother was with you?
Hey! Luf--!
What? Are you guys sleeping?
Straw Hat!
Is it okay to just leave him there?
It's your fault!
Don't cry!
C'mon, do better checks, will ya?
See you again!
How are you gonna fix this situation?
I had a good hand!
I guess he'll be okay! Ace is strong!
What?!
Really? Sorry.
Now, let's go, guys!
Water? There's some in
that trough! Drink that!
He's strong?
Whoa! That's huge!
Yes sir! Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Now we can have some decent meals.
Yeah! He hadn't eaten the
Flame-Flame Fruit a long time ago,
Hey! Let's get the rest
out of here! Gimme a hand!
I've been looking for you, Straw Hat!
Is this edible?
but I still never beat
him in a single fight!
Hm? What's the matter, Chopper?
So you did come to Alabasta!
Right!
Mr. 2?!
Yeah...
He's real strong, Ace is!
Well... Pirates are...
Pirates are incredible after all!
So he is... Mr. 2, Bon Clay...!
There's a flesh-and-blood
person you could never beat?!
Vivi! You didn't know his face?!
I guess the big brother of a
monster is an even bigger monster...
Quit eating!
Yeah? Incredible, huh?
No... I've never met Mr. 2
and Mr. 1 as well as his partner.
That's right! I lost all the time!
Hey, you guys!
A-Am I safe now?
Hm?
This ship is arriving at Alabasta soon.
We don't have time to play around!
Whew! Thank you!
I don't know their powers, either...
But I'd win now if we tried!
Isn't he...
But why did you help me?
I assume that's another groundless claim.
Move it!
though I've heard of rumors...
All right...
You're finally here, Straw Hat Luffy...
"I got no reason. I'm cool, ain't I?"
Mr. 2 is...
Who...
So, what's Alabasta?
Didn't I tell you you can't enter
the Grand Line unless you beat me?
It's the country that Vivi's father governs.
You're so strange!
can win what now?!
a ballerina with a large frame...
who talks like a woman...
A rogue named Crocodile is trying
to take over Alabasta right now.
Thank you so much!
Oh! Ace! This is the crew
I was talking about!
He always wears a swan coat that
has "Bon Clay" on the back...
I hear that Crocodile is one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Oh! Thank you all for taking
care of my little brother!
What?! What?! What's going on?!
He's a little strange,
but he's a nice guy!
Seven Warlords of the Sea?
I ate the Plume-Plume Fruit.
So my body becomes smoke at will.
They're the pirates authorized
by the World Government.
Eh? Oh, not at all.
I feel like I'm going to see him again!
You should've noticed!
He might be a bit much for
you to handle too, but...
What's the matter, Vivi?
Pirates are authorized by the Government?
Still, who were those people?
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Among the faces that he
showed from his past memory...
Yeah. They're overwhelmingly strong.
Oh, well. Now which way is Nanohana?
No, not at all.
You get it? You can't even
enter the Grand Line.
Take good care of 'im.
from his memory...
You probably have lots
of catching up to do.
I saw my father's face...
This way.
Didn't I tell you that?!
And, they crush other pirates one by one.
Why don't you come in?
I'll make some tea.
the face of Alabasta's King,
Nefertari Cobra...
Oh! You certainly are strong!
No, uhh, that's okay.
Don't do it on account of me.
So the Government authorizes
them to crush pirates.
No one can beat me!
If, for example,
you could mimic a king...
Yeah, I would think not!
Not with your strength! My apologies!
Crocodile, huh...? I can't wait to see him.
you'd be able to do
quite bad things, too...
T-Talk about unexpected...
You're that smoke!
What're you doing here?!
No, no! I apologize for
burning your important stuff!
Crocodile is a hero in Alabasta because
he crushes the pirates that attack towns.
We let a troublesome
guy slip away, huh?
That's for sure.
Bastard...
Oh, uhh, no, let's just
call it a mutual apology!
I would've expected him to
be as reckless as Luffy...
Hold it!
Then he's our enemy?
But that's only his public face.
No, this sensible man can't
possibly be Luffy's brother!
In any case, please keep
this powder thing a secret!
He's certainly quite a problem
if he's on our enemy's side.
Thank you for the meal!
Huh?
Behind the scenes, he is pulling strings
to cause a civil war in Alabasta...
He's a nice guy who
cares about his brother!
Hey.
If he realizes that we're his enemy...
Halt!
What was that powder?
Brothers can be so wonderful!
Y-You don't know?
in order to take over Alabasta...
If he transforms into one of us
using his memory from earlier...
Wait, Luffy! It's me!
No. It was yucky.
The sea is just full of surprises...
No one has noticed it.
Hey! Wait up! Hey! Luffy!
That was stuff known as Dance Powder!
Come now, everyone!
we won't be able to
trust our own friends.
The citizens... My father... No one...
See! Aren't these guys neat?!
Dance Powder?
All right then! In any case, all we have
to do is beat up that Crocodile, right?
Ah...!
It's also called
"Rain-Summoning Powder."
Really? Huh?
They ran off without paying...
Listen, Luffy...
This is bad! My Gum-Gum moves
don't work on that guy at all!
It's what caused that
sudden downpour just now!
Well, hold on.
Baroque Works!
Those are the Billions' ships!
Yes. If we can first stop the
civil war and expel Baroque Works...
It's true that his opinion
doesn't have any basis,
All I can do for now is run!
Umm, shall I explain in more detail?
Fire Fist Ace and Straw Hat Luffy!
Don't think you can get away!
but he's right about us not
having to be scared of him.
Tashigi!
I wouldn't understand anyways!
Baroque Works...?
Y-Yes, Captain Smoker?!
Do you want a towel?
You look like you wouldn't.
Ahh... Yeah, you don't know
about them either, do you?
We'll show you just what Baroque
Works' Billions are made of!
We should consider ourselves lucky
that we got to see him now...
This kingdom certainly is hot!
You're a rude guy!
To be honest, I can't
quite understand, either.
Catch that guy! It's Straw Hat!
Those guys again?
I-In any case, this powder can
artificially produce rain, yes.
because we can figure
out counter-measures.
Straw Hat?!
Baroque Works has a complicated system.
Luffy. I'll clean them up.
I'll stop him!
--Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama is in a
very good mood for some reason.
--Un, deux, trios! How do you say 4?!
Eh?
The system itself is simple.
Dance Powder, when released into
the air, forms the cores for rain!
First, at the top, there's a boss, Crocodile...
What's he going to do?
Especially in that little boat...
When moisture collects around them,
clouds form and precipitate!
in other words, Mr. 0.
Tashigi! Gather the marines at once!
I found a small friendship!
Search every square inch of
this town for Straw Hat's crew!
Understand?
Let's see how skilled
There're 12 agents and one animal who
receive orders from the boss directly.
So it's mystery powder, basically?
this Second Division Commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates really is!
Yes, sir!
Well done!
People with powers are fighting!
Each of the 12 agents operates
separately as a pair with a female agent.
You really are a rude guy!
Here he comes! Fire Fist Ace!
Whoa!
Straw Hat's crew! That means...
Why would you wanna use
that powder to make it rain?
Something came out!
Just try to get past five
of our ships, if you can!
Mr. 1 and Miss Double Finger.
You don't seem to know
anything about this country.
Sea Cat!
It's a sea monster!
Roronoa Zoro is in this city!
No. I just landed here by boat.
Mr. 2 doesn't have a partner, though.
He jumped!
It's the first meal in 4 days!
This land of Alabasta has always
been battling with drought.
F-Fire!
Mr. 3 is the candle man we
met in Little Garden, right?
It's a meal!
Shoot him into the ocean!
White Snake!
We're on the right track.
Drought?
Yes. He was paired up
with Miss Golden Week.
It's when it never rains
and the land dries up!
I hope we get there pretty soon...
I know that much!
Oh, that girl...
It's a meal!
So anyway, this land has
always been low on water.
Mr. 4 is paired up
with Miss Merry Christmas.
Straw Hat! Why did you
come to this kingdom?!
What are you after?!
Whoa! It backed away!
And rain's been especially
scarce these past few years.
I don't know much about
these two, either.
What am I after? I'm here to
beat up a guy named Crocodile!
Fire Fist!
Have the ship go back! Go back!
W-W-W-W-W-We can't!
That's really something!
And that snot guy!
Most oases have dried up now!
Mr. 5, right?
What?! Crocodile?!
Snot?
Ah! Don't let it get away!
Capture it without fail!
Yeah. His snot is a bomb.
Huh? Then just use the mystery powder!
How are you and Crocodile connected?!
Mr. 5's entire body is a weapon.
Exactly! But the World Government
has outlawed Dance Powder!
Miss Valentine has the powers
of the Kilo Kilo Fruit.
He disappeared!
How should I cook you, cat monster?!
Bastard thinks he's crafty!
They'll execute you if
they catch you using it!
It's that woman who can change
her weight freely, right?
No!
From Mr. 1 through Mr. 5,
they're called officer agents.
It's also said to be what
started this country's rebellion.
Vivi! You jerk! What're you doing?!
Really?
They all have the powers of a devil fruit.
--I don't know much myself, though.
--Oh.
Straw Hat!
W... Why... Vivi-chan?
And they work only on
really important missions.
Where could Luffy-san have gone?
Whoa!
You can't eat it!
For Mr. 6 through Mr. 13, their job
is fund raising for the company
Sea Cats are a
sacred animal in Alabasta!
Geez! He's always such
a high-maintenance captain!
Oh! Was your dream to use that
mystery powder to save this country?
by leading the employees at
the entrance of the Grand Line.
You should've told us sooner!
Oh! Nami-san!
There sure are many kinds
of creatures in the sea!
Hey, now! This is bad!
Huh?!
You said it was important powder earlier.
Come to think of it, there was
a strange monkey and chicken.
It feels like we'll be in big trouble
if we don't get moving quick!
Being scared of things like that...
You've still got a long way to go...
No, uhh, that wasn't quite
what I had in mind...
Big trouble?
Captain Smoker!
They're Mr. 13 and Miss Friday.
Okay then!
The Navy is here.
I'll tell you a story about when I
bravely fought Sea Kings in the Calm Belt.
What, then?
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew
are nowhere to be found.
The Navy?!
Well, I thought I could
make a bunch of money
They're a punishment squad.
And a strange man!
Let's just find Luffy as quickly
as possible and leave town!
Their main job is to punish
those who fail missions.
by selling water in these hard times...
What do you think, Tashigi?
Fought Sea Kings?!
Yeah, you could! You're smart!
Big ones! They were this big!
Other than these people,
Hey! Hide!
Vivi was with them.
--What for?!
--What is it?!
there're 200 subordinates called
"Billions" under the officer agents,
But, whatever. That has
nothing to do with me.
O... Our food got away...
Vivi? Princess Nefertari Vivi
was with the Straw Hats?
and 1800 subordinates called
"Millions" under the frontier agents.
Guess I'll keep looking
for a food place again.
Get back here!
The Navy!
But don't worry. You'll be
able to stuff yourself soon.
U-Umm! Please, don't
tell anyone about this!
There seems to be a big commotion!
She must be a hostage.
This is the secret crime
syndicate, Baroque Works.
Don't let him escape! After him!
They abducted the princess
for some sort of scheme...
Really?! What cat will appear this time?!
I won't. I don't care.
That means... 1800 plus 200, so...
Some idiot pirate must be
running around town or something.
I beg you! I'll give you whatever I can!
Vivi! The wind and weather
seem to be becoming stable.
No. Vivi was acting like
she was part of the crew.
There're 2000 subordinates?!
--For reals?!
--For real! For real!
2000!
Idiot pirate?!
Yes.
All right! I understand it very well now!
We've entered Alabasta's climate area.
The princess? Part of their crew?
Get back here, Straw Hat!
Oh! Thanks for this lunch, old guy!
In any case, all we have to do
is beat up that Crocodile, right?
A Sea Cat appearing is also the proof.
Something really is
happening in this country.
It's you?!
Not at all! I hope it's to your liking!
And what we see behind us...
I'm sure you don't get it at all!
It's more than enough! Later, old guy!
Heya! Zoro!
Captain Smoker!
If Baroque Works' last big job
is to take over Alabasta...
is probably also proof
of Alabasta being close...
I'm sorry, sir!
Please remember not to tell anyone!
Oh! Is that where you guys are?!
Mr. 11 was done in by someone
while he was tied up on the ship!
the rest of those "officer agents" will all
You idiot! Go get rid of them first!
Don't worry! Don't worry!
There's the Straw Hat crew! Over there!
I couldn't turn you in,
even if I wanted to!
We still haven't located
the Straw Hats, either!
gather in Alabasta.
So, what should we do now?!
No need to fret. I have a good
idea of where they're headed.
Huh?
--We have to run, obviously!
--Hurry! To the ship!
Yes...
After all, I'm a pirate!
There're so many ships!
When did that happen?!
What're you doing?! Let's get back!
I see... Then, in any case,
we'll beat that Crocodile guy...
He's after Crocodile.
See ya! Thanks for the food!
Hey...! They all have
the Baroque Works' symbol!
Hey, you!
Crocodile?! One of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
--Stop!
--Don't let them escape!
That's enough.
You keep your mouth shut!
Fall back!
Oh, yeah?
That isn't fair!
Captain!
Un, deux, ora! Un, deux, krah!
Its employees have started gathering...
Wow!
the pirates given government approval?!
Straw Hat is mine!
This is wonderful!
You know I hate the Seven Warlords.
Yikes! Yikes! Here he comes!
They're probably Billions...
the Officer Agents' subordinates.
I love these kinds of clothes!
White Blow!
Especially that detestable man.
I-I'm sorry, Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
I know I asked you to
shop for us Sanji-san,
Uh oh!
B-But standpoint-wise,
he's a Navy and government ally!
Which means that our
enemy is at least 200...
There's no escape!
but aren't these outfits
for dancer girls?
Gimme a break!
Who do you think I am?
On top of that, they are the
200 elites of Baroque Works...
Heat Haze!
Come, now! It looks marvelous on you!
He's always been a clever pirate.
They're far from those bounty
hunters in Whisky Peak.
--I asked for commoner clothing...
--Dancers are commoners, too!
He's never been the type to just
quietly obey the government!
I'm Bon Clay-sama,
a Baroque Works' officer agent,
--But we're going to cross a desert...
--Don't worry!
who's so fearful that even a
crying child will become quiet.
Should we fire at them while we can?!
Tashigi! All you need
to remember is one thing!
If you get tired, I'll carry you!
Hey, you! You navigator, over there!
A pirate is a pirate,
no matter where he goes!
Let's get on it already!
Y-Yes sir!
There's no getting through to him...
It's quicker if we go
there and beat them up!
Just tell me! What's 0-chan's order?!
But, compared to them,
you two clearly look like bandits.
Straw Hat will show
up wherever Crocodile is!
No, wait! We have to eat first!
You, huh?
Kill Mr. 3 on the direct route
between Alabasta and Little Garden.
Give it up.
Idiot! Don't bother. They're small fries.
Things should become
clear if we go there.
How're you any different?!
Chopper! What're you doing?
He's right.
And next time, you won't
get away, Straw Hat!
So you do know what it is.
If we lose our real target, that'll be it.
You may be smoke, but I'm fire.
The smell is killing me...
--That reminds me, where did you go?
--Various places!
--Woohoo!
--Ace is one of us now!
There're only 8 of us.
A fight between your power
and mine would never end.
Direct route means going
in a straight line, right?
--Is he not feeling good?
--Oh, the perfume's gotten to him.
Cheers!
He had Devil Fruit powers?!
That's why we traveled straight from
Alabasta to this Little Garden, right?
Who said I was joining you?
Perfume?
Who is he, anyways?!
Why is he helping us?!
Oh, right! Tony-kun
has a sensitive nose!
Here's to delicious drinks!
But then, what's going on?!
Anyway, tie it tight.
Ace?!
Cheers!
--Oh, this...
--Some of it can be rather strong.
Don't worry about it!
We got to Little Garden
without meeting Mr. 3!
Our enemy this time
has too many mysteries.
You haven't changed a bit, Luffy.
They're always looking
for an excuse to drink to!
Like this?
I see...
Ace?! Is that you, Ace?!
You ate a Devil Fruit?!
--Stop!
--Mellorine love into the abyss!
If we check this, we don't
have to doubt our friends.
Medicine is horrible!
Doesn't it mean that you
guys missed Mr. 3's ship?!
What are you, an idiot?
Yep! The Flare-Flare Fruit!
Does that Clone Clone Fruit guy really
become so similar when he transforms?
In any case, we've accomplished our
first goal of gathering supplies!
Captain Smoker!
We're securing the perimeter!
Ace! Are you sure you won't join us?
No... that can't be right...
Anyways, we can't chat like this!
I'll catch up! You guys run!
Then are you saying that
it was because I'm stupid?
You've no idea! It's not "similar."
It's "the same"!
Yes...
I'm chasing a certain man.
We're going to a place
called Yuba, was it?
I'll hold these guys off!
No... Mr. 2...
Shut up!
Yes, but first is a
trek through the desert.
--Go!
--Let's go!
It's too bad! You should've seen it.
We even danced with him.
His name's Blackbeard.
"Bon Clay"
Anyway, we can't be failing in the
"beating puny Mr. 3 mission"
Yeah!
Blackbeard?!
But, Luffy!
He's the pirate who
attacked the Drum Kingdom!
It will likely be much more difficult
than you imagine right now.
Who is that guy?!
I'm not interested in a male ballerina.
at an important time like this!
He used to be a member of the 2nd
Division of the Whitebeard Pirates,
We can't afford to fail.
Knowing someone like that
is among our enemy,
There's no telling what might happen.
one of my men.
If we did, Mr. 1 and his
partner will come to kill me.
we can't carelessly act alone.
But he committed the worst
possible sin on a pirate ship:
One wrong step in this burning land,
he killed a crewmember and jumped ship.
and there's no guarantee you'll survive.
Do you get that?!
Hey, what should I do?
I'm still a little uneasy and unsure
about taking you to such a place,
If you don't wanna be my prey,
then look for Mr. 3!
So, as the commander,
I gotta find and get rid of him.
Ahh... Do what you can do.
You don't have to do anything more.
I don't get it.
Why are you helping Straw Hat?
So that's why you're chasing after him?
but I want to return peace to this kingdom!
It's okay to run away from
the enemy you can't defeat!
Super full speed! We're heading
to Alabasta on the Swanda!
I came here because I caught word
that Blackbeard was seen in Yuba.
It's natural for a big brother to
worry about his bungling kid brother.
Aren't you telling that to yourself?
Now listen! Don't overlook
even a single small ship!
So I... So I ask you again!
What? Brother? You mean to say--?
What I can do, huh?
Yes sir!
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Everyone! Please lend me your help!
Got it!
Then your destination
is the same as ours!
I can see the island now!
What? Pirates are attacking
towns in the Kingdom?
Move, Portgas D. Ace!
Let's stop at the town called Nanohana.
We have to hide the ship.
I beg of you...
We've just entered the Sandora River.
You finally said it.
First, we'll land at Erumalu, then
head into the interior of Alabasta
Don't they know this
country has Crocodile?
All right! At any rate,
no matter what happens,
We've been waiting for it!
I'm afraid that's a no-can-do.
There's no telling what happens on
the sea, either. Right, Vivi-chan?
Who knows... Sir Crocodile...
this thing on our left arm is
the sign of our friendship!
to reach Yuba here!
Maybe a country where riots are going
on is an easy target for pirates...
The leader of the rebel army is in Yuba.
Yeah! It'll be no different from before!
I can't wait to see the desert!
I see. So you're headed to Yuba next.
Well then, we'll land!
Alright, guys! Whadya say
we get going to Yuba now?!
I'll follow Nami-san and
Vivi-chan wherever they go!
Wait, Luffy! Who is he?!
To a restaurant! Oh, and to Alabasta.
Are you going?
Get lost, Love Cook.
Yeah!
Sure. I have to do a good job
for my public position, too.
Is he an acquaintance of yours?!
It's a side note?
Say what, you--?!
Yeah!
A-Anyways! It looks like we can
travel together for a short while!
Everyone...
How kind of you...
The enemy this time is an
assassination gang, Luffy.
He's my brother!
Yeah, yeah! His brother
is more than welcome here!
Yeah, it is.
Don't we seem to be missing someone?
Of course.
Be careful about acting
on instinct, okay?
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
are pirates who crush other pirates.
Let's have a fun time, Ace!
Luffy!
You're right. I got it.
Yeah! That's right! Yeah!
Yeah!
We're heroes to people.
This won't be enough at all!
Got it!
That moron!
Brother?!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
I continue on to the ends of emotion
From today forth,
something's going to change
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
no one knows about
Before dawn
Guys! This is my brother, Ace! Say hi!
Where in the world could Luffy have gone?
Hey, make something, you damn cook!
This is Erumalu?
Food! Food! Food!
--Huh? There's nothing here.
--Erumalu, the City of Green...
So this is Alabasta!
I can't because a certain idiot
ate all the food.
Uh oh! Hide! It's the Navy!
This sensible man can't
possibly be your brother!
It's a town full of life!
What's all the commotion?
Did something happen in town?!
The City of Green?!
There's no green anywhere!
What a useless cook...
It's... quite hot...
I would've expected him to
be as reckless as Luffy!
Huh?! Looking for trouble, you bastard?!
Some idiot pirate must
be running around town.
It was a thriving city
until just recently...
The town still seems peaceful.
He's a nice guy who
cares about his brother!
Shut up, you two!
When will the riot actually occur...?
This was?
It's your fault!
Heya, guys!
Karoo. I have an important
favor to ask of you.
Brothers can be so wonderful!
It's you?!
Look! We can now see the island!
We have to stop it, right, Vivi-chan?
Yikes! It's that copycat girl!
Crap! I'm outta here!
All right! We'll land then!
And eat! Oh, and Alabasta!
--Yes.
--Food!
The sea is just full of surprises.
I want you to go to Alubarna!
Come now, everyone!
On the next episode of One Piece!
It's a side note?!
"The Heroes' Reunion!
His Name is Fire Fist Ace!"
"Off to the Desert Kingdom! The Rain-
Summoning Powder and the Rebel Army"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ace and Luffy!
Hot Emotions and Brotherly Bonds"
"Erumalu, the City of Green,
and the Kung Fu Dugongs!"
"Alabasta's Hero and
a Ballerina on the Ship."
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!