One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
In order to take down Emperor of the Sea
Kaido who reigns over the Land of Wano,
Luffy stole a treasure ship with a store of food
from Speed,
"We came from the Land of Wano of 20 years ago."
Shutenmaru, the chief of the Atamayama Thieves Brigade,
made his way to Okobore Town...
Luffy and the others
decided to launch a raid!
Where are they?
TREASURE
and took it to Okobore Town.
Luffy and the others have been told
the shocking truth.
...to take away the food
that Luffy delivered to its people.
Will they be able to avenge the late Oden
and open up the Land of Wano?
Those shitty brats...
What Kin'emon told them next...
Jack from the Animal Kingdom Pirates
also appeared on the scene
So the only ones he's coming after are...
The plan is set for Onigashima
on the night of the Fire Festival.
...was the delightful and wild story of
Kozuki Oden, Momonosuke's father...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
and they undertook a punishing battle.
...me and Straw Hat-ya!
Kaido is coming after us, right?!
...and the tragedy of the Kozuki Clan.
Don't mess with samurai!
Then, I'll stop him!
You've got to be kidding!
Then, appearing suddenly from the sky was...
It's water!
They're hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle!
What a sneaky piece of shit! Orochi!
It's non-poisonous! Help yourself!
Hey, Jack.
Blast Breath!
Kin'emon and the others crossed through time
by the power of Kozuki Toki, Momonosuke's mother,
Yes, sir...
It's been years since we've had
this much drinking water!
That brings back memories...
It is indeed a good place to hide.
and gazed upon the hardly-recognizable Land of Wano.
Bring those brats...
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
...here now...
So that's where they are...
I thought no one would fight together with us.
Everyone's so happy!
A dragon?! What's that?!
But that was not true.
They took SMILE away from me.
Things can't get any worse...
LAW AND STRAW HAT'S PIRATE ALLIANCE
Those hateful punks!
Even after 20 years,
I'm Luffytaro!
Tell them that in case someone asks you!
That's...
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
there are still people who admire Oden-sama
and want to help the Kozuki Clan!
Then, everyone who assembled at
the ruins of Oden Castle...
I won't let them get away!
...Kaido!
Ow, ow, ow...
...were told about a raid operation by Kin'emon.
--We're in trouble, Nami-san...
--What?
ODEN
"Everyone is Annihilated!
Kaido's Furious Blast Breath!"
Our targets are Emperor of the Sea Kaido
and the hateful Shogun - Kurozumi Orochi!
Blast Breath!
"Bringing Down the Emperor of the Sea!
A Secret Raid Operation Begins!"
The execution date is two weeks from now!
On the night of the Fire Festival!
We will make a raid...
...on Onigashima where Kaido lives!
"Finally Clashing!
The Ferocious Luffy vs. Kaido!"
"The Strongest Man in the World!
Shutenmaru, the Thieves Brigade Chief!"
You're okay!
You somehow got away!
Right, guys?!
Horselina!
The Wano people's...
Why are you here?!
...loyalty to Oden-sama...
KOZUKI ODEN
Where's Tama?!
You took her home, right?!
...hasn't disappeared completely!
Is that...
...Kaido?!
Answer, Horselina!
On our way, we were spotted by Kaido-sama...
Kaido is a dragon?!
We were in despair about
how the Land of Wano was changed
...and I fought...
Yes...
and wandered about this tainted land...
...but I couldn't protect...
We thought that the Land of Wano
had no future...
...Master-sama...!
What you see right there is Kaido!
Kaido!
Hi!
I'm here!
It's been a while!
ODEN
Kaido can...
I'm sorry but have we met before?
What?! You've got to be kidding!
...transform himself into a dragon!
You are...
It's too late...
You haven't forgotten about me,
have you?!
Luffy.
Father...
The man who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
The Land of Wano has been ruined by
Orochi and Kaido!
We played together like every day
when we were kids!
Guys, go back to the mountain without me!
Luffy...?!
Oh... Yeah... I remember...
Shutenmaru-sama!
Did you say Luffy?!
I-It's been a while...
I have a bad feeling.
Yeah, we bumped into each other here for a reason!
Let's have a drink sometime!
He's crazy...
We're here with you! So don't worry!
O-Okay...
"Destructive!
One Shot, One Kill - Thunder Bagua!"
Bye!
What?
It was finished in a flash.
Not long enough for him to sober up...
Who is that guy?
Gum-Gum...
When did I get this?
Momonosuke-sama!
BAKURA TOWN
He's not coming this way!
We feel the same as you!
He didn't come to execute me...
Elephant Gatling!
But as a head of the Kozuki Clan...
Th... This is...
you need to stay strong!
OKOBORE TOWN
But... those who would fight side by side with us...
...are all...
How's everything with you?
Is it going well?
...gone...
Even so...
Yeah, if things go well,
I'm gonna be summoned by Orochi soon.
we cannot give up!
Where are they?
Oh, that'll be nice!
Straw Hat-ya!
Franosuke, have you obtained
the blueprints of Kaido's mansion?
Those shitty brats...
No, not yet.
That master carpenter is kind of tricky...
Otsuru-san!
You'd better run now!
Straw Hat-ya!
What's up with you?
Right...
I handed the flyer to
a guy who had the mark of the moon today!
While doing so, I got good news.
Kozuki Momonosuke-sama...
--Good...
--...News?
It's the name of the one said to be
the strongest man in the world alive today...
Who are you?!
What?
Who is that?
Please step back.
Are you Kurozumi Orochi's man?!
The chief of the Atamayama Thieves Brigade...
Shutenmaru!
Kaido-sama!
Okobore Town is around there!
Oh, no!
Mm-hm.
Now, why did Kaido come to Kuri
all of a sudden?
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
Kaido!
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
No way...
To tell you the truth, Straw Hat-ya,
Zoro-ya, and I were identified by them...
You are Kozuki Momonosuke-sama,
What?!
Hey, Kin'emon,
I understood your plan.
aren't you?
But that's all they know!
They don't know about the plan!
But there is one thing
that I couldn't quite get.
Mother!
"That's all they know"?!
Damn! My house...! My house!
What the hell are you doing, Law?!
You look just like you did 20 years ago...
I know! It's not easy to understand...
Father!
...a mature woman's attractiveness!
Toki-sama's last words were true!
You Straw Hats don't have
the right to blame me!
A-A mature woman's attractiveness...
Oh, I'm sure it was Luffy's fault.
Yes, I might be... too young to...
understand that...
Let me just say, I'm sorry.
I used to be a retainer from Kibi...
My name is Jibuemon!
That's okay, young man!
Someday you'll get it.
Nami-san...
Anyway, back to what we were talking about...
Seems like our captain caused you trouble.
Sorry...
For 20 years...
I've been waiting for you.
You said that Oden brought down Ashura Doji
20 years ago...
I believed what your mother Toki-sama said and...
He's probably...
Mm-hm...
Then why is he among the allies
that you want us to find?
Gear Three!
...looking for me and Straw Hat-ya...
...waited for this day!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates led by Kaido...
Mother's... last words...
There are three particular samurai
that I want you to look for!
...need two key things
to maintain their overwhelming forces.
If we can find them,
they will be a tremendous help!
--Tell them to me!
--Yes, my lord!
This is what she said.
Kawamatsu.
First, the weapons that Kaido is
getting people to manufacture in this country!
Ashura Doji.
Denjiro.
"You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
YOU ARE THE MOON UNAWARE OF THE DAWN
They are samurai who used to serve Oden-sama
like us!
Second, the backdoor trade of
the artificial Devil Fruits called SMILEs...
May your purpose be fulfilled
MAY YOUR PURPOSE BE FULFILLED
...which Caesar and Doflamingo were creating!
That's a legitimate question...
and cast nine shadows on the night woven of 20 years
20 YEARS
THE NIGHT
Ashura Doji mended his ways
after being defeated by Oden-sama,
NINE SHADOWS
We destroyed that at its root
which was the factory in Punk Hazard...
Kaido!
and you shall know the brilliance of the dawn"!
and pledged his loyalty to him...
...and captured Caesar
who was necessary for SMILE development.
Toki-sama's last words were suggesting
the Kozuki Clan's revenge 20 years later.
But...
We heard that now under the name Shutenmaru,
he became the chief of the Atamayama Thieves Brigade,
We thought that it was impossible,
On top of that,
and is doing wrong again.
we destroyed the factory...
but as if it supported the possibility,
none of you Akazaya Nine's bodies...
Hmmm, a thieves brigade, huh?
...in Dressrosa where
Doflamingo, Kaido's important trade partner, ruled.
By the way...
...were found.
And we also helped Doflamingo, the buyer,
get locked up and brought him to ruin...
is he strong?
Yes, perhaps, it is not too much to say
that he is the strongest of all samurai.
Mother...
Gum-Gum...
In short,
If by any remote chance...
all of you would appear 20 years later
we picked a fight with Kaido.
As an ally,
no one is more reliable than him.
So the only ones he's coming after are...
I see.
and take command of us
to bring down Orochi,
...me and Straw Hat-ya!
Then we definitely need him to be our ally...
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
we wanted to be ready
to fight along with you...
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy, wait!
So those who are determined to fight...
...Elephant Gun!
Luffy-dono!
You're right!
Don't chase! I'll go!
No matter where they are
or what they are doing...
OKOBORE TOWN
If more of us get exposed,
they'll find out that all the members of
the Straw Hats and the Heart Pirates are here!
Giant Stamp!
They are waiting
with the mark of a moon on their ankles!
They'll start a big hunt!
What?!
W... What?!
So think rationally.
Even after 20 years, we still have allies?!
They're only seen us so far.
I can't believe this!
How many men are there?!
Oh, please!
I thought I could finally eat as much as I want...
We don't know exactly...
I'll send you flying, Kaido!
But there are many of those who have been
waiting for this moment all over the Land of Wano!
Your plan is still safe!
All right?
To take down Kaido,
Then, what are you two going to do?!
we need to have as many allies as possible.
Gum-Gum...
TEN (HEAVEN)
I wish I could let things be...
Could you go and recruit
like-minded people throughout the Land of Wano?
...Grizzly...
But Straw Hat-ya has already gotten involved
with the people of this country.
...Magnum!
SHUTENMARU
CHIEF OF THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE
Kaido-san!
But you have to do it... without being seen.
Yes, sir!
We will devote all our efforts to it!
Kaido-sama is falling from the sky!
If he lets his emotions take the lead,
it'll spell trouble for the plan.
Hello!
Do it!
With that,
If all of us aren't there on the execution day,
the alliance is pointless.
we could keep our hope alive thinking that
there might still be a future for the Land of Wano.
These fools have quite good stuff!
SAKE
Give them back to us!
Luffytaro-san gave...
We asked Kiku to investigate the enemies
I'll take care of it.
Luffytaro-san gave them to us!
Room...
and me, Kanjuro, Raizo, and Momonosuke-sama -
the four of us...
Shut up!
Supreme Commander Kaido...
Who's that?!
Mother!
Oh! He's the guy who beat Yokozuna Urashima
and Holdem-sama!
Oh? There's even fruit, sake, and rice!
How impudent!
Don't show yourselves at any cost!
...set out on a journey to recruit allies.
Give them back to us!
I want my grandson to have them!
Shambles!
Even leaving this country is a crime.
Captain!
Shut up, old man!
Drop dead already...
So as soon as someone spotted us,
they gave chase.
On top of that,
since we didn't know how to sail,
Damn Luffy...
What did he do while we were apart?
we tried to reach Zou
but we were shipwrecked in no time.
You're in my way, old bag!
Do you wanna die?!
The ship was smashed up
and we got separated from Raizo!
Kiku!
Tsk!
Where are you, Kiku?!
See you in Zou!
I'm here!
Who the hell...
Raizo!
I'm here, Kin-sama!
...did something like this?
We were washed ashore at Dressrosa
within an inch of death,
Giving people food and acting like a hero?!
Kiku! Are you all right?!
Retreat to the forest,
Atamayama Thieves Brigade!
but were chased by Doflamingo
who was connected to Kaido
It was just a brief dream for you...
Yes.
We don't wanna get involved with him!
You finally got food,
and got separated from Momonosuke-sama
who boarded an unknown ship by mistake!
But...
but it's gonna be taken away by us
and that's it.
There are no samurai
who will stand up for you poor people!
Momonosuke-sama!
Straw Hat-ya!
That's enough! Come back!
And I got separated from Kanjuro
while pursuing Momonosuke-sama!
Also, there is no real man left
in this country,
Come to your senses!
Don't worry about me!
Oden Castle!
who can lead tough samurai!
Kanjuro!
Kaido!
The Land of Wano is finished!
Momonosuke-sama!
Just like that, we fell apart
after we left the Land of Wano...
Hey, old hag... Even if you live much longer,
Please wait!
Why?! I must hurry to make sure
he is all right!
I kept hearing that...
Even at Punk Hazard where I made it to,
looking for Momonosuke-sama,
all you'll ever see is a cruel reality.
...there is a mighty thief
living deep in the mountains of Kuri.
If something happens to him...!
I feel the same way!
Caesar stood in my way as Kaido's puppet.
Shutenmaru.
But don't you have something else
to worry about now?!
Plus, I was chopped up
by Law-dono who is now my ally...
Let me put you out of your misery!
I...
Tsuru...
...remember you...
He can wake up and rampage again
at any moment!
And I was in deep trouble...
Please run!
Grandma!
If that happens, even Okobore Town will...
That's when I met you guys!
I see.
I am going to go to Okobore Town.
I believe in Otoki-sama's words...
Kiku, take care of Momonosuke-sama!
How cool is that!
Of course!
She's already dead.
Who are you?
Kaido!
The dragon just talked!
I'm sure the nine samurai will...
How obscene!
All you have is a breast-band!
...fulfill Oden-sama's wish!
But let's forget about the past!
Oh, you don't like it?
How silly!
They can't fight a war without a leader!
No, I love it!
If you bend your knee to me...
You can't eat me!
You're okay!
You somehow got away!
If you try to eat me, I'll eat you first!
Behave yourself!
Right, guys?!
Speed-sama!
Stay with us! What happened?!
Looking back, it was crisis after crisis,
Shutenmaru-sama! That's...
I'll wipe the slate clean between us.
I thought she went out of town!
She's just fallen from Kaido-sama's body!
but I met good people.
I was able to find dependable allies
who I can trust with my life, and I came back.
Gear Four!
Orochi's forces mentioned our name,
Bounce-Man!
but they do not really believe this is happening
and that is good for us!
They think of us merely as ghosts.
I finally got to meet you...
That is why we have not even been placed
on the wanted list yet
How dare you...
Whoa! Smells like alcohol!
...mess with my friends, you bastard!
The head of a thieves brigade...
and they have not noticed that
we reentered the country.
Kaido-san, don't tell me you're drunk!
JACK - A LEAD PERFORMER, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
A-A-A-A monster!
I did not know, either,
even though we are on the same side.
I know a pirate named Straw Hat Luffy
came around here...
Idiot! I'm not drunk!
Well... I am sorry about that!
He's drunk!
Hey, get a room already!
Speed-sama! Speed-sama!
Gum-Gum...
Who the hell are you?!
In this battle, it is important to keep
our presence from Kaido and the others...
Hey, it's you, Horselina!
If I say "I don't know," will your attitude change?
...Kong Gun!
Horselina!
What are you gonna do, Shutenmaru?
...an absolute secret.
Speed-sama!
Don't push your luck...
We can't get away! Let's just fight him!
You're...
Huh?!
We are keeping you alive...
Okay! I got it!
Why are you here?!
...only because Kaido-san wants to
have you as his subordinate.
Where's Tama?!
You took her home, right?!
Jack-sama! I'm trying to stop the bleeding
so don't move!
We are up against huge armies led by
Kaido and Kurozumi Orochi!
I don't have to pay you any respect!
He's so drunk.
He could lose his temper at any minute.
Answer, Horselina!
On the other hand, we have...
On our way, we were spotted by Kaido-sama...
We'd better leave here soon, too...
The Straw Hats led by Luffy-dono.
Right. But...
Then, I'm gonna tell you...
...and I fought...
The Heart Pirates led by Law-dono.
...the residents of Okobore Town
are a valuable work force in the factories!
...but I couldn't protect...
The Mink Tribe - Dogstorm's Musketeers
and Cat Viper's Guardians.
My answer to that request is...
It's nice just setting an example,
...Master-sama...!
but if he wreaks havoc senselessly,
...just this!
And samurai with rebellious minds
who we are recruiting now.
they'll all get wiped out along with Kuri...
It is ideal to have five thousand people!
But we are not looking to have a war...
What's the matter?
I am...
I am going to go to Okobore Town, too!
We want to secretly collect information on our enemies,
Kaido and the others, and prepare a plan...
No, you cannot, Kiku!
If you get identified, too,
the plan will be all screwed up!
Well, the fact is...
...to behead...
Kin-sama, I did not tell you
but that's where...
Where are you going, Speed?!
...their leaders!
...Otsuru-san lives...
What?!
Horselina-chan!
Gum-Gum...
Why didn't you tell me that sooner, Kiku?!
I am sorry, Kin-sama!
Oh, Kaido-sama...
He's drinking too much again...
Why don't you go back?!
I will save Tsuru!
...Double Culverin!
I wonder what'll happen
if he gets drunk this time...
No, I am responsible, too!
It's scary even to think about it!
Prepare a plan...
I cannot believe she did not get remarried to
someone who would protect her!
I want more sake! Bring some more!
Gum-Gum...
...to behead...
...their leaders!
It has already been 20 years
since I left her!
Y-Yes, sir!
It's a secret mission!
Alright!
I am on my way, Tsuru!
S-Sorry to keep you waiting!
...Kong Organ Gun!
That'll be our decisive battle!
The battle will take place...
Damn! It's still so far away!
...on an island called Onigashima...
Straw Hat-ya!
...where Kaido and the Animal Kingdom Pirates
have their base!
Tra-guy!
You think the people of Okobore Town are okay?!
An island?!
Idiot! You see?
When a pirate does a good thing,
Even within the Land of Wano,
we have to cross the sea?
Oh, it's unacceptable... Everything that's been going on...
this is what happens!
That's right!
Kaido is coming after us, right?!
I received a strange report...
Isn't it?!
Since it's very close, practically visible from the shore,
we don't need a big sailing ship,
Yeah, oh, well, I mean...
Yeah!
Then, I'll stop him!
but we still need a ship.
Oh, yeah...
Bring them to me...
To raid Onigashima...
Th-Them?
Well, let's think about the ship later.
Can't you even tell who I'm talking about?!
When should we do it?
We should do it on the day of the Fire Festival.
The Fire Festival is a grand festival
for the people of the capital.
Kaido is believed to be a deity
who protects the country,
and on that day, Orochi will lead the Shogun procession
to visit and worship the deity.
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
Don't mess with samurai!
But that is merely a pretense!
What will really take place is
the banquet of officials...
This is the greatest day of my life!
Supreme Commander Kaido!
...and the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
Isn't he..
I see...
...one of the Headliners?
Jack-sama!
So we'll beat the hell out of
those partying drunken fools
Supreme Commander! If you're looking for
Straw Hat Luffy and Trafalgar Law...
Damn you...
It's an apple!
and behead their leaders!
Tama...
But...!
they're hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle!
Okiku-chan, if you see me doing it heroically,
you might fall for me instead of that dirty samurai!
I'm paying you back for feeding me.
I'll never forget...
Oden Castle?
No, no, Sanji-dono,
I think you got the wrong idea!
I'll never forget the taste
of the sweet red-bean soup
I have a wife and Okiku is just a comrade
so we are not in such a relationship...
and the apple that I had today
for the rest of my life!
Hawkins!
See you again!
Otsuru-san was doing well.
Is it true that Straw Hat and Law
are hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle?!
Did you see her?!
Yeah, without being noticed.
No... I lied to him
in order to stop him from rampaging...
I see...
If she's okay, that's good...
Until I accomplish our big goal,
I can't see her...
But that's not all.
Damn!
These days,
maybe because of that particular legend,
Kin-sama...
I should've...
Hey, you're a married man!
Don't win her heart! It's not fair!
some people are saying that they've seen
suspicious lights at the top of the mountain...
...escorted her!
Okiku-chan! Please be nice to me!
Legend?
Get back!
Shutenmaru and Jack-sama...
Straw Hat-ya!
Shut up...
Is that the one that says the Kozuki samurai
who we exterminated will come back for revenge?
Sanji, Kiku is unbelievably strong!
What are you doing?! Let's run!
...Got into a fight!
Since he's so gigantic,
he probably doesn't know what's happened!
We're doomed!
She's not just lovely but also strong?
Yes, instead of letting it incite
Shogun Orochi's terror,
It's not too late yet.
Perfect...
He got Tama.
Who is that guy?
we can kill two birds with one stone
by wiping out that abandoned castle.
Kin'emon and the others...
Now, I drew a symbol
implying the date and the rendezvous point of the battle.
...and your crew and mine...
Two birds on fire and...
We don't know if they're alright!
...a Habu (pit viper) and...
If I kick his ass now,
...a Reversed Crescent Moon
which signifies rebellion!
it's all over, right?
So huge...
Are we trying to fight him?!
"On the day of the Fire Festival.
Twilight - the second hour of the bird.
At Habu Port."
I'm afraid for my life...
Kaido!
"The second hour of the bird"
means 5:30 PM to 6 PM on clocks overseas.
I'm here!
But I'm already dead!
My soul left the body before I knew it!
Don't worry. People who live in the Land of Wano
will understand.
Stop laughing! Don't surprise me!
I wonder if Captain's doing alright...
We must go round and give these flyers to those who have
the mark of the moon on their left ankles immediately!
The mark of the moon is the symbol of rebellion.
They are our allies!
We do not know where they are
in the Land of Wano...
Oden Castle, you said?!
But in order to distribute to
as many people as possible,
Ever since he died, I...
our friends spread out all over the country.
You are...
I was looking for a way to die...
Zorojuro-dono and Usohachi-dono
are carrying out this task in the capital, too.
That brings back memories...
It is indeed a good place to hide.
Luffy.
The man who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Oh, I bet Zoro is not helping at all.
So that's where they are...
But...
Luffy...?!
...getting killed by an underling like you
is not it!
Did you say Luffy?!
Furthermore, in order not to get lost
after arriving at Onigashima,
They took SMILE away from me.
Cut the crap!
we are trying to obtain the blueprints of Kaido's mansion
from the carpenter who designed it.
LAW AND STRAW HAT'S PIRATE ALLIANCE
Those hateful punks!
So we are making Franosuke-dono
work for him.
I won't let them get away!
As for Orobi-dono, we want to know
the exact moves Orochi's forces make,
I...
He's heading towards the
ruins of Oden Castle!
so I asked her to pose as a geisha
and try to approach Orochi while entertaining him!
...should have died!
Blast Breath!
I heard she's very popular now.
I wanna see Robin-chan in her geisha costume!
And now, I want to
delegate tasks to you all, too.
Gum-Gum...
Brook-dono's ability will help getting food
in the capital.
Living is such a pain in the ass...
What? Are you sure?
...King Kong Gun!
Nami-dono's skill to manipulate weather is like ninjutsu.
So pose as a kunoichi!
That's a female ninja, right?!
Thunder Bagua!
A kunoichi - Onami!
Nami-san... a kunoichi?!
Oh?
What Sanji-dono cooks will gather people together in a second
so it will help finding people!
Hey! Isn't he coming towards us?!
So you've come...
...to the Land of Wano!
No way!
Gear Three!
Sanji-dono?
Yeah, I'll do it!
Don't tell me he's noticed that we're here!
What about me?
Carrot-dono and Chopper-dono,
I want you to go and see Dogstorm along with Kiku.
What?!
No!
It's impossible to see us from there!
Kin'emon! I wanna be a ninja, too!
All right!
No...
I will provide clothes
that are suited for each of you!
He's coming!
So put a leaf on your head and get ready!
Get away, guys!
Are you ready?!
Here it goes!
This is my magical power!
Garb-Garb Jutsu!
Poof!
Why is he heading that way?!
J-Jack-sama!
Nami-san!
L-Look... The sky!
Ninja!
Baron Corpse, what is that on your head?
No way... Why?
I don't know...
What's this?!
He came in person... for what?
He did it!
Now...!
You changed into the Land-of-Wano-style clothes
so I want you to work on your tasks.
Now he screwed up everything!
I-Is it because of me? Is it?
Wait, Kin'emon!
Did he come to execute me?!
Is this really a kunoichi outfit?!
That fool!
That's how kunoichi...
I should grab him and run!
Why, all of a sudden...
Is it gonna rain?
...should look!
Are you lying?!
No!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya! Come here now!
I think I have enough stamina for that...
Don't tell me!
Now, I'm going to summon a guide.
Room!
What's wrong, Tra-guy?
She is a real kunoichi.
What the?!
A real kunoichi!
Shamble...!
That's a big treat!
I lost my energy...!
Shinobu!
Oh, no! That's...!
Don't do it, Trafalgar.
It's you again! Not now!
What?!
Ow, ow, ow...
The Sea Prism Stone used across the world
originated in the Land of Wano.
Did you call me?!
--We're in trouble, Nami-san...
--What?
This is totally wrong!
I've never seen this kind of change
in the weather before!
What?!
It's a Sea Prism Stone... nail?!
I won't...
Only the Land of Wano has artisans
who can refine it into something that small.
...lose hope...
Oh, no! He's shaking with shock!
Thank you... You saved me!
It's unforgivable...
Kin'emon! Is this your taste?
Straw Sword!
Kunoichi are either sexy or frumpy.
There are only two kinds of them...
I swear, I'll make you pay!
Run, everyone!
Momonosuke-sama!
Blast Breath!
What?! Momonosuke-sama turned into...
Damn! This is the worst...
If I tighten it up, it should be fine...
...A-A dragon?!
Brook, what are you disguised as?
I will explain to you later,
but his body can now change like this!
Room!
A person who wears panties on his head.
Shambles!
Of all things...
That's what I thought but I was wrong!
the figure of a hateful Dragon!
What an annoying ability...
I see!
Being young...
He can't go that far.
We're in trouble, Straw Hat-ya.
...isn't too bad...
He must be around. Look for him!
My name is Shinobu!
SHINOBU - A VETERAN KUNOICHI
Yes, sir!
I used to be like a younger sister to Kin-sama.
Captain!
But now...
My signature move is Seduction Jutsu...
Move! Out of my way!
Nice to meet you.
I can't believe this.
He's still breathing.
If it weren't for Nami-san,
my spirit would've been broken...
No, Sanji!
I bet so.
Gum-Gum...
I understand, young man...
What?
No way...
I don't know whether it's out of his
indomitable spirit or bravado...
Mature women are...
Why...?
...like deadly weapons...
but he's glaring at me.
I'll never forget the taste
of the sweet red-bean soup
Alright!
Until the rendezvous,
we will split up,
and the apple that I had today
for the rest of my life!
Hey, Jack.
but there are three particular samurai
that I want you to look for!
Yes, sir...
If we can find them,
they will be a tremendous help!
Bring those brats...
To me, he just looks unconscious...
Elephant Gatling!
Kawamatsu.
...here now...
Ashura Doji.
Denjiro.
They are samurai who used to serve Oden-sama
like us!
A dragon?! What's that?!
Let's go! All of our allies assembled here!
Things can't get any worse...
That's...
Our targets are Emperor of the Sea Kaido
and the hateful Shogun - Kurozumi Orochi!
...Kaido!
Kaido?!
What kind of king did you say you'd be?
I didn't expect he'd pop up like that!
The execution date is two weeks from now!
On the night of the Fire Festival!
To put it frankly, we're in danger!
You little punk!
We will make a raid...
Momonosuke-sama, get ahold of yourself!
...on Onigashima where Kaido lives!
So that's...
...Kaido!
Kaido!
Oden Castle has been wiped out in an instant.
Jack who appears in the town looking for Luffy,
and Shutenmaru clash!
Kaido ravages the Land of Wano with his overwhelming power!
In order to stop him, Luffy starts running!
Taken down by Kaido, Luffy is sent to a
mine where hellish forced labor awaits him!
Luffy mounts ferocious attacks on the
invincible Kaido at a breathless speed!
It is unknown whether
everyone is dead or alive!
After learning even Otama has been attacked,
Luffy reaches the breaking point
The Land of Wano is in chaos
with everyone having different agendas!
Is the moment he finally takes down an
Emperor of the Sea just around the corner?!
However, mercilessly,
Kaido's blow of anger strikes the ruins of Oden Castle.
However, he unexpectedly
reunites with someone there!
and makes a mad dash for Kaido!
While the evenly-matched fierce fight carries on,
with a peal of thunder, Kaido shows up tearing open the sky!
However, Kaido's anger which is strong
enough to shake the sky strikes Luffy!
With the memories of his friends in mind,
Luffy's all-out attack blasts!
Are Otama and the Straw Hats alive?!
Luffy stands by helplessly!
Will the Straw Hats be safe?!
He reveals his true appearance and
shakes up Luffy and the others!
And what will happen to the desperate Luffy?!
A blistering battle in which
neither side gives an inch starts!
What will happen to Luffy
who gives it all he has?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Living Hell! Luffy, Humiliated in the Great Mine!"
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Strongest Man
in the World! Shutenmaru, the Thieves Brigade Chief!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone is Annihilated! Kaido's Furious Blast Breath!"
"Destructive! One Shot, One Kill - Thunder Bagua!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally Clashing! The Ferocious Luffy vs. Kaido!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!