One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Luffy and Kaido finally clashed!
Devastated by Kaido's reign, the people of
Luffy goes down before the overwhelmingly
powerful Emperor of the Sea, Kaido.
Nami and Shinobu who obtained
information on their enemies
the Land of Wano have no choice
but to live in poverty.
LAND OF WANO - ACT TWO
The Land of Wano Arc - Act Two now begins!
were discovered and chased by them,
but they successfully escaped.
Luffy and the others developed a raid operation
in order to open up the country.
Meanwhile, Luffy who has been held captive
by Kaido's subordinates...
Gum-Gum...
Lock him up!
The execution date is two weeks from now!
On the night of the Fire Festival!
Oh, y-yes, sir!
...was forced to work at the Excavation Labor Camp in Udon
along with Kid.
Once his spirit gets broken,
we can make him fight for us!
We will make a raid...
...King Kong Gun!
You ate all of my food!
...on Onigashima where Kaido lives!
Okiku!
You are all safe!
However, soon after planning,
Luffy clashed with Kaido.
After being defeated by Kaido,
Luffy got caught
Now, it's time for punishment!
Thunder Bagua!
Anyway, the situation is...
and at the Excavation Labor
Camp in the Udon region,
Oh, yeah!
What happened to Luffy?!
he was forced to do heavy labor.
Gum-Gum...
He looked like he wanted to
pick a fight with Kaido!
I won't give in!
Prepare yourselves and listen...
...Kong Organ Gun!
Wait for me, Kaido!
Special report! Special report!
And his friends started
preparing for the raid.
Oh! Luffy!
What kind of king did you say you'd be?
Oh, Luffy!
Lu...
WANTED FLYER - LUFFYTARO
You little punk!
Thunder Bagua!
Meanwhile, Nami snuck into a residence
with a kunoichi Shinobu
to spy on the enemies.
"A Living Hell!
Luffy, Humiliated in the Great Mine!"
What are you doing, Luffy?!
This is the order sheet for arms and weapons.
"A Great Sensation!
Sanji's Special Soba!"
Somebody's there!
Get them, get them!
Alright, stay in here!
It's the Special Soba!
Sangoro's Special Soba!
There are suspicious figures!
There are intruders in the building!
I'll get even with you...
Oh, no!
Kaido...
Sangoro's Special Soba!
Luffy suffered a terrible defeat
and was taken to a prison in the Udon region.
I want to eat it now!
"The Holyland in Tumult!
Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard Cackles!"
Meanwhile, the injured Otama
was transported to Amigasa Village,
Shinobu-chan!
then, Kin'emon and Dogstorm's group
headed to Atamayama...
Here! Thank you for waiting!
"Rampage!
The Prisoners - Luffy and Kid!"
Oh, it looks good!
...to recruit Shutenmaru.
Lock him up!
Who are they?!
Oh, y-yes, sir!
Once his spirit gets broken,
we can make him fight for us!
LAND OF WANO - ACT TWO
Go up in the attic, too!
Y-Yes, sir!
Catch them at any cost!
Don't even print "pirate" in the broadsheets.
This is Gloom Island in the Grand Line,
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
Calm down, Shinobu-chan!
It's good! It's insanely good!
Yes, sir!
I don't want the foolish citizens of this country
becoming curious about the world outside even a bit.
You're not getting away!
Roronoa Zoro of the Straw Hats
once trained himself here.
Any information on Luffy?
He's in the Excavation
Labor Camp in Udon, right?
--Yes, sir!
--Let's take him!
Train me as a swordsman!
It's far from here.
But I bet he'll make it out of there before the big day.
Hey, guys! Hold his feet!
Be quiet!
What are you doing?
That's just embarrassing.
Yes, sir!
The Worst Generation...
Screw them.
Where did they go?!
I wanna get stronger!
I get to eat Sanji's cooking again!
I'm glad that you came back safely!
ATAMAYAMA, KURI, LAND OF WANO
He's weak as hell!
I don't understand.
You still see me as an enemy.
Oh, is it just a cat?
He's covered with blood!
How disgusting...
Then why are you bowing to me
and asking for my guidance?
I don't care if you like it or not...
--Let's just drag him.
--Yeah.
What's the purpose?
Orobi-chan! How does it taste?
I wanna beat you!
Well, it tastes amazing!
Orobi-chan the geisha is more amazing!
In the old castle near the
lake of this fallen country,
Well...
The soba is good
but it's only attracting girls...
that certain man still lives.
Draw in samurai
with something spicy that would go with sake!
He is a member of the
A WARLORD OF THE SEA
STRONGEST SWORDSMAN IN THE WORLD
Seven Warlords of the Sea and is said to
be the strongest swordsman in the world.
What's with that look?!
Don't you wanna recruit more allies, you fool?!
His name is Dracule Mihawk.
DRACULE MIHAWK
Where did they go?!
A woman crashed into his residence
two years ago.
"It's On!
The Special Operation to Bring Down Kaido!"
Wait, Franky! Male customers.
So you use it, too...
A member of the Thriller Bark Pirates.
Little punk!
Hello!
GHOST PRINCESS PERONA
Excuse us, ladies!
Ghost Princess Perona.
What's the matter with you, Shinobu-chan?!
No way!
Hey! Don't cut in, guys!
That's Oden-sama's technique!
Huh?! What did you say?!
Shut your mouth!
Are you okay?
It's ready!
Was he able to do it despite being unconscious?!
They're the Kyoshiro Family...
Onami...
What?!
There is something I haven't told you...
Who the hell is that brat?!
What?
Hey, outta our way!
Do you want it?
No.
Find them! Catch them!
What?! You're so annoying!
Your place is thriving, young man!
Don't let the intruders get away!
Kid uses the Color of the Supreme King, too!
--Get rid of these ghosts.
--Hmph! No way!
Yeah, I'm pleased!
I took the trouble to cook it!
I'll eat it all myself!
We don't need that many...
Are you guys customers?
If you wanna eat, get in line!
...Supreme Kings!
I...
Today's newspaper?
No, we came to ask you...
...have a fear of sharp objects!
...who permits you to do business
on this land?
Moria-sama...
We're the Kyoshiro Family
and this is our turf...
You're not cut out for any kind of fight!
Unless you pay us, you're not
allowed to run a shop here!
I'll get Trafalgar next time.
KAKU-SAN, KUNI-SAN, SUKE-SAN
KYOSHIRO FAMILY
But Onami...
Let's go back to drinking.
He's... alive...
Oh, is that so?
A mature woman...
...is as deadly as...
Those people... Maybe they're...
Oh, I'm totally sober now.
"Gecko Moria and his zombie
army made a raid"...
...a weapon.
Do you know something about them?
I went to a man named Kyoshiro's banquet hall
the other day...
He's alive!
Moria-sama is alive! He is!
Orochi-sama is a coward!
Look at this! It's so great!
Moria-sama is alive!
He's as strong as Dogstorm-sama!
He's giving Dogstorm-sama a tough time...
How impressive.
Yeah, I read it this morning.
Booze! Bring me more booze!
Why didn't you tell me, you fool?!
It's very important to me!
Let's catch this wind.
Why, Ashura?
Why don't you want to use...
He was quite an arrogant samurai...
It appears he's the boss of a yakuza group.
I don't care...
What?
You should! He's my captain!
...that tremendous power
for the Kuri people that Oden-sama used to love?!
I thought he died in the
Paramount War two years ago!
Ninpo: Great Kite!
And they're probably his underlings.
GREAT KITE
I'm really glad!
Hey, can't you hear me?!
I said you gotta pay up!
If Moria-sama is alive,
maybe both Absalom and Hogback
are with him!
NIN
Why?
Why? Because we can't help you
even if someone comes to attack your shop.
He's dead!
I wanna see him! Let's get going!
A Sea Prism Stone nail?!
Why did you guys come back here
after all these years?!
Shinobu-chan! This is awesome!
I don't need your help
because I'm strong.
I've never heard of it before!
We came back to accomplish Oden-sama's dream!
Haven't you found them yet?!
Gee...
But you-gara have forgotten
what happened to Oden-sama,
Here, thank you for waiting!
Captain!
Thanks!
Oh, yeah...
What did you see in the residence, Onami?
and are just wielding your
sword at your own whim!
I wonder if Bepo and the others are okay.
He let me stay here for quite a long time.
Um...
Shut up!
Oh! I saw the name of the port
and the shipment day!
Good job!
While I was facing the Straw
Hats in Thriller Bark,
Now we know when and where
they're stockpiling their arms!
Hawkins-sama!
I was suddenly sent flying here
by Bartholomew Kuma.
Did you find Trafalgar?
Let's steal them!
You said you're strong?
Don't talk as if you know everything!
Well, we looked all over
but he's nowhere to be found!
Uh-huh!
It's already been more than two years.
Then, try to protect the shop!
Moria is a persistent guy.
Just like the zombies he manipulates.
If there is something you want to say...
Say it!
I guess he's already left town...
Soba!
Hey!
Don't eat soba from this place!
Cuff him!
Huh? Did you speak ill of Moria-sama?!
Yes, sir!
You thankless jerk!
I owe him nothing.
You owe me!
Smells good! I'll have some.
How many times do you
think I cooked for you?!
Foxfire Style - Fire-Willow Flash
Me, too!
Catching Straw Hat alone is enough for now...
Yes! Thank you!
I cooked more than you.
Is she crying or laughing?
I helped you with farming, too!
But I'll run down Trafalgar Law, too, at any cost!
Oh? Something is going on in the town.
Soba!
I let you stay here.
What's that line for?
I won't let him get away!
You're really annoying!
Is it a sale?!
Guys...
There are so many young girls.
Fine!
OKOBORE TOWN
That's enough...
Welcome! Welcome!
Oh, no! That pisses Sanji off the most!
Gorobei-san!
Hey, stay with us!
Dogstorm!
Ashura!
Go home, you fools!
The shop is closing for today!
I'm leaving!
I will treat you now.
Do whatever you like.
Come on and try it, ladies!
Go, go! He ran out of soba!
There are no hard feelings so that's good.
I think that voice belongs to...
That voice... It must be...
I want to apologize...
Come on! Just go away now!
I thought you were better
than this, Ashura-san!
Be careful on your way.
I want to say sorry to Luffytaro-san...
Kiku!
It's sweet when it melts in the mouth.
He took the trouble to bring us food
but it went to waste...
I've watched the Land of Wano
for two decades since Oden-sama died!
Don't, Sanji!
Don't make any trouble!
It sure is al dente!
Do not pay that any mind.
You guys suddenly came back
shouting whatever you like.
I hope he does not feel responsible for
this town being attacked.
Oh, no! We'd better move!
Sangoro's...
...nihachi soba!
Too kind!
I won't listen!
Hey!
SANGORO'S NIHACHI SOBA
Damn you! Don't say a nice thing
all of a sudden!
Since he is a kind man...
San, go, ni, hachi!
What do you want, you fool?!
3 5 2 8
You should be thankful
that I don't rob you blind before I go!
The sum is 18!
I need you to finish your food.
Still beautiful after 20 years!
You have not changed a bit.
Don't you remember?!
My dear customer...
NUMBER 18 (OHAKO)
Huh?! Do you wanna fight, you jerk?!
This is how we were even back then!
OHAKO (SPECIAL) SOBA
But I can only see you again
once I accomplish Oden-sama's dream!
Thank you for everything!
Hey! Suke! Kaku!
I was fascinated by that man, Kozuki Oden,
It's my Special Soba!
Yes!
You're such a noisy woman.
The noodles are glimmering!
Let's beat him up!
Forgive me for being such a selfish husband!
and would risk my life for him as a samurai!
Slightly chewy!
But...
Hm?! A fight?!
It's delicious!
...it's perhaps a good
decision to leave here now.
There's no samurai!
But I've never become a
servant for the Kozuki Clan!
Go to hell!
What?
Thank you!
In the Reverie that's still
in session at Marijoa,
Right?
You bastard!
Momonosuke!
a strange topic was brought up.
Is that...
I'll take one, too!
...Ashura Doji!
Yes, thanks!
He doesn't look familiar...
Ow, ow, ow...
But it's really popular.
Don't you remember what kind of man I was?!
That squirt...
I-It's...
Does he know who's turf he muscled in on?!
None of them can be alive...
I won't give up!
We've got to teach him...
Damn!
I'll make you join us!
Die!
Don't assume that everyone will
be thrilled to see the return
Meanwhile, this is the
Pirate Island of Fullalead.
of the Kozuki Clan's samurai!
Strike the iron!
It's a paradise for pirates.
A massive hole?!
You guys abandoned the country for 20 years!
Everyone! Are you okay?!
Haul the stone!
Everyone!
There is no way to compensate
for all those years!
Okiku!
Ow, ow, ow...
Big Bro!
Don't tell me...
If you can't work,
why don't you at least die
What?! That soba guy is so strong!
Are you okay?
and get out of the way?!
So cool! The soba man!
Yes...
Help us!
A big sinkhole opened up!
Let's go.
Sanji! Let me in!
Okiku-chan!
I am sorry to interrupt you.
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP AND WEAPONS FACTORY
UDON, LAND OF WANO
We managed to survive!
Raizo-san!
I was able to locate Luffy-dono.
--Hey!
--We're here!
Here we go!
Thank goodness!
Stop! Dammit!
What are you gonna do to me?!
He is in the Excavation Labor Camp at Udon.
You are all safe!
I thought so!
Then, can I count on you to handle that?
The sinkhole saved us but...
Franosuke Iron...
Understood!
We're falling!
Everyone!
I-Is this it?
...Suplex!
By hauling five big blocks of rock,
you get one millet dumpling!
Oh dear!
Hold on tight!
You got too old to earn your own food,
Old Man Hyo?!
Thank you!
Otama! Are you awake?!
You saved me!
You're finally close to death!
--That carpenter is also...
--But they shouldn't do that!
Master-sama... What happened to me?
I managed to rescue the ladies!
I worked all day and...
You were attacked by Kaido
and these people cared for you!
Why don't you help us, too?!
Huh?! What did you just say?!
We had a close shave!
Charge!
Oh, I see.
So at that time, you were all saved by
Shino-chan's technique!
Thank you!
Talking back to a guard...
I am grateful!
That's right!
It was only some light scrapes.
You'll get better soon!
...will be punished by dismemberment!
Now, eat! All of it!
At that moment...
Next!
Thanks!
Blast Breath!
The soba you wasted! Eat it all!
Old Man Hyo!
Don't fight. Save your energy!
--Here, eat it! Eat up everything!
--Big Bro! Big Bro!
I fainted from fear right away...
Or you're gonna die!
What? Would you like some?!
so I don't quite remember
how I got attacked...
D... D...
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu!
Don't you forget it!
Where's Absalom?!
Oh, four exchange tickets!
You'll regret this!
I only vaguely remember
how Horselina-chan fought desperately...
Well done!
Where did you hide him?!
Now, wake up, wake up!
Where would you like to go,
Master-sama?!
Guard Point!
CAPTAIN OF THE THRILLER BARK PIRATES
(A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA)
Move! Move! Move! Move! Move!
Thanks!
CAPTAIN OF THE THRILLER BARK PIRATES
(A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA)
BOUNTY: 320 MILLION BERRIES
An enemy became that loyal to you?
Outta my way!
Well, I knew it was gonna end up like this,
but was it okay to kick their asses?
GECKO MORIA
What an amazing power!
Where are Horselina-chan and Big Bro?!
Are they okay?!
You guys are in my way!
Do you wanna get run over?!
Maybe we shouldn't have messed with them...
We don't know what happened to Horselina...
Watch it, Jaggy!
There was a long line
but now, literally no one's here...
Why can't I kill them?!
I'll run you over, too!
Luffy was...
This is right about the
time some bad ass appears.
We survived!
Where's Absalom?!
My Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu can
make everything more mature!
I don't know!
She's the girl who had her soba knocked over.
What?!
Big Bro was pretty badly hurt...
She's a weirdo,
crying and laughing at the same time.
You underlings don't know a damn thing!
and taken to the camp in Udon?!
Yes! Everything Shino-chan touches rots!
Hm? Wait a sec...
What is it?
Where's Blackbeard?!
Oh, no!
I saw her before somewhere...
Rots...
Watch your mouth!
Hey, you're wounded!
Where's Teach?! Bring him out!
I'm more worried about Big Bro Luffy
than my wounds!
Anyway, the situation is...
Don't mess with us!
Oh, yeah!
Don't worry! Luffy is our captain!
What happened to Luffy?!
Didn't you hear what I said?!
He looked like he wanted to
pick a fight with Kaido!
Wait, wait! It's already full!
This is it for today!
All right!
I said, "Bring Teach out"!
I made a lot of money!
Udon is a region in the Land of Wano.
Teach! Where are you?!
I didn't think I'd sold so much!
Prepare yourselves and listen...
Then, bring out another ship!
However, these days,
it is mostly used for the Excavation Labor Camp.
You slowpokes!
Teach!
Teach! I know it's you!
I-I'm sorry!
What do you want?
UDON, LAND OF WANO
It's a dreadful place where serious offenders
will be forced to do
Hey, does that medicine heal
any kind of wound?
Where did you hide Absalom?!
What? Oh, yes!
heavy work until they die,
This will stop bleeding and pain!
and no one has ever made it out there.
How many stones did they haul?
Anything can be remedied with this toad oil!
I was counting up to 500...
--Huh?! What about the Sea Prism Stone?!
--They're wearing it.
That's wonderful!
I met her at the shrine.
Even weakened they can still pull that off?
Here he comes... Moria.
How strong will they be uncuffed?
How dare he do such a cruel thing!
I finished my work! Give me food!
She's still breathing!
I'm sorry to cause you trouble earlier...
Help her!
Yes, sir. People can see us here
so let's go into the forest!
What?!
There was still some soba left!
Please have some!
Whaaat?!
Here you go!
Every five big blocks of rock you haul
earns you one millet dumpling!
Whoa! Thank you!
Who could hurt a little child like this!
Where's Teach?!
Outta my way!
Tell me!
We won't tell you!
Brick Bat!
Damn Kaido!
That bastard...
It...
I-It's delicious!
Now...!
TOKO - A CHILD FROM THE CAPITAL
I'll teach him a lesson soon!
If you don't wanna die,
tell me where he is already!
Oh, yeah? That's good!
How much did they haul
to get that much food?!
--What's your problem?!
--What are you looking at?!
Is he there?
I made one more round-trip than you!
Come out!
I'll drag you down from there!
You fool! I outpaced you!
Screw you!
No, you didn't, Jaggy!
Blackbeard!
It's noisy-meow.
Can't you even count, you stupid monkey?!
You bastard!
It's Gecko Moria, Pizarro-sama!
Damn you!
The former Warlord of the Sea!
Oh, why did you let him in?
I thought they were both badly injured...
H-He broke in! With his zombie army!
They work, eat, and sleep...
After a few days, they're fully recovered.
It's good!
The port is fully destroyed!
Yum-yum!
What does he want?
It's really good!
CAPTAIN OF THE 4TH SHIP
OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
How do their bodies work?!
CAPTAIN OF THE 4TH SHIP OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
"CORRUPT KING" AVALO PIZARRO
It's delicious...
What can we do to break their spirits?!
Luffytaro's big fight in Kuri...
I'm impressed, Sanji...
He wants to see Commodore Teach!
Seeing you makes me smile!
I mean, Sangoro-kun.
Special report! Special report!
Seems like he's looking for the invisible man, Absalom,
who came here the other day!
Say something to them!
What?!
Oh, yeah?!
Well, that's because I put more love into it!
Special report! Special report!
Just for you, Orobi-chan!
WANTED FLYER
...Spread across the Land of Wano.
We have a problem!
Oh, him!
C-Chew well!
I don't know why but I'm happy!
Ghosts appear! "A curse on you"!
If you're not coming out,
Are you their mother?!
Oh, yeah! Listen!
I'm gonna break in!
Ghost sightings at the northern graveyard!
Here's an update!
The Special Soba really has a good reputation
so I wanted to eat it no matter what...
Moria-sama!
Hey, paperboy!
But I was stunned when I saw the big line!
Hm? Is this a broadsheet?
Can I get one?
I'm here!
Thank you!
Oh! Luffy!
There were way more people than
for the toad oil which works really well, right?
Is that Absalom?!
LUFFYTARO
So he's here in...
Boss! It's me!
WANTED - HITOKIRI KAMAZO
My dumplings...
"Hitokiri Kamazo"?
Yeah, there were!
"There are reports of a killing spree
at the eighth block of district two"!
Thank goodness! You're alive!
And I was in line for a long time
so I'm already late for work.
"The killer is Hitokiri Kamazo"...
I'm good as new!
After we went separate ways,
we didn't hear from you at all,
Work?
Dammit!
Do you work?!
WANTED FLYER - LUFFYTARO
Hippo!
Uh-huh! I worked hard
and managed to save enough money to buy the soba,
so we were worried about you!
I'm sorry, Boss! This island is a paradise!
You scared me...
but it was knocked over so I was sad!
Oh, Luffy!
Now I'm happy!
Because I was having so much fun,
I forgot to keep in touch!
So he's here in...
LUFFYTARO
This is the best soba I've ever had!
It's Dobon-sama!
This is unforgivable! Come out!
It's him!
Oh, yeah?! You like it that much?
Thanks!
Well if that's the reason, then that's okay!
TOAD OIL
Whoever did it!
DOBON - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
HIPPO SMILE FRUIT
But...
Anyway, what's your name?
Once you see him, you're likely to die!
How scary!
Special report!
I shouldn't have done that to them.
My name is Toko.
But say it with an "O" at the front!
TOKO
Lu...
LUFFYTARO
Zombies, that's enough!
"O"?
OTOKO
What is his true identity?!
O... toko-chan?
Go back to the ship!
OTOKO (MALE) ?
Oh! It's "Otoko"!
WANTED - HITOKIRI KAMAZO
My husband was killed by him, too!
I'm not otoko (male).
But my name is Otoko!
Which prisoner ate all
the food in the storage?!
Now, gather 'round! Gather 'round!
The Blackbeard Pirates are known for
hunting power-users!
The next is Ushimitsu Kozo
who appears at the witching hour!
I'm a girl but my name is Otoko!
It's Dobon-sama!
He's a cool thief who steals from
very rich people and gives money
That's right.
WASABI
Hippo!
Your Clear-Clear Fruit power that
enables you to become invisible.
Isn't it funny? Isn't it amusing?
to the poor living in row houses!
Perpetrator, come forward!
Is he a superhero or a villain?!
Otoko! Otoko! Otoko!
It burns!
What is his true identity?!
Help...
So many people desire that.
If you want to know, buy the broadsheet!
Oh! Old Man Hyo is trapped!
I know that, too...
Crawl out, Old Man!
Ah! Ushimitsu-sama!
...very well...
--I'll take one!
--Yes, thank you!
--Dobon-sama!
--The perpetrators are behind bars!
He's quite popular.
What?! What about the dumplings?!
Now, get your own!
Hmmm...
What the?!
People always say it's easy to remember!
They ate them all...
It's a broadsheet with some exclusives!
I can't believe a crazy guy like this
appeared in the Land of Wano.
You guys just stood there and watched?!
--I'll take one, too!
--Me, too!
They worked hard and got the
Uh-huh! Yeah! I'm sure I won't forget!
What are you reading?
Ouch! Damn!
proper amount of food in exchange,
so we couldn't say anything...
It burns!
That's a good name!
Oh, a samurai named Luffytaro
fought Kaido-sama...
Who is it?!
Yeah, it is!
Where are you?!
How could you ignore a vice warden...
So cool!
Whoa! That's disgusting, bro!
Don't spew out wasabi sushi!
The Reversed Crescent Moon!
Oh, it was delicious.
I can't really hear
because the hippo closed its mouth...
And you ate too much!
Can you pay for it all?!
Thank you!
Can it shut him up like that?
Okay! Come back again!
Who gave me this?
Let me see that!
Do you know who I am?
Uh-huh!
Hippo?
Oh, no! I'm really late! Very, very late!
It's unforgivable!
Shiryu... of the Rain!
LUFFYTARO
You worked at Impel Down
but defected to Teach!
Oh, yeah!
I'll be passing through this street later!
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Today, we have the Oiran's procession!
That's sort of right.
Dobon-sama...
Oiran?!
CAPTAIN OF THE 2ND SHIP
OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
Toko-chan, by any chance,
are you a Kamuro?
Bring the perpetrators here!
That's right. I'm a Kamuro!
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
It's already started!
I have to run! Bye-bye! See you!
Did you like my power?
The Oiran's beautiful
so please enjoy!
Beat, beat! Beat the iron flat!
You became invisible!
The harder and stronger the weapons we create,
the more the capital will flourish!
See you!
That power belongs to Absalom...
Oh, boy, she's so funny!
Your lives belong to Orochi-sama!
Dobon-sama! We brought them!
Toko-chan's cheerful. Very cute!
If you wanna live, beat the iron flat!
No way...
If you wanna rest, I'll kill you!
These are the perpetrators!
The much-talked-about Oiran's procession
will pass through here!
That's right, Gecko Moria.
Are they really back?!
AN INVISIBLE HUMAN WHO
ATE THE CLEAR-CLEAR FRUIT
Move faster!
Oiran?
OIRAN
Kamuro?
KAMURO
I got a useful power.
Udon, Land of Wano.
UDON, LAND OF WANO
Home to the weapon factories and mines...
An Oiran is...
Damn...
... in which prisoners are made to work in forced labor.
Dammit!
The Kozuki Clan!
Where did you emerge from,
you paper-lantern hag!
Ma'am!
They're stuffed!
Who did you call a wrinkled
paper-lantern hag?!
I've never seen someone
with a full belly here before!
Then, who the hell are you?!
Here you go! Poisonous Fish!
I'll illuminate your hide, you little snot!
Lucky them!
Hey... Isn't this the work of the ghosts?
What's in this cell anyway?
An Oiran is, in a sense, the top idol of the Land of Wano!
A superstar!
Suspicion won't help!
This will start a great fire!
I don't know... The only rules are...
You fools!
..."feed Poisonous Fish once a day"
and "remove the bones from the fish"
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Yip!
I'm going!
There is only one Oiran in the country now!
The chosen woman's name is Komurasaki!
Damn you!
I'm a big eater but there are
only three dumplings left for me
If this was 10 years ago,
I would have fought...
and that's all.
Devon!
That means it likes to eat Poisonous Fish?
A dream woman for men!
A role model for women!
because of you guys!
CAPTAIN OF THE 6TH SHIP OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
DOG-DOG FRUIT, MYTHICAL TYPE
"NINE-TAILED FOX" MODEL
Look at this mouth!
Do you think that's enough?!
Very sophisticated!
And her beauty could destabilize the country!
But what are you guys
going to do for weapons?
At first, they fed it Poisonous Fish
as a means of execution.
No way!
But whatever's in this cell keeps eating
the Poisonous Fish
In this country, if you aren't a samurai,
"CRESCENT MOON HUNTER" CATARINA DEVON
Wait a minute...
you can't even carry swords or other weapons.
and has carried on living up until now!
The gods themselves couldn't
sully her nobility!
Let me digest...
The kendo halls are all closed
That's who the Oiran, Komurasaki, is!
Is it a shark or a crocodile
or something like that?
Devon-sama!
and all martial arts like karate and judo
are prohibited.
Why do we have to kindly remove the bones?
It's a pain in the ass!
Who do you think I am?!
No way!
There's no such woman in the world!
Don't tell me Absalom is...
Orochi has already destroyed
rebellious elements!
If you don't believe me,
see for yourself!
That's because...
He shouldn't have come here
so recklessly!
Even if it's with my bare hands,
I wanna fight!
This will be our last chance!
I've been waiting for so long!
We still have his dead body.
Do you wanna take it home?
There! You hear that?!
The cheers for her
and the sound of exciting music.
I can't help
You like dead bodies, don't you?
...trembling with excitement!
HEINOUS CRIMINAL
What?
"Heinous criminal"?!
What?!
What?!!
That means we have the newcomer
that everyone's talking about!
What?!!
Damn you guys! I won't forgive you!
The Oiran is in procession to Orochi Castle!
What?!
Today, they have the Shogun's banquet
at the castle!
How dare you kill my friend!
The girl from earlier is a Kamuro,
a child attendant for an Oiran.
Welcome, Newcomer!
I'll turn you all into corpses!
I won't give in!
Hmmm, I see!
You have a lot of nerve!
Wait for me, Kaido!
Orobi, I have good news for you!
So I ran around the Flower Capital!
Oh, give it a try.
How do your bodies work?!
Don't think you can survive
after you messed with Kaido-sama!
Everyone eats, digests,
and takes a dump, right?!
For me?!
Congratulations!
Get ready!
I don't wanna see a prisoner
with such a satisfied look!
What?!
No, we don't need geisha.
You've been summoned to the castle, too!
LUFFYTARO
My...
Don't let anyone approach this room!
It's your desire to meet
Shogun Orochi-sama, right?!
...food!
Yes, sir!
Come on! Walk faster!
Yes!
Wow! That's our Robin-chan!
Hey! Don't push your luck, you fools!
Now, let's go home and get ready!
Listen carefully!
If you mess with the guards...!
Yes! I can't wait!
Hey, is he really the guy...
...who fought Kaido-sama in Kuri
and wreaked havoc on a town?!
The first offense, your arms will be cut off!
Onami.
What a kunoichi needs the
most is a calm heart.
I think so.
Keep that in mind.
For the second, your legs!
That little guy?!
Yeah, I thought he was at least going to be huge
like the Lead Performers!
And for the third...
you're sentenced to death!
Hey, say something!
Be careful!
He's right!
You guys have no right to fight back!
He's so weak!
Did this loser really challenge Kaido-sama?!
It's time to use...
No slacking off!
Hey... We're only weaklings
since our powers
Wait a minute, Onami. Don't rush.
UDON, WANO
Gecko Moria!
Hey, no taking a break!
Get up already!
have been drained by the Sea Prism Stone.
That voice...
I like how your youthfulness
gets ahead of you...
All we did was work hard.
But I want you to remember
and enjoy the fact...
Don't corrupt public morals
on this Pirate Island.
You guys should be punished because...
...that a mature woman's attractiveness alone
is a weapon.
Huh? How sharp his eyes are!
Screw you! Show yourself!
...you ate all of my food!
No way!
That's alright. I'll take time to torture you
so that your eyes will lose their luster!
I'm relaxing now.
Hey, straw hat guy!
You're really something!
Which family are you from?!
This is a paradise for pirates!
Son of a...!
It felt good yesterday!
All they talk about is you guys in every cell!
Jaggy!
It's gotta be fun!
What's wrong with him?!
He glared at us - prison guards!
Leave me alone...
You guys!
Don't say that.
Everyone here likes you so much!
Hippo!
Do you like to party?!
I'm gonna teach you what happens
when you defy us!
I will...
You are evil indeed...
Pfft! He's so unfriendly...
...discipline you!
Die!
Straw hat man!
Then...
Thank you very much for saving
my useless life yesterday!
Whoa! They got eaten!
come on board my ship!
OLD MAN HYO - A LONGTIME PRISONER
This is the order sheet for arms and weapons.
AN EMPEROR OF THE SEA
COMMODORE OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
BOUNTY: 2 BILLION 247 MILLION 600 THOUSAND
My neck!
You are evil indeed!
A fishbone came flying from the cell!
I had to beat him anyway
so don't mention it.
MARSHALL D. TEACH
Poor boys!
Idiot! Didn't you remove the bones
when you fed it?!
Oh, yeah. You can have these!
Huh? Am I?
Inside of the mouth is
Dobon-sama's slaughter room!
Ouch! My neck hurts!
Oh, this is a lot!
Is there going to be a war or something?
If you're hungry, you can't even work!
Oh, no! Please don't!
A good-for-nothing like me can't accept those!
What is it?! What's in this cell?!
We don't know what's happening abroad.
Moria!
Now, it's time for punishment!
No one knows!
You like to, don't you?!
We'll just make whatever they want.
Oh, come on, just keep them.
You are, oh, evil indeed!
To party!
Goodbye!
I-I'll use them wisely!
Huh? Am I?
Look closely, Onami.
My eyes are too aged.
Thank you! Thank you!
Alright, stay in here!
You'll be fine!
Just stay calm as you watch.
Thank you! Thank you!
Until your spirit gets broken
and you bend your knee to Kaido-sama!
What a funny guy!
That head is blocking my view...
Somebody's there!
--Prepare to be pushed around starting tomorrow!
--We'll give you a hard time!
Luffy-dono!
Who are you?!
Did you read today's newspaper?!
Raizo! How did it go?!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's never boring!
Um... The key to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs...
I found it, but, um...
--You're too loud, Shinobu-chan!
--Who are you?! Who are you?! Who are you?!
On the fourth day of the Reverie,
Alright then!
Just for today, rest up!
Be quiet!
It's under tight security.
the damn captains of the
Revolutionary Army...
In addition to a guard,
they keep it in a Sea Prism Stone box!
What happened?!
--Get them!
--There are intruders in the attic!
It's gonna be hell from tomorrow!
...finally appeared at the Sacred Marijoa
to take back Kuma
I've never seen the hippo go down like this!
Who are you?! Who are you?! Who are you?!
But...!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
and clashed with Navy Admirals -
Ryokugyu and Fujitora!
Please be quiet!
UGH...
Ugh...
URRGH...
Urrgh...
I'll steal it at any cost.
Please give me a little more time.
DAMN...
Damn...
Vice Warden Dobon?!
Meanwhile,
Okay! I got it!
Hey, Jack...
at the Land of Wano
where the monster Kaido lives...
The offerings from Kuri are too low.
All right!
Straw Hat who is much talked about lately
and some other hot-blooded punks gathered.
Now without Doflamingo around,
And chasing them is...
you know who our next business
partner is, don't you?!
...the crazy Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom!
I'm sorry, Big Brothers!
I'll get even with you...
I'LL GET EVEN WITH YOU...
KAIDO...
Kaido...
What do you think will happen?!
Look what you did!
Now you can't escape the death penalty!
We don't need another burden -
just this idiot Queen is enough.
That's right! Just this piece
of scum King is enough.
It's already begun.
Do you have any proof?
Hm?
HM?
What?!
In order to sit on the throne,
I said, "Do you have any proof?"
the tough ones are crushing each other!
Understood, Jack the Stooge?!
Oh...
OH...
You...!!
YOU...!!
And you, Queen!
Good job, guys!
You guys are the heroes of the prisoners!
Why is it taking so long to
break those brats' fighting spirits?!
You moron!
Shut up, you sadistic pervert!
LAND OF WANO ACT ONE - END
LAND OF WANO - ACT TWO
To take down Kaido,
the Straw Hats make another move!
The imprisoned Luffy and Kid!
The two rookies in fierce rivalry ferociously race around!
In front of the Straw Hats who
are on an undercover operation,
The turbulent Land of Wano - Act Two starts!
As the Straw Hats secretly
proceed with the preparations,
Sanji's soba shop gains a growing reputation and
becomes extremely popular!
Komurasaki, Wano's most beautiful woman and an Oiran,
walks through in procession.
Sangoro, who cooks at a soba
cart where his allies gather,
Meanwhile, at the Reverie, a major incident occurs!
and the kunoichi Onami
successfully play their parts
They stir things up in the camp
where there is supposed to be no hope or future!
When the Kyoshiro Family that comes to make an accusation
infuriates Sanji,
Her gorgeous appearance! That amorous look!
and the operation to take
down Kaido gets rolling!
The tumultuous New World.
Meanwhile, Luffy's indomitable
fighting spirit is raised up
However, behind the beauty, she
is hiding her true identity!
Luffy even fights against prison guards
and is sentenced to death in the end!
At the center of that whirlpool, the Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard
starts moving to become the King of the Pirates!
a melee between the Straw Hats and
the Kyoshiro Family blows up a storm in the capital!
A storm of flowers sweeps
through the Land of Wano!
even more and he creates
a furor along with Kid!
Will he be able to survive?!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Holyland in Tumult!
Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard Cackles!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"It's On! The Special Operation to Bring Down Kaido!"
"Rampage! The Prisoners - Luffy and Kid!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Great Sensation! Sanji's Special Soba!"
"Luxurious and Gorgeous!
Wano's Most Beautiful Woman - Komurasaki!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!