One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
In order to take down Emperor of the Sea Kaido
who is reigning over the Land of Wano,
Hey yeah!
Okay, here we are!
At the castle,
the Shogun Orochi's banquet has started.
Luffy is being forced to work at the Excavation Labor Camp
shackled with the Sea Prism Stone cuffs.
At the Flower Capital, Komurasaki the Oiran
was making her way to Orochi Castle,
Luffy and the others
determined to make a raid.
Everyone, the Fire Festival is coming up!
Hey! I'm back!
If you're hungry, you can't even work!
Will they be able to avenge the late Oden
and open up the country?!
to attend the Shogun's banquet.
Let's have a pre-party!
I-I'll use them wisely!
Her beauty captures people's hearts,
The date is set for the night of the Fire Festival
on Onigashima!
Thank you! Thank you!
however, in the shadows,
there are some who hold grudge against her.
So you have a little sister, Momo-kun?
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others who were trying to
recruit samurai for the upcoming battle...
In this country,
we call everyone's smiling face...
Yes, I have a little sister.
..."Ebisu gao," mister!
...faced the Kyoshiro Family.
To me, men are like dogs who bring me money.
If she is alive, she would be 26 now.
Don't eat soba from this place!
I hope you can see her.
Why not laugh, laugh?
Without it, you're worthless.
No, I won't see her!
Around the same time,
Big Mom and her children
I will only see her once we win the fight!
I... don't like...
What are those dolls?
were trying to reach the
shore of the Land of Wano.
Franosuke Iron...
...poor people.
They were close,
but due to the Lead Performer King's attack,
"A State of Emergency!
Big Mom Closes in!"
...Suplex!
Pone... gliff?
Big Mom was thrown into the sea.
I'm the one who'll take down Kaido
and win glory!
Hey yeah! Hey yeah! Hey yeah!
An Oiran is, in a sense, the top idol of the Land of Wano!
A superstar!
Dammit!
No, I am!
Hey yeah!
Okay, here we are!
Mama!
What?!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Hey! I'm back!
There is only one Oiran in the country now!
The chosen woman's name is Komurasaki!
"A Tale of Chivalry!
Zoro and Tonoyasu's Little Trip!"
EBISU TOWN
A dream woman for men!
A role model for women!
It's an emergency.
Hide somewhere, Black-Leg-ya.
So this is like an "Okobore Town"
of the Flower Capital...
Very sophisticated!
And her beauty could destabilize the country!
--If they come back, I'll beat them again.
--That's not it.
Meanwhile, at the Flower Capital,
Page One was rampaging
looking for Sanji.
Yasu-san!
Some guys who know our faces
are on their way!
Oh, you're back, Tonoyasu!
Sangoro!
Yasu-san, now you're back
but we still don't have any food!
The strongest six among the Headliners
are called the Tobi Roppo...
Maybe it's no use.
"Luxurious and Gorgeous!
Wano's Most Beautiful Woman - Komurasaki!"
--And two among them...
--Two?
If he's a coward, he'll never show himself!
I'm so hungry!
I'm starving to death!
One is Page One from the Tobi Roppo!
They're using trickery!
Our top priority should be on running!
Dice in.
Sanji!
Now, place your bets!
How...
Evens!
How come they're so cheerful?
The other one is X. Drake
from the Tobi Roppo.
We've got a bet on even numbers!
Anyone for odds?!
...could I do that?!
Wow!
Odds!
We've also got a bet on odds!
Now, place yours!
Mister, you're quick to notice!
Everyone looks joyful, right?!
Why do we have to do this?
Odds!
Stop! We have nothing to do with him, either!
It's slightly different
from Okobore Town in Kuri.
Then, call out for him!
Komurasaki the top Oiran is in procession!
Evens!
Everybody!
Amongst all the species,
only humans can laugh!
For Sangoro the soba cook!
Oh, Komurasaki-sama!
Last call, everyone!
Look this way, Oiran!
Yeah!
KOMURASAKI
"The Capital in an Uproar!
Another Assassin Targets Sanji!"
Here we go!
If that's true, why not laugh, laugh?
I'm...
...here!
Five and one, it's evens.
Why not laugh, laugh?
Diable Jambe!
Ah! Oiran!
Concasser Crush!
Why not laugh, laugh?
Wow!
People often say that
it all depends on the roll of the dice...
Oiran! So beautiful!
Pardon us!
But you're special, mister!
You're lucky and on a winning streak!
Stop it!
If Drake and Hawkins come, it'll be all over!
Everyone, the Fire Festival is coming up!
Whoa! Komurasaki-sama!
There.
Let's have a pre-party!
He doesn't know who I really am.
So no one will find it out
and I won't get hurt!
Orochi-sama!
That's for the sushi.
Thanks for paying for it on the boat.
I can beat this fool in an instant.
Oh! She's dazzling!
Wow! This is more than I paid, mister!
Too dazzling to lay eyes on!
Don't worry. I'll win more.
Guys, move ahead!
Don't be reserved! Raise your heads!
Man!
What?
Destroy everything!
We just stopped by
to take shelter from the rain!
Now, what's for dinner tonight?
She really came! That old bag!
It's fine as long as...
If I stay with you, I'll never go hungry!
Yes! It's all ready!
Fire away!
Let her be swallowed by the sea so we're rid of her!
All right!
You're the coolest man in the Land of Wano!
...I keep my identity secret, right?
Bring it here!
Oh!
"Dashing!
The Righteous Soba Mask!"
We slaughtered the chickens
we bred in the beautiful environs of Orochi Farm,
I think the sake will taste good tonight.
I'm sorry I'm late!
Zoro went missing?!
and boiled them lightly...
No! I don't feel like chicken!
NIN
Eat and drink as much as you want!
Yes, sir! We'll discard them!
The soba cook really showed up?!
Take it away!
Is he stupid?! Does he wanna die?!
Hey! Toko!
Next!
Come on! He always does that!
Fresh delicious vegetables...
--I don't want them!
--Yes, sir!
You made me worry.
Haven't you seen him in the Flower Capital?
We'll throw them out!
Next!
No, I haven't!
Big Sis, I'm sorry!
We've got nice and fatty saury.
Now, get to work.
They broke through the third defense line!
Okay!
SOME DESERTED VILLAGE, KURI
I like saury!
And tuna sashimi!
Focus fire!
Oiran! Ah! Look this way!
He is as free as the clouds.
Yeah! Tuna is the best! Tuna!
This is the perfect time to transform.
Drink more!
And we have a variety of selected sake
from across the Land of Wano...
I guess it's not so bad to be unconventional...
What's that? Is it a can of something?
I got it!
Yes, you should have a variety of sake!
I will just trust everyone and wait here!
Eat more!
But how about women?
He should've forgotten about the town.
This is the Land of Wano!
Of course, we've got women!
What is he gonna do?!
Good! Good!
I think that's Germa's...
Komurasaki...
If you come, I'll kill you, Linlin!
Mom, I'm hungry!
If I get to eat yummy stuff,
guarding the food storage isn't so bad.
Even I put this on,
I won't allow myself to become like Germa!
Me, too!
Zeus! You should come back to me!
You're right!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
UDON, LAND OF WANO
Guys, don't push it too far.
I'll at least try it on!
My tooth fell out
from a lack of nourishment!
Wait for me, Straw Hat!
If you don't start,
I'm gonna attack you!
You have no food to chew with it anyway!
Soba cook!
It's fine now. They left.
We're about to fight an Emperor of the Sea...
Now, Tonoyasu, who is this ronin?
Carrot, don't just take carrots...
Perhaps my stubbornness will
get in the way of saving someone.
One, two, three.
Why?! These carrots are
sweet and delicious!
He has three swords belted on!
Maybe I can save someone
if I swallow my pride...
You're right! Three swords!
Stop talking gibberish!
And they're all long swords!
Okay, so we could sneak inside pretty easily
thanks to your hole-digging skills...
Are you trying to be funny?!
It's you again!
Whoa-whoa! I admire this gentleman!
If this thing gives me that much power!
You work so hard.
Mister!
Oh, no! I feel bad for you
for having some strange guy follow you around!
Okay, I guess we got enough.
Just how many dumplings
are you trying to earn, mister?
Here I go!
Let's go back!
No, I'm the world's greatest sycophant!
I'm not gonna give you any!
Not yet! You still have an important task.
Luffy-dono.
Raizo!
Cut it out! Caribou!
At one point, he was worried about my voice
because I talked a lot.
That's too loud!
Don't be so mean... We're friends.
Something wrong?
Oh, yeah!
"Shut up."
No, I have good news.
WET-HAIRED CARIBOU
CAPTAIN OF THE CARIBOU PIRATES
BOUNTY: 210 MILLION BERRIES
--Leave it where it can easily be found.
--Okay!
That's what this kind gentleman said to me!
Wet-Haired Caribou of the Caribou Pirates.
Otama is better.
This ill-famed atrocious pirate and Luffy...
Right, you stud?!
"The Atamayama Thieves Brigade was here.
Oh! She is?!
...met in the Sabaody Archipelago.
I see! But look at him.
He has a scary look!
Shutenmaru."
While attempting to take down the Straw Hats,
Great...
Gee, young man.
Don't look so scary...
So Tama is fine now...
he raided the Sunny on her way to the Fish-Man Island
but failed!
Thank you for letting me know!
Do you think the beautiful Oiran is a good excuse
for coming to work late, Kid Fra?!
After arriving at the Fish-Man Island,
he carried on doing evil,
Smile like this!
No, Boss!
Something good has happened
even to this trashy Ebisu Town!
I'm sorry!
but he was defeated by Luffy and Pekoms.
You mean that man came to town?!
What are you doing?
Well, but I couldn't believe
there was such a pretty woman!
Okay, I'll come back again.
You just changed in the air?
Yeah.
Later, he reached the New World
and tried to worm his way through everything.
Ya-hoo!
Yes, Ushimitsu Kozo came to town again!
Black-Leg-ya...
I know how you feel!
Oh, he transformed?! It's just super!
Cool! How did it work?!
That's great!
He discovered a new way of life there.
But it could've affected my honor, you fool!
Uhimihu?
Wait. I know that costume from somewhere...
They broke through the seventh defense line!
Yeah, he always comes by
when we're in trouble!
But he was defeated by Drake
who appeared unexpectedly.
Everyone at the final defense line,
get ready to fire!
MINATOMO
A LEGENDARY MASTER CARPENTER
WHO BUILT KAIDO'S MANSION
But we don't even know who he is...
He was sent to the Land of Wano
Yes! I'm so sorry!
Stop them at any cost!
and was forced to work as a prisoner
at the Excavation Labor Camp in Udon.
Oh, yeah... But...
I wasn't going to bring dishonor
to the name of Minatomo, the legendary master carpenter!
He appears at the witching hour,
Napoleon!
...why does he have that suit?!
and steals money
from rich, evil people in the capital...
Without doubt, it belongs to
the enemy of Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
Since you work 10 times more than anyone else though,
MONEY BOX
Mister!
I don't mind if you ditch work sometimes.
Give me some, too!
If you show me the blueprints of the mansion on Onigashima,
I'll work 10 times more...
The No.3 member of the evil army, Germa 66!
Millet dumplings for the needy!
He leaves the money
at poor tenements and disappears.
Fire!
Stealth Black!
No way! Work!
I mean, even 100 times more!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
I wonder who he is.
That's too cruel!
Hey, why do you know so much?!
Thank goodness, thank goodness!
The image has been cut off!
These Sea Stone Prism cuffs...
Oh, yeah.
Of course I do!
Everyone from the North Blue knows!
Switch to a different camera already!
About the blueprints of the mansion on Onigashima
that you've asked me for repeatedly...
I heard they made them less powerful
so that prisoners could work.
Fortune comes in by a merry gate!
Whatever!
So we bought a treat together!
Listen! Don't ever call me Germa!
Understood?!
Jeez...
But I'm quite paralyzed...
Those... Um...
Push yourself harder!
Oh! What kind of treat?!
I was a legitimate fan
who supported Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
What?!
You're so harsh, mister.
It's this!
You see?
I hated Germa, those despicable villains.
They broke through the final defense line
and are now climbing up the falls!
Oh, this is just a wipe...
This is it!
If you give me dumplings,
I'll be your henchman.
SORA, WARRIOR OF THE SEA
Please have a cup!
Oh, please!
I've been here way longer than you,
Whaaat?!
You should have some, too!
I hated them, too!
About those...
so I know more things than you do, you know.
Hey, you!
It's clear water!
You're not an ordinary soba cook...
Mister, you'll do it, right?
We bought it with the gift of money!
I remembered...
Identify yourself!
Go!
I pawned them about 10 years ago!
I... am...
No, I shouldn't...
Shut up!
Those fish are climbing up the falls!
Don't worry!
You're a member of Germa 66...
Stealth Black...
It's unbelievable... Lick.
You're gonna do the jailbreak thing, right?
This water is clean,
so you won't have a stomachache!
Dammit! What are you doing, you idiots?!
--Come on, tell me!
--Go away!
Yasu-san brought you here,
so you must be a good man!
Don't let them set foot on the island!
I... am...
But we have no troops
at the top of the falls!
I beg you!
A member of Germa 66!
Don't touch me!
I am...
Take me with you!
And they're all extremely strong!
Identifying himself is a big moment for a hero!
Come on, Sangoro!
What do you think I've worked under you
week after week for?!
Don't be shy!
We don't have time to bring out weapons
that could take them down!
Go ahead and drink!
Everyone has the right to have some!
A soba cook beat you?
Problems hearing, soba cook?
Let me repeat myself.
Ouch! Damn you, stop it, Kid Fra!
Don't get panicky...
SAKYO, FLOWER CAPITAL
That's right! He was quite strong!
Delicious water!
Identify yourself!
Clear water!
Kaido-sama!
He overpowered the three of us...
Delicious water!
I... am...
You jumped on your master carpenter!
Who do you think you are?!
Clear water!
Damn Linlin.
She even brought her brats with her.
I'm gonna be busy today.
Delicious water! Clear water!
You piece of wood!
I'm invited to Shogun Orochi's banquet...
You're driving me crazy!
Delicious water! Clear water!
I am...
Take this! Franosuke Rocket Launcher!
Delicious water! Clear water!
Contact Queen...
All of you get your shit together!
SOBA MASK
...Soba Mask!
Let him...
...send assassins.
Soba Mask...
You're fired! Get out of here, you idiot!
No... He's definitely Germa...
But it'll cause an uproar...
This'll be an all-out war!
Gladly!
I no longer have business here!
--I don't care!
--Yes, sir!
That's awful! Change your name!
PAWN
Give us the rights to name you!
A pawn from 10 years ago? Blueprints?
Isn't it good?!
It seeps into every fiber of your being, doesn't it?!
Orochi-sama...
Did you say Soba Mask?!
Don't mess with me!
The Oiran is heading this way now.
But we rarely take those...
We don't have to sit here and wait for them.
There, you have a cold look again!
Good...
Oh, maybe those!
Komurasaki...
Smile, or fortune won't come to you!
What? Do you have them?!
In this country,
we call everyone's smiling face...
Oh well, of course, they were forfeited...
Where did he go?
Today, I'm gonna make her mine!
What?!
..."Ebisu gao," mister!
I wonder who bought such a thing.
He's floating in midair!
Hmmm, who was it?
That's why this place is called Ebisu Town!
How is that possible?!
Um...
Poverty won't get us down!
I have no doubt...
That's Germa's scientific technology...
Oh, yeah!
Crying won't cure your poverty!
So, why not laugh, laugh?
It was Kumagoro from the tenement,
who said he'd study them. No doubt about it!
The power of the devices on their feet
to float...
Why not laugh, laugh?
Hmph! What's taking them so long
to handle a ship?!
KUMAGORO FROM THE TENEMENT
After all, he's...
Who's that?!
Kumagoro!
KING - DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
PTERANODON MODEL
That's awesome!
Blueprints?
I'll go!
That's just child's play!
I can't wait anymore! Let me see them!
Oh yeah, I certainly had them once,
Please wait, my Lord!
but I fell behind in rent
and they were taken away by Kobei-san, the landlord.
Oh, yeah... Pretty ones!
We're reaching the top!
KOBEI, HIS LANDLORD
Who the hell?!
We're almost there!
ROOMS AVAILABLE
Kobei!
Here I am, Kaido!
Oh, the blueprints.
Those were good, so I gave them to my favorite geisha.
A-Are they good enough?
What's that?!
Kisegawa-chan.
So... gorgeous!
--Do you know her?
--No!
KISEGAWA, HIS FAVORITE GEISHA
Is that King?!
Is that a Pteranodon?!
I didn't know what to do with them
so I used them as a dish mat, but then Tokijiro-san...
This is great! Let's have a banquet now!
Shoot!
Komurasaki-sama!
Drink!
All right, who is that?
TOKIJIRO
Dance!
Sing!
I had them!
But Rakuda-san said they could be sold for quite a price
and took them away!
Don't hold back!
Komurasaki the top Oiran!
Way to go, Soba Mask!
KUROZUMI OROCHI
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
RAKUDA
What? Rakuda (Camel)? An animal?
What kind of feature was that?!
How pathetic!
I'm Rakuda!
In the heels of Germa 66's special suits,
Here she comes! Komurasaki-sama!
Man, because of the blueprints,
I had a terrible time!
there are acceleration devices...
Some guy made off with them!
It's the Oiran's procession!
He was hiding his face
but he said he came from Kuri.
Isn't she here yet?!
There are tons of people here.
Are you new?
Kuri?!
I wonder how beautiful she is.
Yes...
Your attacks are so annoying
and they piss me off!
You're quite beautiful.
Can't wait! Komurasaki-chan!
We're arriving in the Land of Wano!
Um...
Oh, I'm sorry. It's sea bream.
But I don't see the most important one!
KOMURASAKI
Now, let's go kill Straw Hat!
Is that how sea bream always looks?
What's going on?!
Thank you for shopping with us!
Yes, sir!
What the hell is this?!
Franosuke-dono!
I hate... that bitch...
He's still here!
I'm here...
--Wow!
--It's shutting out his punch!
Komurasaki!
You are looking good.
I am! By the way, what are you selling?!
Germa 66's capes can...
Komurasaki...!
No way!
What? I'm peddling fish.
...turn into solid shields...
I think they're looking for trouble!
You're sticking out!
Kids are surrounding you!
Oh, Komurasaki! I missed you!
H-Hey!
Oh, no!
I know your moves!
You can't attack me like you did before!
I've got to...
Anyway, you were in a big hurry earlier.
Is anything wrong?
Me, too...
...kill that bitch!
I'll get kicked out of the city...
My Lord...
Oh... D-Did you?!
Oh, yeah! Sticking out is nothing!
I have an even bigger problem!
Oh, no!
It's all over!
King! You little...!
If I'm gonna die anyway...
If he's the real Stealth Black,
he'll use that!
Did you?!
The guy I was looking to get the blueprints from
didn't have them!
I'll kill her, too!
I won't let you set foot in the Land of Wano!
Whoa-whoa!
I won't let you get away now!
What are you up to?!
Don't do it, guys!
Check the swords over there next.
--Komurasaki!
--You're in the way!
Dammit!
Disappeared?!
What?! The blueprints of Kaido's mansion
must be here in Kuri?!
No way!
Mama!
Move!
People can't just disappear!
Where is he?! Where did he go?!
Tra-guy... What brought you here?
Yeah! I ran all over the capital
but I couldn't find them!
Come out!
Hmph! Get swallowed up by the sea.
You're unwelcome here...
State your business or leave.
I thought so.
I don't know what to do now!
It's an emergency.
Hide somewhere, Black-Leg-ya.
Sorry to cause you trouble.
Franosuke-dono, support the other missions
in the capital!
Mama!
Got it!
Is it about the fight earlier?
If they come back, I'll beat them again.
Clank.
Hmm... Who would want the blueprints of
Kaido's mansion?
Stay away from the Oiran!
That's our King-sama!
That's not it.
That piece of shit is just flying in the sky
looking for attention!
Some guys who know our faces
are on their way!
Could it be...
--So strong! Huh? Where is he?!
--He's moving too fast to see!
Duke-sama! Kin-san!
Is it Hawkins?
Hey!
It wouldn't be so bad if it was just him...
No, that's a special ability of
Germa 66's Stealth Black...
Whew!
We stole so much.
Food... And weapons from the factory!
The strongest six among the Headliners
are called the Tobi Roppo...
Komurasaki...
He became invisible
by projecting the background over his body!
Nice work. Did you leave the note?
And two among them...
Two?
Yes, of course!
One is Page One from the Tobi Roppo!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
Even Sora, Warrior of the Sea,
had quite a hard time with him...
But is it okay?
Because of that note,
Ashura Doji could be attacked by the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Now, sing more! Dance!
NEARLY A YEAR AGO
Damn Germa...
That is what we want.
Being attacked will infuriate him.
Which side are you on?!
I'll buy out everyone's contract
once you become my favorite courtesan!
I mean, how do you know so much?!
This way, we can goad him
into fighting the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Everyone from the North Blue knows!
I have tons of money, you see?!
Oh?
Otherwise, his spirit will never be ignited again!
PAGE ONE - ONE OF THE TOBI ROPPO
ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
If you're rich, you can get whatever you want!
Tobi Roppo... Page One...
When I think of the pain he suffered for two decades,
it feels like it's a little too high-handed...
The other one is X. Drake
from the Tobi Roppo.
What's this suit?! Did I disappear?!
I know!
Drake...
It's the same as the Clear-Clear Fruit?!
I want to be with you forever...
But by fair means or foul,
we definitely need him to take down Kaido!
He's from the Worst Generation...
DEVIL FRUITS
It's the Devil Fruit that
I dreamed of having...
What?
We need Ashura Doji's help!
With an old geezer like me?!
Page One.
With the Clear-Clear Fruit,
I can become invisible.
Why do we have to do this?
If I have to live as Orochi-sama's puppet,
Now, place your bets!
My dream that once crumbled...
I would rather you bought out my contract...
X. DRAKE - ONE OF THE TOBI ROPPO
ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Odds!
Wow! You're extremely unreserved!
Yes. You stole a dream from me!
To set an example, I guess...
But the ransom on me is
an enormous amount of money...
It's important to show
what'll happen to someone who messes with...
Mister!
I don't recall doing that.
It must be a mistake.
We've got a bet on odds!
So it is an impossible dream...
W-What do you want from me?!
...the Animal Kingdom Pirates
in the Land of Wano.
I wanted to become the invisible man!!
This is...
If even just this conversation
comes to Orochi-sama's knowledge...
...a soba shop, right?
Now...
Why are you here?
So you, who ate the Clear-Clear Fruit,
crushed one of my dreams, all right?!
Hawkins...
You must not lose heart!
I came looking for some guy...
All set.
If that is what you want,
You'll get more than what you bargained for
from this job, Drake...
W-What?!
I, Bingoh, will stake my manhood
and make it happen!
Here we go!
It's not his fault!!
Four and two, it's evens!
My dream that once crumbled...
Really?
Oh, you lost!
Even if it's a lie, I'm still happy...
...came true by the technology
of Germa that I reviled?
Well, gambling is all about luck!
You sometimes lose.
PAGE ONE - DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
SPINOSAURUS MODEL
How ironic...
You don't have enough money to pay me back?!
Next round, dice in.
But this ability is very useful...
I'm sorry!
Where's Sangoro?
Are you taking me for a fool?!
Now, place your bets!
This'd be handy in the women's bath...
I-I don't know! Help me!
You think crying will help?!
No, no!
Well, then...
I can use it to protect my friends!
What a dilemma!
I'll take your house as collateral for the loan!
Komurasaki, come here!
No...
I am not worthy of it.
Call out for Sangoro!
Here, Komurasaki.
I've never seen a large amount of money like that!
It's all right! Come on.
Come a little closer!
All my remaining bets...
Komurasaki, this is an advance payment
to buy you from the pleasure hall.
...on evens...
Yes, sir!
Wow! You're going for the gamble of a lifetime!
An invisible man?
There's something fishy about you...
It's not enough yet but keep it for me.
Guys, you can come in now!
How cool, mister!
Evens! We've got a bet on evens!
Then, let me enter it in the ledger...
Do you fancy everything?
Who the hell are you?!
Yeah! Kyoshiro, you guys should drink, too!
Not necessary!
It should be easier for
me to fight in this form
What kind of fool distrusts the woman he loves...
Then, we will have some...
against someone who moves around so much...
Your word is good enough.
Bingoh-sama...
I was gonna work you over,
I cannot wait till you take me with you.
Everyone, the Fire Festival is coming up!
but I guess I'd better just kill you.
All set.
Let's have a pre-party!
Here we go!
Go ahead and enjoy it!
Hurry up, Franosuke!
This is the Land of Wano!
Don't cry...
One and two, it's odds!
Hey, why do we have to run?!
Oh! You lost again...
I know It's just like heaven!
Alright!
I will organize a funeral for you.
They're after Sangoro the soba cook!
Eat and drink as much as you want!
And I will lend you money for it
and for living expenses.
Together with that soba cook,
you took down a member of the Kyoshiro Family!
No-Sword Style...
Dragon Twister!
Stop crying already!
You need to pay me back double!
Mister, have you thought about
my offer from earlier?
Sorry! Couldn't help it.
It's your own fault for being too naive!
They're linked to Orochi.
An invisible man?
There's something fishy about you...
If you're gonna break out,
take me with you!
That's why they sent out the Animal Kingdom
Pirates' Tobi Roppo to get revenge!
Here is your money!
No... That is a lot!
I'd do anything!
Who the hell are you?!
But...
Oh, no! The enemy?! Damn!
Oh?! That's a cheat!
If you and I join hands,
there'll be nothing to be scared of!
What's wrong?
I am...
To tell you the truth, someone else
recently bid to buy me...
They're so uncool.
...Soba Mask!
Shut up! Why don't you team up with Jaggy?!
That's exactly who I am!
What?!
With Kid?
So you can't reveal your true identity...
I must hurry!
Guys! Come out!
Thank goodness. It's you guys.
No way. His reputation is not so good.
I need more and more money to buy her...
Is there anything that I can sell?
I'll kill you and tear off that mask!
It's not safe here. This way!
Did you know that he tried
to take down Big Mom?!
Okay!
Oh, you can offer cool hospitality, too.
Give yourself away!
I sold my storehouse, Komurasaki!
Let's get out of here for now.
But rumor has it that he had his arm torn off
by her subordinate,
I'm so happy...
Enough, already!
not even by her, and he escaped!
I'm sick and tired of you!
Rumor? You're such a pathetic loser.
I'm going back to my parents' house!
Stealth Black!
The situation is bad.
It doesn't matter what triggered this.
Do whatever you want!
No, I heard it from a trusted source, mister.
I told you not to call me that!
If one of you gets caught and
your true identity is revealed,
I'm on my way... Komurasaki!
it's gonna be quite messy.
I'm neither evil nor righteous!
They'll start searching
for the rest of the crew!
I'm nothing more than Soba Mask...
Guys! Get him!
Who is that trusted source?
I even abandoned my family!
Oh, no! Nami-san and Robin-chan
are in danger!
I've never tried to take down Big Mom!
Oh, no, your health...
It's still fine if it's just you guys!
Don't worry about me. Just go ahead!
K-K-K-Kid!
Buying medicine is a waste of money...
But if they find out
you're even involved with the Kozuki Family,
I injured one of her Sweet Generals,
I'm fine.
One-Sword Style...
this vengeful plan of 20 years
will be ruined!
He's...
and took what I meant to take!
Once I get what I want,
I'm going to be the happiest person in the world.
...just perfect for testing
how powerful this Raid Suit is!
B-B-B-But your arm...
No!
Dragon Quake!
Even if you get caught and tortured...
I'd already lost my arm before that,
in the battle against the Red-Hair Pirates.
I dream of... a life with you...
every night, too...
What...
Don't tell them about the
samurai and the Minks.
Any other questions?!
Keep quiet and...
Oh... Komurasaki...
No.
Then, let me tell you something!
You listen to this, too, stupid monkey!
...let them kill you!
You're terrible!
Luffy wouldn't say such a thing!
I'm more practical.
What?!
I'm the one who'll take down Kaido
and win glory!
It's fine as long as
they got no idea who we really are, right?
I got all the money...
I no longer have a house!
Wow! Everyone collapsed
without so much as a cut!
Let's live as we like together
starting from zero!
Well, then...
No, I am!
What?!
This is the final 500 Gold coins...
Why don't we fight hiding our faces?!
With this, I can buy your contract, Komurasaki!
Well, um...
Whoa, wait a minute, mister!
Best to avoid fighting for now.
Hey, Jaggy!
What?
As they say, there are evens and odds in this world.
Both good and evil come in turn.
Don't act like you're our captain!
I'm sorry. The Oiran is sick today...
If I get caught...
Where's Bonekichi?
He said he's already snuck in.
I'll spill everything to get away!
I bet you still have some dumplings!
Oh, no!
Let's put an end to this here!
Then, we must go, too.
Screw you!
Hand this to her at any cost.
I'll come back again...
Jaggy!
Then I'll protect you at any cost!
Okay?!
Yeah.
Jaggy! Don't pretend to be sleeping!
--Yay!
--What a lovely friendship!
Now, manager,
there was an objection to the last game.
I'll repay you so give me your dumplings!
Komurasaki...
So how about giving this gentleman
what he won up to that point?
I know you're hearing me, Jaggy!
It's a lady!
Komurasaki!
I'll rescue you from the pleasure hall!
Let's live together!
Damn! Take it!
Don't ever come back!
Good! Good!
SOBA SHOP
--Oh, shoot!
--Is someone already after us?!
RUINS OF KIBI, LAND OF WANO
Oh, I was so scared! Were you, mister?!
Could you shut up?
You're okay now!
This is also what a mature woman's capable of!
Wow! How kind of you to say that!
All right!
You really did it!
You subtly care about my voice.
How nice. Thanks!
You saved me. Thank you!
Way to go! You old pervert!
Oh, sorry for not introducing myself sooner,
my name is Tonoyasu.
Oh, guys!
Stop laughing and get Komurasaki for me...
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu!
Everyone calls me "Sycophant Yasu."
Nice to meet you!
Stop! We have nothing to do with this!
Gee, you're enticing
even when you don't speak!
She'll live with me in happiness!
This is an old and mysterious room...
We serve soba, but we have nothing to do with
Sangoro the soba cook!
You stud!
Girls won't leave you alone, mister!
This country has been
isolated for centuries...
Now, dance!
Idiot! Stop dreaming!
How could you destroy our shop?!
Drink!
Why are you following me?
Without it, we can't stay in this city!
Eat! Don't be shy!
Do you have enough money
to liberate her?
At the gambling house earlier,
I realized.
Of course! Komurasaki has it!
I asked her to keep it for me!
And the Ponegliff was invented here...
"If I follow this man,
everything will be alright"!
I'm sure they have one.
If you wanna hold it against someone,
blame it on the fool named Sangoro.
But normal people don't mess with those men.
There must be a hidden door somewhere...
They're underlings of the Kyoshiro Family,
the terrifying yakuza group from the capital.
Tell me about other soba shops!
Oh, Bingoh-san.
Otherwise, call out for Sangoro!
Oh, Komurasaki! Tell them the truth!
Are you looking for something?
Oh, that was so staggering!
They have no idea how serious our relationship is
and are saying whatever they like!
No way! How could I have missed it?!
He's an idiot who messed
with the Kyoshiro Family!
If I were a woman,
I'd go weak in the knees!
If you two resist...
Huh?
What's the matter, mister?!
Good!
That looks familiar.
Good, good, good, good...
You said you were giving me the money,
didn't you?
I'll eat you, too!
Oh-ho, you are incredibly perceptive!
What you see in the distance is the Flower Capital!
Komurasaki.
I want you to play that one now!
What?!
Sangoro!
And before that,
there is Ebisu Town aka Okobore Town!
Sangoro!
As you wish...
That's my hometown!
Ebisu... Sounds like it's wealthy.
I spent it all.
Oh, I feel lighter without flesh
to weigh me down.
Hey!
Why is it named Ebisu, you wonder?
You'll see once you get there!
I mean, I don't have any flesh.
Thank you.
Sangoro, show yourself!
Because I'm a skeleton.
That old man really thought
Komurasaki-san fell in love with him!
It's only vain to tell a
skull joke to myself...
You guys don't want us to open up the country, either!
That's enough.
Let's start searching!
You shouldn't have done anything suspicious
since ninja were here...
Right?
Sangoro!
Because you're looking to buy weapons to fight pirates,
from pirates.
How ridiculous!
Maybe it's no use.
Don't you know who ninja are?
If he's a coward, he'll never show himself!
Who's that old fart?
It's really strange...
She could be from overseas.
Sangoro!
What?
Isn't it?!
Komurasaki...
Oh, I wanna eat something sweet next!
B-Boss Kyoshiro!
A strangely reinforced door...
Now without the broker, Doflamingo aka Joker,
OROCHI'S ONIWABANSHU
SHOGUN OF WANO PERSONAL NINJA FORCE
They're using trickery!
I smell something here.
So...
I don't have a nose though.
you guys lost your cover,
so you have no choice but to deal with us directly...
...you're the old man who's been hanging
around Komurasaki these days...
Our top priority should be on running!
Sanji!
Hanging around... Th-That's not true!
Oh, hello.
What are those dolls?
How...
You're a troublesome geisha...
I know you are anxious
so we can take unfair advantage...
Komurasaki, you're joking, right?
...could I do that?!
I give you a chance to explain.
Pone... gliff?
Hey, wait, Sanji!
I really sacrificed everything!
FUKUROKUJU - CAPTAIN OF THE ONIWABANSHU
But...
But you're already making unreasonable demands.
...you get only one.
Stop! We have nothing to do with him, either!
I don't have anything now!
Kaido-sama, I'm here to report!
The Land of Wano is fully self-sufficient!
Then, call out for him!
I threw away everything I had for you!
Everybody!
Aboard a giant ship,
approaching from southeast!
For Sangoro the soba cook!
She really came! That old bag!
Everyone seems happy, right?
If there is something we need,
that would be greater power!
Fire away!
Let her be swallowed by the sea so we're rid of her!
Oh, no...
I'm...
How many of these guys has it been now?
This time, we only asked for a warship...
...here!
You're interfering with our business
by crying out here, old man.
We're already prepared to attack!
Diable Jambe!
Don't let her enter the country!
If you're done, leave!
But next time, we want Dr. Vegapunk!
Concasser Crush!
But there is a problem...
You okay, Sangoro?!
You lecherous old geezer!
That's impossible!
The Ancient Type power users are so powerful!
But...
...it's not enough to beat Stealth Black...
I didn't ask if it's possible or not!
Stop!
They're charging forward
being hauled by carp!
Stop...
That's him...
I'm leaving!
It hurts a bit, but this thing is durable.
What?!
The Celestial Dragons? The Navy?
He's...
Why do they know how to
climb up the waterfall?!
I'm leaving so stop!
...Sangoro of the Special Soba!
You know we're not afraid of them, don't you?
Well... The Big Mom Pirates have a reputation
for their ability to collect information...
But the capital can't take it too long...
So you're the soba cook.
Shut up! I don't care!
Even if you attack us all at once,
you can't defeat us.
Hey! Why are we leaving Sangoro behind?!
We knew they were coming!
You finally showed up...
You gave me trouble.
Just sink them!
He told us to go ahead.
Komurasaki...
Because Kaido is backing me up!
Yes, he did, but...
Um, this is Page One.
I found the target at the sixth block of district two!
All right... Let's deliver his dead body
to Boss Kyoshiro.
That old bag! I'm sure she
remembers that I warned her...
Roger! We'll be there as soon as we can.
No one can stop me!
Komurasaki the top Oiran...
But who was he after all?
You can't escape now!
...is in procession!
If you come, I'll kill you, Linlin!
A dinosaur power-user...
KOMURASAKI THE OIRAN
WANO'S GREATEST COURTESAN
There'll be more pursuers
and it's gonna get messier.
Komurasaki-sama!
We shouldn't stay in the capital for the time being.
Let's go to Ebisu Town!
So pretty!
So splendid!
You asshole...
Open the gate!
Oh, how gorgeous...
What are you doing, Sangoro?!
Stop it!
If Drake and Hawkins come, it'll be all over!
Too bright! My eyes!
Komurasaki the top Oiran has arrived!
I know.
Komurasaki!
I turned my house, family,
and everything into money!
Give me back the money I entrusted to you!
You thief!
But...
...he doesn't know who I really am.
So no one will find it out
and I won't get hurt!
Asking for your gift back?
I can beat this fool in an instant.
Shooting Star! Soba Kick!
How pathetic you are...
To me, men are like dogs who bring me money.
What?!
So you have a little sister, Momo-kun?
It'd be nice to have more allies...
Without it, you're worthless.
Hey, Tama!
You're being rude!
Who do you think I am?!
But it would also be nice
to have fewer enemies.
You're Momo-kun.
Now you guys can't get away!
Stop talking gibberish!
Forget it...
Don't give us trouble,
you penniless fools!
Yes, I have a little sister.
People who can't make money
have no right to live in the Flower Capital.
If she is alive, she would be 26 now.
There were people who saw my mother dying,
but no one said Hiyori died.
In the name of Shogun Orochi,
we'll expel you from the city!
Guys, move ahead!
Tsk! He's so tough...
What?
So I truly believe she is alive somewhere!
Where are you?!
Show yourself, Soba Mask!
Please don't!
Outside the city,
we can't even have a human life!
I hope you can see her.
No, I won't see her!
It's fine as long as...
Damn! Go to hell!
Soba Mask, huh?
Once Orochi knows her identity,
he will go after her!
Komurasaki!
I should ask Franosuke and Usohachi
to redesign this!
I will only see her once we win the fight!
I... don't like...
...I keep my identity secret, right?
KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
SON OF THE LATE DAIMYO OF KURI, LAND OF WANO
...poor people.
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat...
Luffy and Kid are incarcerated.
A jet-black Raid Suit and a skull belt!
Glaring sharp fangs!
They can only count on themselves.
A move at lightning speed! Bizarre weapons!
When the two rookies are about to clash, a fearful singing voice
echoes over the rough sea around the Land of Wano!
Giant feet that crush everything!
Page One's roar echoes!
Zoro's strange wanderings
with a sycophant named Tonoyasu creates turmoil!
On his feet are devices that accelerate
him to the speed of light!
Orochi's Oniwabanshu, the great ninja force,
launch unexpected attacks!
Wearing a cape with the number 3 on it,
a new hero appears in the Flower Capital!
After catching a dealer cheating,
they face Wano's worst criminal group, the Kyoshiro Family!
When Sanji hears the hard-working
people's screams,
It belongs to Emperor of the Sea Big Mom!
Kaido and Big Mom start a fierce fight over Luffy!
Robin, Nami, and Brook are cornered!
heedless of his own pride and safety,
For the success of their raid operation,
a perilous fight begins!
Shouldering the people's expectations,
he fights the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
To pay back his debt for sushi, Zoro makes a big bet!
he stands in Page One's way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dashing! The Righteous Soba Mask!"
"A Tale of Chivalry! Zoro and Tonoyasu's Little Trip!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A State of Emergency! Big Mom Closes in!"
"A Desperate Situation! Orochi's
Menacing Oniwabanshu!"
"The Capital in an Uproar!
Another Assassin Targets Sanji!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!