One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Six deadly figures among the Headliners -
the Tobi Roppo.
Robin infiltrated Orochi's Castle,
Are you prepared?
Listen to what I say!
I am.
but was attacked and caught
by the Oniwabanshu.
To fight one of them, Page One,
This animal called Sharkodile is
pretty calm and sweet!
Stop laughing!
Sanji splendidly transformed himself.
Otoko-chan!
Wait! I do not understand why you have to go to Udon
with that Big Mom person?!
No matter who does it,
rebelling against the Shogun is a grave offense.
With her help, we will save Big Bro!
She's gone?!
Where did she go?
I'm hungry. Aren't we at Udon yet?
That's the iron rule.
Meanwhile,
Shogun Orochi was having a big banquet
along with many of his subordinates.
In the Flower Capital,
Sanji and Page One put up an intense fight.
I'm quite hungry so I...
Komurasaki...
Don't look at me drooling like that!
Meanwhile, at Orochi's Castle...
Oh, how pleasant!
I will never abase myself before anyone!
Thank you, straw hat man!
Oh, hello.
"The Bond Between Prisoners!
Luffy and Old Man Hyo!"
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna eat them with appreciation.
You're a troublesome geisha...
Hey, Komurasaki...
Oh, Orobi the new girl!
Where have you been?!
I give you a chance to explain.
I was going to...
Hey!
Come closer!
But you get only one.
FUKUROKUJU - CAPTAIN OF THE ONIWABANSHU
Oh, yes!
...make you the Shogun's wife...
Let me have some!
This is...
...the five-colored rice! Must be Shinobu!
Those dumplings look delicious!
Komurasaki!
If you want a weak woman,
You're so mean...
Don't you have something to do with Kid's escape?!
"Wait you at the dried-up well"...
go ahead and cut me up!
Are they there?!
You guys were talking so often!
Don't pout, don't pout, Komurasaki!
"A Desperate Situation!
Orochi's Menacing Oniwabanshu!"
His spit stinks...
I am glad that you are all alive!
I am a samurai's daughter!
How cute! You're very, very cute!
Stinks?! Are you messing with me?!
Shut up!
I did not think that you ran all the way to the region of Ringo
to hide from the pursuers...
I will not live in disgrace!
Don't forget that you have the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
At Kuri Beach,
Chopper and the others bumped into...
Orochi's men will not pursue this far.
The rule says you can only eat
what you earn by working.
Big M...
You are impertinent...
I didn't expect the famous Oiran,
Komurasaki, to be killed.
If you can't work, just starve to death!
Don't you agree, old man?!
I'm gonna kill her right now!
Mm-hm. That has thrown the Flower Capital
into an uproar.
OFF THE COAST OF THE LAND OF WANO
Hey, are you trying to get away like that?!
You are just some whore!
I mean,
all she did was speak against Orochi.
How could he be so quick to kill a woman like that?!
Now, you can't even work,
Lick...
so how did you get so many food tickets?!
Who gave them to you?
Boy, that was terrible.
Do not act like you know
a damn thing about samurai!
I didn't expect King would attack us himself!
I'm scared of samurai...
Dumplings...
The man who cut Komurasaki
was Napping Kyoshiro.
Dumplings...
Yeah!
My precious dumplings...
I didn't see it coming.
Kyoshiro...
I have never heard that name...
Now we're separated from Mama...
But it's only a matter of time before he gets caught!
Who...
20 years ago, the greatest yakuza boss
in the Land of Wano was...
His jailbreak was not well-planned.
Hey, Brother Peros!
What should we do now?
...am I?!
Foolishly he still has the Sea Prism Stone cuffs on...
...Hyogoro the Flower.
Well, let's see what we can do. Lick.
So he'll get caught soon
and face the consequences!
What a colorful name.
"Pandemonium!
The Monster Snake, Shogun Orochi!"
Stop it! Your spit really stinks!
Boss Hyogoro who values
honor and helps the weak,
Komurasaki...
would never handle the situation
in such a cruel way.
Don't tell me you're messing with me?!
I found you, Straw Hat!
Do you wanna go over the rules again?!
Apologize!
If you plead for your life,
The first offense, your arms will be cut off!
Big Mom!
Napping Kyoshiro... How horrible that man is.
you will get a lighter sentence!
For the second, your legs!
Here I go!
Maybe we shouldn't take Otoko-chan
back to Kyoshiro's brothel...
And for the third, you're sentenced to death!
I...
What was I doing here?
Idiot!
...will not beg for my life!
Even though she made the Shogun mad,
You guys shouldn't mess with us!
Are you hurt? Let us treat you!
I don't think Kyoshiro will
chase after a child...
Life or death?!
What are you doing?!
Are you all right?!
You have no right to eat anything!
But he even killed the most
popular woman in his brothel.
Chopperemon!
She doesn't seem like herself...
Komurasaki!
Death!
Old man! Why?!
I'm worried...
It serves him right!
That's what you'll get if you mess with us!
Let's go back to the Flower Capital...
Chopperemon?!
Keep that in mind!
It's cold, isn't it?
It's so warm! Thank you, Shinobu-chan!
Damn you!
Now, spill it with dumplings!
Everyone, if we're going
back to the Flower Capital,
We shouldn't get mixed with her!
What idiot has been giving you the tickets?!
All right, Komurasaki!
let's take a bath to rest our weary bones.
As you wish,
If we do...
I will kill you with my own hands!
Since I'm just bones.
Give it to me!
I ate them!
Yeah. It's so nice to warm ourselves up at a bathhouse
in the Flower Capital while doing research.
How much do you wanna mess with me?
Wedding cake!
I won't go easy on you.
I'll make you say your accomplice's name,
A bath sounds good!
We'll get killed!
Yeah. We wanna refresh ourselves.
and kill you both!
We have to wear disguises.
The hot water and drinking water are managed by Orochi.
Hey, do you know who I am?
In the Flower Capital,
every single aspect of life is controlled.
"The Flower Falls! The Final Moment of
the Most Beautiful Woman in the Land of Wano!"
I don't remember a thing...
Before that, Orobi-dono,
I would like to hear the information you've collected so far...
"A Lead Performer!
Queen the Plague Emerges!"
I know your name!
The Oiran!
It's a shame... All I've
found out so far is...
Komurasaki-dayu!
That's it! That's it!
That's the music!
You do?!
...what time Orochi will wake up
on the day of the battle,
I love it!
Don't tell her!
the offerings that they
will take to Onigashima,
UDON
Um... Bi... B-B-B...
Kaido's favorite food and organization chart,
the number of
his soldiers and weapons...
Big...!
EXECUTIVE TOWER IN THE EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
So efficient!
I wonder why...
By the way, I discovered a Ponegliff!
Whenever Big Sis Komurasaki plays that music,
she puts on that mask.
Chopperemon?!
This is pandemonium!
It wasn't a red one though...
I-It's Olin! Olin!
What do you want?!
Your name is Olin!
You sure?!
I found this.
You surely have luck with stones, Bonekichi!
It was in a basement room
with a reinforced door.
A kani (Crab)?
Olin?
It's not a kani, it's a kagi (key)!
It was a strange room with wooden puppets.
If a prisoner escapes, it will be your fault!
Then, the Road Ponegliff that'll lead us the way to Raftel,
might be on Onigashima as I thought.
Get ready!
Thanks-kani!
Olin...
Onigashima, huh?
Put it away in the safe now!
Now, I give you one chance to answer my question.
Mm-hm. With so much information,
we can say the mission was quite successful...
It's a lovely name!
Komurasaki!
Jeez! We are taking the trouble of
keeping the keys to the power-user prisoners' cuffs...
Daikoku!
That is not the name you told us.
Thank you...
It is all because of your support.
...safe in the Sea Prism Stone box,
Who are you and what were you doing?
If you ninja are here, stop the Shogun!
I don't wanna remind her of anything!
Save the Oiran!
so it is very important for you guards to stay sharp.
He's free.
Nothing is tying him down.
If you speak true,
I'll kill you at once, so you won't suffer.
Thank you. You're so kind.
Now, Orobi-san, Onami-san!
Let's go to a bathhouse
for healing and to see panties!
When you see someone in trouble,
you help!
More importantly,
If the power-users release themselves
from the Sea Prism Stone cuffs
--You can't come since you draw attention!
--What?!
Chopperemon is a doctor!
we're currently dealing with an invader!
Oh, is he?!
Come on!
and stage a rebellion,
My name is Tama!
Breaking news!
An invader?!
The biggest icon in the Flower Capital,
Komurasaki the Oiran,
our heads will roll!
Otherwise, you'll be subjected to
merciless torture...
I'm sorry-kani!
...was cut down by Boss Kyoshiro
at Shogun-sama's banquet!
By the way, you don't look familiar...
I'm hungry...
You can find out more in here!
Orobi-san is an invader?
Kani!
My name is...
KOMURASAKI, THE TOP OIRAN, DIES
--An intruder!
--Get ready to die!
Oh, yeah! I've never seen her before...
...Ushimitsu Kozo.
Komurasaki-chan!
I came here to see how money flows
in the Flower Capital.
How could this happen?!
You must always crush your enemy
with overwhelming force!
I obtained the keys!
EBISU TOWN
Hey, lady, please save the Oiran.
Why so mournful?!
You barely met her only once.
That's impossible!
RAIZO OF THE MIST - AKAZAYA NINE (A NINJA)
I see...
I don't even know if I can save you
since you made the Shogun mad!
What's happening is more than just
some of your underlings getting beaten.
The death of such a beauty is the world's loss,
idiot!
So you're saying that you were doing research on
who should be your next target?
The funeral will be held tomorrow.
Kyoshiro.
You're so insensitive!
That's a very smart answer...
Some strangers snuck into the capital!
The Raid Suit...
But we know that you didn't give out your real name!
Seems like you can only walk sideways.
Do you think Orobi and the others got caught?
Since you are a crab!
I'm worried.
Should I try to contact them by Smail?
Listen, guys!
Since I have you together, let me say this again!
What do you think, Sanji?
Ninpo: Flower Shuriken!
This year marks the 20th year
since Kozuki Oden died!
The ability to become invisible...
I guess I have to try it there...
Help me!
His wife, Toki said there would be retaliation
this year!
Hey, Sanji!
In the women's bath!
I will take the keys, but I will not take your life!
It's a curse of death!
Oden's legacy persists!
Oh, yeah, you're right!
Speaking of which, Tra-guy,
isn't there anything about Udon? About Luffytaro?
I won't let you get away!
What's going on over there?!
By seeing how you moved,
I know you're not a common geisha.
Yeah, it's about time he loses patience
and starts rampaging!
Fujin! Raisin! What are you doing?!
Now, goodbye!
To hide your identity, you used Ushimitsu Kozo's name
and tried to blame a crime on the thief.
That ghost story again...
Nin, nin, nin...
We don't remember Kozuki...
You're right! Can't wait to see him again!
Right, Komurasaki?
That's very mean!
There is no article on Straw Hat-ya...
Right. Ushimitsu Kozo has
just appeared in the capital.
Do you remember how unusually strong
Oden's retainers, the Akazaya Nine, were?!
Wait...
Spit it out already!
Eustass-ya?!
I-It's a specter!
What?! Did you say "yuya (bathhouse)"?!
Is it the women's bath?!
Who gave you the food tickets?!
Gasha-dokuro creatures really do exist!
Their leader, Kin'emon, is a bright guy!
Let me ask one more time.
Oh, I mean, so he's here
in the Land of Wano?!
A curse on you!
Who are you?
And what have you been doing?
They've come back to the Land of Wano after 20 years
and are preparing!
Since his ally Hawkins is here,
it's no wonder that he's here, too...
Tell me or I'm gonna kill you!
I won't tell you even if it means death!
What?!
SERIOUS OFFENDER, KID, ESCAPES
I guess you really want to be tortured...
But he was held in the prison at Udon...
Ghost!
Then, he escaped.
You little punk...
Well then...
--Escaped?!
--Hey, what about Luffy?!
They will come!
Otoko-chan!
A curse on you!
He acts up to the cause of justice
and helps the weak...
I guess something more
will take place in Udon...
Do it!
...without yielding to fools...
To cut off my head!
Robin-san, glad to see you fine!
He has such chivalrous spirit,
By the way...
Bonekichi, you're a hero! Thanks!
is there a bathhouse?
--Damn you! This is not the time for that!
--You're not listening at all!
and I have to honor that with my own chivalrous spirit
or I'll disgrace myself!
I'm awesome, right?
We have already buried a bunch of people
who were related to Oden...
Keep it up!
You fool!
Let's make it out of here!
Hey, wait!
BEACH OF KURI, KURI
Old Man Hyo...
Is he still scared of Kozuki?
Are they the specter's allies?!
What is it?!
Mil Fleurs!
I'm worried. Bepo and the others went scouting
and haven't come back yet...
Kaido has already taken an enemy down,
Otama! Let's have a fair fight!
Gigantesco Mano!
but the yokozuna and Jack's men
got attacked in Kuri!
I could ask for nothing better, Chopperemon!
I hope we won't have any more trouble.
Now, kill me!
A soba cook in the capital,
and a ronin from a post town
attacked some yakuza!
--How could you!
--Damn you!
Meeting him makes me nostalgic for a bygone era.
Oh, gee. Lick.
Ninpo: Leaves Jutsu!
Of all places, Mama fell out of the ship
on the top of the waterfall!
Ninpo!
We can't go back there
since King is defending by air...
This is it!
I am Hyogoro the Flower!
Zigzag Run!
Maybe they were all on Kin'emon's orders!
Take this!
G-Gasha-dokuro...
After so long, my heart is filled with joy
and my stomach is full!
It's already miraculous that
the Queen Mama Chanter didn't roll over...
Let me guide you to the land of dead.
...after falling from that height...
Young lady!
Hey! All we can do is wait?
Foxfire Kin'emon and the Akazaya samurai...
This is a land of samurai!
Yes, for now.
It's a long way to go
to become a bewitching kunoichi...
Once we fall off the ship,
we power-users will be paralyzed...
Go away!
There used to be...
No!
I cannot wait to face them!
No! Then, Mama sank into the sea?!
...a bunch of men like him!
I will cut them down with a single stroke!
I somehow dodged all of it...
Don't worry!
You guys killed them all!
Both of you, good job!
This is also a miracle...
Robin and even Brook...
I'm still worried about Big Bro Luffy...
Mama's Vivre Card shows she's alive!
What should I do?!
Hey!
You are dependable, Kyoshiro!
Stop! Luffytaro!
There's no point in hiding now.
Don't worry! He'll be alright!
Great! She's alive!
INSIDE THE CASTLE - IN THE ATTIC
You know what'll happen to you
when you talk back to guards, right?!
Let's go!
Oden died! Before my eyes!
But then, where is she?!
Okay, Shinobu-chan!
That means she probably was hauled up
by the Animal Kingdom Pirates and is being held captive!
But his son Momonosuke is still alive!
Kill me, you fool!
Onami!
But we haven't heard from Raizo yet, either.
It's hard not to be anxious...
By Kaido's group? That complicates things...
What did you say?! Say it again!
The body of that brat was never recovered
along with others!
Mama and Kaido used to be crewmates,
Master-sama said that no one has ever
left the prison in Udon...
The Kozuki Clan hasn't died out yet!
I said that you guys are irrational fools
who use unreasonable violence!
but now they're called Emperors of the Sea
and became enemies that are competing with each other...
Thank you, Shinobu-chan.
They're aiming to revive the Kozuki Clan!
I said he'll be fine! Nin-nin!
Don't mention it, Onami!
He'll kill her for sure.
You moron!
Of course, they are going to
chop off Kaido's head, too...
All we can do now is train ourselves!
But...
What?! What's gonna happen to us then?!
...we couldn't defeat you fools...
Ninpo: Tree-climbing Jutsu!
Who's that?! A ninja?!
They will definitely come!
Lick!
There, you said it again...
The Big Mom Pirates will become...
If I were strong enough,
I would go to save him now...
I'm gonna kill you!
Hey lady! You were called Shinobu just now,
weren't you?!
...the Perospero Pirates?! Lick!
Stop! If you hit a guard...
No one will chop off Kaido's head!
You're...
Hey! What are you talking
about, Big Bro Peros!
Oh?
They execute you on the spot,
Luffytaro!
...Hanzo?!
The next captain will be Katakuri!
What is that?
How cowardly can he be?!
Old man!
So you're alive! You man-seducing...
You're drinking too much!
We value seniority! Lick!
Hey! No! Don't do it!
If he hears that,
your head will be cut off!
Don't be a fool! Quality matters!
...sexy kunoichi.
Stop...
The eldest son should lead!
Otoko-chan, take this one next!
Okay!
Do you want me to summon a genie?!
I'm gonna do it now!
Hey, I'm out of sake!
Stop it!
Yes, we'll be right with you!
Don't assume Mama'll die!
Can you take it to him?!
Yes!
Don't think of her as a commoner, you fools!
Listen up, guys! This is the year!
Shinobu the Man-killer!
Big Mom?!
Remember Toki's last words!
Yes, she is a very strong
person from overseas!
Do not drop your guard!
Huh?!
What?!
She's gone?!
He's too scared.
Where did she go?
This animal called Sharkodile is
pretty calm and sweet!
How pathetic.
When will he stop believing that bullshit poem?
I would've died if I didn't use
the Shadow Clone Jutsu...
"You are the moon unaware of the dawn."
How did you know?
You hit the animal two times to tame it!
Stop...
No, you're not her.
This is Orobi!
Wait! I do not understand why you have to go to Udon
with that Big Mom person?!
No... Don't...
Forget it!
Onami! Shinobu-san! Bonekichi!
Here we go again... It ruins the taste of sake.
That's me!
Stop...
I'm sorry, but I was discovered
by the enemies!
"May your purpose be fulfilled
With her help, we will save Big Bro!
Ninpo: Ball-Crusher!
What? They found Robin?
...making me cry...
and cast nine shadows on the night woven of 20 years
Is that a type of ninjutsu?!
Oh no! That's a big deal!
I-I do not understand!
Just come back, Otama!
Fill me in on the details!
I can't believe they found Orobi-san!
This is why... you're
called... the Man-Killer...
and you shall know the brilliance of the dawn"!
Daifugo-sama!
There are some ninja in the castle!
11 of them at least!
Kin'emon-dono told me
to guard Momonosuke-sama tightly!
Is that what it means?!
Whoever attacks a guard
will be executed immediately!
You know what it means!
I-I can't move...
11 ninja?!
20 years later, on a moonlit night,
in order to settle the grudge,
We saw it this time! There can be no excuses!
It will be all right, Master-sama!
Ninpo: Paralysis Jutsu!
Fukurokuju!
nine samurai will appear as ghosts...
As a kunoichi, I will protect Momo-kun
at any cost!
Fukurokuju is the leader of the ninja force!
What?! You made that part up!
--Kill him!
We must get going!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Orochi's Oniwabanshu led by him is
a group of capable ninja!
--Let's go, Onami!
--What?
They will... kill me...
W... W...
Who is a kunoichi?!
You are not even half-fledged yet!
...and open up the Land of Wano!
I'm sure they'll go after Orobi!
Let's protect her, Onami!
Sexy Ninpo!
Do not be ridiculous
and get back here already, Otama!
Rot Garden!
Uh-huh! Robin, where are you?!
Hitetsu-dono! We are already on our way...
Oh! You're a geisha!
What?! No! Okiku-dono!
Oh, yes!
What are you doing here? Oops...
Head back now!
Orochi believes in the prophecy quite firmly...
Whoa-whoa, watch your step.
Say hi to Komachiyo and the others!
Clank.
Even so, his subordinates don't care...
I'm so drunk.
Solitaire-sama! The keys have been stolen!
I gotta go to the bathroom...
Hey, considering Hitetsu is worried,
maybe we'd better go back...
Why did Hanzo fall down from the attic?
No wonder.
Someone stole the keys
to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
Now, I'll take a leak so I can drink more!
Who are those two kunoichi?!
He's so delusional.
We will save Big Bro, Chopperemon!
What are you doing, you fools?!
Did someone see who did it?!
Oden and the Akazaya members are all dead!
--What's going on?!
--The banquet room is a mess!
Right, Olin-san?!
By the way, I heard you
say "Big Mom" earlier...
I don't even remember them.
SOLITAIRE - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, MONKEY SMILE FRUIT
What a coward.
Disconnected...
A man with a big face-kani!
We have to find her ourselves.
That sounds awfully familiar...
We will not let them do as they like!
Never mind, Olin! You're Olin!
He told me to put a fake key into the safe.
Brook, did you hear that?
Find Robin and protect her.
Right, Olin?!
I was fooled-kani!
Olin, Olin, Olin!
Okay, okay! I got it.
I can only walk sideways
and he took advantage of that,
That is why we cannot lower our guard...
You're so cute, Chopperemon!
Clank.
and stole them-kani!
Whoa, Onami-san!
And here I finally got to do something
other than gathering food...
Anyway, the people in Okobore Town
were all nice...
A curse on you!
You fool!
You're useless as a guard!
A curse on you!
Why?!
They don't know me
and I don't even know who I am,
Onami!
I came as back-up!
Who is it?! Idiot! Stop it!
He must still be in the tower!
Search high and low, even in the attic!
but that woman treated me to
the sweet and delicious red-bean soup...
Was she a ninja?
Or a specter?
Where are you?! Komurasaki!
This voice... Oh, please no!
Whether it's ninjutsu or magic,
the main body should be around here.
That talking hat hasn't spoken at all,
so did he lose his memory, too?
This is a ninja's true worth!
There you are!
You can't laugh! Stop it!
I got the keys!
Listen!
Now I remember...
Orochi-sama is having a banquet!
I wanna eat the red-bean soup again...
--Stop!
--An intruder!
Don't make trouble over a rat!
Don't look at me when you say that!
Who is it?!
I couldn't help it because you're so cute
I could eat you up...
A shadow?!
Yes, sir!
Stop, you prowler!
Do not tell me you laughed at me!
Who would stop in a situation like this?!
I'm not food!
Makibishi!
Otoko-chan!
Kyoshiro?!
You are working hard, Momo-kun!
Now, let's drink more!
Because everyone is taking him for a fool!
I am at the center of this battle!
I must stay sharp!
Oh no, you're drinking too much.
Sunacchi!
That's enough! Go away!
Oh, how pleasant!
It took a little too much time...
Oh, sorry! I am sorry!
Luffytaro-dono, wait for me!
It's time to escape!
I can't stop! I'm sorry!
Oh, Orobi the new girl!
Where have you been?!
By the way, what is "Sunacchi"
that you have been yelling?
All I need to do now is run stealthily!
--It's a child!
--She's the Oiran's attendant!
Come closer!
Oh, yes!
Sunacchi is a word that gives you energy!
Stop her!
"A wise man would hide a leaf in the forest."
Otoko-chan!
Sunacchi!
You should not have done that, Komurasaki...
I know I shouldn't laugh!
It's impossible to get out of here now.
Plus, I still have things to do.
Sunacchi!
Sunacchi! Sunacchi!
You are right! I got a lot of energy!
I'm sorry...
Are you prepared?
Yeah? Great!
I've taken too much time!
I am.
How obnoxious!
Sunacchi! Sunacchi! Sunacchi!
My Lord!
I am the Shogun!
Stop, both of you!
This way!
What is it, Chopperemon?
What, Kiku?
What?
Where did you learn that word?
Wait a minute, Boss Kyoshiro!
It's what they yell in
a sword fight overseas!
What's that?! A person?!
I learned it from Zorojuro!
Stop her!
What a huge person...
He said it's a good-luck word to uplift your spirit
when you lose courage...
Queen-sama!
Still smaller than the Giants though!
The grudge from 20 years ago...
Then, I forbid you to say it!
Queen! Queen! Queen! Queen!
K-Kaido or this person - which one is bigger?
What?! Why?!
It could be just a coincidence,
Do you think I am...
Is that person a woman?
but there is the same battle cry in an old dialect from Kuri.
Do you think I am afraid of it?!
It is not appropriate for you to say.
--What?! Come on!
--No!
I am the victor!
It is a word that gives you energy...
No means no!
My Lord!
What?! No way!
I defeated Oden!
I'm hungry. Aren't we at Udon yet?
You should not have done that, Komurasaki...
Please! Stop it!
I'm too hungry so I...
A Lead Performer, Queen-sama, is here!
Don't do it!
Are you prepared?
Don't look at me drooling like that!
I am.
Oiran!
The fact is, Olin-san,
the Udon region is still a long way from here...
Let us open the gate!
She's unreliable!
That black-hearted woman
can't do anything!
You lovely one. I'm feeling good!
Is that right?!
My Lord!
This is a rough map of the Land of Wano.
Here you go, my Lord!
She is just a little child.
That's right!
Stay out of this, Komurasaki!
The Land of Wano has six regions
divided by a river,
and each region has a different climate.
At the far west, is the region of Kuri.
It's delicious! Sake tastes better
when you pour it!
KURI
We met on the beach near
Amigasa Village in Kuri...
AMIGASA VILLAGE
My Lord... Please forgive her!
Oh... Thank you very much!
Did you laugh at me?!
ATAMAYAMA        OKOBORE TOWN
BAKURA TOWN
Bakura Town used to be a
castle town of Oden Castle.
--By the way...
--What?
Squirt!
This banquet is really enchanting.
Otsuru-san was in Okobore
Town right next to it.
I'm so honored to be invited to something like this.
That's where I had the red-bean soup!
And Atamayama is where Shutenmaru is based.
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
She's prone to laughter!
She means no offense!
I'm happy, too!
Now, where is Udon?
We can't stop him anymore...
Give up on her!
To have you...
If you head east from Kuri,
you'll find the region of Udon.
I want to drink the night away with you!
Eh?!
UDON
My Lord! She's just a child!
Have mercy!
We are heading for the
Excavation Labor Camp there.
UDON
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
Listen to what I say!
Those words...
Even if you're joking, they make me happy...
Big Bro! We will rescue you at any cost!
Stop laughing!
Alright! Suna...
No no. I'm not joking. I'm serious!
Oh! Sorry!
The region of Kibi is a wasteland.
Otoko-chan!
Fujiyama is at the center
of the Land of Wano.
FLOWER CAPITAL
Oh... I'm so grateful!
At the foot of it, is...
...the great-extravagant Flower Capital.
Now, my Lord...
Its prosperity is purchased with
the sacrifice of the commoners.
EBISU TOWN
I heard you would have a big banquet
at Onigashima on the day of the Fire Festival...
The hateful Orochi is responsible for it.
I have to make it right!
Why is it so noisy inside?
Oh yes, I will!
Suna...
I am sorry!
Every official of the Land of Wano
and all of the Animal Kingdom Pirates will be there!
East of the Flower Capital,
RINGO
NORTHERN GRAVEYARD
is the snowy region of Ringo.
That many people?!
I think Brook is in the Northern Graveyard!
I cannot believe how powerful you are...
How amazing!
O... Oiran...
The region of Hakumai has port towns.
HABU PORT     HAKUMAI
It's an annual festival!
We must do it in a lavish manner!
And located directly in
south of the Land of Wano...
Big Sis...
ONIGASHIMA
...is Onigashima!
Where we plan to attack!
I want to attend...
We have to recruit allies
from across the country.
Kyoshiro-dono, why did you do that?
...that banquet...
It's heartbreaking...
Please summon me.
--Mm-hm!
--First, let's save Big Bro!
But this time, he can't get away!
The most beautiful woman
in the Land of Wano...
All right! All right! Count on me!
I won't forget you, Luffytaro!
Luffy is indispensable for us!
It's heartrending!
Are you sure?! I'm so happy!
This is finally it for Old Man Hyo, too!
Udon is so far away...
After I saw the map, I got hungrier.
So cute!
You did great, straw hat man!
Like I said, stop looking at me and drooling!
Orobi-san!
Komurasaki...
Where are you?
Why are you talking like it's over?!
Why...?
Orobi-san!
Let's get out of here!
Why did you hit me?
I have to look for her until I get bone-tired
because I'm basically made of bones.
Apologize, Komurasaki!
Why did you do that, Kyoshiro?!
It's no use! Don't resist!
Bow until your forehead sinks into the floor!
You're weakened by the Sea Prism Stone -
what can you do?!
Is she here?
Did I tell you to kill her?!
Or here?
I will not!
Shut up... If you wanna fight,
You bastard...
Oh! No!
bring it on!
I will never abase myself before anyone!
--Who are you?!
--Stop!
What are you doing over there?!
It is...
How dare she!
--Oh?
--Where did that person go?!
...the mercy of a samurai for Komurasaki...
When I know I am right,
I do not need to give an inch!
No matter who does it,
rebelling against the Shogun is a grave offense.
You saw me!
Hey, Komurasaki...
That's the iron rule.
S-S-Something is here!
I was going to...
That tool is too heavy to
be used by one person...
It's a specter!
...make you the Shogun's wife...
He did it to show his loyalties?!
Old man, let me help you!
Kyoshiro has gone too far...
No, straw hat man!
You don't have to help me!
If you want a weak woman,
go ahead and cut me up!
It's nothing!
I am a samurai's daughter!
Shut up!
Straw hat man, thank you.
I will not live in disgrace!
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for myself!
You are impertinent...
I'm gonna become stronger
and get out of here at any cost!
You go next!
Damn! I'll kill him!
Give that kid...
I can do this, too!
You're just some whore!
...to me!
All right!
I will chew her to death!
Hey! Old man!
What's going on with that prisoner?
Must have imagined it...
You okay?!
Why can he fight without any difficulty?
Do not act like you know
a damn thing about samurai!
Take these.
You're too hungry to work, right?!
If you did not laugh at me,
she would not have died!
Following regulations, all power-users wear
the Sea Prism Stones to allow them just enough to work.
Straw hat man...
He should only be able to do the bare minimum...
Brat!
Thank you for these again, straw hat man...
Whoa! Such treasures will be
taken to Onigashima?
Hand her over, Orobi!
Go eat dumplings now!
Are you saying that I'm still no match for him?!
And who the hell are you?!
Thank you very much, straw hat man.
No, that's not what I meant!
Thank you very much!
Indeed!
Do you want to hear more about
the Fire Festival, Orobi?
Robin!
He's a funny old man.
Come on, Zeus!
He's running out of breath...
Now...
Yes, I want to become acquainted with you
more and more...
Hey! Did you summon me, Nami?
How disgusting!
I'll give you a Weather Egg.
Orochi-sama...?!
Warden!
Then would you like to compete
to become my primary consort?
Hey, you!
Yeah?!
The Sea Prism Stone is working!
I need to ask you something.
He transformed.
But he has extremely strong willpower!
A curse on you...
What is it?!
BABANUKI - A WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, ELEPHANT SMILE FRUIT
Komurasaki...
This is no time for us
to be chased by a ghost!
ALPACA-MAN - A GUARD (A GIFTER)
ALPACA SMILE FRUIT
As you may know, the prisoner
Eustass Kid escaped!
Komurasaki!
A curse on you...
SNAKE-SNAKE FRUIT, MYTHICAL ZOAN TYPE
(MODEL: YAMATA-NO-OROCHI)
You're so mean...
Why isn't it attacking?!
I bet you know something.
A curse on you!
Don't pout, don't pout, Komurasaki!
It troubles me...
It stinks!
Oh, no! He noticed!
...that you seem to be able to
violate the law of physics!
How cute! You're very, very cute!
What a waste...
It's time for me to go...
Orochi-sama...
I haven't eaten this much for a long time...
It's a shame to lose that beauty!
Doesn't he know the other side of her?
Come out and fight!
I do not want to chew up your head!
I'm in training now,
There is trouble in the banquet room!
Ever since that straw hat
man came, I've been blessed.
Even if he learns about it,
she will evade reproach with that prettiness.
Capture the invaders
and get rid of the specter!
to become stronger, even a little bit,
by the time I'm released from these!
Apologize!
If you're hungry, you can't even work!
So cute!
If you plead for your life,
Not just once - he's
saved me so many times...
you will get a lighter sentence!
Hm? What's the matter, Orobi?
Stop the rampaging Orochi-sama!
You have no future,
Thank you, straw hat man!
Oh, nothing...
so why do you bother?!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna eat them with appreciation.
What are you waiting for?!
Why don't you be my sparring partner?!
Hey!
You should know your place!
Here you go, my Lord!
Apologize from the bottom of your heart!
Let me have some!
Everyone, on the floor!
Take this! The elephant's sneeze!
Ninpo!
Those dumplings look delicious!
Lightning Blast!
Komurasaki's sake sinks into the marrow!
DAIFUGO - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
SCORPION SMILE FRUIT
Elephant's Marchoo!
Komurasaki the top Oiran!
Oh, she's beautiful!
You are the Shogun...
What the hell?!
I mean,
You should learn to let things go...
don't you have something
to do with Kid's escape?!
I wish I were Orochi-sama...
But I'm scared of her darker side!
You guys were talking so often!
His spit stinks...
They say whoever falls in love loses out.
Don't worry!
She won't fall in love with you!
Stinks?! Are you messing with me?!
Right?!
She is more tamed
than any woman from your pleasure hall.
What?!
Don't forget that you have
the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
I...
You're pretty young,
but that was quite a ninpo!
...will not beg for my life!
Straw hat man, are you alive?!
But it's only a matter of
time before he gets caught!
Boss Kyoshiro.
That was close!
Only you could've done it, Onami!
Don't talk about the courtesans
like they are dogs or something...
His jailbreak was not well-planned.
She's provoking him...
Damn, he's strong!
People are flowers.
Stop! Komurasaki!
Foolishly he still has the
Sea Prism Stone cuffs on...
If you are not clean water,
your ladies won't bloom elegantly.
Warden Babanuki!
So he'll get caught soon
and face the consequences!
NEXT MORNING
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
Queen-sama is already here!
You got us there!
What?!
Komurasaki!
Stop it! Your spit really stinks!
But I heard that you brought out the Tobi Roppo
just to take down one soba cook!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
Don't tell me you're messing with me?!
You're relentless as always!
You're full of energy even in the morning,
straw-hat man...
Do you wanna go over the rules again?!
We yakuza become parents
to any underling once we exchange cups of sake.
The first offense, your arms will be cut off!
Go eat your breakfast already!
Damn you!
For the second, your legs!
Let's get to work!
If Queen-sama's showtime has already begun,
I'll kill you!
If your child came home beaten up,
what would you do?
I'll be thanking you when I use these...
And for the third, you're sentenced to death!
I'm sorry!
Idiot!
Damn! If I could use at least Haki...
You guys shouldn't mess with us!
I'm always impressed by your chivalrous spirit...
Don't mention it!
You're right, Kyoshiro!
Orochi-sama, why are you attacking us?!
You must always crush your enemy
with overwhelming force!
Stop hurting Old Man Hyo!
You're killing him!
How rude!
To make sure they'll never stand against you!
Are you messing with me?
Komurasaki-tan...
No, we're not...
She's so cute!
Even if it's...
I'm doing this for your sake as well!
...a ghost!
I'm excited!
You prisoners are getting the dumplings
for your work, right?
Oh, yeah. Hasn't he gotten up yet?
She's too good for Orochi!
We have a problem!
What if there's someone...
Huh? You're the lady from the soba shop?!
Ghost, huh? Here we go again.
Orochi-sama will talk about the Akazaya Nine again...
An inmate, Eustass Kid, escaped!
...who doesn't even work to eat them
and uses tickets he got from someone else?
Otoko-chan!
I'm glad that you're okay.
What?!
That magic user! Where did she go?!
He is still afraid of Kozuki Oden's retainers
who were wiped out two decades ago.
Komu-tan... Komu-tan...
Since you guys work hard,
can you forgive a cheater like that?
Oops.
AT THE SAME TIME
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI, LAND OF WANO
This is sweet red-bean soup.
Go ahead, Olin-san, try it!
It's showtime.
How ridiculous...
We'll stop by the brothel later!
--Of course you can't!
--My...
Give up now!
Roger!
How could you fool us?!
--Rules are rules. If someone can't follow them, he has to die!
--...precious millet dumplings...
Whoa! It smells good!
I found that woman!
Don't you think so?
Thank you!
No way!
Don't let her get away!
Dumplings...
The rule says you can only eat
what you earn by working.
So good!
When should we tell him that Komurasaki's dead?
It's delicious!
If you can't work, just starve to death!
Please stop, Orochi-sama!
We can't tell him! He'll kill us!
This soup tastes good and sweet!
Don't you agree, old man?!
Help!
I'm glad that you like it.
Hey, are you trying to get away like that?!
Big M...
Here we go!
BIG MOM (CHARLOTTE LINLIN)
CAPTAIN OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
Now, you can't even work,
All right, Komurasaki!
I'm sorry, Olin-san, but
that's all we have...
so how did you get so many food tickets?!
As you wish,
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
What is wrong?
I wish I could have more.
I will kill you with my own hands!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
Who gave them to you?
Don't speak! It'll wake her up!
But you fed me even though you're poor.
Thank you, Tsuru-san.
Dumplings...
We've got to run!
It's all over once she wakes up!
Dumplings...
If I get thinner, I'll be too popular
My precious dumplings...
No... It's no good!
Even if we run...
You greedy old man!
So I don't get thinner - that's my kind of...
Is she that strong?
If she came after us...
...funk!
What are you talking about?
Yeah, more than you'll ever know...
Do you know who she is?
Then I want her to rescue Big Bro
who is being held captive at Udon!
Everyone knows her! She's...
What?!
I may look chubby, but it's all muscle
Oh, that's a good idea!
The Oiran!
Whaaat?!
Komurasaki-dayu!
It's not so simple!
So delicious!
I can sing and dance - that's my kind of...
She is the infamous Big Mom?!
What are you doing?!
She'll never listen to us!
...funk!
You're too loud!
You have no right to eat anything!
Let's go, Chopperemon!
I'm excited!
Who is Big Mom?
Let's go!
I'll tell you later!
Don't eat dumplings if you don't work!
Thanks for waiting!
Spit them out! Spit them out, shitty old man!
This is it!
You pieces of crap!
Prepare yourself!
Are you sure?
Once she gets her memory back, we'll be screwed!
I'm gonna kill her right now!
QUEEN THE PLAGUE
A LEAD PERFORMER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Bounty: 1.32 BILLION BERRIES
Please stop!
That's right! Think of her as Kaido!
It's better than just waiting here!
She's the same as Kaido!
I want to go! This is the chance!
You damn specter!
Go away!
Climb on my back!
I won't spit them out...
I am going to haunt you! I am going to curse you!
Oh, okay.
Straw hat man, you gave me these dumplings...
T-Too late!
Um...
What is it, lovely Chopperemon?
Anyway, just run!
I will never... ever...
Paw.
All right.
...waste them!
Let's hear it one by one, Babanuki.
There! You've got to see this, too!
O-Okay...
Ranking what troubles you the most recently!
Where...
I'm hungry...
Old man! Why?!
Where... am I?
I wanna eat more...
It serves him right!
That's what you'll get if you mess with us!
I can't help but be scared!
Keep that in mind!
We need your help. Olin.
Number three!
What?!
Eustass Kid escaped.
Let's go to Udon together!
Now, spill it with dumplings!
What?!
What idiot has been giving you the tickets?!
Udon? That's where I'm going?
This is...
What?!
That is right!
Number two!
I heard that Udon's Lead Performer
likes sweet red-bean soup!
The keys to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs
have been stolen.
...pandemonium!
I ate them!
What?!
How much do you wanna mess with me?
Yeah, yeah! They have tons of red-bean soup!
And number one!
I won't go easy on you.
I'll make you say your accomplice's name,
Straw Hat Luffy is on the run.
Who...
I lied before I knew it...
Whaaat?!
and kill you both!
...am I?!
If there's no red-bean soup,
she'll kill me!
Chase him, you idiot!
There's tons of red-bean soup there?!
Let's get a move on!
Komurasaki's determination can't be destroyed
even by Orochi's fangs!
Wano's special mixed bath! Nami and
Robin's sexiness catches everyone's eye while they bathe!
Taking down Kaido!
Being laughed at by a girl, Otoko,
Orochi is infuriated by his humiliation!
Luffy takes down the Headliner guard
That goal gives Luffy indomitable fighting
spirit and he makes a heroic move!
and climbs up the wall
in order to break out.
She sees imminent danger,
but this samurai's daughter won't back down an inch!
The banquet turns into hell! Orochi loses his senses and changes
into something ghoulish in order to destroy everything!
In that hellish camp where guards
act mercilessly and atrociously,
However, a funky singing
voice suddenly echoes around!
Meanwhile, Luffy fights against heavy odds
and Queen gives him a dreadful sentence!
Kyoshiro closes in to kill her!
Life, pride, and schemes... What will be the outcome?
there is only one man who
Luffy became close to!
To the sound of enthusiastic cheers, Queen, a supreme officer
Who is the surprising figure who stands in Orochi's way
to save the girl's life?!
The emotional bond they share that was born in hell
will blow up a storm!
Luffy and Old Man Hyo's deadly challenge begins!
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates, begins the show!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pandemonium! The Monster Snake, Shogun Orochi!"
"A Lead Performer! Queen the Plague Emerges!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Climb up! Luffy's Desperate Escape!"
"The Flower Falls! The Final Moment of the
Most Beautiful Woman in the Land of Wano!"
"The Bond Between Prisoners!
Luffy and Old Man Hyo!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!