One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
BATH
BATHHOUSE
Hey, Balloon!
They're not good enough!
Nin, nin, nin...
Don't you have someone stronger?
This is a ninja's true worth!
That's true.
If Boss Hyogoro the Flower were here,
You can fight me if you want!
I got the keys!
The first Haki he showed me was
a very high level one.
he could've united the samurai at once.
Unguarded!
Hmm... Is he that great?
Having obtained the key to Luffy's cuffs,
Raizo raced to meet him.
Who's next?!
They're not even a good enough warm up!
Help!
Yeah!
You stole my sword, didn't you?
He was the most influential man behind the scenes
in the Land of Wano 20 years ago,
It is not your sword...
and the great boss who had complete control
over the Flower Capital underworld.
I'll make use of this for now...
Meanwhile, Luffy and Old Man Hyo
who dodged the attack of the guards...
He was also trusted by
the bosses of the other five regions,
...were trying to break out of
the Excavation Labor Camp.
Are you a weapon collector?
and nice even to commoners.
He was a real chivalrous yakuza
who had both power and magnetism.
What are you gonna do with all those?
Thanks for waiting!
You pieces of crap!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
Here we go!
We happen to need a lot of weapons, too.
Climb on my back!
Oh, okay.
And number one!
Your weapon collection...
Straw Hat Luffy is on the run.
How strong...
Whaaat?!
I'm gonna take the whole thing!
S-Samurai-sama!
"Climb up!
Luffy's Desperate Escape!"
Without laying a finger...
I will bring you down instead,
you damn mountain bandit!
Send him flying!
It's Queen-sama's Special Device Performance!
I'm sorry if I confused you.
The Sumo Inferno!
I'm...
Forget it.
...a pirate!
Let's move on!
Queen! Queen! Queen!
"Gyukimaru!
Zoro Fights a Duel on Bandit's Bridge!"
"Zoro, Stunned!
The Shocking Identity of the Mysterious Woman!"
Queen!
You'll be fine as long as you keep winning
sumo matches!
Damn!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
That was close!
Now you're getting serious.
It's impossible, straw hat man!
But stepping out of the ring means instant death!
You guys are a tag team!
If both of you fall out of the ring, the execution is complete!
You'll never know until you try!
I wanna eat the red-bean soup already...
But if you ever change your mind
and wanna join our group,
Hey, haven't we reached
the place called Udon yet?
only Straw Hat will be released!
Chopperemon!
Wait a minute!
If we fight as a tag team,
I'll give Straw Hat-san trouble!
I'm hungry.
Don't look at me drooling like that!
Could you at least execute us separately?!
It won't be long, Olin-chan!
Hey, come on!
Hey, Balloon!
You pieces of crap!
Balloon?!
Once we get to Udon,
we'll save Big Bro Luffy.
Come on, come on! Kick their asses now!
Straw Hat-san!
If I kick your ass...
Catch him already!
And then...
"A Big Turnover!
The Three-Sword Style Overcomes Danger!"
will you let us out of here?!
...we'll eat...
...the red-bean soup!
I wanna join a sumo match myself!
What did you say?!
Otama-chan, do you like it, too?
Gross!
Yeah, I love it!
"Dead or Alive!
Queen's Sumo Inferno!"
I was treated to it by Otsuru-san
on my birthday!
We're almost there!
My mouth slowly filled with
the sweetness of the red-bean paste...
My taste buds were truly dancing!
Maybe, he can...
I know!
You idiot!
Does he really think
he can get out of here?!
Red-bean paste is the best!
I told you that you'd get killed
if you mess with us!
Yes! Yes! Absolutely!
Come on! Get back here!
Oh, the spit guy from earlier!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Not just Alpaca-man!
Red-bean paste! And a rice cake!
My stomach hurts!
He said he's gonna kick my ass!
I've never had such a soft and delicious thing
in my life!
Feels like I'm missing something...
I know, I know!
A white rice cake shines
like a living frog's eyeball!
What?!
You crack me up.
A frog's eyeball?
I'm Madillo-man! A Gifter who ate...
Olin-chan, that's a little freaky.
Oh, yeah? Just by thinking about it,
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
the Armadillo Smile Fruit!
MADILLO-MAN - A GIFTER
ARMADILLO SMILE FRUIT
I can't help drooling.
No, no!
I'm sorry, old man.
We fell quite far down...
Oh, your body looks so tough!
This isn't good practice at all!
Queen-sama! He'll understand once it starts!
I'm not edible!
Perfect for my training!
No, don't be sorry!
Practice?
You fool!
I can't wait to have the red-bean soup!
He doesn't realize how unreasonable its rules are!
He's not dead yet!
The bullets that are loaded in these
are made of the Sea Prism Stone!
Hey, Balloon!
They are getting quite excited
talking about the red-bean soup.
Guys, get out of my way!
They're not good enough!
He has no idea that
he's got no chance to survive!
Straw Hat!
Babanuki-sama!
It's no good.
Don't you have someone stronger?
Since you're a power-user,
go ahead and curl up in a ball!
I'll take care of them!
You can fight me if you want!
What should I do?
You're right!
Elephant's Marchoo!
Then, get ready and enter the ring, guys!
Just like an armadillo!
Once she finds out there's no red-bean soup,
the shock might bring back her memories,
That bastard... He's pushing his luck!
You guys are finished!
and she'll return to herself!
Straw Hat!
I think you still don't understand
the situation you're in.
Instead of saving him,
we'll put Luffy in harm's way!
They're finished?
Why can't he see? They're
not finished at all!
Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
What should I do?!
What am I supposed to do?!
Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
Deathmatch!
To set an example for other prisoners,
I'll take my time torturing you!
Hell hasn't been unleashed yet.
Luffy-dono!
Th-There are too many of them...
Straw Hat!
First you, old man!
On top of that, all of us have weapons.
We'll begin with you, you worthless shit!
I have good news!
I'm hungry-bear!
You guys are unarmed!
The key to your cuffs...
If I defeat Straw Hat,
can I get the prisoners' dumplings all to myself-bear?
--Bring me more red-bean soup!
--Yes, sir!
Old man!
Look! I got it!
Now do you realize that you're gonna die soon?!
Go right, crouch down, and jump!
What?!
BEAR-MAN - A GIFTER
BEAR SMILE FRUIT
Go to hell!
Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
--Run!
--Okay!
Luffy-dono?
Yes, you can. Rock the place up!
Go right!
Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
Isn't he here?
That's my Queen-bear!
Crouch down!
I became 100 times more motivated-bear!
--And...
--Damn you!
Deathmatch!
Jump!
Rest in peace... Old Man Hyo... Straw Hat...
What?!
You're so greedy!
I won't let you have the dumplings!
Lock eyes with your opponents!
This time, it's a bear Gifter...
Are you okay, old man?
What?!
Don't look away!
Y-Yes, I think so...
He's quite pretty...
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn, damn, damn, damn, damn, damn!
Let's go-bear!
Observe what happens to those
who disobey us in this place!
Good job, old man! Keep it up!
What the...
Can you foresee the future or something?
Bear!
Screw you!
Luffytaro wins!
No one can do that!
What did you actually do?!
Ready...
You did it, Luffytaro!
Those punches...
Gee... You took down all the Pleasures.
I'll make you understand
that escape from Udon is impossible!
I'm sorry, straw hat man...
...aren't working at all-bear!
What?!
I put you through this...
I can't get him! Dammit!
Straw hat man!
Stay close to me.
Outside he looks pretty,
but he's still a bear!
That's not it.
U-Unbelievable...
What's not it? You won again!
Go!
They say that bears' claws are
powerful enough to sever human bodies!
Watch this, damn prisoners!
Well, Rayleigh was doing it effortlessly.
Be careful!
Go!
This is what'll happen to you
if you disobey guards!
Rayleigh?
Old man! Go left next!
Yeah.
Your body's...
--What?!
--You fool!
...tough.
Luffy.
Left!
When you use the Haki of the Color of Arms,
imagine you're wearing invisible armor.
So what-bear?
Dammit, that old shit!
This is more like it...
Take this!
Because Kaido's body is even tougher!
At that moment, Rayleigh sent the elephant flying
without touching it.
Go to hell!
Shut up!
Left! Left! Left! Left!
Bear!
The first Haki he showed me was
a very high level one.
Without laying a finger...
You can't get away from me this time!
You fool!
Who's next?!
They're not even a good enough warm up!
Send him flying!
If I can use that...
Damn, you little shit!
Whaaat?!
Stop moving!
Gum-Gum...
Don't tell me he's...
How annoying!
...Grizzly...
Leave them to me!
Right there!
...Magnum!
So he uses the Color of the Supreme King...
Damn, when I try to use force,
I can't help hitting them!
It's him again!
Elephant's Marchoo!
You can't take me down with guns!
I can take down Kaido!
What have you been...
You...
Y-You bastard!
It's taking too much time!
...up to?
I guess this is gonna be interesting...
If you let me do it,
the execution will be done in no time!
Forget it.
Let's move on!
Pleasures, enter the ring!
Next!
You don't really understand
how the Sumo Inferno works!
Oh, Dogstorm!
Old man!
Where have you been?
What's the matter, Kin'emon?
I have no other option!
Look!
The length of the fight
We have a huge problem!
AN ABANDONED VILLAGE, KURI
KIN'EMON AND MINK MUSKETEERS
and the number of opponents.
Those are the toughest elements in fights.
Go to hell!
It's been uproarious since he came...
They found out about
the flyer with the symbol and the moon tattoo?!
Give up now!
He'll lose his spirit and energy little by little
and die miserably.
Damn! I feel weak!
Yes, and now it's a big mess!
In any case, don't let Boss Hyogoro die.
What should we do, Duke-sama?!
"The execution will be done in no time"?!
Without laying a finger, send him flying!
We were handing them out covertly...
Don't be silly.
I do not know how it leaked...
I'm counting on you, Luffytaro.
Tsk. You gave us so much trouble...
That's not exciting at all!
We wrote it in the coded symbol
in case it fell into unintended hands.
That's not it.
I want a refill!
That's just the normal Color of Arms...
Again?! You've already had
so much red-bean soup!
I got something to tell you two!
But they somehow know the link between
the ankle tattoo and this flyer.
Screw you!
Red-bean soup is like oxygen to me!
Damn!
EBISU TOWN
Arma-Defense!
Here you go.
I feel refreshed!
No one else can have it!
No, don't worry at all!
Now in the capital,
A BATHHOUSE, FLOWER CAPITAL
My red-bean soup! It's my favorite!
This isn't it...
You can use the empty house all you want!
Again, this is just the
normal Color of Arms...
I heard our allies are getting caught
by Kaido and Orochi's underlings.
We can have tea upstairs.
Oh, my soup!
What?! You're not gonna hit me?!
If you're Zorojuro-san's friends, feel free!
Let's go see then.
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
Alpaca Fencing!
Thanks.
It's a raid!
No, no, you see,
people are dying of hunger one after another.
Send my opponent flying
as if I'm wearing invisible armor!
Hey! Which way should I go next?!
Stop resisting, you rebel!
Straw hat man!
So there are a bunch of empty houses!
Straw hat man, what are you...
I found the flyer!
All right! Stop right there!
A Headliner of the Animal Kingdom Pirates - Hawkins!
You really don't have to worry!
What?!
What's so funny?
All right!
Easy!
He laughs a lot.
Nobody move!
I wanna practice! Bring it on!
He's got the moon tattoo, too!
What do you want from a bathhouse?
It's easier this way!
Those who have the mark on their ankles
are rebels!
All you can do is laugh
when you're this hungry!
I'm sorry!
Oh, a bathhouse is perfect for this
As you wish!
Let's do it, Alpaca-man!
If anyone sees it, let us know!
because everyone's naked
and we can see everything.
Okay!
Your next opponents are...
Anyway, you just missed meeting Zorojuro-san!
Put me down!
I don't wanna give you any more trouble!
...the Gifters!
Drake, what are you doing? Get inside.
Where did he go?
I won't miss any secret talk.
Well, he suddenly rushed out of here!
Rumors spread quickly...
Everyone in the capital already knows about it.
My duty is to take down the fool
called Soba Mask.
No, actually, the heavier the better!
Bat Smile Fruit!
He said his sword got stolen!
What?!
We shouldn't take our time
patrolling bathhouses now.
Bat-man!
Take care of those chores by yourselves.
I don't know how far he's gone...
The beautiful leg.
You're lucky.
It's highly likely that he got lost
and can't find the way back.
I'm a swift runner!
For my training!
What should we do, Shinobu-chan?!
I think they know about us.
What do you mean by that?
Gazelle Smile Fruit!
As always...
You're Germa. Cut the crap!
Gazelle-man!
FLOWER CAPITAL
By the way, why isn't Blackleg-ya with us?
They came for us.
It's no fair!
People are defenseless here!
We're the Gifters!
RASETSU TOWN, FLOWER CAPITAL
Yeah, I haven't seen him for a while...
Shall we fight?
That's the last resort.
Go to hell, Germa 66!
That fool!
Mature women don't use weapons carelessly...
The ability to become invisible...
PRISON
Oh, no! There are two Gifters!
RASETSU PRISON
Soba Mask!
I guess I have to try it there...
RASETSU TOWN PRISONERS' QUARTERS
AKA: PUBLIC CELLS
They kidnapped Tama, didn't they?
I didn't expect to see this
many ruffians in here!
Hide behind me.
Is it Stealth Black's transmission device?!
How dare you mess with Holdem-sama
and Bakura Town!
By the way...
People, have a good look at them!
It's time to show
the power of the enticing sexy body!
Hang on tight!
is there a bathhouse?
You can't get away with it!
These are the faces of the fools
who want to rebel against Orochi-sama and Kaido-sama!
Don't tell me...
Great! They're perfect sparring partners!
Everyone, line up
and show us your ankles!
...he's already gone to...
BATH
What?!
Only Stealth Black could've done it!
BATHHOUSE
Lock eyes with your opponents!
If you have a Reversed Crescent Moon
tattooed on your ankle, we need you to come with us!
A BATHHOUSE, FLOWER CAPITAL
I'll take him down next time!
It wasn't just my fault.
You also let them get away.
It's so relaxing!
All of those people who are in the tub
must come out, too!
I can't believe it.
How does he know?!
Get your ass in there already!
So this is how a bath is in the Land of Wano.
Oh? Oh, boy!
--Go check.
--Yes, sir!
But isn't it a little too hot?
This is...!
Was the plan leaked?
On the night of the Fire
Festival... Habu Port...
Well, we think it's cool...
I feel sorry for you guys!
...to endure it and say something like,
"Today's bath is a bit too chilly, isn't it?"
Your plot has already been revealed...
And the Reversed Crescent Moon,
the symbol of rebellion!
Ready...
It's a complete failure.
Fukurokuju-dono, wait!
I can't relate to that...
Go!
Someone's hiding there!
What makes you think that
this ankle tattoo is the symbol of rebellion?!
Say, Shinobu-chan.
I've been thinking...
This is just a popular design!
We have nothing to do with any kind of rebellion!
Come out!
What's that low entrance way?
Nami! I'll back you up if something happens.
Cut it out!
Then, how do you explain about this flyer?
Oh, that's called a Pomegranate Gate.
Beautiful Leg Spin Kick!
They put the wooden piece low so that
the bath won't get too cool and the steam won't escape.
No, I didn't mean to hide!
The Reversed Crescent Moon
at the center of the flyer...
Oh, I see. Thank you for your explanation.
I'm just an ordinary customer...
I assume it is a symbol pointing to a rebellion
against Orochi-sama...
You are...!
Komurasaki-dayu!
By the way, Orobi, do you get hot easily?
Don't you wanna bathe in the hot water?
It looks just like your tattoos.
I'm not comfortable soaking in a tub
in a public bathhouse.
If anything happens...
It is an order from Orochi-sama.
Just shut up and stay in there!
All right!
How dare you!
You're as cautious as a ninja!
It was just an ordinary punch.
Magic users such as me and Orobi
get weaker when we soak in water.
Boss Kyoshiro...
Komurasaki's wake has been canceled.
But don't worry! No enemies will come.
If so many upset people like them pour in,
there might be an accident...
I'll do it right this time!
A BROTHEL, FLOWER CAPITAL
The enemies aren't here but...
Look at that. Should I charge them?
I think the funeral tomorrow will be
even more crowded...
--Dynamite!
--Oh, my! That body is a national treasure!
That wasn't it!
We're in big trouble...
Luffy.
Will everyone think...
It's invisible armor.
--May she rest in peace!
--Komurasaki-dayu!
Invisible...
I can't believe...
How deadly!
...that we told them about the plan?
--Komurasaki!
--Komurasaki-sama!
...armor!
I can't believe it!
Quite a lot of people
hold a grudge against you,
...it's a mixed bath!
Don't worry...
That's very powerful, Nami-san!
I know Captain will believe us...
Yes, it is.
Gum-Gum...
Happy punch!
so please be careful.
Aren't you familiar with
a mixed bath like this?
What?!
They don't know what they're talking about...
...Bullet!
Well, I know...
What the...
He's the guy from yesterday.
...that those men can't
take their eyes off of me,
Soba Mask!
Kyoshiro!
but it can't be helped!
Nami-sa...
KYOSHIRO SLASHED KOMURASAKI TO DEATH
Young men are all...
The shape of Nami-san's body
was like a magnificent mighty river flowing...
Sanji! Why is he here?!
--Hey, move!
--Old woman, you're in the way!
Alpaca Fencing!
What is he wearing?!
You've got to be kidding!
The winner is Luffytaro!
Get out of the way!
Drake!
Move! Move! Move!
Soba Mask?!
He was inside all along!
Ninpo!
NINPO
You bastard!
Ball-Crusher!
BALL-CRUSHER
Hey! Where is Soba Mask?!
This Straw Hat is quite strong!
What?!
Hmmm... That wasn't it.
Where...
There was no other way...
What?
That hurts!
I'm not supposed to touch them.
The one who'll suffer the biggest loss...
I wish I could try something more.
Why didn't you tell me that
you're sensitive to naked women?!
What's wrong?! Finish it up already!
Alpaca-man! Madillo-man!
...is me.
I'm not...
Certainly.
Oh, well!
Just take them down!
Drake...
You're from the North Blue, aren't you?
All right!
Orochi-sama is frustrated.
So are you... Why are you asking?
Next!
Are you trying to help us
by carrying the old man, Straw Hat?!
Bring it on!
I guess that it's because of this.
Let's move on to the washing area.
Then you know him, don't you?
Okay! Bring me more!
Y-Yes, sir!
When you get warmed up enough,
you ask Sansuke to wash your back.
You fool!
You're already playing into our hands!
Who's Sansuke?
Take this, Straw Hat!
--Let's use a combination technique!
--Okay!
Germa 66's...
He's Sansuke.
Madillo Spin!
...Stealth Black!
That's what we call the person
who washes our backs at a bathhouse.
Alpaca Fire!
I met Ryuma.
Why an octopus?
Komurasaki!
Well, he has eight limbs.
He's suited to the job.
Don't lie to me!
Oh, they've merged together!
That's not the point.
Here comes the combination technique!
All right.
Great! Go get them!
Grab one of these.
Orochi-sama... has not
come out of his room...
Oh, okay.
Kyoshiro is scary.
I don't know what he's thinking.
You met Ryuma?!
It cannot be helped.
His love interest, Komurasaki, was killed in front of him.
How could I believe such nonsense?!
Of course you don't. He's a yakuza.
Just keep it up!
What're you talkin' about, you idiot?!
Well, the soul belonged to
someone else I knew.
Hey! Bring more!
The Land of Wano's yakuza are
supposed to be the commoners' allies.
On top of that, there is this.
Yes, sir!
Stop talking gibberish!
Young people may not know it,
but there used to be...
This symbol points to a rebellion
against Orochi-sama and Kaido-sama.
How could you know Ryuma?!
Everyone from the North Blue knows
the story of Sora, Warrior of the Sea...
...a great yakuza boss named
Hyogoro the Flower.
Ryuma is a great swordsman
who was said to cut any opponent in an instant!
The fire suggests the Fire Festival.
The two birds indicate twilight.
Is that the person Kanjuro was talking about?
The habu snake implies Habu
Port, the rendezvous point.
Germa... Is he the real thing?
You do not know how valuable
the great sword Shusui is!
20 years ago, the greatest yakuza boss
in the Land of Wano was...
Kaido's body is far tougher than this!
That means some people will raid Onigashima
on the night of the Fire Festival?
...Hyogoro the Flower.
Shusui is the Land of Wano's treasure!
It belongs to Ryuma!
But we found out beforehand, so all we need to do
is find the rebels and keep them under control.
That's true.
If Boss Hyogoro the Flower were here,
Stop running!
The search is not over...
he could've united the samurai at once.
And we will teach them the hard way
who reigns over the Land of Wano.
This is our chance to escape!
That wasn't it! I can't do it right!
To be honest, I don't think
we can recruit 5,000 troops in a week like this.
A long time ago, when the Land of Wano
I won't let you!
What?!
was recognized as the Land
of Gold by other countries...
You sent them flying.
Wasn't that good enough?
Maybe 500, at most.
Hmm... Is he that great?
Gold? What are you talking about?
No, it wasn't, old man!
Unguarded!
You bastard!
You can't attack women!
Yeah!
Every time you hit someone,
you've been saying, "That wasn't it" this whole time.
He was the most influential man behind the scenes
in the Land of Wano 20 years ago,
Pirates around the world wanted gold.
What are you trying to do?
and the great boss who had complete control
over the Flower Capital underworld.
An acceleration device?!
What am I trying to do? I'm training myself!
I have to become strong!
Nobles tried to rule
the Land of Gold - the Land of Wano!
Stop, you two!
He was also trusted by
the bosses of the other five regions,
Nothing will be solved by arguing!
What? Training yourself?!
and nice even to commoners.
He showed those enemies from overseas
how formidable he was...
Despite being in the middle of a deadly show,
EBISU TOWN
He was a real chivalrous yakuza
who had both power and magnetism.
We're friends!
Let's talk!
Even a flotation device...
is he training himself?!
I don't have anything to talk to you about!
and burned the Land of Wano's samurai
in their minds!
Oden-sama had respect for him, too,
since he was young...
Stealth Black!
You're a member of the evil army.
Why are you helping people?!
Hey, what's up, kids?
Then, if we can find him...
That is who Ryuma is.
It seems like you're having fun!
I wanna throw a punch that will send my enemies flying
without touching them!
Stealth Black!
It's been over 20 years.
Don't call me that!
They're fighting!
I'm Soba Mask!
Fighting? That's not good...
Rumor has it that...
There are so many legends related to him
as a swordsman.
Here, you can have this,
so go someplace else.
You're Germa. Cut the crap!
One of them...
...he refused to be subordinate to the Kurozumi Clan
and was killed by Orochi!
--Yay!
--Thank you, Yasu-san!
...says that he slayed a dragon
that appeared above the capital!
I'm not gonna give up on my crew!
In contrast, Fukurokuju
who leads the Oniwabanshu
Go to hell, Germa 66!
I'll go save them!
that supported the Kozuki Clan
with Boss Hyogoro the Flower...
After his death, he was laid to rest in a temple
with the great sword Shusui...
Are you out of your mind?
It'll be like you're turning yourself in!
...chose to serve Orochi.
Soba Mask!
...as this country's God of the Blade.
That way,
Is it Stealth Black's transmission device?!
I worked for him at that time,
but I couldn't take it so I ran.
Our allies who wanna take down Orochi
are getting caught one after another...
I think I can break Kaido's tough scales!
Shusui is a national treasure!
Hang on tight!
So I became their enemy!
...ever since your crew messed up!
--He's flying!
--Chase him!
I see...
What do you mean?!
You're...
That little bear and the others...
...Hanzo?!
So you're alive! You man-seducing...
...definitely told them about our plan!
Only Stealth Black could've done it!
Okay. I understand.
I'll take him down next time!
...sexy kunoichi.
Bepo and the others would rather die than talk!
Don't underestimate them!
That's why he knew you!
Shinobu-chan, you're so cool!
Sanji-kun, what is this all about?!
NORTHERN GRAVEYARD, RINGO
It's a long story! I'll tell you later!
But it has nothing to do with me!
I kind of am!
Wait! That's exactly what
the enemies want, Tra-guy!
Aren't you losing too much blood?
I miss him...
I could die happy right now!
You can't tell me what to do, Blackleg-ya!
I'll take back Shusui!
Boss Hyogoro...
Let's get to Ebisu Town!
Usopp and the others will be there!
I don't feel comfortable
with just two swords.
He's become a part of history now...
Both of you, simmer down.
You're the one who needs to cool your head!
You're not okay, are you?!
I think I have overestimated you.
It's not a big deal...
Anyway, it's not a good thing
that they know about the ankle tattoo!
You've got to...
Shusui is a Black Blade!
You've got to trust your friends!
Stop making me repeat myself...
In other words, it was forged
through the battles that Ryuma fought!
Yeah, I wonder how they found that out...
You're the most untrustworthy person I know!
I said if you join our pirate group,
Kaido-san will pardon you for everything!
Before I went to the bathhouse,
I heard more bad news.
Happy punch!
I was only trying to figure
out if you were a punk
What?!
with no backbone who just wanted to have it!
Shut up! I refuse!
Bepo and the others were captured!
What the...
He's the guy from yesterday.
What?
"Forged"?
Talk about bad timing!
Sword...
Soba Mask!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates are looking to
lure Tra-guy using his friends as bait.
Oh, yeah, I was wondering about that...
Luffy-dono!
Nami-sa...
Sword!
I have the key!
The shape of Nami-san's body
was like a magnificent mighty river flowing...
I'm sure he'll go rescue them.
It brings back memories,
doesn't it, Hyogoro?!
He may not look it, but he cares about his friends.
You were approached quite feverishly
by Kaido-san and Orochi back then.
Sanji! Why is he here?!
We must stop him for now!
You are...
The legendary yakuza became
such a malnourished old man,
What is he wearing?!
You've got to be kidding!
Or the Flower Capital will be in chaos!
You surprised me!
Please do not get up yet.
What were you doing at such a serious time?
and he will die a miserable death!
Don't tell me that Black Blades are...
I didn't see anything at all...
It is not good for your wound...
Go!
How did you get punched
to end up looking like that?
She's right! You don't need to get up yet!
What? Did he say Hyogoro?!
No way! That small Old Man Hyo?!
Where am I?
Are you trying to run?!
Help!
I don't care about myself,
You must eliminate those who got caught!
but have mercy on this young man!
Unguarded!
To silence them!
--What are you waiting for?!
--I wanna see Straw Hat's blood splattered already!
What did you say?!
I'm begging you!
That's what we do in the ninja world!
Thank you very much for
saving our lives earlier.
Please!
You bastard...
You're scary, Shinobu!
What's wrong with him?
Don't try your best to catch me off guard!
What should I do?
Catching people off guard is the only way to
win deadly battles, so that is all I am trying!
Thank you!
Okay, I got an idea!
We're not doing this for fun!
I came up with something exciting!
But you got badly injured in return...
Since I had the Sea Prism Stone cuffs on for so long,
I feel so much lighter!
Luffy-dono...
I really don't know what to do
to repay you...
I cannot believe it...
You really look exactly like you did back in those days.
Somebody, help!
Someone is trying to kill us!
Gum-Gum...
For two decades...
Oh, there's a samurai!
...Jet Gatling!
Who is it?!
I got hurt because I suck.
Is anyone there?!
Hey! Help us!
You guys have nothing to do with it...
For 20 years, we've been waiting for this!
It is me, Raizo...
My technique got stronger, too!
Are they serious or just fooling around?
I can't tell!
If we fail now, there
won't be another chance!
Where did he go?!
Is Momonosuke-sama alive?
He still has Shusui!
I'm not getting tired at all!
Swordsmen, please help!
Don't tell me you are...
No, you cannot go out
with such a grave wound!
Let's get rid of the old man first!
...Kawamatsu?!
Ouch!
Blood?
Go to hell!
The wound is on that side, idiot!
I guess they're not joking.
I am sorry!
Gee...
Stop it, Shinobu!
Goodbye!
K...
Kan-sama...
Straw hat man...
Do not go! Your wound has not yet healed!
Kawamatsu?!
I'm sorry to give you so much trouble...
Is it...
Things do not always go the way you want!
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
I said my wound is right there!
Why can't you see?!
...really you?!
I can relate to your frustration!
Please pay no mind to a dotard like me
and fight with all your might!
I-I am so sorry!
But without help from these people
who miraculously have the same purpose as us,
You are alive!
Fighting with all my might isn't enough.
Ow, ow, ow...
Yeah... I am glad that I was able to put up with
all that rotten fish for 13 years.
we cannot fulfill Oden-sama's wish!
What?
Uh, um, are you okay?
I feel like I still need something more...
Don't touch me!
You're gonna be fine, Samurai-san!
Let me see your face, Kawamatsu!
You'll get better soon!
I can't. I am chained!
I stole this toad oil
ointment in the capital...
What?!
I mean, I bought it!
Excuse me, thank you!
Hold it right there!
You stole it...
When will the fight be?
No...
Unguarded!
N-No, I bought it.
I heard your voice outside!
Nine days from now, on the
night of the Fire Festival!
Well, I don't care either way.
Chopping Kaido's head off
during the festival to pay tribute to him is a great idea!
You all have good voices!
Toad oil is amazing!
No... This isn't good enough...
Hey, who are you?!
If you apply it to a sword-cut,
it'll just go away!
Why don't you wait?!
Oh?
I am sorry, Raizo,
but could you get me out of here first?!
Toad oil, huh?
Well, I hope it'll work!
Whoa! You're so beautiful!
Are you a goddess?!
Of course I will! I will
get to it right away!
He's still...
Hey, you, take a hint!
Stop it!
Our duel is not over!
Gum-Gum...
Say, Samurai-san!
In order to set you free,
Would you like to come in?
Oh, thank you.
I guess I need the key to the
cage and the key to the cuffs.
I'll fight you! But could you wait?!
Hey!
Yeah, I do not know if they will open
since they are rusted.
Stay with us!
...Kong Organ Gun!
Don't tell me...
There's someone at the forbidden cell!
...you're Shinobu-chan?!
Who is that?!
That's the guy!
Well, at least until the wound heals,
you had better stay here...
Solitaire-sama!
Kanjuro-kun!
We found the key thief
from the Executive Tower!
Oh, I see, I see!
Don't let him escape!
Then this is the real thing!
Oh, no!
You are the murderer - Zorojuro, right?
Smoke Escape Jutsu!
This is what everyone's
talking about in the capital!
You got something to eat?
A WANTED PERSON IN THE FLOWER CAPITAL
Yes! Do you want some now?!
--He disappeared!
--He must be a ninja!
I got excited!
Find him!
Will the decisive battle start soon?!
HITOKIRI KAMAZO
Zorojuro, why would you
wanna help that woman?
Now, leave the key thief to the others and...
Thunder Bagua!
Why do you wanna slash a woman?
...bring the thing here!
I'm only trying to kill that brat
who won't stop laughing.
Would you like to have more?
Gyukimaru?
Oh, yes.
Everyone knows him in the capital.
Gyukimaru on Bandit's Bridge.
Don't worry, Toko.
Hitokiri Kamazo.
All right.
I've already taken the great sword - Shusui
back to where it belongs.
You're a street slasher
who randomly kills people in the capital.
We'll execute the fools!
Yes, sir!
But you're actually an assassin working for Orochi
while disguised as an outlaw!
Hey! Come this way!
That is a treasure which was stolen from
the legendary samurai of the Land of Wano - Ryuma's grave!
Here we go!
Otherwise, why would you want to kill Otoko?
We do not know where he lives,
You address the Shogun, Orochi-sama,
with no honorific.
but the warrior monk shows himself
whenever an armed person tries to cross the bridge.
...out of my reach!
Who are you?
Samurai-sama, please help us!
So I can always meet him there?
Then there's no need to hurry...
Unguarded!
Well, of course, I'm not gonna just stand here
and watch a kid and a woman get killed...
I wonder who that Gyukimaru is,
but first, who are you two?
It's Queen-sama's Special Device Performance!
That Grim Reaper was after your lives...
I will give you anything you want!
The Sumo Inferno!
Oh, yeah!
That's it!
Sake and food would be nice...
LAND OF WANO
Queen! Queen! Queen!
You got it!
The thing is we made
the Shogun of the Land of Wano angry...
Queen!
All right! Deal!
Meanwhile, in Ringo
on the east side of the Land of Wano...
Sumo?
What the...?!
RINGO, LAND OF WANO
The Shogun, huh?
This collar is the same as the ones
I just put on you guys!
Oro... Oroshi?
No, Orochi.
I can't pull it out!
You made him angry
so he sent that assassin after you?
Imagine this stone pillar is you!
No problem. I've been told that I can kill
as many as I want if they get in my way.
If you leave the ring with that thing on...
Yes, if one makes him angry,
they must die in the Land of Wano.
I often get in trouble afterwards
when I slay someone who has a boss.
I'll make use of this for now...
How scary!
Say, Samurai-san!
Don't worry!
If you leave the ring,
the sharp blades will be ejected as you saw,
My name is Toko!
You'll be the one dying!
TOKO
If you say it with an "O,"
it's Otoko (Male), but I'm not male!
OTOKO
and your head will get cut off in an instant!
Isn't it funny?
No, not really.
Three...
Damn! It's just like the
Celestial Dragons' collar!
What? What?!
...swords?!
I will help myself to that weapon!
Everyone says it's funny!
Why don't you think so?!
Of course, it's not designed to be taken off by force
so it's no use!
I don't know.
Three-Sword Style!
I can't remove it!
You are attired as a samurai from the Land of Wano,
but you are from overseas, aren't you?
You'll be fine as long as you keep winning
sumo matches!
I still have to collect more...
Purgatory...
But stepping out of the
ring means instant death!
You don't look like a bad...
You guys are a tag team!
If both of you fall out of the ring, the execution is complete!
A bad per...
A bad person.
--Say it smoothly!
--I am sorry!
But if you ever change your mind
and wanna join our group,
...Onigiri!
Samurai-san, you look scary!
only Straw Hat will be released!
But you're a really nice person
because you saved us!
There you are.
On this side, we'll use weapons,
fight in numbers, and have no collars!
You stole my sword, didn't you?
He's quite strong!
We'll deploy as many people as we want.
It is not your sword...
So I'll do you one favor!
I'll remove your Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
I've already taken the great sword - Shusui
back to where it belongs.
What? Whaaat?!
That is a treasure which was stolen from the
I went through a lot of trouble!
legendary samurai of the Land of Wano - Ryuma's grave!
Then, this is not the key
for Luffy-dono's cuffs!
I know!
Then, shut up and go away!
Yay!
How strong...
You're a really nice person!
This means you're letting us out!
Otherwise, I will swipe those two swords
on your waist, too!
Aren't you forgetting about the collar?
I put something worse on you!
Um...
Are you a weapon collector?
Damn... Not before the decisive battle!
I will tell you a secret,
but you must keep it...
Oh, yeah!
What are you gonna do with all those?
Wait a minute!
If we fight as a tag team,
I'll give Straw Hat-san trouble!
We happen to need a lot of weapons, too,
What is it?
I want to find my older brother!
Could you at least execute us separately?!
so the timing is excellent...
Hey, Balloon!
We were separated 20 years ago...
Now you're getting serious.
Balloon?!
Your weapon collection...
Straw Hat-san!
If I kick your ass...
I'm gonna take the whole thing!
He might be in the Land of Wano now!
will you let us out of here?!
What did you say?!
His name is...
I will bring you down instead,
you damn mountain bandit!
Kozuki Momonosuke.
I'm his sister...
I'm sorry if I confused you.
S-Samurai-sama!
I'm...
My name is Hiyori!
...a pirate!
Against the two formidable opponents,
Kamazo and Gyukimaru, Zoro wields only two swords!
The worst-ever deathmatch, the Sumo Inferno!
Zoro and Gyukimaru get in a fierce sword fight over
the great sword Shusui.
Luffy keeps on fighting,
seeking to learn the way to strike a blow against Kaido!
Luffy tries to elevate his ability to use
the Color of Arms as tough enemies keep assail him!
Ryuo is the name of the Land of
Wano's Haki! To share its essence,
Its deadly rules force its unarmed
challengers to fight Kaido's armed troops
With this deadly training,
he pushes himself ahead to take down Kaido!
During the severe fight,
Zoro comes to know the secret behind Shusui.
The fierce scramble drives him into a corner!
Old Man Hyo challenges a formidable enemy!
who come attacking fiercely
from every direction!
And Zoro is taught a stunning
truth by the woman he saved,
Facing the worst crisis ever without Shusui,
he risks his life and takes the chance of a lifetime!
However, at the same time, another assassin appears
When Old Man Hyo's all-out punch roars,
Luffy breaks new ground!
In this hellish situation,
Luffy launches an offensive to survive!
and gets to the core of
the incident 20 years ago!
in a spray of snow as a new crisis hits Zoro!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Gyukimaru! Zoro Fights a Duel on Bandit's Bridge"
"Get the Hang of It! The Land of Wano's Haki - Ryuo!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dead or Alive! Queen's Sumo Inferno!"
"Zoro, Stunned! The Shocking
Identity of the Mysterious Woman!"
"A Big Turnover! The Three-Sword
Style Overcomes Danger!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...