Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Please tell Kin'emon-kun and the others!
First, I want to apologize to everyone
about two things!
Excuse me, thank you!
Um...
What?!
What is it?
This is what everyone's
talking about in the capital!
That we'll fight along with you at any cost!
I want to find my older brother!
Then I want to say one thing
to the stupid Orochi!
I got excited!
We were separated 20 years ago...
Kin'emon... kun?
He is...
He might be in the Land of Wano now!
Will the decisive battle start soon?!
I will read the charges of the accused.
I'm glad to see you two, too...
His name is...
Now, it's getting busy!
H-He is... alive?!
Last night, he committed a
theft in the Flower Capital.
Kozuki Momonosuke.
Hey, wait!
There are tons of people
who won't last the week before the great battle!
I'm his sister...
He has fallen dreadfully.
Ushimitsu Kozo got caught?! No way!
He is the former Daimyo of Hakumai
who makes a living as a male geisha!
He knocked him back!
But it's true.
My name is Hiyori!
If this is something that you want to do,
So if you'll excuse me!
Look, it's written in the broadsheet.
He'll be executed in the capital today...
And they found out his identity.
His name is Shimotsuki Yasuie!
maybe I can help you a little bit.
"Get the Hang of It!
The Land of Wano's Haki - Ryuo!"
For the heinous crime of rebelling against
the Shogun Orochi-sama in the past,
I think he's popular in Ebisu Town...
"Tonoyasu!
Ebisu Town's Most Loved!"
You said Ebisu Town?!
Yes. And his name is, um...
as an offering to the
Oiran Komurasaki's grave,
I guess you're pretty exhausted, officer.
...Yasu-something...
we hereby sentence him to dishonorable death.
Momonosuke's...
Teach me! That's exactly it!
Tonoyasu?!
I'm hungry, too.
...sister?!
Look at the beautiful Flower Capital!
I thought so!
That geezer did this?!
I am glad that I gathered
my courage and said it!
What?!
I'll repeat myself over and over again
until you believe me.
I kind of took a chance.
I am the great thief Ushimitsu Kozo
who created turmoil in the Flower Capital!
Where do you think you're going?!
Your life is in danger!
You know my brother, don't you?!
The view of the Land of Wano is magnificent!
And he is okay, right?!
Wait! Calm down!
Let go of me!
Old man! That was awesome!
Oh, shut up! If you're really him,
I need to organize my thoughts.
I've got to go!
How did you use Haki?!
Hey! Get yourself together!
For generations, this scenery was developed
These days, people are talking about
the return of the Kozuki Clan.
Let go of me!
by the Kozuki Clan and the common people.
why did you appear around midnight?!
What's going on?!
At the same time, a strong and kind samurai
from overseas is here.
Toko!
We take pride in it.
He'll be executed!
It's too much for an old body...
Don't laugh! You're taking me for a fool!
Hurry up!
Let go of me!
So I thought he might be my brother's ally!
Faster!
You bastards!
He'll be killed!
You won't get out of here alive!
He's started talking shit!
Or are you an enemy who is after my brother?!
He's my father!
Do you hear me, Orochi?!
I'm his ally.
Go! Madillo-man!
There used to be immense forests
and fields with vegetation.
First of all, I'm his ally.
Hold on, old man!
I am so relieved.
Rivers!
He is...!
Seems like it will be a lovely day
in the Flower Capital today...
Villages!
Move!
Do you know if Kin'emon is alive?
And you are just contaminating them
with dirt of greed!
I see. No wonder we did not notice...
Daddy!
Are Kanjuro, Raizo,
and Kikunojo all with him?
You're nothing but vermin!
You call it Haki,
but we call it Ryuo in the Land of Wano.
Kikunojo?
That bastard!
"Shaking the Nation!
The Identity of Ushimitsu Kozo The Chivalrous Thief!"
Ryuo?
Oh, you mean Kiku?
Yeah, but wait...
Something has me wondering.
RYUO
"Zoro's Fury!
The Truth About the Smile!"
It has the meaning of "flow."
Big news! Big news!
Are you really Momo's sister?
The great thief Ushimitsu Kozo...
"The Straw Hats Run!
Save the Captive Tonoyasu!"
I'm sure your Haki flows in your body, too.
FLOWER CAPITAL
...who caused trouble
in the Flower Capital...
First, feel it.
...finally got caught!
Let me explain.
No way! I can't believe it!
All right!
I see.
You're right.
His number is finally up...
FLOWER CAPITAL
How could this have happened?!
Momo from 20 years ago
appears to be 8 years old,
Flowing Haki...
Special report! Special report!
There's big news!
Komurasaki-sama!
and you're supposed to be his younger sister,
but you aged 20 years and you're now 26...
Ushimitsu Kozo?
Yes.
What I wouldn't give to see her once more!
Don't press too hard!
By the way...
Damn Holdem!
Orochi-sama.
How dare he set fire to my hideout!
Orochi-sama,
there is something that I want you to know...
Is it okay for her to hear all of this?
It's about Ushimitsu Kozo
who we caught yesterday...
It's okay! Because I already knew!
Where are you?! Come out!
This isn't the Oiran procession
I wanted to see...
Damn! That's not it!
Oh, shut up!
Holdem!
Where are you taking her?!
It was a secret between Big Sis and me!
None of you can understand the pain of
losing a beloved woman!
Don't strain yourself!
She rebelled against Orochi-sama.
Otoko is one of the few close friends
who knows my true identity.
Allow the unused Haki in your body
to flow to your fist!
We'll cremate her at the Prisoners'
Quarters in Rasetsu Town.
About the Oiran, Komurasaki's death,
my sympathies are with you...
Is that...
Her cheerfulness sustains me day-to-day...
As soon as you arrive, Orochi-sama,
we will execute him as an offering!
But with all due respect,
All right!
Kyoshiro's move was wise.
20 years ago, I was still
a little girl like her...
Mm-hm, I will be there soon!
If he let someone
who stood against you walk away,
Yasuie-sama, don't go too far!
Bring in more!
Hearing his dying scream...
You won't be able to turn back!
it would have undermined
your authority and reputation.
...will heal the pain of losing Komurasaki
a little bit.
...but I will never forget
what happened that day.
There is another thing...
Today is a great day!
...that I want to apologize for.
UDON
Leave... to the future!
About the flyer with the symbol
that went around recently...
Don't push your luck!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
Mother, please don't do that!
It has been 20 years
since the name Kozuki perished.
Mother! Mother!
Kick the old man's ass, too!
Orochi-sama!
I do not care about Ushimitsu Kozo!
Now I cannot gather enough soldiers
to seek my revenge,
Push them against the
wall already, you fools!
I didn't know what was going on
and I was confused.
and I feel bad about the Kozuki Clan...
There is no other woman as beautiful as Komurasaki
in the world!
Where is Komurasaki-tan?!
In the blazing fire,
So I made the flyer!
my brother and the others
disappeared right before my eyes...
What?!
Can't you see that?!
It is so great to see you, Orochi-sama!
The symbol does not mean anything.
I don't see her anywhere.
Please listen to me.
They're still transporting her.
That is...
...just a prank!
I'm starving to death...
On the same day, I lost my father, Oden,
Ushimitsu Kozo was not
just another petty thief!
What's that place on the screen?
and even my mother...
What?!
That day, I suddenly lost everything.
That's the Prisoners'
Quarters in Rasetsu Town.
How long will it take to
get there, Okiku-chan?
Ushimitsu Kozo, the cowardly burglar
who caused trouble in the Flower Capital...
What's this all about?!
I was told that my brother would come back
20 years later,
Many criminals are held there,
though not as many as here.
I think we will enter Udon sometime tonight.
He is a hero-wannabe, small-time
crook who gives away
but I could not hold out hope for
such an uncertain thing...
It's taking so long...
the money and goods he steals to poor people.
There you are, Ashura!
I did not have the will
to live all those years.
We are holding him at the Prisoners' Quarters
in Rasetsu Town,
I wanna eat it...
Oh, Kin'emon! Dogstorm!
I can't believe it!
Why didn't they make you cross through time
with the others?
The sweet, sweet red-bean soup!
but the truth is his identity is...
In case something happened
either to my brother or to me,
Look!
It seems like Yasuie-sama is alive!
What?!
Yeah, I just found out, myself.
they did not want the
bloodline of Kozuki to end.
The red-bean soup...
PRISONERS' QUARTERS, RASETSU TOWN
FLOWER CAPITAL
That's too cruel...
It has become quite a spectacle.
He is...
20 years ago, Oden died,
But my father's retainer,
and Orochi asked the four remaining Daimyo
including me...
Kawamatsu the Kappa
supported me emotionally with patience and raised me.
H-He is... alive?!
Stop!
Don't look at me!
...if we would serve under Kurozumi...
Kappa?!
Indeed.
...or fight them.
It is hard to believe that those creatures exist,
but he takes great pride in being one...
No way... I cannot believe it!
Stop laughing!
EBISU TOWN
He is...
Raise the post.
On the day that the castle burned,
we were surrounded by the enemy,
Go away!
So you are from the Kurozumi Family.
Why didn't you tell me?
What a laugh!
but we escaped from the moat
through a drainage channel without being seen.
I see, I see...
Princess! Please be patient!
You had a great debt to Oden!
By seeing this flyer,
we learned about the great battle.
But you seized the position of Shogun
by a cunning trick.
After losing my father, mother, and brother,
It was unacceptable!
Two birds on fire...
That means twilight on the day of the Fire Festival!
He is... He is...
I lost my voice from shock,
but he always cheered me up.
Daimyo and people from every region
drew their swords without hesitation,
The rendezvous point for the raid
is Habu Port!
Lord! Lord!
Princess! This is the Kappa Dance!
What should we do about Ushimitsu Kozo?
but the monster named Kaido
got in the way of their retaliation,
Oh, Kin'emon-kun must've given
a lot of thought to it!
Come on!
Kappappa, kappappa, kappappa and pa!
and the Land of Wano was consumed in flames.
Why do you need to ask?
Kin'emon... kun?
Kappappa, kappappa...
Execute him! And show it to public
to set an example!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Go ahead and eat, princess.
Shinobu-chan!
Illuminate the Light-Scrolls across the Land of Wano
immediately!
I did not wish to, but I survived
and lived secretly in Ebisu Town,
Well, I understand.
It's no wonder that you have a glum look.
It's beautiful...
You are hungry, too, aren't you?
The Light-Scrolls are already prepared.
No, I have a little indigestion...
That's why it's growling...
The plan is ruined.
Kyoshiro!
but I did not want to just live on
and die a natural death.
Today, Komurasaki's funeral will be held
in the Flower Capital.
Even the enemies know about it.
Oden (stew) wouldn't be "oden"...
if it wasn't boiled!
So, channeling my inner child,
I came up with
Please... Please eat at least half.
Mm-hm... That is right...
We are expecting a crowd of people
and it will be chaotic...
the flyer prank idea and gave it a shot.
PRISON
Our allies with the Reversed
Crescent Moon tattoo
No, no, I found a grilled fish
swimming in the river earlier.
That is why we have already prepared.
Please forgive me!
signifying rebellion are getting
caught one after another...
That's my Kyoshiro!
But Orochi was a bigger
coward than I thought...
It'd be nice to take it back
and say, "It was all fake,"
A grilled fish in the river?
What shall we do?
That's right.
but then it'll mislead your allies, too...
He got flustered and
jailed the innocents who
I filleted it and ate it already.
EBISU TOWN
Okay! This is what we are going to do!
had the moon tattoo which
was a popular design!
Before this, however, I didn't know about
the crescent moon ankle tattoo.
Tonoyasu's been caught?!
We will let Ushimitsu Kozo
follow Komurasaki to the grave!
What the hell is going on?!
He did not eat much himself,
but he tried to feed me...
What?!
It's all in Orochi-sama's mind?!
I can't believe Tonoyasu-san
is Ushimitsu Kozo!
To accompany her!
You were able to secure allies like me.
What should we do?! We caught so many!
Thanks to kind Kawamatsu
protecting me with all his soul,
Oh!
Ushimitsu Kozo...
I'm sure there are tons of people
who got motivated by seeing this!
What?!
The great thief who steals money and goods
from the rich,
Does that mean they aren't even rebels?!
What a pity to lose the two biggest stars of the capital
at the same time!
I gradually began to laugh again.
and gives them away to the poor and the weak
every night...
Where's he now?
Please tell Kin'emon-kun and the others!
Only you could come up
with such a nice idea...
Yasuie-sama!
I think when I was about 13,
Thief?
Get out of our way!
Neigh!
That old geezer?
I will be there, too!
we were separated...
That we'll fight along with you at any cost!
Ushimitsu Kozo...
I will witness his execution to the end!
I need a palanquin now!
But Kawamatsu is a strong samurai,
I heard people talking about him
in the Flower Capital.
Kin'emon... kun?
Orochi-sama! Now I see it!
What is this all about?
I thought he was a saint.
so I am sure that he is waiting for
the day of the great battle.
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
That's a lie!
Damn Yasuie!
Stop making bad jokes
so early in the morning, Kaido-san!
I'm glad to see you two, too...
I will fill you with bullets!
I want to see him as well as the others...
Now, it's getting busy!
Big Sis! I want to see a kappa, too!
Hey, wait!
Here he comes...
It's not a joke!
There are tons of people
who won't last the week before the great battle!
Orochi, it has been a while!
Word came from the Flower Capital.
Kappa, kappa, kappappa!
Do you have any last words, Yasuie?!
Tonoyasu-san!
So if you'll excuse me!
Uh-huh!
Orochi! Let's see...
Zorojuro-san.
Why's everyone laughing?
Who else is there preparing
for the great battle?
Your friend's been strung up!
Komurasaki died!
Do you want me to recite the curse
that binds your heart?
A handsome man,
She died!!
a beautiful woman,
Well...
If you think it's a lie,
hook up your Light-Scroll Snail!
and a town girl!
What?!
The doggy and the kitty are there, too?!
Is Tonoyasu-san really Ushimitsu Kozo?
"A man of such small caliber...
No way! No...
Well, good to see you all!
Yeah.
Even if it's true,
that's not what's really important.
I heard that they were both dead,
so I thought I would never see them again!
No!
...shall never know the taste of oden
for as long as he shall live!"
A MAN OF SUCH SMALL CALIBER SHALL NEVER KNOW
THE TASTE OF ODEN FOR AS LONG AS HE SHALL LIVE
Maybe Cat Viper hasn't arrived
at the Land of Wano yet...
Komurasaki-tan!
I remember! That hairstyle...
Now, who's that old man?
I was listening, but I couldn't tell
how you guys are connected to him.
Tonoyasu is a fake name.
Hey!
He found out that Komurasaki died!
What are you doing?
Who is he?
I am very, very happy...
I'm sure that he'll be in
a bad mood for a while.
Me, neither!
BAKURA TOWN, KURI
Well, he was quite cheerful!
Who is that Tonoyasu-san?
Seems like something exciting is
happening in the Flower Capital...
We're in trouble. What should we do?
Turn on the Light-Scroll Snail!
Hey, balloon!
You're funny, Big Sis!
Come out already!
Let's look for Ashura!
Yasu-san! Play with us!
Shut up! No time for that now!
But I will not cry!
All right!
Because I am a samurai's daughter!
If the doggy and the kitty will be there,
Hey, balloon!
Can we start today's sumo match already?!
What is that?
it's possible that all members of the Akazaya Nine
could come together!
Well, I must say...
It's getting interesting!
Hurry up!
I don't know...
Did you idiots gain weight from yesterday?!
We have no idea!
Kin'emon.
No, we didn't! It's just your imagination!
Kanjuro.
No way... That's...
What do you mean?!
You were talking to him
not knowing who he was?!
Raizo.
I guess he's a good guy...
--O-Okay.
--Hey!
Well, he just went on and on, so...
Okiku.
--Forget it!
--Should we tell him that the red-bean soup is all gone?
He is alive!
Dogstorm.
Yes, he's very loyal to others!
How could you forget someone like him?!
Cat Viper.
Well, since he addressed
us with "kun" and "chan"...
No way! Another shock could drive him mad!
Do you know him?
AKAZAYA NINE
I thought if he had been someone important in the past,
it would be rude to ask him!
I agree!
Yeah, I know him pretty well.
Oden-sama and Yasuie-sama were
just like sworn brothers...
All we know is those six and Momonosuke.
But I wonder where the red-bean soup went...
That gentleman...
We haven't met the other three yet.
He was addressing you casually,
so could he be your childhood friend...
That is why I told Luffy-dono
not to eat too much...
...used to be one of the Daimyo who served
under the Kozuki Clan along with Oden-sama...
Those three are Kawamatsu
who I told you about,
Or an instructor of some kind?
Or an older friend?
Eating up all the soup in the pot
was too much.
KAWAMATSU   DENJIRO
Denjiro, and Ashura Doji.
ASHURA DOJI
How can an idiot like him survive?
His real name is...
I do not know where they are
or if they are safe...
Who is he?!
...Shimotsuki...
Let's just have the sumo match!
What?!
Come on! Dosukoi!
Gramps, Gramps, how's the abdominal pain?
But everyone is talking about this flyer
in the capital now,
This is no time for dealing with a fool!
I have to find out the truth!
Oh, Yasu-san!
so I bet they will show up!
Hey! Let me see the Flower Capital now!
Yasuie-dono!
No way!
Is that the flyer we handed out
to the rebels?
Get the Light-Scroll Snail ready!
Yes.
Yasuie-dono!
Straw Hat!
Thanks to the uproar,
information has spread very fast and that's a good thing,
Disappear!
The Light-Scroll Snail has been set up!
The Daimyo of Hakumai! Yasu the Hedgehog!
but it's obviously unfavorable for us...
Connect it to the Flower Capital!
He was very austere and never smiled!
...that the rendezvous spot leaked out
and our allies have been caught.
Daddy!
Is it a Video Transponder Snail?
Wait, Toko!
This isn't it!
I wonder what's gonna happen.
It will be all right.
I didn't realize
because he's nothing like he used to be!
This isn't it, either!
What? That must be the Flower Capital.
I believe so.
Damn!
Stop the execution!
Well...
No! No!
--I'm from Hakumai!
--I'm glad to see you again...
Dammit! Where is it?!
ATAMAYAMA, KURI
Too many captains sink the ship.
I'm gonna stop fretting...
Untie him, damn you!
My Haki!
Yasuie-sama!
Momo!
Why don't you take a break?
That's right!
It's not flowing to my fist!
Before anything else, I want you to get well!
This is nothing!
The great battle is approaching!
Now, get some rest.
People did not forget me yet?
Yeah, you don't have to tell me...
That makes me happy.
Whoa-whoa, he took down too many, that idiot.
I can't believe they are attacking Atamayama!
Screw them!
Otoko, this is miracle!
What's wrong?!
The raid operation that we were preparing for
was somehow totally exposed.
I am so happy!
HAKUMAI, LAND OF WANO
Damn!
This Hakumai is the only region in the Land of Wano
that has a legitimate port.
Shutenmaru, this is it for you!
Haki won't flow to an angry fist!
My brother is alive!
What?!
We thought it was all ruined, but...
I'm happy for you, Big Sis!
This is my revenge!
I'll make you pay!
Who's next?!
Some visitors wish us
well, others wish us harm.
I think Yasuie-dono is trying to
get us out of trouble all by himself!
Bring it on!
I'm so happy!
That is why...
I'm happy for you, Big Sis!
...we need to be an unassailable army.
SHIMOTSUKI YASUIE (LATER KNOWN AS TONOYASU)
DAIMYO OF HAKUMAI
Toko, this is great!
Can't they shut up?
I can't sleep...
This is it for me.
They are definitely the strongest samurai
in the Land of Wano...
You know what to do, Kin'emon...
Akazaya samurai!
Thank you as always.
My body feels heavy.
But he is 8 years old!
That's so strange!
It's not that much,
but I brought you some millet and water!
And the future Shogun, Momonosuke!
He is still a child.
Damn you Atamayama Thieves Brigade.
They'll give you energy!
I guess Kin'emon and the others
have not changed since 20 years ago, either.
How dare you steal all
of my food and weapons!
Want some?
You're such a nice person, Yasu-san...
Stop fooling around, Oden.
Your plan is now reset!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
I wonder how I will react when I see them.
You're good at praising!
I'm so happy to be called a nice person!
H-Holdem-sama...
Maybe I better not see them
before the great battle.
To your allies who are
captured in Rasetsu Town,
I'll give you two more millet grains!
How long are you going to hang out at my place?
You are the son of the Shogun!
I gave a new rendezvous point.
I should not interfere
with a samurai battle...
I won't forgive you, Shutenmaru!
I'll leave them here, so don't forget to eat!
What do you think, Otoko?
Thank you very much, Yasu-san.
I got kicked out of the castle.
I do not know if there is still a blood tie.
It is not much, but that is
all I can do with my life!
See you, Gramps!
I'll smash you fools to pieces!
Is he trying to sacrifice himself
to keep our plan alive?!
Hey! Seaweed Shop Granny!
Do you have enough medicine?!
Everyone is saying...
...that Oden will not be the heir
to Kozuki Sukiyaki...
No, but just seeing you cheers me up.
That's hysterical! What can you do?!
Oh, no! I have to get more wood!
Yasuie-dono!
You're such a man-killer!
Yasuie will become the Shogun.
Oh, mister, how's your knee?!
Yasu-san! Let's play!
Thank you!
Hanko! How's your sick mother doing?
You idiot!
Ouch!
Osaki-san, how's your baby?
No matter what the cowardly Orochi yells,
his soldiers will not listen to him anymore...
Up, up!
What are you doing?!
I wish we had at least one comforter...
Don't take silly talk like that seriously.
--Yasu-san!
--Come see us, too!
I'm sick of the Shogun's paranoia!
You are the true successor
of the Kozuki Clan!
Here, everyone! Take these!
Stop! Someone'll hear you!
Thank you as always!
Sukiyaki-sama kicked you out
because he loves you!
Tonoyasu must be making a lot of money.
Try to live up to his expectations.
Daddy!
No one else can give out food.
W-What should we do?
Yasu!
No, he is not...
He only gets paid peanuts.
I didn't expect stealing food and weapons
would cause this much trouble...
Yasu-san.
What?
I would rather go out to the sea!
His only daughter named Toko-chan
was sold to the capital and has been working there,
That wasn't it! I can't do it right!
Duke-sama! Kin-san!
What?!
Hey!
You sent them flying.
Wasn't that good enough?
but she sends most of her
earnings to Yasu-san.
For 20 years, no one could
chop off Kaido's head!
Whew!
Why doesn't this country allow that?
We stole so much.
Food... And weapons from the factory!
No, it wasn't, old man!
Toko?
The isolation policy is just annoying!
I wanna throw a punch that sends enemies flying
without a touch!
Nice work. Did you leave the note?
I'm not otoko (male)!
But this time...!
That way,
Cover your children's eyes!
Yes, of course!
It must be her!
I think I can break Kaido's tough scales!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
The last Daimyo who served under Kozuki...
He said Toko-chan took the trouble
to send it,
Are we responsible for this?!
Shut up!
A punch that sends enemies flying
without a touch?
so he shouldn't have it all to himself.
I mean, Ebisu Town's happy-go-lucky guy...
Don't panic!
Say whatever you like
after becoming a real samurai.
Yeah. I won't know if it works
until I actually try.
He gives out food to those who can't work
every day.
This is part of Kin-san's plan...
...will cross over to the other side!
But I saw it before...
Watch closely!
Yasuie!
He doesn't eat much himself.
Okay!
Both Rayleigh...
...and that battle-axe guy...
His facial expressions and body movements are so goofy,
but everyone's always loved him.
You are hurting me!
How dare you keep punching me.
Not just the food and the weapons!
Let's sing as I go!
...used the same Haki of the Color of Arms.
Here we go!
Who do you think I am?
How is theirs different from mine?!
--You coward!
--What?!
He's a saint.
Haki must be a foreign concept.
You are still a nobody...
Just a hoodlum.
Don't play innocent!
Do you know anything?!
In the Land of Wano, there is a concept of power
that will cover your blade via your body.
Daddy...
Look at me!
Your subordinate made such a ruckus in Bakura Town
and messed me up!
Yasuie-sama!
A good sword will cut even iron
when you need it to,
Daddy!
but when you don't,
it won't even cut a sheet of paper.
Gum-Gum...
It's all up to the swordsman!
It's bedtime! Go to sleep!
...Red Hawk!
Damn!
Continue this again tomorrow?
What?! What are you talking about?!
I had nothing to do with that!
Yasuie!
Let me fight more!
Old man.
Let's sing as I go!
Are you pretending that you don't know?
All right.
You fool! Are you stepping
forward to get killed?!
Here we go!
Let's just sort it out!
It is no use, everyone!
Orochi will not let me go!
Straw hat man.
I'm hungry...
Watch as I show the skill
that I used to hone through sword fights.
Won't you even let me eat something?!
Take this Trick Mechanism Sword's attack!
Shoot!
First, I want to apologize to everyone
about two things!
Stop barking like a dog!
Shut up and go to sleep!
Then I want to say one thing
to the stupid Orochi!
I'm gonna become a mummy by tomorrow!
Old man!
Can I ask you something, straw hat man?
One more!
Straw hat man! Give me directions!
What is it?
Why would you want to fight Kaido?!
I heard you once lost to him in Kuri.
Okay!
Your cheap trick won't work on me!
Invade Onigashima!
Yeah? Then, I'll increase the heat!
Kamijiro!
Avenge your lord!
They're annoying...
Look at this fire!
I shall await the good
news in the other world!
HAKUMAI, LAND OF WANO
I told you that your cheap trick won't work!
Don't forget that you suspected my crew.
Why did you try to steal this much money?
Toko!
Fight me fairly!
Oden-sama is running short!
After I say those things,
I can leave for kingdom come, laughing.
Haven't you noticed yet? Look around you!
Why don't you just kill us already?!
Okay, this is good.
How can people who don't trust each other
fight together in a deadly battle?!
Old man!
Hedgehog!
You see? The fire has
spread in all directions!
Do you know the Four Emperors?
Oden... He took on such strange followers...
No...
There are four great pirates
called emperors across the world,
Why would I even bother
fighting you head-on?!
Guys!
and Kaido is one of them.
You can have all the
money you tried to steal!
Hey, wait! Tra-guy!
I'm here to destroy Atamayama!
I'm gonna become the King of Pirates,
What?!
Daddy!
so I have to take them all down!
Wait a minute, Yasuie-sama!
The King of Pirates?!
Tra-guy left in a rage.
Then Hakumai will face
financial difficulties!
Our Atamayama...
You mean a man like Roger?
Is he going to come back?
I do not care...
More importantly, untie them!
Do you know Gold Roger?!
Damn Shinobu! How could she say that?!
He came to this country a long time ago.
What?!
Forget about Holdem for now!
Let's retreat!
But you know why Shinobu-chan grew impatient!
Kaido took over her country
and screwed up her life.
Oh, that's what Kin'emon said!
Yes, sir!
Yasuie-sama!
What?! Kin'emon?!
Guys, you can use this, too!
But she has endured it
and waited 20 years to fight back!
Take it!
Don't let them get away!
How do you know that name?!
More money?!
Wait!
I know.
You've got to be kidding!
This must a trap!
But even if Bepo and the others told them about the plan,
I wouldn't blame them.
That's enough...
The next hit will be a killing blow.
Yasuie-sama, enough is enough!
Shutenmaru's hideout has been destroyed!
They no longer have a place to hide.
Because you'd do so, right?
What is that?!
Do you like Oden?
I will read the charges of the accused.
I think you'd talk, too.
This is the end of the
Atamayama Thieves Brigade!
Of course, we do!
We're deeply indebted to him!
Torture, huh?
That's right!
What?!
Last night, he committed a
theft in the Flower Capital.
Over in three seconds.
You're... R-Raizo!
That's too short!
I see...
Go away!
In that case, use this money...
I don't need you lowly
shits to take care of me!
Too late! The fire's spreading too fast!
He has fallen dreadfully.
Straw Hat-san...
...for fixing yourselves up, learning manners,
buying books, and getting an education!
He is the former Daimyo of Hakumai
who makes a living as a male geisha!
It's impossible to extinguish
it, Shutenmaru-san!
What's this? Yelling in Ebisu Town
that is always filled with laughter?
You...
This is Raizo, right?
Damn Holdem!
Having hoodlums like you as retainers
will bring shame on Oden!
His name is Shimotsuki Yasuie!
I am!
Let's go to Bakura Town!
You must be that monster - bean-washing hag!
Bakura Town?!
Kaido's army will come after us!
For the heinous crime of rebelling against
the Shogun Orochi-sama in the past,
What?!
Stop it!
They're new here! They fled the capital
and arrived yesterday.
He will eventually...
What's going on with you guys?!
So what?!
...become the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
How are you alive?!
Raizo!
as an offering to the
Oiran Komurasaki's grave,
I'll kick all of their asses!
Let me explain, Hyogoro-dono!
What are you looking at?!
Those who support him must be
the best samurai in the Land of Wano!
Go away!
No way... This can't be happening...
we hereby sentence him to dishonorable death.
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
We didn't plan for this...
ARREST
Let's notify Duke-sama.
There he is! Ushimitsu Kozo!
AN ABANDONED VILLAGE, KURI
Now, according to his statement,
Surrender!
he was Ushimitsu Kozo
who caused a disturbance to the public...
I see... I feel sorry for Ashura Doji.
Fled the capital?
Catch him!
Yeah.
Only people who are loyal to the Shogun
and earn money can live in the capital.
Mm-hm... But we did it for the greater good.
That was a lie.
Is it true, Raizo?!
I... cannot believe...
that you're the famous Hyogoro-dono...
It cannot be helped.
What did you just say?
I heard that those men were
doing pretty bad things.
Let's go to Bakura Town!
I said it because I wanted to get all the attention
if I die anyway!
Our plan is foiled
and we do not know what to do yet...
This is hard to take in.
I'm sorry that I lied.
Bad things?
Are you saying that you really crossed through
20 years of time
But for the time being, we need Ashura to be
hostile towards the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
First...
I'm no hero like that!
--...the underling, Bungoh...
--You little shits!
and came from the Land of
Wano on that fateful day?
Because we definitely need him!
Needless to say,
you must protect your lord.
Yasuie-dono...
He set fires throughout the town
every night.
Yes! By Toki-sama's power!
Why did he tell such a lie?
And become the capital's...
NORTHERN GRAVEYARD, RINGO
But he didn't get punished
because he paid off officials.
I mean, eventually become
this Land of Wano's guardian angels!
The sorrow from Komurasaki's funeral
has been directed to Yasuie's execution.
I can't believe it!
BUNGOH - AN ARSONIST
I can't believe you, Caribou!
Maybe Nami-san and the others
have come back.
Understood?!
An arsonist?!
I'm back...
Why bother paying off officials
to start fires?!
Yasuie-dono!
Please don't say that, Straw Hat-san!
What?!
Drake-san! The people of Ebisu Town
are charging into the Flower Capital.
Someone was making money off of it...
Daddy!
What do you mean, Raizo?!
You thought it was the key to my cuffs,
but it was to his?!
Daddy!
He's a lumber dealer
who sold lumber for rebuilding houses.
What?!
Who are you?! What is this?!
Don't hate me like that!
W-W-What's going on?!
His name is Bongoh.
BONGOH - A LUMBER DEALER
Daddy!
I may come in handy.
I guess he is a bigger
figure than we imagined.
Oh, Brook... What's up with you?
Why are you here?
What?!
Otoko...
There's more to it.
I'm your subordinate from now on, mister!
The other man exploited mourning people
who lost their family members in the fire,
Zoro-san!
You're almost making my eyes pop out!
But, in exchange,
Yasu-san, don't die!
and charged them an outrageous price.
I mean, if I had eyes to begin with!
He's a priest and undertaker named Bingoh.
let me get on board when you're leaving!
Yasu-san!
Are you tired, Toko?
BINGOH - A PRIEST AND UNDERTAKER
If we lose you,
who else will support us?!
Oh, so you're stuck here!
I'm sorry to interrupt you!
Yes, Daddy!
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry for what I did to you in the past!
Don't tell me those three were...
Don't enter this town without permission!
Go back to Ebisu Town, you beggars!
Okay, okay!
I'll give you a ride on Daddy's shoulders!
Hey, you got the wrong idea! Come back in!
I have changed now...
That's right. Bingoh, Bongoh, and Bungoh
were in cahoots.
What? Oh, okay... If you say so...
There you go!
Yasu-san!
Okay, there's no problem if you've changed.
Whoa, how beautiful!
I thought so.
Here we go!
That's terrible!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm sorry, but may I see your panties?
What?!
Right, but no matter how
much crime they committed,
Forgive me, Otoko...
Thank you... very much!
they bought off officials,
so they escaped arrest.
For leaving you behind...
Is this some kind of trap?!
It scares me how easy that was!
They pretended to be good people,
but they're actually the
worst kind of people.
A ghost!
Luffytaro-dono!
This guy has quite an interesting power.
Wait! He's safe!
Those ruffians didn't receive
any divine punishment?!
These small actions won't draw the attention of
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
He could be useful!
But the funny thing is...
I'm hungry. A curse on you!
Daddy!
...all three of them fell in love with
the incredibly beautiful Komurasaki the Oiran...
Daddy! Daddy!
Without giving up...
Daddy!
I'm scared!
greedily...
Okay! Cease fire!
...who died yesterday!
Kin'emon-san told me to
stay here and say that to people...
I held on to life...
All three of them spent tons of money on her
and went broke!
I'm glad that I did!
Oh, that's why...
...there are so many offerings out front.
So the gods really watch over us!
Those are the rumors!
Yasu!
Hyogoro-dono?!
Well, I can't believe that
you're Momonosuke-san's sister!
Yasu-san!
That's a good story.
Yasu-san, hold on!
But that's too specific to be rumor.
They're the lowly beggars from Ebisu Town!
Kick them out of the capital!
You're as lovely as the Oirans!
That was close...
I thought I was only gonna
die miserably here...
It must be a true story.
In that case, that Oiran knew who they were
and tricked them.
Of course! Because she's an Oiran!
The residents on the main street
are raging!
Yasu-san!
I was accepting my death.
It must be so nice to have someone like her by your side.
I wish I were you!
Well done!
In the west district, too!
Who is Komurasaki?
Yasuie-sama!
Had this not happened,
I would've died...
It's one thing after another!
I was just sleeping, but she...
Oh! Them!
I'm sorry! I thought you were really cold...
Orochi-sama's decision to broadcast the execution
through the Light-Scrolls could backfire.
...not knowing anything.
D-Daddy!
Yeah! I remember!
Daddy!!
So the Akazaya samurai are alive!
But I always make men drool
whenever I sleep alongside them!
Keep an eye on other areas, too.
Oden's son, Kozuki Momonosuke, is alive!
They were making a scene
at the Oiran's procession!
Did you like it? Well, I know you loved it!
Shogun-dono is such an idiot,
I feel sorry for his subordinates!
The fire of rebellion....
--You're pretty straightforward...
--Yes!
Yasu-san provided them a place to live
and took care of them,
...isn't extinguished!
Anyway, I wonder where
Nami-san and the others are...
but they still act arrogant
and are out of control.
Now, everyone!
Da... ddy...
They went to a bathhouse yesterday,
so I tried to go meet them, but I couldn't find them...
Tonoyasu is such a caring man.
He even took care of those vermin!
Yasu...
Oh, by the way, the Flower Capital is
in total chaos now!
Is Yasuie finally dead?
Raizo! Straw hat man!
Look at the beautiful Flower Capital!
Today is the funeral of Komurasaki-san the Oiran,
the most beautiful woman in the Land of Wano...
When it comes to this,
even a dotard like me still can contribute!
Will you please let me join you?!
On top of that, Ushimitsu Kozo the great thief
who spread the money he stole to the poor got caught,
Oh, we could ask for none better than him!
The view of the Land of Wano is magnificent!
Luffy-dono! He used to be the greatest yakuza boss
in the Land of Wano!
and that's causing a fuss, too!
Yasuie-sama...
Ushimitsu Kozo got caught?! No way!
But it's true.
What?! I knew you were a big deal back
in the day, old man!
Look, it's written in the broadsheet.
He'll be executed in the capital today...
And they found out his identity.
USHIMITSU KOZO GOT CAUGHT
You said that you were recruiting allies
in the Flower Capital now, didn't you?!
I think he's popular in Ebisu Town...
That is right!
Straw hat man! Give me directions!
It's surely fate that brought you to Udon!
You said Ebisu Town?!
Okay!
Yes. And his name is, um...
In this labor camp,
...Yasu-something...
there are four other excavation sites
just as large as this one!
For generations, this scenery was developed by
the Kozuki Clan and the common people.
Tonoyasu?!
Yes, that's the name!
He'll swing down his right sword full force!
There are tens of thousands
of prisoners in Udon!
We take pride in it.
I got it!
Toko!
However, not everyone was imprisoned
for robbery or assault...
Hurry up!
Faster!
Most of the prisoners are here for...
He's started talking shit!
...treason against Orochi!
Oh! Why didn't I think of that?!
You cannot take the credit
for that, you fool!
Hey! What's the matter?!
Wait, Toko!
You damn geezer!
Rage from across the country is pooled here!
Thank you for saving us yesterday!
We will not forget your kindness!
The yakuza bosses who once supported the Land of Wano
behind the scenes are all here, too!
Wait, you fool!
Kurozumi Orochi!
You couldn't protect her yesterday!
I'll talk to them!
I'm sure they'll be happy to fight for Kozuki!
What's going on here?
What?! I've just come back!
And Raizo! In that cell...
Please wait! Hey!
What's...
I know.
...happening?
I have had a word with Kawamatsu.
I will release him first!
Somebody died...
Do you hear me, Orochi?!
What's so funny about it?!
I see!
There used to be immense forests
and fields with vegetation.
Then if I break this place down,
everyone will ally with us!
Daddy...
Hey, let's go!
Luffy-dono! You are too loud!
It is not that easy...
Rivers!
Oh, you came to escort me?
That's very generous.
My dad died!
Villages!
All right! Our plan has been set!
Bring me something to eat!
And you are just contaminating them
with dirt of greed!
You little...
I got it!
Please wait!
You're nothing but vermin!
He knocked him back!
Mister!
They're all... crying...
That bastard!
When did you get that?!
What?!
The people from Ebisu Town
are always smiling...
N-No way...
Yum-yum!
That man is...
It's red-bean soup!
...because even when they're hurt or sad...
Hey, you got to have some, too!
Old man...
Yasuie-dono...
Old Man Hyo took the Gifter down!
Thank you.
...they can't let it show on their faces.
Where do you think you're going?!
Your life is in danger!
Alpaca-man!
Let me...
How impressive.
...eat...
That dotard...
I thought he had one foot in the grave.
Let go of me!
I've got to go!
I'm hungry... and tired...
Hey! Get yourself together!
But he's still pretty young!
No red-bean soup yet? Okiku-chan...
Old man.
Let go of me!
What's going on?!
Sharkodile-san is exhausted, too.
But we have already entered Udon!
Toko!
Could Old Man Hyo actually be...
He'll be executed!
...the famous Hyogoro the Flower?!
All facial expressions other than a smile
were taken away from them...
Let go of me!
Wait for me...
He'll be killed!
My red-bean soup...
Straw hat man...
He's my father!
...and now, all they can do is laugh!
If this is something that you want to do,
Is this really a good idea?
Toko...
maybe I can help you a little bit.
What did you say?!
Because of what Kaido and Orochi
brought here...
Oh, it's good!
Another bowl!
Red-bean soup!
It's a fruit called Smile!
Seems like it will be a lovely day
in the Flower Capital today...
Teach me!
Daddy!!
That's exactly it!
I'm gonna stuff myself silly!
To master Ryuo and break out of the labor camp,
Luffy lets his fighting spirit burn even more!
News of the Flower Capital's beloved
Ushimitsu Kozo who sides with the weak
The time for Tonoyasu's
execution is approaching.
Entrusting the Land of Wano's future to the Straw Hats,
Tonoyasu dies with a smile on his face!
The Straw Hats shake with rage
against the merciless Orochi.
The Straw Hats clear away unassailable guards
and rush to stop the execution.
But now, Orochi points
his gun at a new target!
and crushes the strong
The people of Ebisu Town grieve,
but Zoro sees them laughing hysterically!
spreads like wildfire
across the Land of Wano.
Meanwhile, other prisoners who wish to rebel against Orochi
and Tonoyasu join the raid operation!
In this desperate situation,
everyone's favorite duo finally strikes out!
Will Tonoyasu share the fate of the cherry blossoms?!
Meanwhile, after meeting up with Brook,
Flying sparks and a flash of light!
Zoro and the others learn about
Orochi's despicable plot and a cruel truth.
When he learns the truth behind their smiles,
he becomes furious!
More allies to take down Kaido come together
and the road of hope starts opening!
The truth behind his smile will be revealed!
With smoke and flames,
they blow up a storm over the Flower Capital!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tonoyasu! Ebisu Town's Most Loved!"
"The Straw Hats Run! Save the Captive Tonoyasu!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Toko's Tears! Orochi's Pitiless Bullets!"
"Zoro's Fury! The Truth About the Smile!"
"Shaking the Nation!
The Identity of Ushimitsu Kozo The Chivalrous Thief!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...