mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Just give me...
Two-Sword Style!
Those fools...
I knew they couldn't hold back!
That is right, everyone!
Tower Climb Return!
Shimotsuki Yasuie, Hakumai's former Daimyo
that you loved has died!
D-Daddy!
This is gonna be trouble.
...red-bean soup!
Daddy!!
But we can't really blame them!
How dare you interfere with her execution!
Soul King!
Send him off with the sound of your laughter!
What?!
Olin-san!
More friends of the rat have appeared!
Sooouuul!
Daddy!!
Queen-sama!
A curse on you!
Daddy! Daddy!
Yasuie's daughter...
That accursed brat is a serious criminal!
It appeared again!
Hey, samurai! Go ahead and kill everyone
who interferes with the execution!
Somebody died...
Gashadokuro!
What's so funny about it?!
Diable Jambe!
There you are, you damn brat!
Take care of her!
"A Grudge Over Red-bean Soup!
Luffy Gets into a Desperate Situation!"
Extra Hachis Hash!
What?! H-Hey!
If you... If you...
720-Pound Phoenix!
If you...
My dad died!
...did not laugh like an idiot at that time,
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Komurasaki would not have had to die!
They're all... crying...
I have four lives now.
You little shit!
Outta my way!
What?!
Red-bean soup...
I will execute you!
I think not!
The people from Ebisu Town are always smiling...
In that case...
Go to hell! You little shit!
Sniff, sniff...
I'll cut you!
...because even when they're hurt or sad...
Otoko, run!
...they can't let it show on their faces.
Olin-san...
Disappear from my sight!
You can only cut me up
after you've killed...
Olin is as strong as she was
when she was Big Mom!
I am the Shogun's dog.
All facial expressions other than a smile
were taken away from them...
...the three from your own crew.
Meanwhile, at the Excavation
Labor Camp in Udon...
...and now, all they can do is laugh!
I remember how you didn't like the way you laugh...
Luffy!
Because of what Kaido and Orochi
brought here...
You even stopped laughing out loud at some point...
Who do you think you're talking to?
It's a fruit called Smile!
Everyone who mocked your laugh
would be nearly beaten to death by you!
Don't push your luck!
What a strong old lady!
You bastards!
She's not just an old lady...
"The Straw Hats Step In!
An Uproarious Deadly Battle at the Execution Ground!"
She's...
"Toko's Tears!
Orochi's Pitiless Bullets!"
Please... stop...
Who did this to my buddy?!
"The Storm Has Come!
A Raging Big Mom!"
...an Emperor of the Sea!
Hey, balloon!
No... way!
Straw hat man?
Hey, balloon!
What do you want, Straw Hat?!
Why are you yelling?
I did not expect...
...that the Flower Capital would be in such turmoil
after Yasuie-dono's execution...
Come on, let's just start the sumo matches!
I know how Zorojuro-dono
and Sangoro-dono feel...
Come on!
Queen-sama!
Daddy!
It can't be helped.
"Luffy's Determination!
Win Through the Sumo Inferno!"
Let's go beat the hell out of Holdem!
Yeah!
Daddy!
Wait a minute, Ashura!
Don't scream so pathetically...
Th-They are...
I have something to tell you.
...Zorojuro the magistrate killer
and Sangoro the soba cook!
I'm not gonna get taken down...
Sangoro!
The Smile fruit is more than just an artificial Devil Fruit?
Leave Otoko to me!
...by that crappy attack!
Thanks, Usohachi!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
OUTSIDE OF BAKURA TOWN, KURI
Is that true?
Those fools...
I knew they couldn't hold back!
I won't give you any red-bean soup!
Yes, it is all true.
This is gonna be trouble.
But we can't really blame them!
I'll leave the dinosaur to you!
I'll make a cracker out of you and eat you up!
We provoked Holdem...
Yeah, they did a good job saving Otoko!
Yasuie-dono!
I mean, I did.
Yeah! I'll take care of it!
It was my order.
I told them to steal food and weapons
from Holdem,
Tonoyasu got...
and make it look like Atamayama
Thieves Brigade did it.
Damn! We were too late!
Get squashed!
Two-Sword Style!
Tower Climb Return!
That is why Holdem became mad
and attacked your clan.
Zoro! Sanji!
How dare you interfere with her execution!
Diable Jambe!
More friends of the rat have appeared!
Concasse!
Yasuie's daughter...
That accursed brat is a serious criminal!
How could not I recognize him
until he was tied up there!
What a blunder.
I should commit seppuku...
Hey, samurai! Go ahead and kill everyone
who interferes with the execution!
You really use any means.
This is...
...a battle between a beast and a monster!
Yasuie-sama!
Don't you, Kin'emon?
Yes, sir!
Zorojuro's so strong!
Hey, aren't they pointing
their guns this way?!
He's a good match for Boss Kyoshiro!
Oh, no!
Tonoyasu-san...
Yasuie-sama...
You better stop, ronin.
Because of that, Atamayama
was destroyed by fire!
Run, you idiots!
Who is he?!
He died!
Get them!
I'll have the head of the Emperor of the Sea!
I told you that your cheap trick won't work!
Seems like fortune favors me.
The red-bean soup is all mine!
Fight me fairly!
W-What's going on here?!
Haven't you noticed yet? Look around you!
The people from Ebisu Town
loved him so much.
Our Atamayama...
Why are they laughing?!
I'm sorry, but I have no time for you.
Red... bean... soup!
OROCHI'S ONIWABANSHU
SHOGUN OF WANO PERSONAL NINJA FORCE
Neither do I!
Well then, go away, Browgoro!
Orochi's Oniwabanshu is here!
Kin'emon!
"Browgoro"?
Did you try to entrap us?!
Red-bean soup!!
It's Sangoro!
You go away, Mossjuro!
Stop, Ashura! We are deeply sorry!
"Mossjuro"?!
Your head looks like a moss ball!
Orochi has a sick sense of humor...
We know who you are.
What?!
I did it because I wanted to motivate you...
Do you want me to chop you up
before Orochi?!
Roronoa Zoro from the Straw Hat Pirates.
Shut up! Then I'll kick you to death
before Kaido!
Hawkins was right. It seems like
all members of the Straw Hats are here in the Land of Wano.
What did you say?!
Daddy!
Hey...
Quit lying around, you damn lizard!
I was driven by that thought!
Otoko... Thank goodness she is okay!
All we need is one of you. I do not care who it is.
They must be crazy!
Is he... Zorojuro-san's friend?
But...!
They're laughing at
the execution of their former Daimyo!
Your capture and subsequent torture will tell us your purpose!
I am so sorry, Ashura!
Yes, he is.
Stop, you old bag!
He's our friend, too.
His name's Sangoro the soba cook.
I should have come to you like this instead!
Orochi's so cruel...
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Don't you know who I am?!
I was justifying my actions
in the name of our lord,
Sangoro-san... the soba cook?
and I did not have much time,
so I could not help but use such a drastic measure...
The Straw Hat Pirates' Roronoa Zoro,
and the other one is...
Yasuie-dono...
I can't believe he was alive until today...
But I was completely mistaken!
So the enemy knew about our raid plan.
Luffy!
...Vinsmoke Sanji...
So the Straw Hats are really here
in the Land of Wano...
Sorcery?
That is why you... Yasuie-dono...
I can't believe that
they showed their faces so brazenly.
Red... bean... soup!!
Ninpo!
20 years is a long time!
You sacrificed yourself...
Hey!
Do you have a problem with
the way we appeared?!
The world itself would change,
let alone people's minds!
...to keep the plan safe?!
Hell Biwa!
Yeah, do you?! And...
I have never thought about it!
That's just a damn gun!
No, I tried not to see it!
...don't ever call me Vinsmoke, okay?!
Give me red-bean soup!
There must be a reason, right?
But I realized there were still unchanged minds
and unshakable beliefs left in this country!
Well then, I'll just finish you off!
Red-bean soup!
It doesn't matter who he was...
Toko!
Red-bean soup!
No one in this world deserves to be laughed at...
When I saw Yasuie-sama...!
Give it to me!
...as they die!
Shoot!
Don't worry!
Please flee the capital now!
That damn ronin...
I'll take care of them!
Next! Get ready!
Our plan is still safe!
Soul King!
That's probably because of the Smile.
Get down, old man!
Yasuie-sama misled the enemy for us
at the risk of his life!
Shoot!
Sooouuul!
You can find some of those people
who can only laugh here, too...
A curse on you!
The mark on the ankles of
those who were captured by Orochi...
Take Otoko and run already!
No, not yet!
It appeared again!
Those samurai know the best
that the moon tattoo is not just a popular design!
Gashadokuro!
He needs to be...
Dogstorm, Kin'emon...
That rat is behaving impertinently...
That's it, Bonekichi!
Do you guys know about the Smile fruit?
Take care of her!
On the night of the Fire Festival,
we will raid Onigashima!
What?! H-Hey!
U-Udon is...
Is he going to attack?!
Those samurai in the capital
will be released because of what happened,
Udon's in danger!
Fight him! Fight him!
That ronin is going to attack me!
and I am sure they will join us!
That woman...
She was with Zorojuro.
Run, Browgoro!
In order to take down Kaido and Orochi,
we definitely need you!
Fujin, Raijin.
I should have... told you earlier...
Yes, sir!
How could that lowly bastard be so rude?!
Chase that woman.
Will you please fight
together with us, Ashura?!
Yes, sir!
The smiling faces of Ebisu Town's people...
I gotta cut you myself!
Hey, Moss!
Don't rush into a fight on your own!
...are merely masks.
Prepare to fire!
Masks that can't be taken off...
Oh, damn!
Shoot!
...for the rest of their lives!
Hey! Stop, you idiot!
Tonoyasu sacrificed himself for what?!
A few years ago, Kaido and Orochi...
Thank goodness. They're...
Hey, are you okay?!
...started importing some kind of artificial fruit...
Twenty years...
Whoa, wait a minute, mister!
Shut up!
...in exchange for the weapons
that are made in this country.
As they say, there are evens and odds in this world.
Both good and evil come in turn.
We don't need your pity.
We're not that helpless!
Smile fruit?!
Let's put an end to this here!
When you eat that horrible fruit,
the sea will hate you and you'll lose the ability to swim,
You'll never understand the
weight of the past 20 years.
Okay?!
In this country,
we call everyone's smiling face...
but in return, you'll gain the ability of an animal
and it'll make you ferocious.
What a great view.
..."Ebisu gao," mister!
It's an artificial Devil Fruit, right?
That's why this place is called Ebisu Town!
We destroyed the factory
that was making them.
Poverty won't get us down!
Yes, Kin-sama told me about it...
Yasu...
But tons of them had already been
brought into the country.
Could it be that he is Akazaya's soldier?!
Come on, you samurai! Protect me!
Now,
Follow me...
go to...
There's something I want to show you!
...hell!
Kaido's objective was to make his subordinates stronger
like ferocious beasts with that fruit,
720-Pound Phoenix!
Queen-sama!
Queen-sama! Stay with us!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
Queen-sama?
and build the world's greatest pirate group!
He passed out...
Hey! What was that noise?!
I can't believe that a man with a 1.3-billion-berry bounty
got knocked out in just two hits!
But there is always a catch to
something that's too good to be true.
It was from outside of the gate,
but we just lost contact with the guards...
They both ate the Devil Fruit.
Who is that man?!
Water torture must be agonizing.
Boss Kyoshiro...
The success rate of that artificial strength enhancer
was about 10 percent...
He repelled Zoro's sword attack?!
I can smell red-bean soup more strongly now!
Red-bean soup...
I think he was the one who cut Komurasaki...
If 10 people ate that fruit,
only one of them would gain the ability.
She beat the formidable Queen so easily...
It's Boss Kyoshiro.
Red-bean soup!
So, he is the boss of the hoodlums
who caused that trouble at my soba shop?!
She's on another level...
That's how strong the Emperor of the Sea Big Mom is!
Don't mess with me!
You son of a...!
Do you have a problem?
Report to Kaido-san!
The other nine won't see any improvement
and will face only the consequences.
Roger!
Lord, you are too careless.
Save Big Bro at any cost!
Of course, they won't be able to swim again.
You should not come to the execution ground
with such poor security.
Oh, yeah. I came up with an exciting game.
The Never-Opening Cell's been destroyed!
Go for it, Olin-chan!
As the side effects of the defective chemicals,
We don't know what's in it!
Yeah, you are right...
No, no, don't try too hard!
I believe it was chained up...
they won't be able to express their sorrow or anger.
They'll only be able to laugh...
And that ronin...
Red-bean soup!
Not being able to escape,
it must've died inside.
He was really going to kill me!
There is no way that they
have that soup here.
What?!
If Big Mom finds out,
the shock might bring back her memories...
Hey, Moss! What are you thinking?!
The key ingredient of the Smile is
SAD that Caesar was making, right?!
EXECUTIVE TOWER IN THE EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
Chill out!
Roger! I'll report to Onigashima right away!
Thank you for waiting, you damn fools!
That has a terrible side effect like that?
X. DRAKE
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ALLOSAURUS MODEL
And we'll be killed!
Kaido doesn't care about his subordinates' safety.
The Sumo Inferno...
This is none other than the Excavation Labor Camp.
It's sturdier than I expected.
A surprise attack from one so big?!
He just wants strong soldiers.
Take this!
...is back on!
Even if it is Big Mom, isn't it impossible to
break the thick steel gate?!
I smell red-bean soup this way!
The combatants of the Animal Kingdom Pirates
are grouped into three categories.
Prepare to fire!
Babanuki-san! Can we open fire?
What?!
Red-bean soup!
No! Don't agitate her!
Well, well. This is going
to be a scene of bloodshed.
Those who haven't eaten and are waiting
for a chance to gain an animal ability...
That's it, Olin-chan! Keep going!
What's Kaido-san's order?!
What should we do?
Are we gonna stand here and just watch?
Chief Warden! The thing is...
No, that's enough!
...are the Waiters!
...the smails aren't able to get through!
When it comes to this,
we gotta fight, too!
Don't keep going like that!
None of us can reach Onigashima!
The tough ones who obtained animal abilities
from a one-in-ten chance...
Wait a minute!
That will ruin the whole plan!
What?!
...are the Gifters!
And if we get involved with this,
we can no longer stay in the capital!
Red-bean soup!
The laughing fighters who ate the fruit,
but failed to gain abilities...
Even so, we can't let them expose Yasuie-sama's body
to public view!
Red-bean soup...
...are the Pleasures!
Red-bean soup!!
Hey! What's wrong?!
We must take it away somehow!
Hello! This is Building B...
Then as if they mock those unlucky ones
who couldn't gain any ability,
You are right, but...
Huh? The Smail isn't working!
She did it!
Let's split up.
Where should we meet?
Hello?!
they named the artificial fruit
after those soldiers' facial expression.
I'll help fight, too!
No, wait! Now is not the right time for
Oden-sama's allies to show themselves.
I knew you were coming.
Namely, a "Smile"!
Because of the turmoil outside,
security is so poor here.
Olin-chan, you're so strong!
That's right. Shinobu-chan and Kanjuro,
head out discreetly.
Caribou is quite helpful.
Oh, no, she did it...
Trafalgar Law.
Captain!
What's going on?
But...
The enemies are in close contact,
"They went that way" or "They're over here."
We're under attack!
The front gate has been destroyed!
So that's where the name "Smile" came from.
It's our crewmembers who created this mess,
so we'll take care of it!
Captain, I'm sorry!
Us getting caught really put you in a bind!
Even if it's artificial,
I thought it was a weird name for a Devil Fruit...
No way!
Who did such a thing?!
That communication uplink is a pain!
What did you do with our polar bear?
Thank you!
Let's go, Shinobu!
Leave it to Onami-dono!
Accursed invader! I'll teach you a lesson!
That's horrible!
With your ability,
you can get them out in an instant.
Now, here is the important part.
Wait!
Prepare yourself!
What kind of fool would keep all the hostages
in one conspicuous place.
The tragedy only begins there!
Look.
The Land of Wano's Smart Snails
have one disadvantage. They have weak signals!
SMART SNAIL (SMAIL FOR SHORT)
Take Shogun-sama to the castle!
I'll put you in that jail, too.
BOSS SNAIL
Orochi took notice of
those failed Smiles that were bitten once.
To compensate, every Smail's outgoing signal...
You know what to do! Kill them!
Don't push your luck.
Kill every single person
who rebels against me!
Sniff, sniff... Sniff...
...is first sent to what's called a Boss Snail
that's set up in every region,
Didn't you learn anything?
Did you?
They still harbored bad side effects,
Hey, where do you keep that
delicious red-bean soup?
I won't let him go!
and it relays the signal to the receiving Smails.
Shoot!
You can't take me down.
so they could produce more Pleasures.
Lick.
Do it!
All right!
Can't you hear me?! I said red-bean soup!
I understand how the system works, but...
No...
In the town of leftovers outside the Flower Capital,
Come on! You're so thickheaded!
Bulletproof?!
people were dying every day and crying out in hunger.
If I gobble up the Boss Snail in Udon...
What's up with that carpenter?!
And Orochi couldn't stand it,
Strong Right!
so he mixed those failed Smiles in
with the leftovers from the capital.
What do you think will happen?
All of Udon will lose signal?!
Who are they?!
Who in the world are they?!
This is it! I'm gonna die!
I'm definitely gonna die!
Oh, there he is!
That's correct!
There are apples! They're still fresh!
No! He stole Yasuie-sama's body!
I haven't been captured this long for nothing...
Everyone, let's share!
These will be great!
What's going on here?!
Ouch!
Don't worry!
I won't let them desecrate his body!
Shachi!
Incidentally,
I happen to know where the Boss Snail is.
Oh, no!
What's happening?
I have four lives now.
Is that true?!
Is that?!
After the first few times,
anyone would figure out...
Oh! Usohachi! Thanks! You saved me!
So trust me to cut their communications!
...what kind of fruit it is!
Why don't you go steal all the keys,
Raizo-chan?
On top of that ladder! Aim!
But the townspeople...
The intruder has broken
through the second gate!
Now approaching the third gate!
Whoa-whoa! A sniper getting sniped
is too much irony!
You can only cut me up
after you've killed...
...couldn't hold back their hunger!
What?!
Wait for me, Kawamatsu!
The third gate is...
I will get you out at any cost!
...the three from your own crew.
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano Spank!
What the...?!
Thanks, Orobi!
Another one appeared!
Yes. That's good.
She was...
...the geisha from that time...
I knew she was a magic user.
That is how Ebisu Town
where everyone is smiling and cheerful...
That's...
The enemies are strong. Surround them!
Red-bean soup!
Diable Jambe!
Concasse!
...was made.
Onami!
Leave them to me!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
The tragic town where everyone looks happy,
but they cannot even grieve over the death of their parents...
Is there red-bean soup here?
It's so close!
Where is the red-bean soup?!
Outta my way!
Red-bean soup!
So...
I think not!
Oh?
...please do not blame... those laughing people...
In that case...
You've surely got the Vinsmoke's blood in your veins.
I'll cut you!
Here it is!
I told you not to mention that name again!
What the...?!
This smell!
There's no mistake!
Red... bean... soup!
You also disguised yourself as Soba Mask, right?
Amongst all the species,
only humans can laugh!
Who knows.
How sweet and rich the smell is!
I guess I'm only popular with dinosaurs.
Yeah!
And there is so much of it!
If that's true, why not laugh, laugh?
Bi...!
Outta my way!
It was worth coming all the way here!
Big Mom?!
You really want me to cook a meal out of you?
What?! Am I dreaming?!
Now...
You'd better not think
that I'm as weak as that guy.
I think not!
Babanuki-sama!
I have an urgent update!
--Big Mom...
--That's Big Mom!
In that case...
What? I'm busy now!
What? Is it delicious?
I'll cut you!
That pot is actually empty!
Why is she here?!
Nasty ingredients always make the cooking more fun.
Empty?!
I heard that her ship was sunk!
What'll happen when Big Mom who is obsessed with food
finds out that there is no red-bean soup?!
Daddy...
That's the voice...
I am the Shogun's dog.
Daddy!
Who will she be mad at?!
She may kill us all...
...of a beauty!
I'm hungry!
She's getting attacked!
Zorojuro-san... Kyoshiro...
You need to get out of the capital!
I-I can't believe...
...that she destroyed the steel gate!
That was...
Red-bean soup!
But what about Toko?!
That old bag is too dangerous!
She'll be fine because
she's with the strong man named Sangoro!
...Shogun Orochi's heaviest sin...
Diable Jambe!
Just like Kaido-san,
Big Mom is the Emperor of the Sea...
Poele A Frire Spectre!
He made people's lives miserable...
Extra Hachis Hash!
What brought her here to Udon?!
...and even forbade them to grieve!
Let's wrap this up and get out of here!
Red-bean soup...
Okay!
If...
Red-bean soup...
Everyone, evacuate now!
Special Attack Atlas Comet!
...this is not hell...
Save yourselves!
...then what is?!
Mil Fleurs, Gigantesco Mano!
Red-bean soup!
Zorojuro-san!
I don't how bad it'll be,
but this is gonna be a disaster!
Hm? Red-bean soup?
Weapons Left!
Otama-chan! Come quickly!
Damn! Who in the world ate it?!
Tornado Tempo!
I smell red-bean soup!
Olin-chan is calling me!
I see. So she really wanted to eat it.
Let's eat it together!
I understand why she's sad
because I wanna eat it again, too!
What?!
She needs help.
Let's go eat red-bean soup now!
All soldiers! Fight them! Fight them!
The red-bean soup was so delicious!
Rebels are rioting in Rasetsu Town!
Why is there red-bean soup here?!
I'll be there soon... for you!
I told that deadly lie
at the risk of my life!
According to the Shogun's command,
it does not matter if they're dead or alive!
And the gate has been opened.
Feel free to kill them!
Straw hat man!
Go, guys!
I thought how to get inside
would be a problem...
Kick their asses!
So...
--Way to go!
--Hey, straw hat man.
--So...
So you're the one...
Now, we can rescue Big Bro!
Are those your crew
that the Light-Scroll Snail is showing?
...who ate it!
Momo-kun, let's go!
What? I think I've been told
to keep it a secret...
Y-Yeah! Let's go save Luffy...
Why's everyone looking at me?
Well, who cares...
No!
Well, you just said...
Zorojuro-san!
You got the death you deserved, Yasuie!
Otama-chan and Momonosuke-sama,
you must hide and wait outside.
...that you ate the soup out loud...
Go!
--There! Do it, do it! Take them down!
--This is no good...
Ya...
What?!
What?! How come?!
You're protecting her!
Did I say that out loud?!
Yasu-san passed away...
Zorojuro! You can do it!
It is obviously too dangerous for you
beyond this point, Otama-chan.
So she's your ally!
The red-bean soup was so delicious!
Hey, Straw Hat!
I just said it silently to myself!
That green-head is your friend?
And Momonosuke-sama,
you must not be spotted at any cost.
You do realize you just said it again, right?!
That's Zorojuro, the serious criminal
who killed a magistrate, right?
I cannot believe how impudent he was
to survive in my Land of Wano.
Luffytaro-san...
Hmmm... If you say so...
Like I said, I don't know him!
You were so rude, Hedgehog!
Okiku, you don't want them to know
that you're alive, either!
I finally found Luffy...
Why are you getting chased?!
It's too obvious!
But as usual, you're in the center of trouble!
I'm sorry! I tried to hide my face, but...
No, I mean, Sewer Rat!
You are right!
Thank you for your advice!
How interesting!
Of all people, he's trying to kill Orochi!
Moss knows that beautiful woman?!
I will disguise myself with this!
That scum deserves to be chopped up!
That is right, everyone!
Do it!
That bastard!
Shimotsuki Yasuie, Hakumai's former Daimyo
that you loved has died!
But he's up against Kyoshiro
who is quite tough.
This is...
His bounty is... lower than mine!
...perfect!
No one will ever know who I am!
Hey...
Send him off with the sound of your laughter!
What, Babanuki?
It's getting exciting now. I'm sure this can wait.
Did you...
Why do you samurai think
those cloth face coverings are so convincing?!
But a criminal has just arrived
from the Flower Capital...
...eat all of the red-bean soup?!
This is the Land of Wano!
The cheerful Land of Wano!
Chopperemon-san!
From the Flower Capital?
Who came now?!
Udon is reined over by...
It is just like heaven!
...the Animal Kingdom Pirates'
Lead Performer, Queen!
The criminal will arrive soon.
You smell like red-bean soup!
The Sumo Inferno...
Through that gate.
Oh, no!
...is back on!
Laugh! Laugh more!
Let's be careful!
Red-bean soup!
HITOKIRI
SERIOUS CRIMINAL
But we have a new rule.
Nice...
Red-bean soup smells great,
doesn't it?
Who's that?
He's a useless piece of garbage who couldn't fulfill a mission
assigned by the Shogun at the Flower Capital.
The moment you step out of the ring,
you'll be killed by the spikes in those collars!
Red-bean soup?
We have a message from Orochi-sama
saying you can punish him as you like!
It's really delicious, isn't it?
That was close...
That hasn't changed.
I forgot that if we step out of the ring,
we'll die!
Red-bean soup!
But the new rule is...
Toko?
Toko!!
Red-bean soup?!
I won't forgive you...
...as long as you guys are alive,
those two will be submerged in the water.
Wait a sec!
We brought Hitokiri Kamazo!
Queen-sama!
I'm begging you! Wait, Big Mom!
So you're Kamazo...
I've heard so much about you.
Again, the name Big Mom...
Red-bean soup! Red-bean soup!
Where is it?! Red-bean soup!
Which means only when you and that old geezer...
Who is that?!
And there's one more!
No, Toko! Come back!
And you who ate the soup! Who are you?!
...die,
Oh, no! We're in big trouble!
Daddy...
will we pull them out of the water.
Daddy! Daddy!
Hey, old bag! Did you say red-bean soup?!
Don't be ridiculous!
They have nothing to do with me!
What?!
Daddy!!
Okay, stop!
You don't know who I am?!
I have a report!
Yeah, that's probably true...
While we were escorting Kamazo here,
we caught another crook!
I did! Give it to me already!
Oh, yeah! I'm disguised as a samurai now,
so she doesn't recognize me!
But then, why do you seem a bit upset?
The escapee, Captain Kid!
Whoa-whoa, you'll get it soon.
Making Big Mom angry over food brings disaster...
Is it because you two are rivals
from the same generation?
Jaggy!
I heard that I could eat a lot of it here,
so I came all the way!
Well, you could always sacrifice your lives
for them immediately.
Didn't you know?!
All jailbreakers are to be executed immediately!
Screw that!
Who told you such nonsense?!
Daddy!
No matter how notorious or how many
hundreds of millions of berries a bounty is,
If she's lost her senses
and slipped into a Hunger Pang attack now,
Yes, death penalty!
You came back so quickly!
all humans...
no one can stop her!
I have good medicine!
By the way, how did you catch him?
...will drown in a mere five centimeters of water.
You can eat a lot of it?
Well, it was so easy!
That girl! She came to eat soba...
Did you come to steal it
knowing that it's my most favorite?!
This fool came towards us
yelling something,
This is bad! Really bad!
Otoko-chan!
I guess she's Tonoyasu's daughter!
so I shot him a couple of times,
but he didn't even try to run and here we are!
Now, the game begins.
What?!
Daddy, come back!
It rang again!
Maybe he forgot that
he has some Sea Prism Stone cuffs on!
This medicine will heal your wounds.
We're in trouble...
If we get pushed once more, we'll be dead!
Hey, wait, you fools!
Pull them out first!
Kid! You're so dumb!
We can't yield even an inch!
It's called toad oil
and it works super well!
While you're talking idly,
Jaggy and the other guy will drown!
If that pot was filled with red-bean soup,
You'll be fine...
I could have shared it with everyone from that town!
This is not idle talk!
He took the trouble of escaping,
so why did he surrender himself?!
I'm sorry, Otoko!
That town?
No! That medicine is...
She means Okobore Town?!
This is sweet red-bean soup.
Go ahead, Olin-san, try it!
Damn! He's totally losing it!
Hey, stop!
Hiyori-san!
I said stop!
Then,
Please, Toko! Come back!
Whoa! It smells good!
why don't you enter the ring?!
He's starting to transform!
I remember how you didn't
like the way you laugh...
Thank you!
Red-bean soup is like oxygen to me!
Daddy!
I'll kick your ass and end this!
It keeps me alive!
You even stopped laughing
out loud at some point...
So good!
It's delicious!
Everyone in that poor town was so kind to me...
Everyone who mocked your laugh
would be nearly beaten to death by you!
There you are, you damn brat!
So I wanted to bring back a lot of red-bean soup to them!
You're gonna fight?!
Who do you think you're talking to?
Please wait, Queen-sama!
Please... stop...
Don't push your luck!
If you fight Big Mom over food,
you'll end up in big trouble!
What?!
You started wearing a mask to hide your face
at some point...
You bastards!
That delicious red-bean soup...
Get out of my way!
I wanted them to have it, too!
That's the person I knew...
Straw hat man!
What happened to you?!
Sh... Sh...
Too late! We can't stop him now!
After we got separated,
what did Kaido do to you?!
She's not having a Hunger Pang attack?
Or did Orochi do something to you?!
Where's everyone else?!
Hey.
It's her kindness!
She's rampaging because of her kindness!
You punk.
Answer me!
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
BRACHIOSAURUS MODEL
Red-bean soup!
Hey, answer... Please!
I don't see how you can be so hopeful.
I see... So you are Yasuie's daughter!
Why did you eat it?
Killer!
Why did you eat it?!
That explains why you are so rude!
You little brat!
What?! That's him?!
Do you really think you can get out of here alive?
I just heard a tremendous noise...
Stop!
If you... If you...
Straw hat man, do you know him?
If you...
I'm scared!
Do you think you can beat us?
...did not laugh like an idiot at that time,
But Big Mom paved the way for us!
Yeah...
Komurasaki would not have had to die!
Old man!
You fools are gonna die!
Alright, Straw Hat...
I'm glad I got a chance to meet you.
You little shit!
Come off!
Damn! I won't let him die!
I'm not gonna die!
One by one!
Daddy! Daddy!
Both you and your father are driving me crazy!
Come off!
But next time we meet,
I won't show any mercy.
Shut up!
Come off!!
Hmm, okay.
But...
...I'm going to find the One Piece!
Red-bean soup!
This is it...
Come back, Daddy!
I will execute you!
Hey, we're in a terrible situation.
Come off!
Go to hell! You little shit!
We've already run out of red-bean soup...
What should we do?!
Come off!!
Hey, Kid! What're you
just standing there for?!
Otoko, run!
I do not want to lose you as well!
You know, Killer...
On our journey up to this point,
we've been laughed at and ridiculed
Disappear from my sight!
You're right.
We have a great amount of red-bean soup here.
When it comes to where I die...
whenever we mentioned getting our hands
on the One Piece.
...I'll do the choosing!
But it's all mine!
And each time that happened,
I slaughtered everyone who laughed.
You can't even have a drop of it, old bag!
Red-bean soup...
But what lies ahead is a sea of death
for those who don't got the guts to mention it.
What?! The collars!
Olin is a nicer version of Big Mom,
Let's meet again in the New World!
so she might be bullied
or hurt by Queen!
Let's go, men!
What?
I see... So you've got red-bean soup.
The collars came off!
Hey! What was that noise?
Old man! What did I do?!
Is that the masked guy who was with Jaggy?!
Don't ever say red-bean
soup in front of me again!
Yay!
Jaggy must've tried to save him...
--It came off!
--I can't believe it... That was...
Go away, old bag!
How cruel...
He was forced to eat the Smile fruit
and was given a mask of laughter that he can never take off...
You got away again!
Alright! Let's run, old man!
Damn Orochi... How could
he do such a thing...
Hey, what's wrong?!
Hey, respond!
Straw hat man!
Queen-sama!
We lost contact with the guards outside!
Before you forget that feeling,
What did they do to change you completely?!
protect me!
A moment of crisis will reveal your true power!
Come on!
Who did this to my buddy?!
Those are...
The wanted man who killed the magistrate!
What?!
Just give me...
Practice now?!
WANTED - ZOROJURO
If I fail, you'll die!
Where's my crew?!
And the soba cook who stood against the Kyoshiro Family!
...red-bean soup...
Dammit!
I know!
WANTED - SANGORO
...already!
What a fool.
Ryuo, huh?
What?!
Hey, balloon.
Olin-san!
Straw hat man?
Hey, balloon!
Queen-sama!
Alright!
Red-bean soup!
What do you want, Straw Hat?!
Why are you yelling?
At last, I made it!
Come on, let's just start the sumo matches!
Red-bean soup!
Bring it on! Emperor of the Sea!
Come on!
To take down their formidable enemy,
the Straw Hats keep fighting!
The enraged Big Mom is on a rampage!
She fights furiously against Luffy whose back is to the wall!
Her strength is not of this world!
Here comes Big Mom!
An emergency occurs! It's out of control!
If Luffy dies, Kid and Killer
will be freed from torture!
Sanji bravely fights back against fierce attacks
from Drake of the Worst Generation.
Big Mom rampages about looking for red-bean soup
and finally breaks in on the Sumo Inferno!
She takes down the Supreme Officer Queen
and fiercely attacks Luffy over red-bean soup!
Queen, who toys with people's lives,
resumes the Sumo Inferno!
As the labor camp is about to be destroyed,
Luffy's enemy Queen plans a strategy to capture Big Mom!
In anger, Zoro takes a slice
at Kyoshiro who stands in his way!
Queen and Big Mom!
Facing those two monsters, Luffy is driven to the wall!
He gets thrown out of the ring
and his collar is about to explode and kill him!
Thunder roars and each of the Straw Hats shows
their great technique!
Bearing responsibility for their fate,
Luffy is as determined as ever and gives it all he has!
However, an unexpected turnaround
happens at the chaotic Inferno!
What will happen to Luffy?!
And how will the deadly operation end up?!
Will they be able to
break through Orochi's encircling forces?!
He finally faces off against Queen!
Will he be able to survive?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Determination! Win Through the Sumo Inferno!"
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Straw Hats Step In!
An Uproarious Deadly Battle at the Execution Ground!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Storm Has Come! A Raging Big Mom!"
"Stop the Emperor of the Sea! Queen's Secret Plan!"
"A Grudge Over Red-bean Soup!
Luffy Gets into a Desperate Situation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org