Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba"              "Nanohana"   "Katorea"
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
After arriving in Alabasta,
Luffy and the others
encountered Navy Captain Smoker.
There to save Luffy
in the nick of time
was the man who controls fire:
Fire Fist Ace.
Ace turned out to be
Luffy's older brother.
"Ace and Luffy!
Hot Emotions and Brotherly Bonds"
Move.
I'm afraid that's a no-can-do.
Fire Fist Ace...
To think you're Straw Hat's brother...
White...
Spark!
Wh-What is that?!
--Is a house on fire?!
--No, it's no ordinary fire!
What in the world is happening?
It's a fight between flame and smoke?!
He did say he ate
the Flame-Flame Fruit.
But Luffy! Is it true
that guy's your brother?!
Yeah! His name's Ace!
You having a brother
isn't that surprising,
but what's he doing
in the Grand Line?!
Ace is a pirate!
He left the island three years
before me to find the One Piece!
A-Anyways, let's hurry back to the ship!
Let's escape before
anyone comes after us!
Yes, Nami-san!
Still, I never thought I'd
see Ace in a place like this!
The path splits into two!
Usopp, left! Hear me, guys?!
Yes, Nami-san! I'll follow
you wherever you go!
Enough, pervy cook!
Cool! The fireball's gone even higher!
It seems there really is no end to
a fight between flame and smoke.
Though it was already obvious enough.
Where did Straw Hat's crew go?
Th-They're gone!
So is Ace! We've lost sight of him!
I caught Straw Hat for the
first time in the Grand Line...
But Portgas D. Ace.
You simply had to get in the way.
Hurry and load the stuff!
We're leaving right away!
Hurry!
Set the sails!
S-Say. Are we leaving again just
after we finally reached the island?
Yes. We only stopped by this town
to get what we're going to need.
Now we're going to head up the
river into the interior of Alabasta.
Our next destination is Erumalu,
the City of Green.
Erumalu?
Hurry!
Pick up the pace!
All set!
Okay! Let's set sail!
Y'know...
Huh?
I get the feeling we're
missing someone...
So do I...
Yeah. We're missing
approximately one person.
That moron!
Huh?!
That's weird.
Why am I the only one here?
Where did they go?
Sheesh! I guess my letting you
escape was pretty much pointless.
Yo!
Ace!
Haven't seen you in a while, Luffy!
You too, Ace!
How many years has it been?
Good question.
But, Luffy. It looks like you
still go at your own pace,
just like you did
since you were a kid.
You too, Ace! I was surprised
you ate a Devil Fruit,
but besides that, you're the same!
Like when you'd sneak into the fields,
eat 100 watermelons,
and then spit the seeds
out like a gun and run!
That wasn't me! That was you!
And then you got big bumps right here!
That was you, too!
I watched and laughed!
I guess we're both the same!
Yeah!
This brings back memories!
Say, weren't your friends
looking for you?
Yeah.
But, Ace. What are you
doing in this country?
Huh? You mean you didn't get
the message I sent to Drum?
Drum?
Yeah. It's no big deal
or anything, though.
I'm just in these waters
on minor business,
so I thought I might look you up.
Minor business?
I'm a member of the
Whitebeard Pirates now.
Whitebeard Pirates?
This is the mark of the
Whitebeard Pirates. It's my pride.
Oh?
Luffy. Won't you join
the Whitebeard Pirates?
Your friends can come too, of course.
No.
I figured not. Just thought I'd ask.
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate I know.
I wanna help him to be
King of the Pirates...
And not you, Luffy.
That's fine!
Then we'll just have to fight!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
Hey! Don't drink it all, Luffy!
Something must've happened in town.
Smoker and all the
marines left the ship...
But...
This is perfect! I'll use this
chance to escape somehow!
Mr. 11.
You must be members of Baroque
Works if you know my codename!
Are you Millions?! Hurry and untie me!
Yeah, we are members of Baroque Works.
But we're Billions. Meaning we're
candidates to be Number Agents.
Mr. 11. You're barely an agent.
You're not much stronger than us.
O-Oh! I see!
Sorry about that, Billions.
But could you hurry and untie me?
Don't be silly!
With you gone, one of us can
be promoted to a Number Agent.
So let's empty one of the Agents' seats!
W-Wait!
Hey!
Fire Fist Ace is in this town!
What?! Fire Fist Ace?!
The Second Division Commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates?
If we can take down Ace,
we're guaranteed to be Number Agents!
Anyways, let's look for your friends.
Getting spotted by the
Navy's always a pain.
They might've gone back to the ship.
Which harbor is your ship in?
Actually, I can't remember at all.
Oh, geez.
Pirate ship captains usually
remember where they leave their ship.
Don't worry about it!
You are the same as ever.
Say, what kind of crew do you have?
A swordsman who wants to be the
world's greatest sword master.
He's always wearing a haramaki.
A navigator who likes maps
and tangerines and money!
Then there's a cook who
makes really yummy food...
Oh, and there's a liar, too!
And then a reindeer!
That's quite the variety you got there.
We also have a princess and a duck now!
Oh?
They're all so interesting!
I'd say you're probably the
most interesting of all, though.
Still, only a handful of people for a
pirate crew... That's just like you.
I also want a musician!
Stop right there, Fire Fist Ace!
As you can see,
there's no place to run now!
Fire Fist Ace! Your head is mine!
Prepare yourself!
I-Is it really okay to
set sail without Luffy?
The Navy will be all over the harbors.
We need to hide the ship first.
There should be a cove ahead
that's hidden from view!
So we'll wait for things to
cool down, then look for Luffy.
Yeesh! He's always, always
causing trouble like this!
He's a real reliable captain...
Fire Fist Ace! Your bad luck ends here!
Hey! Isn't that Straw Hat Luffy?!
N-Now that you mention it--!
H-He's worth 30 million Berries!
Talk about lucky! Fire Fist Ace
and Straw Hat Luffy!
Once I have your heads, our promotion
is a hop, skip, and jump away!
Anyway, let's find your ship.
Let's go to the shore.
Yeah.
Hey, you!
Hold it right there!
Bastards!
Get them!
Take this!
What the--?! What the--?!
So sorry!
Hold the bastard down!
Wh-What the--?! His arms stretched!
He has Devil Fruit powers?!
Don't scare me like that, you jerks!
Gum-Gum...
Oww! Hot!
...Bazooka!
D-Don't let 'em scare you!
The rank of Number Agent
is riding on this!
After them!
Oh! The ocean!
See your ship?
There's no escape!
You guys just never learn.
Oh! There it is!
Hey! Over here! Guys!
Hey, Luffy. Go on--
Never mind.
Oh! There he is! It's Luffy!
--I found Luffy!
--You did?
Yeah. That stupid face is definitely his.
Huh?!
I'm back!
Sanji-san! Tony-kun!
Oh, come on!
Not again...
Sorry 'bout that, Sanji, Chopper!
Do you not know how to learn your
lesson?! I oughta gut you whole!
Yeah! Do you have any idea how
much trouble you've caused?!
Try to act somewhat like a captain!
Sorry.
Oh, that's right! Ace!
--Ace?
--Your brother was with you?
Is it okay to just leave him there?
I guess he'll be okay! Ace is strong!
He's strong?
Yeah! He hadn't eaten the
Flame-Flame Fruit a long time ago,
but I still never beat
him in a single fight!
He's real strong, Ace is!
There's a flesh-and-blood
person you could never beat?!
I guess the big brother of a
monster is an even bigger monster...
That's right! I lost all the time!
But I'd win now if we tried!
I assume that's another groundless claim.
Who...
can win what now?!
Oh! Ace! This is the crew
I was talking about!
Oh! Thank you all for taking
care of my little brother!
Eh? Oh, not at all.
He might be a bit much for
you to handle too, but...
No, not at all.
Take good care of 'im.
You probably have lots
of catching up to do.
Why don't you come in?
I'll make some tea.
No, uhh, that's okay.
Don't do it on account of me.
T-Talk about unexpected...
That's for sure.
I would've expected him to
be as reckless as Luffy...
No, this sensible man can't
possibly be Luffy's brother!
He's a nice guy who
cares about his brother!
Brothers can be so wonderful!
The sea is just full of surprises...
Come now, everyone!
See! Aren't these guys neat?!
Baroque Works!
Those are the Billions' ships!
Fire Fist Ace and Straw Hat Luffy!
Don't think you can get away!
We'll show you just what Baroque
Works' Billions are made of!
Those guys again?
Luffy. I'll clean them up.
Eh?
What's he going to do?
Especially in that little boat...
Let's see how skilled
this Second Division Commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates really is!
Here he comes! Fire Fist Ace!
Just try to get past five
of our ships, if you can!
He jumped!
F-Fire!
Shoot him into the ocean!
Fire Fist!
Whoa!
Captain Smoker!
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew
are nowhere to be found.
What do you think, Tashigi?
Vivi was with them.
Vivi? Princess Nefertari Vivi
was with the Straw Hats?
She must be a hostage.
They abducted the princess
for some sort of scheme...
No. Vivi was acting like
she was part of the crew.
The princess? Part of their crew?
Something really is
happening in this country.
Captain Smoker!
I'm sorry, sir!
Mr. 11 was done in by someone
while he was tied up on the ship!
We still haven't located
the Straw Hats, either!
No need to fret. I have a good
idea of where they're headed.
He's after Crocodile.
Crocodile?! One of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
the pirates given government approval?!
You know I hate the Seven Warlords.
Especially that detestable man.
B-But standpoint-wise,
he's a Navy and government ally!
He's always been a clever pirate.
He's never been the type to just
quietly obey the government!
Tashigi! All you need
to remember is one thing!
A pirate is a pirate,
no matter where he goes!
Straw Hat will show
up wherever Crocodile is!
Things should become
clear if we go there.
And next time, you won't
get away, Straw Hat!
--Woohoo!
--Ace is one of us now!
Cheers!
Who said I was joining you?
Here's to delicious drinks!
Cheers!
Don't worry about it!
They're always looking
for an excuse to drink to!
Medicine is horrible!
Ace! Are you sure you won't join us?
I'm chasing a certain man.
His name's Blackbeard.
Blackbeard?!
He's the pirate who
attacked the Drum Kingdom!
He used to be a member of the 2nd
Division of the Whitebeard Pirates,
one of my men.
But he committed the worst
possible sin on a pirate ship:
he killed a crewmember and jumped ship.
So, as the commander,
I gotta find and get rid of him.
So that's why you're chasing after him?
I came here because I caught word
that Blackbeard was seen in Yuba.
Then your destination
is the same as ours!
We've just entered the Sandora River.
First, we'll land at Erumalu, then
head into the interior of Alabasta
to reach Yuba here!
The leader of the rebel army is in Yuba.
I see. So you're headed to Yuba next.
I'll follow Nami-san and
Vivi-chan wherever they go!
Get lost, Love Cook.
Say what, you--?!
A-Anyways! It looks like we can
travel together for a short while!
Yeah, yeah! His brother
is more than welcome here!
Let's have a fun time, Ace!
Yeah!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
This is Erumalu?
--Huh? There's nothing here.
--Erumalu, the City of Green...
The City of Green?!
There's no green anywhere!
It was a thriving city
until just recently...
This was?
Karoo. I have an important
favor to ask of you.
I want you to go to Alubarna!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Erumalu, the City of Green,
and the Kung Fu Dugongs!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!