Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
25 YEARS AGO
I am worried to death about Otoko...
Rewinding to 25 years ago...
This is the rendezvous port!
Why hasn't anyone come?!
The Reverie always triggers big incidents.
but still, Kawamatsu,
Even if there is a disagreement,
as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
I am not going to meet everyone now.
I am begging you!
Somebody, please help us!
People should not get
emotional before battles.
A little before the Great Pirate Era began...
On the night of the Fire Festival,
we'll have the greatest party ever!
But what happened this time is no good!
It's a bit late to mention this,
but there's actually one thing that I haven't told you about.
Yes, it's gonna be an anniversary.
Together with everyone else,
--Hey, listen up, guys!
--What is it?
please save the Land of Wano!
An incident had already taken place
the night before.
Right after the Reverie was dismissed and we set off,
an incident occurred,
We, Animal Kingdom Pirates...
First, I must tell you that the only person
who was able to manage Enma in this country...
and the Big Mom Pirates...
and I received the report aboard ship.
Let me stand up.
We the Navy will do our best to resolve it,
but please don't be afraid of...
"The Number-One Samurai in the Land of Wano!
Here comes Kozuki Oden!"
...decided...
...was Kozuki Oden
and no one before or since!
...to form...
...an alliance!
...the surface world as well as humans!
I am counting on you guys!
Tokage (Lizard) Port is in Udon.
TOKAGE PORT
Yeah, leave it to us!
Wait! What is this all about?!
NIGHT BEFORE THE GREAT BATTLE
By changing the rendezvous point
from Habu Port to Tokage Port,
See you at the port!
Akazaya...
even quick-witted enemies
won't be able to get in the way of our plan.
Yeah!
"Fog"!
And...
...Oden!
As always, you're conscientious...
Yasuie-sama...
Well, it's a rule...
...must have considered every possibility
and taken steps early on for us!
Oh, yeah! Listen!
I am going to show you hell!
There's something that I need to report...
...to you, Captain!
We will take Kaido and
Orochi's heads at any cost...
BEACH OF KURI
X. DRAKE - CAPTAIN OF "SWORD"
NAVY HQ TOP SECRET SPECIAL FORCE
--Did you find the ship?
--Yes.
Just you wait, Kaido!
...to avenge the late Oden-sama!
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea
naturally forfeit all of their rights,
We found it.
Is everybody having a good time?!
ISSHO
But you sure about this?
Just do as I say!
and their connections with the World Government
are cut off.
SEA AREA AROUND THE ENTRANCE OF THE NEW WORLD
"Ticking Down to the Great Battle!
The Straw Hats Go into Combat Mode!"
That means...!
I am glad that I followed you.
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Do it!
Buggy!
Roger!
You're just another pirate!
Huh?!
Why are you saying such a thing now, idiot?!
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the International Military Draft,
That's not fair, you fools!
Is it really...
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
A decision was made without telling us
and since we're no longer useful, you'll arrest us?!
AMIGASA VILLAGE, KURI, LAND OF WANO
...true?!
Oden!
Yes, it is true.
We must thank you instead!
Hiyori-sama is alive?!
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
The Navy.
You being outwitted by Crocodile and Doflamingo
is none of my business!
The Seven Warlords.
Yes, she is.
The Four Emperors.
What do you think will happen to
the balance of power?
Don't take it out on me!
Mission complete!
You're drinking too much!
Control yourself!
I don't know. Who can
tell before we upset it?
I am worried to death about Otoko...
We've got the whole coast surrounded!
I will not let them have their way!
What should we do?
but still, Kawamatsu,
Shut up!
I won't take advice from a drunken doctor!
Of course, we'll fight them in a flashy way!
Next, bridges!
I am not going to meet everyone now.
That vicious pirate was approved as a king of a country
under the Seven Warlord system
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KIBI AND UDON
I'm concerned about your health!
The great bridge between Kibi and Udon
has been blown up!
People should not get
emotional before battles.
Show some guts!
You bastard!
Destroy them!
and allowed to reign over this island
by none other than...
You fools!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KURI AND UDON
The great bridge between Kuri and Udon
has been blown up!
Together with everyone else,
Lie there quietly!
That's our Chairman Buggy!
please save the Land of Wano!
...the World Government!
Ow, ow, ow...
They had it coming!
That hurt.
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER, BUGGY'S DELIVERY CHAIRMAN
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN RINGO AND HAKUMAI
What I want to destroy is...
Look!
The great bridge that connects the regions is...!
That was the cure for stupidity.
Your Majesty! You should not do that!
...the system.
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
Why, all of a sudden?!
Cut it out!
Raise your head!
We no longer need the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
We cannot get to the other side now!
It's so unforgivable...
Damn you!
All that remains is the port!
Weevil! I give you approval to take them down!
That little devil said such a polite thing?!
Really?! Then...
Orochi-sama! All the ships
have been destroyed!
ITACHI PORT, KURI
"Big News!
An Incident That Will Affect the Seven Warlords!"
I'm gonna kill them!
That is fine. We will rebuild
once everything is over.
She really grew up!
EDWARD WEEVIL, WHITEBEARD JR. (SELF-PROCRAIMED)
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Kawamatsu! Since you were in prison,
I imagined something bad had happened to her,
In the name of Whitebeard!
I still have not seen the Akazaya members
or samurai troops who they recruited with my own eyes.
I feel a tremor of excitement...
I must go back...
MARIJOA
It's been a long time...
so I could not ask you!
The World Conference known as the Reverie.
To the Land of Wano?
Yeah, there is still something major left to do...
DRACULE MIHAWK, "HAWK-EYE"
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
People skipped forward in time
from 20 years ago?!
It's a grand conference of 50 representative kings and queens
held every four years,
...since I was the one being chased.
Where is she now?
Is she with a bodyguard?!
Is there anything we can do to help, Oden?
Do not worry. She is in a secure location.
Granny Nyon!
representing more than 170 countries
that are affiliated with the World Government.
How can anyone believe that?!
There are Navy ships off the coast!
If you need a hand...
Unless they see one of their heads.
What?!
I can lend one, Oden-san!
Anyway, that is great!
They've already gone into action?!
That is really great!
You fool!
You'll get in his way instead!
No, even if they see it,
it is still hard to believe.
Don't panic!
Hey, Oden-san. I'm sure I can help!
And that damn fool, Yasuie,
made it sound even more ridiculous!
The Reverie was dismissed
in a state of great confusion as always,
Snake Princess!
She is alive...
I think they're...
and all the representatives went home.
Rayleigh...
...forgetting something!
Redtaro, Buggyjiro...
But the information is credible.
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
Then...
Thank you!
The Akazaya members are alive!
But...
Big Bro!
...a week later...
BOA HANCOCK, PIRATE EMPRESS
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...because we were strong!
Hiyori!
Gee... I'm finally home-jamon...
Dropkick!
I do not care if my men think
that I am talking nonsense.
RYUGU CASTLE, RYUGU KINGDOM, FISH-MAN ISLAND
It's getting interesting!
We, the Kozuki, must do it!
Boy... The surface world is so far above...
I have authority to take action!
I've asked you so many times,
why do you call me "jiro (second son)"?
Hiyori!
Um, thank you for escorting us!
I have blocked all the routes to Tokage Port.
Let it go!
Zorojuro!
TOKAGE PORT
Did you save her?
Oh, yeah. The Kozuki, huh?
Luffy-sama's grandfather-sama!
"A Legendary Battle!
Garp and Roger!"
Thank you!
I learned a lot through this journey...
Four thousand troops?
Good job recruiting so many.
Well, don't mention it.
She is a bit rough,
but she is actually a bit weak,
It was a pretty long trip, huh, Neptune?
But no one will make it to the port!
I always wondered
why the Land of Wano closed its door.
and cries a lot, so she is quite a handful.
You must be tired!
Hey, Momo.
You still think it's just like the old days?
NAVY
I will not give them even
a chance to get revenge!
I left the country by my own choice, so I won't say
a selfish thing like, "Let me become the Shogun"...
I'm exhausted-jamon.
Garp, stay here with us and rest well.
She is now 18 years older than you.
Damn you Akazaya ghosts!
Well, maybe I'll have a cup of tea,
Wallow in the despair from
being isolated and helpless!
But I must pass this will on at any cost!
but considering the situation,
I can't stay here that long...
Dropkick!
A dropkick from someone
18 years older than me?!
You must be happy, Issho...
The Reverie always triggers big incidents.
With my great retainers that I left behind,
That is not good...
The abolition of the Seven Warlords of the Sea
was what you all really wanted...
When 50 countries gather,
a simple "Let's get along" won't do.
I will open up the Land of Wano!
That beautiful lady who was with you
at that time...
I was against it, but the leaders' decision
can't be reversed.
Stop, you all!
And I will wait for the "future"
that will come more than 20 years from now!
...was Momonosuke's sister?!
Taking that small boat is like suicide!
Each country has tons of
problems of their own.
Dammit, how can everyone be so naive?!
Large and mighty countries
just quietly stare at each other,
W-What?
Let's do it, Oden!
Justice comes with a price...
Yeah!
and let their proxies bicker...
I will do it, Roger!
And there's no escaping it?
Let's regroup and begin again
when we get another chance!
Momonosuke-kun!
You can't understand
because you've never been one of them...
If we miss this opportunity...
Is there anything you want?
To them, resources and technologies
are a weapon.
25 YEARS LATER
Now 25 years have passed.
Don't suck up to her brother, idiot.
we have to wait for a year.
The world where innocent weak people
get ignored...
Sangoro-dono.
They say that all countries are equal,
but that's just lip service.
Enough fooling around.
But we cannot hide anymore.
They will find out that we took control of Udon soon.
...is worthless!
LAND OF WANO ACT THREE
Kawamatsu! They are ready!
Wealth and poverty and religious differences,
won't allow them to be equal...
Hurry up! Keep moving!
Kaido's whole army will come to hunt rebels.
Are you sure about this?
Hurry!
Yeah.
We have already come to an agreement...
OROCHI
I see.
We cannot continue to steal
their food anymore, either.
Then I will hold my tongue.
Even if they shake hands,
they step on each other's foot with a grin.
Before we left Kuri,
you surely heard what happened.
Hitetsu-dono!
Take this first.
I wonder how many leaders there are
who can speak for their
This is Kitetsu II which was confiscated
from Luffytaro-san at Udon.
The Seven Warlords of the Sea are no more.
The people of Okobore Town
who were believed in our great battle...
citizens and for other countries...
Let's believe in the SSG,
the Navy's Special Science Group...
HABU PORT, HAKUMAI
Oh! Thanks!
The round table must be weeping...
...were burned alive.
You're right.
The conversations among the leaders were explosive.
Orochi-sama!
That big-stomached brat!
Among them...
The balance of power in the world
is about to change drastically!
He took it without permission.
...was my wife.
We're no exception, but quarrels between countries
can't be solved so easily.
Kitetsu!
Please allow us to go!
Just how it'll change is unknown!
"The Rendezvous Port!
The Land of Wano Act Three Begins!"
I knew it was one of the famed blades.
If there is a long history,
the conflict must have deeper roots.
No.
I heard that Kaido and Big Mom
will team up in the Land of Wano...
Do you want us to flee
and live in disgrace?!
Hark! My name is Tenguyama Hitetsu!
Even if there is a disagreement,
as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
What?!
I am a swordsmith from the Land of Wano!
Today is a good day!
What about me?
Look at that view!
ISSHO
Does it mean the return of Rocks?!
For two decades,
We want you to live with Hiyori-sama!
I have been awaiting the day that
I can hand back these swords to
But what happened this time is no good!
It is a perfect day for a banquet.
Do not be so selfish!
It's a bit late to mention this,
Our Orochi-sama is even favored by good weather.
but there's actually one thing
that I haven't told you about.
Momonosuke-sama and Hiyori-sama!
Even your father had no support at first!
Don't speak of it
like it's legend or something!
Right after the Reverie was dismissed and we set off,
an incident occurred,
This time, Kyoshiro will stay at the capital to look after it!
Tell him we are counting on him!
If we had not met Oden-sama...
It's all true...
Yes, sir!
and I received the report aboard ship.
We would not be samurai
since we were all immature.
Poor guy! He can't attend the banquet!
and a disaster that menaces us
despite how busy we are at the moment!
These were Oden-sama's precious swords.
We the Navy will do our best to resolve it,
but please don't be afraid of...
Ame-no-Habakiri that can slice heaven in two!
This Habu Port in Hakumai
is known as the largest port in the Land of Wano.
That is why we want to be...
JUSTICE
...the surface world as well as humans!
And Enma that can even cut
through the bottom of hell!
...Oden-sama's samurai
retainers until the end.
What happened?
Garp, what kind of report did you receive?
Maple trees line the giant pier
which projects from the shore into the sea,
Both counted among the 21 Excellent Grade Swords
along with Shusui.
Do not go!
Do not go, Kin'emon!
It's an incident concerning Alabasta Kingdom.
Do not go!
I do not want to lose even one more person!
and the lovely scene of fluttering red leaves
sends ships off.
Momonosuke-sama, what would you like to do
with my masterpiece?!
Alabasta Kingdom...
What?! Two Emperors of the Sea joined forces?!
Vivi-sama!
W-Well...I am not ready yet!
It is a good day!
Listen, men!
--No way!
--Of all times, now?!
Before all of this transpired...
Not that I am scared of it,
Bring sake! Let's have a cup
while admiring those red leaves!
This centuries old national isolation
is deeply tied to Kozuki...
To be precise, we got information
that they'll team up in the days ahead...
but I want you to keep it for now.
At the World Economic Journal
right after the Reverie was dismissed...
Orochi-sama, you should not drink
until you see Kaido-sama...
And that Enma is yours!
They haven't done any harm so far
Wow! It's incident after incident!
And...!
Who cares! I know he is drunk, too!
and we don't know their purpose or how to deal with it yet.
Can't believe this many
things happened at once.
The time will eventually come!
First, I must tell you that the only person
who was able to manage Enma in this country...
It is a big banquet with 30 thousand guests!
Let's have a great time as always!
The only thing that connects those two...
Listen! Come up with the
greatest heading ever!
Before the world starts to change,
...was Kozuki Oden
and no one before or since!
...is the legendary Rocks Pirates.
open up the Land of Wano!
Sir, which one should make the front-page?!
On the night of the annual Fire Festival,
But there isn't much information about them, either...
the two leaders who rule the Land of Wano
come together at Onigashima.
Listen! Someone has died!
The big obituary sells papers!
And they throw a big banquet
at which all of Orochi's army and Kaido's army gather.
Big Mom and Kaido have hated each other
for a long time...
--Then, that'll be the headline...
--No, wait!
The resolution they passed is also good.
I didn't expect such a thing would happen.
But a murder attempt makes
you excited as well!
Try cutting one of those trees.
Sengoku-san, what are Rocks Pirates?
That's right!
FLOWER CAPITAL ON THE DAY OF THE FIRE FESTIVAL
Okay, let's have two front pages!
The back page will have the same format as the front!
Oh, yeah.
You are too young to know about them...
Okay!
Sir!
Forty one years ago, in the Flower Capital...
Express mail from the Government.
Hey! Hurry up!
Zoro-dono.
A check, huh?
I am going to say this frankly out of kindness,
but if I were you,
Hurry up! It's already started!
Oh, that's a lot!
The Rocks Pirates were a gang of unique characters
who gathered together...
Kozuki Oden is back!
Wait! I don't like the way my bangs look!
I see. It's an order to
manipulate information.
I would not take it.
--Hide your wives!
--And daughters!
But for which case?
...around just one money-making scheme
on the Pirate Island of Fullalead ages ago.
Hushing up this incident?
Hide the livestock!
I can't do that!
Throw this back in their faces!
They were all so violent,
they even battled to the death on board their own ship.
--He failed to set sail again!
--He wants to get out of here that badly?!
Hey, what's wrong?
No, no, no...
There was a very popular man in the capital.
Its members were, first, Captain Rocks...
Do what you're told, Morgans!
The secret agency, Cipher Pol?!
Whitebeard in his younger days!
The whole cliff has been cut off!
You must obey orders
from the World Government.
Big Mom!
Don't move!
And Kaido!
Don't underestimate "Big News" Morgans!
Those three used to be on board
the same pirate ship.
Look at Zorojuro's arm!
When did he sneak in?!
It is so restrictive!
What?!
Sir! Members of Cipher Pol are
the Government officials!
--N-No way!
--I-I can't believe it!
Damn...!
I know!
Guys, it's dangerous to stay here.
There are other pirates from the Rocks Pirates,
who later became infamous.
Give it back!
Let's relocate!
Shiki the Golden Lion who used to be a big name
and even vied for supremacy in the New World.
Come on! Dance!
Drink! Sing!
I may be a miser,
but I'm first and foremost a journalist!
It's the Fire Festival in the capital today!
There were still others
like Silver Axe, Captain John, and Wang Zhi...
It is so restrictive
that I might be squeezed to death!
The only day we're allowed to drink!
Sometimes I spin lies and make people dance.
I'm a DJ of words!
You've got to be kidding!
They're all big-name pirates!
We'll drink hard and have a good time today!
I...
I decide what to publish!
Why was such a pirate group lost to history?
That's Enma!
Here I come! Here I come!
One of the reasons is that they disliked each other so much,
It will suck out the owner's Ryuo
as it pleases,
they took no pride in publicizing their exploits.
Mr. Morgans!
You got a call from King Wapol of Drum Kingdom...
I...
Oh...
and cut more than needed.
Secondly...
The sky's so clear!
We'll see a beautiful full moon tonight!
Captain Rocks had the ambition
to become the king of the world...
King Wapol?
If you were a regular swordsman,
you would have dried up and collapsed by now...
What does he want?
Well, sounds like he has information to leak.
I...
Impressive!
What?!
...want to see the big world!
What do you want to do?
Do you want other swords?
As I like!
So they showed their teeth at the World Government
as if they were a terrorist group,
No, I'll take this!
Oops... I want to eat oden!
and the Government has been
covering up incidents since.
The seasons of each region of the Land of Wano
differ wildly.
What's going on?
Enma, huh?
A special report?
Once I get used to it,
But everyone knew how threatening they were
at that time...
TOKAGE PORT
The weather also varies tremendously
by location.
I'm gonna be even stronger, right?
Don't worry...
It's gonna be okay...
A particularly fateful incident took place at God Valley
38 years ago.
At that same moment,
at the rendezvous point, Tokage Port...
AT THE SAME MOMENT
THE RENDEZVOUS POINT, TOKAGE PORT
He is a fool!
A vast expanse of green forest.
38 YEARS AGO
It was reported on the news that the world's
In addition to the incident that
the Government failed to hush up,
strongest Rocks Pirates were annihilated on that island...
Through flowers, plants, and trees that are growing thick,
a fresh stream runs.
the decision of the leaders made at the Reverie
and the incident that occurred there...
Gear Four!
...became known throughout the world in a flash
and stunned people.
And a beautiful sea.
Bounce-Man!
This is a story that takes place in the Land of Wano
when it was still teeming with life.
Wait! What is this all about?!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
That can't be true!
It's just a story in the World Economic Journal, right?
REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
King Kong Gun!
TEAHOUSE
You got away from a moving mountain?!
That's right!
It's the WEJ!
That bird president must've written nonsense!
It was groaning.
Not a single ship is in sight!
Maybe the mountain god became angry!
Where are the four thousand soldiers?!
I'm sure of it!
I am positive we conquered Udon!
It's Sabo! That's impossible...
Just kidding!
Anyway, you all look so happy.
That wasn't good.
I don't buy it!
Yeah, you're straining yourself too much.
But no one is there at the labor camp, either.
What happened?
Calm down!
MISS TSURU, WAITRESS AT
THE MOUNTAIN PASS TEAHOUSE
What?! That wasn't good?!
We finally caught it!
First, we must confirm the facts.
It seems like this port was attacked!
But all of them are out of contact...
How can we confirm?
It appears the cat couldn't make it.
This isn't true, right?
Sabo-kun...
No one could stop the advancement of the evil,
What a splendid boar!
The Smail is not responding.
ROYAL ESCORT SHIP, GOA KINGDOM
If we take it to the capital,
we'll get one Platinum coin!
My lady!
but Navy HQ Vice Admiral Garp was able to!
He was in Marijoa?!
We cannot contact anyone...
What?!
B-Big Bro-sama?!
That's enough to build a decent house!
His name became known throughout the world
Yeah! The Kurokoma boss is looking for
a legendary white boar to display in his storefront,
At twilight on the day of the Fire Festival,
at Tokage Port!
What happened to Makino?
and people started calling him the hero of the Navy.
Keep working hard! We don't have time!
--The bar is closed today.
--What?!
so he posted a reward for one.
There was so much news in the world...
This is the rendezvous port!
Make it strong enough
to carry a hundred thousand people.
THREE DAYS UNTIL THE RAID
So that's the beginning of
Vice Admiral Garp's many tales of heroism!
He shouldn't display it!
I could use a drink.
Why hasn't anyone come?!
Where did they go?!
White boars are divine messengers.
We're not expecting that many.
Idiot! We want as many allies as possible.
Sabo-kun...
There are countless tales of heroism
involving Vice Admiral Garp,
Let's make a bet on
how many people will come!
It has been only a day...
I just found out that he was alive...
What is this all about?!
Orobi-dono.
Do you know how big the enemy's military force is?
but I didn't know
there was yet another great episode like that!
Kin'emon!
Ow, ow, ow...!
Tell me it's not true!
Something happened to everyone?!
You stole money from our store again!
According to what I heard,
KIN'EMON - TOWN THUG
Sabo!!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
He's really something!
Miss Tsuru!
We've known each other since childhood!
the Animal Kingdom Pirates have
about 20 thousand troops.
Dance! Dance!
It's the annual Fire Festival!
I'm like your big brother
and I need money!
The Shogun Orochi has
about 10 thousand companions.
Big Mom and Kaido?!
Why don't you let loose
and burn off some stress tonight?!
UNDERSEA PRISON IMPEL DOWN
That's because you gamble!
Do you know how much you owe me?!
Enough already...
I never get bored with this world!
That means there'll be 30 thousand enemies
at Onigashima on that day.
But he often refuses to talk about it.
It's getting interesting!
Luffy-dono, where are you?!
There are no commoners to get in the way,
so they have a geographical advantage.
The next time you put your hands on my money,
What? Why?
Hyogoro-dono, please respond!
Even with the blueprints of the mansion.
I'll sell your organs!
I'll fill you in
so you can learn some history...
And all we have is about four thousand.
Hey, guys!
If you cannot pay me back,
leave all your clothes!
Dogstorm Musketeers!
Let's set sail!
One of the reasons he doesn't share
was never reported in the papers.
Law-dono!
Jibuemon of Kibi!
It is not going to be an all-out war,
but we are hugely outnumbered.
Rather than just watch as the Navy takes it,
We are Kozuki Oden's retainers!
I'll take it for myself!
KIN
Damn Tsuru!
It was necessary to work alongside a pirate
to fight that battle.
Nevertheless,
we have no other option than the raid plan!
She really stripped me naked!
From 20 years ago...
A pirate?!
We must execute it!
But I got to hear a money-making idea.
The other reason is he happened to
save the Celestial Dragons.
Now, back to the current action...
We came from 20 years ago
to avenge our lord!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What?!
The Celestial Dragons were part of that story?!
We should have died at that time!
OUTSKIRTS OF EBISU TOWN
So we came to die for a cause!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Luffy...
Well, it's a Navy soldier's duty
to protect the Celestial Dragons.
Are you okay?!
Ring, ring, ring...
However,
What's wrong with that?!
KATSUZO
Grandpa Katsuzo!
it takes more than just our lives!
Clank.
Luffy! We must get going!
It's me, Koby.
Garp's moral compass tells him that it's not his duty.
The enemy has 30 thousand soldiers!
We need help!
A CREMATORY, FLOWER CAPITAL
Don't cry. I mean...
Sorry. Could you wait a little longer?
It's a funeral so you get to cry...
Can you master it in time?
Hold on a second.
I am begging you!
--I can't speak to you here.
--Okay.
One of the reasons that Garp refuses
to become the admiral is...
What's the matter?
Somebody, please help us!
Ryuo?
The cremation is finished,
so we were about to gather his bones.
Yeah, I'll master it in time at any cost!
Somebody, respond!
Please help!
...because admirals are
the Celestial Dragons' direct subordinates.
Oh, yeah! "Sea"!
Enough, Kin'emon!
Then, that man...!
"Fog"!
He openly shows disrespect for them, but he is spared
because of his achievements and popularity.
We found him cooking oden
with the flame that burned my father's body!
As always, you're conscientious...
Look at the sky and sea!
Well, it's a rule...
Now, the truth of the matter is...
We are already abandoned even by heaven!
Settle down!
...to protect the Celestial Dragons and their slaves
at God Valley,
Oh, yeah! Listen!
No one will help us!
There's something that I need to report...
Seems like Oden-sama is
not capable of sailing.
Something must have happened to everyone...
Garp and Roger who happened to be there
worked together and defeated the Rocks Pirates!
...to you, Captain!
X. DRAKE - CAPTAIN OF "SWORD"
NAVY HQ TOP SECRET SPECIAL FORCE
It was his 38th attempt
to leave the country illegally.
Momo, don't you have to train yourself?
It's known as the God Valley Incident!
How could he return alive?
Oh, yeah. Remember you once told me
the word "Sunacchi"?
I suspect you probably know,
but let me tell you briefly of his life.
RETIRED
Worked together with...
...the King of the Pirates...
...and fought?!
Yeah.
KOZUKI SUKIYAKI (ODEN'S FATHER)
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
When he was not even a year old yet,
The Celestial Dragons and Roger and Rocks?!
You said it's a good-luck word
to uplift your spirit.
he sent his nanny flying.
I can't believe they were all at the same place at the same time!
What was on that island?!
Right.
When he was two,
he caught two rabbits at once.
TWO DAYS AGO
Rewinding to two days before the Fire Festival...
But Okiku told me not to say it.
What?! Is that the situation out there?!
When he was four, he threw a boulder
and knocked out a bear!
AMIGASA VILLAGE
I just learned it from an old man in my village
a long time ago,
I've never heard of God Valley!
Yeah, it's too much to handle...
When he was six, he spent all his time
at the pleasure hall wasting the castle's money.
but I've never said it even once.
It's no wonder...
Mm-hm. Now we have 4,200 soldiers.
Even with all Navy soldiers in the world...
What?!
The name, God Valley...
When he was eight,
he went to a gambling parlor by himself,
I am glad... I am glad that they joined us...
Hey!
So just as we planned,
the Navy won't get involved with what's going on over there.
TWO DAYS UNTIL THE RAID
Master-sama!
...is nowhere to be found on any map now.
and started a brawl
with some hot-blooded gamblers.
Everyone...
Otama!
Thank you for your work!
They don't have enough soldiers...
I was worried about you!
When he was nine, he was blacklisted by yakuza
and repaid them...
I think that's fine.
The Land of Wano is not affiliated with the World Government.
In fact, it disappeared without a trace...
Use the remaining time for
travel and preparations.
Chopper! Luffy!
Nami!
Well then...
...by setting their gambling parlor on fire,
instigating a gang war.
Now, about Big Mom arriving at Onigashima...
See you at the rendezvous port!
Then, he got arrested for assault.
Yes.
The island that the World Government wanted to hide
disappeared...
Ring, ring, ring...
Kaido and Big Mom have had a vendetta
for so long...
That was at the age of 10.
Clank.
This is Kin'emon.
ITACHI PORT, KURI
While serving his time at quarries,
he showed his ability.
The Navy is expecting those two pirates
to ruin each other.
Do you still wanna know about the island?
What is the military potential in each region?!
How many allies did you recruit?
Finish fixing enough ships
to carry five thousand people!
Yeah, I guess.
Once, the ambitious Rocks tried to become
the king of the world,
As we expected,
Kaido and Big Mom were at each other's throats...
He even became a master stonemason!
The fire of rebellion is still burning.
Yes, sir!
Bring those ships to the port by the appointed time!
Can you do it?!
It must be in the Kozuki's blood!
but broke one too many taboos,
so information regarding him is no longer available...
I have a bunch of lively allies!
But they joined hands!
We are ready.
Then he came back on the street
as a better person!
Count on us, Big Bro Franosuke!
Kin'emon-dono.
All right!
W-W-W-W-What do you mean?!
He is only remembered by
some Navy soldiers of our generation.
When Oden-sama was 14 years old!
ITACHI PORT
AMIGASA VILLAGE
Then, we'll meet up with our friends
in Amigasa Village,
Kibi!
Hakumai!
The capital suffered a drought.
Ringo!
Udon!
and come by the Sunny on that day!
Wells dried up
and he could not stand watching people suffer.
We have 200 additional troops in total!
Even it was a long time ago,
As for Straw Hat Luffy,
there's been no word of a breakout.
I can't believe there was a man who led three pirates
So he changed the river's course
and made it flow to the capital.
We'll leave the rest to you!
Yeah! Thank you for helping us!
who'd later be called the Emperors of the Sea!
Really?!
The situation is at a standstill.
You guys are great shipwrights!
For Roger, maybe Rocks was
his first and strongest enemy...
And there's one more thing.
This is unpleasant,
But it caused a massive flood.
Thanks! Let's take those Animal Kingdom Pirates...
but I saw Cipher Pol Zero in the capital
the other day.
Yay!
And an arrest warrant was issued again.
Now we have 4,200 troops!
Strangely enough,
Roger and Rocks had something in common.
What?! Why are they in the Land of Wano?!
...and kick their asses, guys!
He tried to flee from the country
through the channel.
I have not heard from Law-dono yet...
I hope I'm wrong,
Rocks' full name is Rocks D. Xebec.
but that must mean the World Government is
doing business...
Who cares if he calls or not?
UDON
No matter how much timber we have,
it's never enough! Cut up everything!
...with this Land of Wano
which is reigned over by a pirate.
Well, he's pretty strong!
But he failed quite miserably!
Even though he has already died,
Ocho's group will bring
swords and the like from Ringo!
he was one of those pirates
who have the name "D."!
Then when he was 15, he strong-armed
a mountain temple master and stayed hidden there.
When I was made aware,
I became stunned...
Big Bro trained so hard
that he's not waking up.
So...
We'll craft armor from whatever we have!
...for a few minutes.
He brought back women from the capital every night
and formed a harem!
I don't know if they're usable,
but we have tons of weapons and those sorts of things
for export here!
Hey, officer!
Good!
There'll be a festival soon.
We wanna participate.
He must be some kind of monster...
If we go to the rendezvous point too early,
we will draw people's attention.
KIBI
RASETSU PRISON
No, you can't! Knock it off!
I should add that
all those women were always free to leave.
By the way, where are you now?
Damn! This will be our last chance!
Yes.
But...
...on the morning of that day, the Shogun's procession
will wind from the capital to the port.
HABU PORT            FLOWER CAPITAL
To capture Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock...
Everyone will fight to the death!
But some people became furious
and stood up.
Once they leave for Onigashima,
the Fire Festival will take place in the capital!
I know those who were caught in the capital
They were those women's boyfriends,
parents, and husbands!
Let me return to my story.
are frustrated,
but there is nothing we can do.
we're heading towards the Island of Women!
No one will pay us any mind!
A group of strong samurai backed them up!
Even their families who protested
got caught.
Oh, my...
"Two birds..."
We better get there before twilight...
UDON
Those ships coming towards us
crossing the Calm Belt are...
RETIRED
It's true that Kaido and Big Mom
were on board the same ship...
That is where our toughest samurai are...
Oden-sama welcomed their challenge
and fought back!
...a Naval fleet?!
But some officials will still be on the mainland!
ITACHI PORT
But we are running out of time.
Margaret!
But their capabilities are totally different
from 38 years ago.
KIBI
We cannot let them report to Onigashima,
so stay alert the whole way!
That is what is known as the Harem War!
What is going to happen?!
Everyone!
Even the Hyogoro Family who tried to stop them
got involved,
Thank you for your work!
Okay!
If they really team up,
we're about to see the world's worst pirate group.
That news that spread across the world...
Use the remaining time for
travel and preparations.
and a great scuffle took place!
They should've gotten rid of that damn thing
a long time ago!
Enough!
Are you allowing us to use these?!
Roger!
Brannew! How much are their bounties now?
See you at the rendezvous port!
It was a mistake to team up with pirates...
Wow! It's a samurai helmet!
I wanna show it to Usopp, too!
Oden-sama is now 18 years old.
Right, yeah, we have to decide new bounties for
They're evil!
We're warriors!
He has made trouble at a steady pace up to today.
That is all I have to report.
For those who think all pirates are bad...
those who were stripped of their title of Warlord, too.
I do not need your commentary,
just deliver this to Oden.
Let's go over all of their numbers.
Those Government dogs will finally go away!
NOTICE OF DISAVOWAL
Screw that Pirate Empress, Hawk-Eye,
and Clown!
Your enemy is that ill-famed Kaido.
I will break off my relationship with him!
Are you all prepared?!
They're nothing but looters!
Kaido?
That loser...
And for those who hate looters,
it's good news...
Momo-kun.
...is about to be sliced up!
Starting with Blackbeard who started to be
called an Emperor of the Sea about a year ago...
But I thought they did great
in the Paramount War!
Here, take this.
I don't think we'll lose!
A braided hat...
You braided it for me?
Bring it on!
The Reverie made the decision?!
He recruited some powerful subordinates
when he raided Impel Down two years ago,
Uh-huh!
I think the Navy will go into action
immediately...
Chobro and the others look good!
I made one for everyone.
ONE DAY UNTIL THE RAID
Is it gonna be okay?
Oh, how cute. Just like bugs.
and now has gained control over
the Pirate Island of Fullalead.
They were one of
the three great powers in the world!
Thank you.
Bugs?!
He's still extending his influence
taking Whitebeard's place!
For those who knew
how they did in the Paramount War,
C-Cute...?
Now, Luffy-dono.
Why don't you wear one, too?
We are leaving now.
We must get there before anyone.
and those who are concerned about
losing the balance of the three great powers,
No, it'll just slow me down.
The commodore of the Blackbeard Pirates, Marshall D. Teech!
Okay!
Wear it.
Our ship, the Sunny is docked here.
it's a truly alarming situation.
Since your bounty is so low!
2 billion 247 million 600 thousand berries!
Don't get caught!
One of the news stories
on the latest Reverie,
Enma!
What?!
Katsuzo.
We have never dropped our guard!
that stunned the people across
the world the most was...
Next up, he has only been called an Emperor of the Sea
for six years...
The next time we drink together,
it'll be in the afterlife.
...the abolition of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea system!
I am counting on you guys!
Do you wanna fight?! I'll kill you!
He's the youngest of the four
and deeply trusted by his subordinates...
Yeah, leave it to us!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
are officially recognized pirates.
Try it, you bastard!
See you at the port!
Take it easy.
Beckman.
Yeah!
While they're allowed to loot,
FLOWER
Roux.
What are you fools doing?!
Yasopp.
the Government uses them as deterrents
against other pirates.
His top officers gained notoriety individually,
Now, if you'd excuse me,
ladies and gentlemen of the bereaved family.
and his undefeatable group has a high average bounty
and the best balance of any groups...
Orochi said that it's winter
at the entrance to Onigashima.
The composition of the Seven Warlords
has changed repeatedly with the times.
What? Is it cold?
What do you mean by "entrance"?
The chief of the Red-Hair Pirates...
The mainland of the Land of Wano
has different seasons in different areas.
There are countless smokestacks
in this country,
Red-Hair Shanks!
4 billion 48 million 900 thousand berries!
Crocodile.
We're coated with fur,
so we're okay with cold weather.
He collided with the Straw Hats
over Alabasta Kingdom.
and even more unfortunate laborers.
DOGSTORM THREE MUSKETEERS
Yeah, for us, the weather is more crucial...
What was that? So cool...
CONCELOT     SHISHILIAN     GIOVANNI
Is that it?
...than the season!
He was trying to take over the kingdom,
Next is...
--Do you think it's true?
--What?
This must be the Oden
speech people talk about!
It's supposed to be a full moon that day,
but if it hides behind the clouds, it's useless.
She's a natural-born monster who allegedly
destroyed the village of Elbaph when she was little...
but he was defeated by Luffy
and expelled from the Seven Warlords.
Yasuie-sama...
...covered for the Akazaya samurai.
Did you hear that rumor?
You're right!
The man who replaced Crocodile
and joined the Seven Warlords...
If all Minks transform like Carrot,
that'll help us a lot!
--What?
--That flyer...
She only trusts her blood relatives
and along with her 85 children,
...wasn't Yasuie-sama's prank,
but it was actually a real signal for the raid, I heard.
...was Marshall D. Teech.
Now I am in luck.
This is like winning the lottery.
However, after achieving his aim,
he announced his resignation.
this autocratic queen built Totto Land,
the queendom made of candy!
Don't make us feel hopeful.
If I give this to the Kurokoma boss,
Garchu!
Remember what happened to the Kozuki Clan
20 years ago.
I will...
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
But the Sulong transformation
will depend on luck.
who was opposed to the Paramount War
and became antagonistic to the Navy.
The captain of the Big Mom Pirates!
Even if Kin'emon and the others are alive...
Come on! Give me all your clothes!
He, too, declared his resignation.
It's more important to have
Master Cat Viper and Guardians here...
Charlotte Linlin!
4 billion 388 million berries!
their spirits must have been broken.
Gecko Moria.
I won't let you get away today!
This man who once got in the Straw Hats' way
was also summoned for the Paramount War.
Whoa-whoa-whoa! Wait!
They'll never stand up again!
And in the old Rocks Pirates,
What's wrong, Luffy?
I'm about to get big money!
This country is so isolated.
Don't lie!
he was just an apprentice pirate...
It's true!
Let me go to the Kurokoma Family's mansion!
However...
Big Mom is here...
No one'll come to help!
after the war, he was attacked off guard
by an order from high up in the Government.
Besides, no one can stand up against Kaido!
But Jimbei isn't here yet!
But thereafter, he earned the respect of
vicious pirates by his strength alone,
Kin'emon?
and was expelled.
Oh, that kid who stole our money!
Thanks to him, we got away from Big Mom!
Heavenly Demon Don Quixote Doflamingo...
Now, silently setting out,
Catch him and flay him alive!
and ended up being called an Emperor of the Sea!
HYOGORO THE FLOWER
A YAKUZA OF THE CAPITAL
are seven Akazaya samurai, one ninja
and one important personage.
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
At the same time he governed
Dressrosa as its king,
But do not engage one-on-one.
The Supreme Commander of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
he was trafficking an artificial Devil Fruit, Smile,
as an influential underground broker.
He is stronger than you guys!
Thank you!
They step on the dried-up land
which crunches like frost in winter.
King of the Beasts Kaido!
Jimbei!
4 billion 611 million 100 thousand berries!
Don't die no matter what!
However...
I was entrusted with 60 Silver coins!
he lost the battle over the kingdom
against Luffy
If I just use it, it'll be gone!
The sun shines high up in the sky.
and the others and his
Warlord title was revoked.
I feel depressed...
There are some dark clouds,
Can I have the smaller pot?
By the decision at the Reverie,
He joined us after he settled things!
And Trafalgar Law.
but the shadows of the nine...
I'm running an errand for someone.
we can't deploy the Seven Warlords
to fight these Four Emperors anymore!
He allied with the Straw Hats to take down Doflamingo
and was stripped of his title.
...who are in fact not ghosts
Okay. It's 30 Silver coins!
and who intend to avenge their
lord after two decades...
--Here you go.
--Thanks!
Oh, I bought the wrong pot.
...are clearly seen on the ground.
The four pirates who reign supreme
as if they're emperors.
I needed the bigger one.
Whether removing that poison was correct or not...
Once we win the battle,
let's build nicer tombs.
We're happy to have him...
The bigger one is 60 Silver coins.
We've still got time... He'll come!
YASUIE
The Four Emperors.
60 SILVER COINS
It's up to how well SSG,
the Navy's Special Science Group, performs.
I've already paid you 30 Silver coins,
The Navy Headquarters
that is trying to contain them.
If he's alive.
NAVY
I'm sure he is!
so giving you this pot makes it 60.
PEDRO
And the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
For your reference,
Okay!
These three great powers
have kept the peace in the world.
He'll come!
Thank you!
here are the bounties of other legendary figures!
FOUR EMPERORS       NAVY
SEVEN WARLORDS OF THE SEA
That brat fooled that man
and saved 30 Silver coins!
EBISU TOWN, OUTSIDE OF THE FLOWER CAPITAL
Hey, guys! Come here! Ushimitsu Kozo came!
That Kitetsu looks different now.
However...
The captain of the Whitebeard Pirates!
there are two kings who took
enormous losses from the Warlords.
It seems like he met a good owner.
But there's no talk of a robbery in the capital!
Easy money!
DENJIRO - AN ORPHAN IN THE CAPITAL
Edward Newgate!
King Nefeltari Cobra of Alabasta Kingdom,
Hey, Denjiro.
He's the only person who would do this!
5 billion 46 million berries!
Oh, Kin-san!
Kitetsu III which you wield is my craft.
and Riku Doldo III of Dressrosa Kingdom.
We can't take part in the Fire Festival tomorrow,
but let's drink water with these!
Look at this!
I got a pretty valuable thing!
Is that so?!
They stood up for
the abolition of the Seven Warlord system.
Squirt.
The captain of the Roger Pirates!
Hiyori-sama gave you Enma,
We burned down the mountain bandit's mountain!
And after a heated debate at the Reverie,
You came to arrest me?
The King of the Pirates Gold Roger!
which I'm guessing fits oddly
comfortably in your hand, doesn't it?
But instead of seeking revenge,
a large majority supported the proposition
and it was passed.
Yes...
5 billion 564 million 800 thousand berries!
But it's not like I really wanna arrest you,
so you can bribe me...
It follows the same logic of cursed swords.
they keep stealing tons of food from our farm!
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI
The weak cannot handle them.
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea
naturally forfeit all of their rights,
But the biggest reason why it fits comfortably in your hand
is, in a twist of fate,
Do you guys have something to do with it?!
Now why isn't everyone avoiding me?
No pirates have ever surpassed these two...
and their connections with the World Government
are cut off.
...that Wado Ichimonji and Enma
were crafted by the same person!
W-We don't know anything!
Seems like all they care about is a fire.
I heard samurai are preparing to make a raid...
Is that why, maybe?!
That means...!
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
You don't know it, Kin-san?!
Buggy!
You're just another pirate!
You shouldn't bring that!
but once Kaido and Big Mom's alliance is formed,
The legendary swordsmith,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo.
If so, we can't let them know!
What? You mean this white boar?
the sum of their bounties will surely top those numbers!
More than half a century ago,
he illegally departed from this country.
That's not fair, you fools!
Kurokoma boss is trying to destroy the Hyogoro Family
by using it as a decoy!
What are you guys whispering about?!
A decision was made without telling us
and since we're no longer useful, you'll arrest us?!
I will guide you!
Hiyori-sama might have given you the
What do you mean?!
OTSURU - KIN'EMON'S WIFE
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
So do not hurt anyone!
I mean wherever that little boar is,
memento from her father
because she recognized that sword.
You being outwitted by Crocodile and Doflamingo
is none of my business!
O-Otsuru-san!
its parent boar will come
charging any minute!
Guide me?
But now in the Land of Wano
which isn't affiliated with the Government...
Enma has not been
forged into a Black Blade yet!
Don't take it out on me!
Do you know anything about this?
We've got the whole coast surrounded!
You will see once you get there.
It is a little far though...
Its rank can be raised depending on you.
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
What should we do?
Forget about the Land of Wano!
I'll do it!
My whole life plan has been screwed up!
We have no resources to put towards it, Sengoku-san!
All right!
You must need tons of food
because you are with so many allies!
Is all well in Udon?
Oh?
Yes, everything is fine.
The Navy's supposed to be on our side,
but we're surrounded!
Oh, so that was a false report!
Huh, Kin-san?
What should we do, Mommy?!
Yes, this is Udon. Nothing has changed here.
You are here in the Land of Wano, right?
Mommy!
Parent boar?
According to an ancient document,
it's a massive white boar like a mountain!
We'll keep watch on prisoners.
I was stunned when I saw Kikunojo...
RUINS OF MUGGY KINGDOM, GLOOM ISLAND
Surrender yourself now! "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk!
--Well then.
--Clank.
That's why they call it the mountain god!
Surrender yourself!
What an untrustworthy fool!
Of course, I wasn't intending to get involved...
Kin-san...
What?!
Kin-san, let me handle this!
I will draw their attention!
KUJA
One story tells that several centuries ago,
it destroyed the whole region in one night.
Snake Princess, we have a problem!
But as long as I have this information,
it's more than enough.
I was just conveying my knowledge as an old soldier
to young soldiers.
Your title as a Warlord of the Sea
has been stripped away!
I will not let them search for you all!
I thought it was just a myth,
"Changed from Habu Port to Tokage Port.
Granny Nyon!
Kin-san... Take back Kozuki's country!
but...
There are Navy ships off the coast!
Kozuki Hiyori is alive somewhere
in the north," huh!?
...since the white boar really exists...
Even pirates have relationships.
What?!
They've already gone into action?!
No, Otsuru-san!
You don't have to cover for us!
They have purposes for their actions.
The mountain god really exists!
Don't panic!
You can't see what'll come next
if you don't know history.
It's okay now!
We just wanted to eat as much as we wanted before we die!
It'll swallow us and kill us!
It's already right there! Run!
Snake Princess!
Oh, yeah... There was a pirate from the Land of Wano who
I think they're...
What?
So it's you guys who did it!
was favored by Whitebeard, Roger, and Red-Hair.
...forgetting something!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON, THE PRESENT
This is no good, Chairman Buggy!
Should we run?!
Oh, no! It's my fault that the capital is...!
You mean Kozuki Oden? The man who once served
as a commander on Whitebeard's ship...
Of course, we'll fight them in a flashy way!
Oden was later headhunted by Roger
and accompanied him on his last journey...
Show some guts!
You fools!
There is a small boat...
We can use it.
There's no way that Oden has something to do
with what's happening...
That's our Chairman Buggy!
What are you doing, Dogstorm?! Stop it!
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER, BUGGY'S DELIVERY CHAIRMAN
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Let's do this another day, Kin'emon!
That is not an option...
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
But why do those big-time pirates
who disturb the world...
It's so unforgivable...
...always get involved with the Land of Wano?
Weevil! I give you approval
to take them down!
Kin-sama!
Really?! Then...
Let go of me, Shinobu!
I think it's too much of a coincidence...
I'm gonna kill them!
Just you wait, Kaido!
Ko...
EDWARD WEEVIL, WHITEBEARD JR. (SELF-PROCRAIMED)
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Kin-sama, we can't do this tonight!
In the name of Whitebeard!
Sakazuki!
Ko...
We must do it tonight!
Gather 'round!
I feel a tremor of excitement...
You know that, Shinobu.
It's been a long time...
The sky is clear and cherry blossoms flutter
in the Flower Capital!
Kozuki Oden!
DRACULE MIHAWK, "HAWK-EYE"
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...since I was the one being chased.
That was an interesting conversation.
The day of the Fire
Festival has finally come!
Meanwhile, in the shadows, the battle
that might sway
What?
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
I don't know who you are...
It has got to be tonight!
the fate of the world is about to begin!
BOA HANCOCK, PIRATE EMPRESS
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...but give that white boar to me!
...because we were strong!
I'm counting on you, you guys!
An incident had already taken place
the night before.
LAND OF WANO ACT TWO - END
While you're doing that...
I'll get the hell out of here...
We have big news!
The One Piece manga that will be in
the January 4th edition of Weekly Shonen Jump
The daring Oden's unrivaled
strength impresses Kin'emon!
On the day of the annual Fire Festival,
Kaido and Big Mom!
The Sunny is blown up!
Not knowing of Luffy and the others' safety
Does that mean the vicious Rocks pirate
group which
at the rendezvous point, Luffy and his clan are nowhere to
Kin'emon pledges his loyalty to Oden
and they meet imperfect allies across the country!
Akazaya samurai move on with
their lord's words in their hearts!
once ruled the whole sea is back?!
be found and Kin'emon and the others stand helplessly by!
marks our one thousandth chapter!
CONGRATULATIONS!
1,000TH MANGA CHAPTER
The legend that Luffy's grandfather Garp
Thanks for everything
and please keep rooting for us!
Here comes a storm!
Will they give up on the raid plan?!
once allied with
the King of the Pirates is now revealed!
The hero of the age, Oden, went his own way.
Oden and Akazaya Nine later become legend
in the Land of Wano!
The balance of power is lost!
No one can resolve the confusion now!
Raging waves and sea wind
seem like they're trying to block their way to Onigashima!
Now, how he lived replays
like cherry blossoms taking flight!
Conspiracies boil!
The raging waves of time are drawing near!
This is how they began their
rollicking, vagrant journey!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Rendezvous Port! The Land of Wano Act Three Begins!"
"A Legendary Battle! Garp and Roger!"
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Number-One
Samurai in the Land of Wano! Here comes Kozuki Oden!"
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tearfully Swearing Allegiance! Oden and Kin'emon!"
"Big News! An Incident That Will Affect the Seven Warlords!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
THANK YOU!
WE'RE FRIENDS FOREVER!
[Events]