Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba"              "Nanohana"   "Katorea"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
As Luffy and company left
the green city of Erumalu
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
for the Yuba oasis,
where the rebel army is,
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
they met sand pirates, and set out
after attaining new friendship.
and a mighty swell.
The once-green city of
Erumalu now lies in ruins.
Meanwhile, to reach Yuba,
where the rebel army is,
To stop the fighting,
In the Alabasta port town of Nanohana,
Luffy and company travel
to the green city of Erumalu
Luffy's group set into the desert...
Luffy reunited with his
older brother, Ace.
"False Fortitude!
Camu, Rebel Soldier at Heart!"
and then head for the Yuba oasis,
where the rebel army is.
...where numerous, unimaginable
hardships fell upon them!
To stop the rebel army, Luffy and
company now head into the desert
Ace demonstrates the power
of the Flame-Flame Fruit.
for Yuba, the oasis town.
With Ace by their side,
"Rebel Warrior Koza!
The Dream Vowed to Vivi!"
the party follows the Sandora
River upstream toward Yuba.
"Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely"
Ahead is a village called Ido.
You should be able to get water there.
"Adventure in the Country of Sand! The
Monsters that Live in the Scorching Land"
Huh? You're not coming?
So hot... Water...
We sand pirates can't
go any further ahead.
"Erumalu, the City of Green,
and the Kung Fu Dugongs!"
This land belongs to the people
Thanks, Zoro. This heat
is too much for me...
who've lived and died here
for generations, you see.
Don't act polite. It's stifling.
Nami-san! How far did you go?!
Is that how it is?
Yeah. The desert is the land of the free.
That side of you is wonderful too!
Burning up...
Sweat won't even come out...
But not everyone can
survive in the harsh desert.
Huh?
--Halt!
--What business do you have here?!
What's the matter, Luffy?
Quit moaning so much, Luffy.
You'll only tire yourself out.
Please! Let us see the king!
The village ahead is a place
where such people eke out a living.
How long is this civil war
going to keep up?!
Guess he's not listening.
So, what're you gonna do?
With this civil war and drought,
we have nothing left to eat!
This is much easier
thanks to you, Lashes!
But will the others be all right?
Please help my child!
There's no milk left!
I can't go on...
I can't take hot weather...
Nothing much!
We've freely lived as we pleased
on this ocean of sand,
They'll just follow the footprints!
Stop! Quit pushing!
I'm fine in cold weather, though...
We can't let you through!
and that's what we'll keep on doing!
--Let us speak with the king!
--You want us to just die, then?!
It's 'cause of all that fur...
You should take off that animal suit...
That's just like us, then!
Hey, quit it!
Yeah? That's great!
Look at how much
you spilled! You big waster!
What was that, you jerk?!
Tsunami!
Don't make fun of reindeer!
What's the big deal?!
Ace brought a whole bunch with him!
--So long!
--Take care!
What now?
Monster!
--A tsunami's coming!
--What's going on, Luffy?!
See ya, old umbrella guy!
There's a limit to everything!
Chopper! Don't turn big!
Or else I won't pull ya!
Maybe it wasn't such
a good idea after all?
You've been guzzling away for a while now!
--They were great guys!
--Yeah!
Who're you calling a monster,
Humongo-Nose?!
What wasn't a good idea?
He's tryin' to drink, too.
D-Don't be stupid!
I-I'll have you know this nose--
I told him not to, but he said he
was so thirsty he couldn't stand it,
By the way, where'd your brother go?
This is so when Nami-san says,
"Oh, I'm so thirsty!"
--Hey! Say somethin', will ya?!
--Are you just gonna abandon us?!
Just turn back already!
Dunno. But he's Ace.
Nothing to worry about.
And you call yourself a king?!
I can take it right to her!
so he chomped down on some
cactus growing back there.
Why, you! Don't you dare
insult His Royal Highness!
He'll suddenly show up
again out of nowhere!
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
Would you like some water?!
Cactus?
Why do you keep making
such groundless claims?
Cease that at once, guards!
You don't seem to be having
a hard time, Vivi-chan.
Yeah. Over there.
Don't be dumb! I'll drink it!
Those round things.
Anyways, let's hurry to this Udo village!
I was born and raised here,
so it doesn't bother me much.
We're fine for now.
Eh?! Those are bad!
Gimme that!
--You mean Ido.
--Ido?
I'm sorry.
But what's with all these hills?
Those are mezcal cacti! They're
used to make hallucination drugs!
Yeah.
You're gonna spill it! Quit it!
My lack of strength has put you
through such unbearable suffering.
I figured a desert would be more flat.
You want some, too?
What?!
Thanks. But I'm fine.
Oh no!
Th-That's a desert pirate flag!
Those who wish to speak,
please come inside
We're gonna drown!
This is a very old desert,
Crap! I gotta tell Big Bro!
and tell me of your qualms.
Alright! Bring it on, if you dare!
so some sand dunes here
are over 300 meters high.
All I can do now is share your
suffering as if it were my own as well.
Say, Vivi. Could you tell
me about the rebel army?
I'll beat all of you up!
Th-Three hundred meters?
No wonder this is like
climbing mountains...
Yes, I probably should tell
you about it in advance.
Yes, you utterly are rebel army soldiers!
This is bad!
I ask that you endure a little more.
I will return calm to this kingdom.
Gum-Gum...
It's too much... It's so hot...
It was 11 years ago...
Ever since you and your
companions arrived, Camu-sama,
Just one drink, Luffy.
Just one mouthful.
Tranquilizer!
attacks on the village
have utterly stopped!
Even at the expense of my life!
Way to go, Chopper!
Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
Yup! You'd have to be
pretty crazy to take us on!
Don't drink so much!
Let me have some, too!
That was 13 mouthfuls just now!
Father! Someone set this up!
Well? Do you see Nami's group?
Hold on! You just had some! I'm next!
It's clear that someone is trying
to throw this kingdom into ruin!
Rest easy and leave it to us, Mayor!
L-Luffy?
Stop fighting!
You'll only waste strength!
What?!
Yes! You're utterly correct!
--But she started it!
--It's your fault!
Damn. We're completely
separated from them now.
But word is the rebel army and the
royal army will be clashing soon.
"Alabasta Kingdom, 11 Years Ago"
Yeah! This is because of you!
And their footprints are disappearing.
So hungry...
Won't staying in a place
like this interfere with that?
Come to think of it, I haven't
seen Ace for a while, either.
I hope you're all right...
Don't be so greedy!
It's still raw! Don't eat that!
When did he disappear?
Nami-san! Just a minute,
it'll be ready soon!
No, we can't just leave a
place that lets us eat all we--
Where are you now,
and what are you doing, Vivi?
I bet he got separated from us.
--Oh, looks pretty good!
--Get away, you!
Nah, this is this, that is that!
Oh, come on!
Cheapskate! Let us eat!
Sheesh! What a troublesome big brother!
Tea's ready. Come on up to the kitchen.
We may be rebels, but we haven't
completely given up on the king!
Get away!
We're the ones who got separated!
It was so hot during the day!
What's going on?!
Thank you, Sanji-san!
--All because of you!
--Quit acting so carefree!
Our village... Our village dried up!
Yes, we have utter faith
in the king as well,
With nothing to block
out the temperature,
Why didn't you help us?!
the desert scorches during the day
but falls below freezing at night.
Heya! I'm Captain Rice Ball Usopp!
What is it, Usopp?
so we were hoping things
could be handled carefully.
But the weather is the doing of the gods.
Do you hear something?
The desert is fraught
with unpredictable dangers.
Oh! And who are you?!
I may be king, but I cannot
control the forces of nature.
Say no more!
I'm a riceman!
After careful consideration, we've
decided to keep you guys safe, too!
Quit playing with our food!
But my dad said the king
could do anything!
Oh! Look at all those stars!
If you got free time,
go wash dishes or something!
All we ask for in return
is booze and food!
I can only do what can be done by man--
Geez! I need to finish our packed
meals before we cross the river!
Didn't you see stars
on your winter island?
Yes! Of course!
Winter island skies are always
covered with thick snow clouds,
Your Majesty! This boy's
father has come to the palace!
Need a hand?
Well, I must be going now...
No, no. You are a guest on board.
Just sit back and relax.
so I've never seen
so many stars before!
My deepest apologizes, Your Majesty!
I don't have the luxury of
looking at stars right now...
Big Bro Camu.
Forgive my spoiled son!
I take full responsibility!
Would giving up on the king
make us real rebel soldiers?
All right.
Cold weather doesn't bother me!
That's because you wear
such a warm suit!
I'll accept any punishment!
I will do better! Please, I beg of you!
Don't wash the dishes
in that mop bucket!
C'mon, get real.
Hey, you! Get away!
We can't leave this village until
we've sucked all of its sweet nectar!
I can't help that you're so fluffy...
I can't believe what a fool you are!
Quit making fun of reindeer!
What a nice breeze!
You fool! You fool! You fool!
Monster!
Chopper. Don't turn big.
We need your warmth.
A pirate ship?!
Big Bro! Terrible news, Big Bro!
Yahoo!
Toto, was it?
Aah! It's--!
So warm!
Come closer!
What do you want?!
Pipe down, I'm trying to eat!
Nami-san. I'd like to land
the ship here for a moment...
Nami and Vivi've been caught!
Oh, and the camel.
Yes, Sire!
See? Warm, isn't it?
The kingdom will temporarily
guarantee the livelihoods
Yeah!
Sand pirates!
Sand pirates are attacking!
What?!
Eh? What for?
It must be a real surprise for you.
of those villagers affected by the drought.
I have an important task for Karoo.
--Hey! Luffy!
--Don't be rash!
For real?! What do we do?!
I mean Luffy-san.
I was surprised too, at first.
You may live here, in Alubarna,
and make plans for your future!
Damn! Let's go, too!
Karoo?
What do you mean?!
There's nothing we can do against them!
Yeah!
Maybe it's that he isn't captain-like,
Oh, what thoughtfulness!
Thank you! Thank you!
Gum-Gum...
But we can't stick our tails
between our legs and run, either!
or that normal pirate captains are
respected by their crewmates...
Karoo. I want you to go to
Alubarna Palace on your own
Tell us, Big Bro! What should we do?
Whatever! As if you'd understand
the feelings of the villagers!
and deliver this letter to my father.
...Give-Me-Water!
But just this afternoon, a simple
drink of water caused that big fight.
Water?!
I've written down everything
Igaram and I learned
Alright! Let's stick our tails
between our legs and run!
Wait! Koza! Get back here!
I'm out of strength...
But...
We're running away?!
about Crocodile and
Baroque Works' schemes.
But, you know...
But what happens after we run away?
Toto.
The longer I've been with them,
the more I've come to understand.
Yes, Sire!
And that I've returned to Alabasta
alive with supportive friends.
Live on the edge of starvation again?
He's a good boy. He spoke
of the villagers' feelings.
You moron! Staying alive is all that matters!
That's how Luffy does things.
Did I just hear something?
Eh?
There are plenty of other villages like this!
He stormed in here for
the sake of the villagers.
He hasn't changed a bit
since he was a kid.
Now let's scram!
Despite how he seems,
people always gather around him.
Can you do it? You'll have to
cross the desert on your own.
That's for sure...
Even though he's my little brother,
he has a mysterious charm to him.
What're you?
Oh. You already knew.
Listen. You have to drink your
water with care in the desert.
You cowards got real guts to
call yourselves rebel soldiers.
Hmph. Crybaby.
He and I do go way back.
Karoo! Good luck!
I wouldn't if I were you.
If you ask me, it's a pretty despicable
thing for four grown men to do.
Now let my father know
this kingdom can be saved!
But thanks.
What did you say, runt?!
Oh, my bad!
Eh?
Runt?
You were worried that
I was concerned, right?
I'm so thirsty I misjudged...
Who the hell're you?!
Mind your own business!
By the way, do you have any water?
Yes. But it looks like I didn't
need to worry after all.
When did you get in here, anyway?!
Cobra-sama.
You mean you didn't come to save us?!
Food thief!
What is it, Igaram?
Drink your water with care!
With all due respect,
I only came to get water.
the kingdom doesn't have enough
money to support all of them.
Help, Luffy-san!
Lashes is about to be eaten!
Karoo... Thank you...
More.
You fool!
That thing's edible?
Yes, yes, yes! I'm sorry, sir!
We can just trim down our own
living expenses or whatever need be!
I knew Crocodile, one of the Seven
Warlords, was in this country...
This place has good food.
Understood. As you wish.
Yes, thank you!
Whoa! I found a shrimp!
But a pirate trying to steal a kingdom?
That sounds like a bad joke.
It's terrible, Your Majesty! It's Vivi-sama!
So this is a shrimp?! Wow!
A pirate dropping anchor in
one spot and settling down?
--Shrimp don't live in the desert!
--See?!
Oh, you're right!
Is it a "desert shrimp"?
Don't tell me he's trying
to usurp the throne.
I'm sorry! I now realize
you're no ordinary person!
--It looks yummy!
--Hey, now! Are they edible?!
I had a fight. I lost.
We, the Barbar Sand Pirates, have a saying.
Alright! Let's set sail!
As you can see, we stand no
chance at all against sand pirates!
Probably! Crawfish are edible, after all!
--Vivi!
--Vivi-sama!
Hold on! I'm not on board yet!
Saying?
I've never seen a real shrimp before!
That little punk!
How dare he harm a princess!
Aside from friends, nothing alive
in the desert can't be eaten!
There could be another side
to this takeover thing.
Please lend us your help!
--I'll pulverize him!
--Wait! Wait! Igaram!
Hmm. I'm not against the idea...
Another side?
I'll even eat stuff off the ground!
Stop, Luffy-san! Throw that away!
Some sort of deeper goal...
My deepest apologies!
No! That'd be a waste!
...but on one condition.
That'll make you sick.
That's a scorpion! It's small
but it's very poisonous!
Then I'll be careful!
I'll die to make amends!
Yes! Anything you want!
Enough, both of you!
You'll die if it stings you!
What a funny pipsqueak!
Hey!
Alabasta, the kingdom of sand...
Oh. It's not edible? How boring.
You're funny too! Well, let's eat!
--Hey!
--Ace!
--You can have it.
--Don't give it to me!
Even if you build cities
atop the sandy earth
Fools! It was a children's quarrel!
Then I'll throw it away.
and exist there for
thousands of years,
That's where he was?
I'm sorry.
I should've mentioned it earlier.
Why?!
the desert will always be
filled with the stench of death.
What is this thing?
That's for sure!
Oh! So you're the sand pirates?
I'm Barbarossa, captain of
the Barbar Sand Pirates!
From its very inception, this land
has embraced the shadow of death.
Huh? What do you mean?
We just left the sand pirates.
Luffy, was it? I'm sorry for our
rough treatment of your friends.
What is it, Chopper?
Oh? Really? Well, whatever.
Welcome! Come on over!
I've just received word that the
Billions' ships stationed in Nanohana
It's just that we're all so hungry...
Come on over! Low prices!
Anyways, great news, Luffy!
I brought plenty of food and water!
Something's... coming.
It's yummy! Here you go!
No, I don't mind!
have all been wiped out by someone...
Something? What?
That's not for you to say!
Oh! Much appreciated!
It's a showdown!
I'm having this verified as we speak.
But, Captain! We don't have any
wood at all to repair our main mast!
--Come on over!
--Fight! Fight!
This should be more than
enough for a good while!
Ace is incredible...
Don't go easy on her
'cause she's a princess!
Teach that sassy princess a lesson!
That's for sure! He's nothing like
a certain little brother we know!
There are more replacements for
the Billions than we even need.
Without a main mast,
we won't have enough thrust!
Oh? Is the wind picking up?
You can do it, Vivi-chan!
You can say that again.
Yeah! Yeah! What're we gonna do?!
--I was so thirsty...
--Oh! Drink up, drink up!
Hey, you! Koza's our leader, you know!
A single drop of water spilled in the
desert is no obstacle for my plan.
If we don't do something,
Me too!
we're going to die like dogs
in the middle of this desert!
Umm, Ace-san?
But, if anyone who would
dare defy me has appeared...
If I win, I get to be your leader!
I assume you don't have
the money for that.
--We're gonna die like dogs!
--Huh?! What?!
Don't tell me you stole
it from that village...
Everyone!
--The Barbar Sand Pirates are gonna die!
--Huh?
Hide behind the rocks!
crush them.
Like I'd ever lose to you, pipsqueak!
Nothing of the sort!
The rebel army gave it to me!
We sand pirates are born
in sand pirate ships,
What?
Understood.
A storm! A sandstorm is coming!
I've always been our leader in the village!
and we'll die in sand pirate ships!
I've already sent the Lizard
Runners to contact the others.
The rebel army?!
Oh?
Well, I should say "clearly fake
rebel soldiers" to be more precise.
Here goes!
Abandoning our ship is unthinkable!
Whoa! Cool!
Yeah! That's right! We'll die in our ship!
--Eh?
--Fake? What do you mean?
Excellent.
Again?! Deserts are nothing but storms!
Basically, they call
themselves rebel soldiers
We'll die like dogs in our ship!
and were hired to protect the village.
What is this?
We're finally here!
I forgot to mention it, but sandstorms
are one of the desert's dangers!
The villagers are so grateful that
they've been completely fooled.
That was fate, this was fate!
We're finally going into the desert!
I bet it'll be hot...
They're really just some hoodlums.
We sand pirates will never do
anything to defy the flow of sand!
Mention these things sooner!
--It gets over 50 C in the daytime!
--Eh?! It does?!
Listen, guys!
And they're bodyguards?
Wouldn't they get found out right away?
As of today, Vivi is the
vice-leader of our Sand-Sand Clan!
What happened, Nami-san?!
Where did your dancer outfit go?!
Apparently, the mere
mention of the rebel army
Anyone got a problem with that?!
Aah! Not you too, Vivi-chan!
Why are you dressed like that?!
No!
will send most bandits running.
It's real convenient.
In the desert, any exposed skin
will wind up terribly sunburned!
Look, Igaram.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
Makes money and prestige come
rolling your way on its own.
Vivi has made friends.
Yes.
This is terrible... My dancer girls...
That is the most important thing to have
Rebel soldiers aren't hoodlums,
nor does the title serve as decoration.
Put this on, Luffy-san.
if she's to carry Alabasta
on her shoulders someday.
Okay! Thank you!
--Let's get ready to disembark.
--Yeah.
What the hell was that?!
Can't people get some rest?!
But there is timber at the Meriyasu Oasis.
Vivi-chan. Should we teach 'em a lesson?
I dunno. Duping the villagers isn't
so different from what bandits do.
Where is it?! I'll rush there real quick!
Hey! Sanji! Let's have a lunch!
A Pirate Boxed Lunch!
Toto-ojisan! Ma'am! Good morning!
Okay! Let's land!
But the sands've changed lately.
It's dangerous for outsiders.
Not yet. Not until Vivi-chan says so.
Where's Leader?
At the very least, the villagers
live in peace with them around.
Oh, good morning! If you're
looking for Koza, he already left!
Come on, Vivi! Let's eat!
I'm out of strength!
What's that?
I'm responsible for it! I'll do it!
Should we get 'em just the same?
I assume he's at the usual spot.
But we're only one-tenth of
the way to Yuba, Luffy-san.
But, big brother. Consider it
from Vivi-chan's perspective.
See you later!
Oh, Vivi-chan!
What will you do about lunch?
Yeah?! You will?!
--Turtles?
--Aren't those seals?
Surely you'd want to
pulverize people like them.
Bring back wood with this sand-sled.
You're so dumb! Haven't
you heard of this proverb?
I'll eat with you! Thanks!
Kung Fu Dugongs!
Yeah, she should do what she wants.
I only gave my own thoughts.
I'd say this is more of
a canoe than a sled...
"If you're hungry, eat!"
What a strange country this is!
"If you wanna come on shore,
you'll have to beat me first!"
You liar! Quit making stuff up!
The princess of a kingdom,
mingling with commoners like us!
Zaba and Rasa will show you
to the Meriyasu Oasis.
"Or else go back to
the other shore, cowards!"
All right.
I don't want to hear your excuses!
Then what do you say we take a
break at the next rocks we find?
Is what he says.
--Rasa?
--Yes.
It's proof of peace!
Rasa is our ship's finest sand-sledder.
I waited all alone in the
middle of this vast desert!
Alright! Rocks!
I can't sit quietly by when
someone calls me a coward!
Igaram-san. Will you join us for lunch?
Guys! Let's hurry to the next rocks!
A sand-sled can carry two people.
What'll you do?
No, no, that's quite all right!
I brought rice balls!
--Let's do it!
--Wait! Usopp-san!
Whoever wins rock-paper-scissors
has to carry everyone's stuff!
I'll be fine on my own!
There's no reason to
cover for these bastards.
Well, I must be going!
Come on, now! Quit saying
baseless things like that!
Kung Fu Dugongs are strong!
Quit deciding things!
I'm not. I just know you
guys are in a hurry here...
Shouldn't the loser carry the stuff?
It'll probably be demanding work.
Want me to go with you?
Alright, here goes!
--One is winning over there!
--Winning is bad, too!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Now that the kingdom can't keep
watch over every little place,
Hold on, now!
Your Majesty! What are you doing here?!
--Hey! You went after!
--Woohoo! I win!
there's nothing wrong with
villages upholding public safety
Urgh! Sire!
Huh?
Idiot.
on their own whenever possible.
It's a Kung Fu Dugong rule
You're following me again?!
Then...
that if someone loses,
they become the winner's pupil!
H-Heavy... So heavy... And hot...
No. I want to test them first.
B-But I'm worried about Vivi-chan...
That's very martial arts-ish.
I won rock-paper-scissors,
so why me?
--Test?
--Yes.
Oh! That was cool, Rasa!
It's because you won.
Now shut up and haul.
The number of pupils just went up!
If these impostor rebel soldiers
truly wish to protect the villagers,
Go home! You'll only cause me more work!
Alright, everyone! After me!
Don't drop it, now!
The others seem to be outsiders...
but you're from here.
Stance!
What?!
No! Like this!
I don't think it matters
what they call themselves.
Don't give me, "What?!"
Wow! How could she tell?
Yeah! Now go like this!
So you want to test what's
in their hearts, huh?
You must have some
experience with a sand-sled.
That's it! Like this!
Yes. So, I hate to ask, but there's
something I'd like you all to do.
Like this! Like this!
Rocks spotted a small ways ahead!
You'll come along.
Like this!
Vivi-chan can't do
anything that dangerous!
For reals?!
Break time! Food!
Yeah! That's crazy!
--Sounds like it was a nice country.
--Yes.
No sweat, Vivi-chan!
All right. I'll come with you.
--Gimme that water!
--You wish!
Whoa! He's fast!
Alright! Things are
getting interesting now!
Oh? So these go on top of
the sand? How does it work?
But a lot happened...
Eh? It's going to be interesting?!
Hold on, Luffy! This isn't
going to be a game! Understand?!
I'll pilot the sled.
I did this once long ago.
Shade! Feels so good!
Yeah, I get it!
Alright! Let's set out for Yuba!
It's not too different from a ship.
This goes like this, right?
We're basically gonna beat these
fake rebel guys up, right?!
Hold on, now!
He doesn't understand a thing!
Someone do something about him!
Are you bringing them with us?!
Heya, girly!
You can't, Luffy!
He's been gone a long time.
Headed out? Want us to come with ya?
The Dugongs can't cross the desert...
It's been almost an hour since he said,
"Leave it to me!" and left...
You saw his strength!
Attack, Sand-Sand Clan!
I bet he's beating the
sand pirates up as we speak!
So cute...
I-I'm back!
No, think about who he's fighting!
I don't know why, but I feel like
we're doing something very sad...
What's with these guys?!
They still haven't kicked the bucket?!
They might've beaten him
before he even got a chance!
Don't waste your strength
doing stupid things!
In which case, we're next, huh?
Me, too. What should we do?
Hey! Say something!
Leader! Everyone!
You can rest there, Luffy-san.
I know!
Run, Vivi! These guys are out to get you!
Let's see here...
No, I can't do this!
I'll go get you a doctor!
Now, let's see. I believe
this goes like this and...
I hate to lose such good room and board...
What're you doing?
--Get going, Vivi!
--They're gonna kill you!
Here!
Bad news!
...but staying alive is all that matters!
You can have this! So stay here, okay?
Ugh. Let's go, Zaba!
But... Leader!
Huh? He's coming back!
That's for sure.
Yeah, Rasa!
There's lots of hurt birds
that can't move! Chopper!
--Help!
--Chopper!
We ain't gonna kill ya!
Yahoo!
We want ransom money,
so we're just gonna kidnap ya!
Right!
This feels great!
--Alright! Let's go, Chopper!
--Yeah!
If we borrow this,
can't we reach Yuba right away?
Damn you!
See ya!
It's hard to control sand-sleds.
It's not something easily mastered.
We gotta help the birds!
Now come here, Princess Vivi!
Birds?!
Wait, Luffy-san! Don't tell
me these birds are--!
Hey now, Luffy! Do you understand
the current situation?!
--Good luck!
--We're counting on you!
Then how come you can control it?
They said they were coming with me,
so why couldn't we let them?
Eh?
I used to practice with a sand-sled
I received when I was little.
I won't let you have her!
We couldn't go to any city with
that big of a group! You're so dumb!
--You can do it!
--Camu-sama!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Camu-sama! We're relying on you!
Honestly!
We would've been in big trouble
had Chopper not persuaded them!
But what should we do while we wait?
I was utterly about
to come calling for you,
Yeah! They kept saying,
"We'll accompany you!"
Want to eat the camel?!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
but I should've known you already
knew the sea pirates were here!
They really would've come if
we hadn't given them food!
All for it!
Sheesh! Thanks to you, our food
supply's gotten a lot smaller!
Eh?! Sea pirates?!
Just joking!
Not sand pirates?!
All our stuff is gone!
Doesn't sound like a joke to me...
We've been had...
That's correct. Sea pirates.
--He knows how to cause trouble.
--That's for sure!
They're far more
ferocious than sand pirates.
It's the truth! There really
were dying birds here!
Plus one is a special-edition pirate
with a 30 million-Berry bounty!
What is that?!
I'm sorry. I should've
mentioned it earlier.
What is this thing?!
Hey, you! What's the big idea?!
Huh? What is this?
Once we heard you were going to go,
"Hiyaaah!" and get rid of them,
Warusagi birds are
"desert bandits" that trick travelers
Poke, poke, pokey, poke.
and steal their belongings.
--What's this?
--Is this the town of Yuba?
Hey, Rasa! That's--!
we were so utterly moved and grateful!
What?!
We know you can do it!
No...
Birds playing dead?!
That's dishonest!
Good luck, mister!
This is Erumalu. It used to be
known as the City of Green...
Hey, Vivi! We're getting
pulled in more and more!
It's quicksand! If we get
swallowed into the sand,
Don't lose to some stupid sea pirates!
Yes, that's how they are.
It's huge!
City of Green?
we'll never come back out!
I'm gonna get strong just like you!
They tricked me?!
Wow!
The sight of this town
explains everything.
Luffy! Is that all you can
say for yourself?!
What the Baroque Works organization
has done to this country...
Rasa. Wasn't that going too far?
There were three days
of provisions in there!
Let's go!
If luck's on her side,
she'll make it through alive.
And you just had to let some
damn birds steal everyone's stuff
What the people of Alabasta
are going through...
Huh? You know that girl?
H-Hey, Big Bro. Are you serious about this?
smack in the middle of this desert?!
Yeah. As if I'd ever forget!
Don't be stupid. Of course he isn't serious.
How're we supposed to cross the
desert without food or water now?!
Say. Tell me more about what happened!
Shut up, you guys!
It's not my fault. They tricked me.
Wow! There's nothing here at all!
Yes. Our leader, Koza,
was a very strong-hearted boy...
Once we've left town, we run in
the opposite direction of the pirates!
Is your brain less than a bird's?!
Yes. It's a ghost town now,
We run to our last gasp!
What other way is there?!
Say what?!
But I was worried for that heart once...
Stop it, you two!
but up until just recently, it was
a thriving city full of greenery!
There's no use.
That's for sure.
I won't let you have her!
At times like this,
it's best to let them have it out.
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
This place was?
Rain was always scarce, but even so,
the city was able to manage
Yeah, huh?
Let's take a short break.
This heat is what has them fuming.
You alright, Vivi?!
by saving every last drop
of rainwater it could.
Dammit.
I'm sure we'll manage food-wise.
We're in trouble if we don't do something!
But, for three years now,
They're following us...
It's nothing that'll kill us.
Let's just put it out of our minds.
not a single drop of rain has
fallen in any part of this country.
We're done for!
What pathetic excuses for bodyguards!
What a bunch of jerks...
Yeah. Just thinking makes me thirstier.
Vivi! Duck!
There are more of 'em?!
Gum-Gum...
--For three years?!
--That long?!
Oww! Oww!
But even without rain, what
about the river we just crossed?
Damn! She got away!
Yeah! Couldn't they just pipe
water in from that big river?
The ruins are that way! Catch her!
Despite how he seems, you can
always count on Luffy in a pinch!
Alright. We got one shot at this.
The answer to that is up ahead.
Once we're out, immediately figure
out which direction is pirate-free
Yeah. But what concerns me
more is the desert's fickleness.
Don't let 'em go!
and then run for your lives! Got it?!
Give us our stuff back!
Move!
Gotcha, loud and clear!
The desert's fickleness?
Never in the thousands of
years of Alabasta's history
Here goes! One! Two! Three!
Yeah. The desert is honest.
Luffy-san! Don't chase them!
What on earth?!
has the rain stopped completely.
That idiot.
A slight change in weather or
people's hearts will change it greatly.
Hey, you! Will you be
able to come back?!
But, there was one place where
the rain fell more than usual...
Come back, Luffy!
A change in people's hearts?
Hey! What happened to you?!
What happened here?!
Alubarna, the capital.
The city with the king's palace...
Stop! You can't get away from me!
What's that?
Some bad guys came to get Vivi...
O-Oh, crap...
Get 'em, get 'em, rebel army!
What?!
Give that a rest, will ya?!
Grownups, with blades...
Get back here!
They just went into the ruins!
Koza went after them, too!
What?!
Oh, Princess! Where are you, Princess?
Get back here!
The people called it
the King's Miracle.
Until what happened
that day, at least...
Where the hell are you hiding?
What's that?! You're a rebel soldier?!
Find her! Find her!
Don't let her get away!
Lower the cargo!
What are these?!
Princess Vivi! Come on out!
N-No, nothing of the sort!
We're just travelers passing through!
Boss! It's them!
Say your prayers, sea pirates!
They're coming!
These rebel soldiers are gonna
make mincemeat out of you!
--Turn to starboard! Hurry!
--Battle stations!
It's falling over!
Look out!
Oh, there ya are!
Be quiet, you!
Hey! Are you alright?!
Right! How utterly rude of me!
Good luck, Camu-sama!
Please, just let us catch
you like a good little girl!
Oh, no! This is bad!
You wanna get in my way, too?
We were supposed to deliver
this to King Cobra in Alubarna!
He seems especially spineless to me.
Not so fast!
What is this green powder?
What is this thing?
Leader!
A mystery desert plant?
Doesn't seem reliable at all.
What is it?
Yes...
H-How should we know?!
We're only following your king's orders!
Neat!
You alright, Vivi?!
Are you sure about this?
It might be best for the village
if we take care of them now.
Oww...
--Right?
--We're just couriers!
Don't underestimate the
Sand-Sand Clan, villain!
Run!
A little more. Let's watch
things just a little more...
--There are so many of them!
--Who are they?
Leave this city at once!
Desert bandits! Pests who're
always desperately fighting us!
--Get 'em, rebel soldiers!
--You can do it!
Wait... Could this be?!
What are you doing?
Listen, boy. Shut up and
give the princess here.
Dance Powder?!
Hey!
That's funny!
Conflict seems imminent these days!
That has them on edge, too!
You've heard of it?
You really are rebel soldiers after all!
Huh? You want me to help you?
It's not smart to make grownups mad.
Yes. It's also known as
"Rain-Summoning Powder."
N-No, it isn't, uhh...
Gum-Gum...
A blade! Let's run away, Leader!
Wh-What now, Big Bro?
...Pistol!
Rain-summoning?
Looks like you can't move!
You're finally ours today!
We lost our chance to escape...
I'd only heard stories about it,
--That doesn't scare me!
--Huh?!
but a researcher in a country
where it doesn't rain created it.
Hey, you guys!
Men! Don't let a single
one of them leave alive!
--Ace-sama?
--Please help...
By creating a misty smoke from it
and letting it rise into the sky,
Good thing you didn't get eaten!
This is your fight.
Our pleasure! Our pleasure!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
The birds got away while
I was beating these guys up!
Try to get through it on your own.
you can artificially cause it to rain.
Leader! Don't do this!
What is this, a pub?
We can't do that! We're fakes!
You wanna fight, huh?
That's what Dance Powder is.
The desert sure is full
of strange creatures!
The desert has pit us together!
Oh! I get it!
Will the desert choose us,
the Barbar Pirates, or you?!
If you're men, act like it!
You mean that mystery powder!
How long are you gonna keep
up this petty crap of yours?
Hey, camel. What're you doing
out here all by yourself?
I ate some a while back!
It tastes really bad!
Let's let the desert
decide our fate in battle!
What is it?
It isn't food.
Fool! Fool! The desert'd never choose you!
It's for making rain.
What do we do, Big Bro?
What?! You think I'm lying,
don't you?! Hey, you!
Wh-What do you mean, what do we do?
Did you find something?
Hold on! Wouldn't something like
that be perfect for this country?
We have no choice now but to lie
our way out of this, impostor-style!
What's that?
--Grand Dung Beetle!
--There's a Grand Dung Beetle!
As the name suggests, the country
that developed Dance Powder
Impostor-style?
--Grand Dung Beetle?
--Say what now?!
was almost happy enough
to dance at first.
Listen, you! Don't be shocked
by what I have to say!
Desert bugs that haul giant balls of dung!
But there was a big catch:
We're not the only rebel soldiers here!
No less than 100 people a year
are squished by their rolling dung!
In the village there are...
the neighboring country had a drought.
What the--?!
...100 million more soldiers like us!
Eh?!
Understand?
Dance Powder quickly and
artificially matures clouds
Oh, geez. That's worse than a kid's lie.
You're no one to talk.
Leader!
that would normally grow into
rain clouds further downwind
Bastard knocked our boss out!
What?! 100 million?!
What's taking Luffy so long?!
and causes them to rain.
Boss! It's headed right for our ship!
Hold on, you!
That's not even believable!
Yeah. Do you think he got lost?
What the hell?! Let's give him a thrashing!
So...
Oh, I get it!
He's obviously bluffing!
It steals rain that would've normally
gone to a neighboring country!
What?! It's a lie?!
Obviously!
Alright! Come here!
--Oh, it was a lie?
--Oh, geez!
Eventually, war broke out
between the two countries
Leave it to me!
He has a horrible sense of
direction but always has to run off!
Hey, you!
You! How dare you trick me?!
and many lives were lost as a result.
And there are so many desert
dangers he doesn't know about...
You dimwits!
Damn! They realized I was lying!
Ever since, the World Government
has put a worldwide ban
Daddy! Igaram!
Did you really think
that would fool them?!
Y'know, isn't he hungry
from not eating anything?
on the production and
possession of Dance Powder.
Vivi-sama! Are you all right?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Curse you! Thought you could
kidnap my daughter, did you?!
Powder that can bring both
happiness and dread when used...
You lousy vagabonds!
Take this! And this! And this!
When all that Dance Powder was
brought into the port town,
He's such a lost cause.
You can say that again.
Alabasta was in the middle of
a strange weather phenomenon
These appear to be their friends.
Sorry.
where rain fell nowhere but in
the town where the king lived.
Chaka! Pell! What are you doing here?
For my little brother's ineptness.
I apologize for the trouble.
What was that?!
We haven't had a single drop of rain
He has Devil Fruit powers!
Why? That's what we'd like to ask you.
One hit knocked him out!
because the king's been
using Dance Powder!
Good luck finding him!
Not even rebel soldiers stand a
chance against something like that!
What is the king doing in a place
like this, away from the palace?
Yeah.
Alubarna's rain wasn't a miracle at all!
Thanks, guests...
Luffy, you idiot! It's all
over if you knock him out!
You should refrain from
acting so recklessly.
What's that?!
It's all because of the king
that we're parched and starving!
Then what would we do?!
We'll let you off easy this time!
Your lives are spared for now!
Igaram! Koza's been hurt!
Hold on, Vivi! That means
your dad is the bad guy here!
Yes! Let's get him to a doctor immediately!
What's this rumbling?!
You idiot! He was framed!
The Sand-Sand Clan members
atop the hill, as well!
That deserves a
warm shower of applause.
Vivi-chan's father would
never do any such thing!
Chaka! Pell! Make arrangements at once!
Yes, sir!
Never... Never...
Rasa! Don't you think
you went a little too far?!
What brave children!
--They're not following!
--That's fine!
Another sandstorm?!
Big Brother Camu!
You can do it!
Of course, my father had
nothing to do with it,
No, wait! That's--!
If she won't come
however much we wait,
The sea pirate is coming!
--You can do it!
--Big Brother!
that's just the level of a person she is!
What's wrong, Vivi? Why so glum?
but at around the same time,
Luffy?!
Stand up!
a massive amount of Dance Powder
was found inside the palace...
No... it couldn't be!
I was so scared...
They even had people
working inside the palace?
Why is he on a camel?!
Yeah, I was scared too.
They had blades with them and all...
What's this road, Vivi-chan?
So?! What's that chasing him?!
That's right...
No!
When I was a kid, I looked up
to the warriors of Alabasta
This was a canal that used to bring
water in from the Sandora River.
I can't really see!
But it seems more like
something's in the sand!
You told them to protect
me to the death, Leader...
and wanted to be as strong
as them someday...
Someone destroyed this canal, too...
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
No, even now I do...
We caught up!
With its canal gone, the City of Green
could no longer secure water.
Someday, I want to be as strong
as the warriors I saw as a child...
Yay!
Don't talk about dying, Leader...
As if praying, the people continued
to wait, but rain never came.
It's huge!
Someday...
How long are you gonna keep up
this petty crap of yours?
What is that?!
Oh, more than anything,
she was afraid of losing her friends...
A Sandora Dragon!
This oasis is completely buried in sand.
A what now?!
Ever since the Dance Powder incident,
distrust in the king grows daily.
They're the largest of the
reptiles living in the desert
It was once a flourishing city, but...
and they wait under the
sand for their prey!
You've been here before?
And it's all how Crocodile planned, huh?
They have sharp claws and fangs,
but they hardly ever use them!
The people of this city gave me
a small sand-sled as a memento.
And then the fighting finally began.
The reason being that they tend
to swallow their prey whole
To escape the fighting, the
exhausted people abandoned the city
Vivi is still little, but a princess, Koza.
because they're so large!
Big Bro!
That was a very long time ago, though.
He really does have a gift
for attracting trouble.
Your deed today was an immense one.
and left for other oases
in search of water.
I stopped by here once with my father
Setting aside the camel for the moment...
You have my gratitude. Thank you.
Yes, we're fake rebel soldiers.
...what star was he born under to be
able to attract trouble like this?!
when he was traveling around the country.
And then...
Even if all we want is to be as
strong as the heroes we saw as kids,
Vivi's a friend. It was only natural.
the City of Green withered away.
I've been waiting all this time.
Hey! Camel! Stop!
we're just a bunch of scoundrels now.
I see.
I can tell the next generation of
Alabasta will be in good hands.
But, even if my dream never comes true,
--Luffy! Is it too much for you?!
--We'll lend a hand!
Back then, the king told us,
I can't take those kids' dreams away!
Do you like this country?
Yeah! I brought some meat!
Yeah! I was born here!
Here goes, lizard!
"If anything happens to this oasis,
I will come rushing to help.
Even if I'm no match for you,
Gum-Gum...
--Tatsu...
--paule...
I'm the same way!
I'm going to fight so that someday
those kids can beat you all!
...Whip!
--...Maki!
--...Shoot!
The kingdom won't ignore any voice,
no matter how small."
I'm...
--Huh? Is that someone's voice?!
--Is it the rebel army?!
If my only other choice is to remain
a punk in those kids' memories,
Don't tell me Baroque Works
has been following us!
So you were that girl!
I'm also a bit concerned.
How so?
Eventually, this oasis was
buried in sand and abandoned.
Y-You didn't have to go that far...
then I'd rather die as a hero right here!
Standing above others requires
difficult decisions in no small measure.
When they're fighting,
you almost pity the monsters...
Every last person in town left.
Vivi-sama is too kindhearted for that.
--No. It's just wind.
--It has to be someone's voice!
Even so, I stayed behind
and waited for you.
Igaram.
It's coming from all directions!
What do we do, Big Brother?!
I believed in you...
Yes, Sire?
This is fine. Alabasta is
fine just as it is now.
But the king never came. Nor you, of course.
Big Bro!
There's no danger.
There's more?!
Bastard!
It's just wind blowing across the
town and echoing off old buildings.
I forgot to mention it,
but Sandora Dragons hunt in pairs!
That's because similar incidents
were happening all over the country
What's your deal?
Mention these things!
Allow me to accompany you,
for as long as I live!
and the king was busy every
day trying to combat it!
It's as if...
I'll fight, too!
It's as if the city of
Erumalu is crying...
--Ace!
--Look out!
I don't want to hear your excuses!
Your dream is my dream, Big Bro!
What a nuisance.
Yuba?
I waited all alone in the
middle of this vast desert!
Yeah! Your dad talked
to my dad about it!
You wanna play?
We've done all sorts of petty
things since we were kids,
Oh, okay. If that's what you want.
Old man Toto?
but you were always there
to protect the weak, Big Bro!
Here it comes!
He asked if he'd want to start a
town at the empty oasis of Yuba!
Eventually, I couldn't
differentiate between dawn and dusk.
Hyaaaa!
By the time Barbarossa took me in,
I couldn't feel anything,
That area's like the
crossroads of Alabasta,
I-I'll always be there with you, Big Bro!
where all kinds of travelers
and merchants pass through!
not even the midday scorching heat
or the freezing cold after sunset.
I'm gonna be a hero with you!
Just wait until a town is built there!
So many citizens will be happy!
Check it out! These rocks
are natural frying pans!
The fact that I was even alive baffled me.
He's...
But, inside my head,
the king's words continue to ring.
So, what's with the camel?
Awesome, huh?!
That's for sure!
What do we have to lose?!
And my dad was asked
to be its representative!
I can show you my spirit, too!
I dunno.
It was getting eaten by a mystery
plant when I was chasing the birds.
Yeah! There's no running
away now, anyways!
Whoa, what was with that wind?
Even now, I don't understand it.
Are you going too, Leader?
Of course!
Things were so difficult,
so what exactly was I waiting for?
It doesn't seem to be a wild camel.
My dad says to stay here...
No. It even has a saddle...
Someone's collapsed!
Guys...
...and starting a city is no easy matter...
There are still people in this city?!
Just what kept me going?
They're looking different now...
...but I'm gonna do it!
Though part of it seems because
their backs are to the wall...
Hate? Anger? Or inexistent hope?
I'm gonna build a new city
with my own two hands!
Yes.
This country needs the city of Yuba!
But I don't think they
could change like that
I knew it!
What was it?!
unless they're holding
something dear in their hearts.
What did my father...
Someone tell me...
Then... they're okay?
Oh! Good for you!
What did the citizens
of this country ever do?
Yes. Let's go. We'll entrust
this place to them for now.
Huh? You know each other?
Yeah! He gave me a ride
when I escaped from Katorea!
These people have worked
so hard to live,
being natives of a desert land who
are forced to fight with nature.
We're counting on you, Toto.
Yes, Your Majesty!
We will build a wonderful city!
That's great! We can ride it?!
That'll make things easier!
Yet he's destroyed their lives!
Hey! Retreat! Retreat!
What gives him the right to do that?!
Yeah, that'll be a real help!
Looks like it could carry two people!
Well, Vivi-chan.
This is goodbye for a while.
Sea pirates or not, bring it on!
I'm sorry...
Come visit sometime,
once the city's taken shape!
What?!
Camels do go hand-in-hand with deserts!
Over my dead body will I let you
take one step into this village!
Then I'll be the first one!
All the while,
as one of the Seven Warlords,
I'm so sorry for making you wait...
Okay, Toto-ojisan!
What was that for?!
he pretends to be a hero of the people!
We're gonna make an awesome city
"I am a freedom-loving,
hard-boiled, compassionate camel!
Yeah, now that's more like it!
and make this kingdom even lusher!
No one realizes he's
deceiving the entire country!
I'm so sorry!
Now I can go beat up
Crocodile without worrying!
Time to go!
Thanks for helping me out of that pinch.
Bye, Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
Whew! What a relief!
I can give you a lift,
but no men allowed!"
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Shut your trap and come on!
Those bastards!
Those are rebel soldiers for ya!
This guy's a punk!
Yeah!
Yeah! You let Chopper ride you!
I've never seen such strong people before!
"I'm manly!"
I...
Koza! Don't act so high and mighty!
I suck at plays like this!
can't let him get away with this!
--Quit being stupid!
--Why, you--!
Oww!
They sure ran off in a hurry!
W-Wait for me!
Koza is right.
I'm so sorry!
My crewmates are so ill-bred!
Though it's too bad we didn't get
to swipe any of their food or water.
Wh-What just happened?
Yuba will surely make
this country lusher.
You're a good boy!
What should we call you?
Sand pirates sure have it tough, too...
--Idiot!
--Moron!
Geez, you're all such kids.
Doofus!
Everything living in this
desert has it the same.
"Lashes" it is, then!
I see. This Koza friend of
yours was a really nice boy.
Utterly well done, rebel soldiers!
Uhh, that's the weirdest one of all.
Long ago, I used to feel this
desert belonged to everyone.
But that has something
to do with the rebel army?
Okay! Get on, Vivi!
No, I can still walk!
But when I think about it now,
I feel like that's a bit conceited.
Yes. It does.
Just get on.
We're going to the city of Yuba,
where the rebel army is stationed.
Pervy camel! Pervy camel!
Vivi!
Lately, I've come to think that
it might not belong to anyone.
Let's get moving!
And the name of the rebel army's leader...
Now we should make a little better time!
I'm itching to do this now!
...is Koza.
That we're able to live freely
because it belongs to no one.
You don't mean--!
We need to get to Yuba as fast as
we can to talk to the rebel army!
Let's go to Yuba!
The boy I just told you about.
That's where the rebel army is, right?
Giddyup, Lashes!
Do you think the sea is the same way?
Nami-san! Would you
like some too, Nami-san?!
--Hey, Luffy!
--Oh, Ace!
Hold on!
Good question.
Yes. I'm going to persuade their
leader to stop the rebellion.
Hurry, guys! If you get separated,
you'll never leave the desert alive!
How long are we gonna run?!
The act's over by now, right?!
That's something you'll have
to find out for yourselves.
This desert shrimp is yummy!
Persuade?
All of Alabasta's calamities
are Crocodile's doing!
Quit being stupid!
The way they abandoned
their lives was scary!
I like this side of Nami-san, too!
It's not a shrimp! It's a scorpion!
There it is! We made it!
After them! Hurry!
I'm going to tell him the truth
--Get on, Chopper!
--Yeah!
C-Can't eat any more!
I see.
and have him stop the
pointless shedding of blood!
Wait for us!
Got it.
Knock that off, you guys!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Let's go, Lashes!
Bye, Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
What's she so mad about?
Beats me.
Luffy! Where are you?!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
Say, Vivi. How are we going
to stop the rebel army?
Ace hardly seems like
a wanted criminal, huh?
--Say, Luffy. Where's your brother?
--Dunno.
I can't go on...
I can't take hot weather...
--So hot...
--Nami-san! How far did you go?!
Yet, pirates all over the world
fear the name "Fire Fist Ace."
Then take off that animal suit.
When we get to Yuba,
I'll meet him-- Koza-- first.
He's worse at directions
than this guy?!
You jerk! Are you making
fun of reindeer?!
We're completely separated now!
Huh?! Who're you
talking about, Pervy Cook?!
--Koza?
--We just need to beat him up, right?!
Come to think of it,
I don't see Ace, either.
Hey. What in the world is Luffy doing?
What kind of pirate is this
Blackbeard he's chasing?
Who else is there besides you?
--Please stop!
--Pay attention more!
--Do you think he got separated?
--What a troublesome big brother!
--He's riding a camel!
--Wait! Something's chasing him!
Hey! I got food and water!
I hear there's someone who beat Blackbeard.
Who is this Koza guy?
--Huh?! What's that?!
--Do you see Nami's group?!
--Big brother! How?!
--Got it from the rebel army!
--Yeah, a bounty hunter named Scorpion.
--There's someone that awesome?!
Ugh! How is he able to
summon trouble like this?!
Koza is my friend, and the
leader of the rebel army!
A ship! A pirate ship in the sand!
Come again?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Adventure in the Country of Sand! The
Monsters that Live in the Scorching Land"
"Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely"
"False Fortitude!
Camu, Rebel Soldier at Heart!"
"Rebel Warrior Koza!
The Dream Vowed to Vivi!"
"Showdown in a Heat Haze!
Ace vs. the Gallant Scorpion"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!