Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
The once-green city of
Erumalu now lies in ruins.
To stop the rebel army, Luffy and
company now head into the desert
for Yuba, the oasis town.
"Adventure in the Country of Sand! The
Monsters that Live in the Scorching Land"
Burning up...
Sweat won't even come out...
Quit moaning so much, Luffy.
You'll only tire yourself out.
Guess he's not listening.
I can't go on...
I can't take hot weather...
I'm fine in cold weather, though...
It's 'cause of all that fur...
You should take off that animal suit...
What was that, you jerk?!
Don't make fun of reindeer!
Monster!
Chopper! Don't turn big!
Or else I won't pull ya!
Who're you calling a monster,
Humongo-Nose?!
D-Don't be stupid!
I-I'll have you know this nose--
Just turn back already!
You don't seem to be having
a hard time, Vivi-chan.
I was born and raised here,
so it doesn't bother me much.
But what's with all these hills?
I figured a desert would be more flat.
This is a very old desert,
so some sand dunes here
are over 300 meters high.
Th-Three hundred meters?
No wonder this is like
climbing mountains...
It's too much... It's so hot...
Just one drink, Luffy.
Just one mouthful.
Don't drink so much!
Let me have some, too!
That was 13 mouthfuls just now!
Hold on! You just had some! I'm next!
Stop fighting!
You'll only waste strength!
--But she started it!
--It's your fault!
Yeah! This is because of you!
So hungry...
Don't be so greedy!
It's still raw! Don't eat that!
Nami-san! Just a minute,
it'll be ready soon!
--Oh, looks pretty good!
--Get away, you!
Oh, come on!
Cheapskate! Let us eat!
Get away!
It was so hot during the day!
What's going on?!
With nothing to block
out the temperature,
the desert scorches during the day
but falls below freezing at night.
The desert is fraught
with unpredictable dangers.
Oh! Look at all those stars!
Didn't you see stars
on your winter island?
Winter island skies are always
covered with thick snow clouds,
so I've never seen
so many stars before!
I don't have the luxury of
looking at stars right now...
Cold weather doesn't bother me!
That's because you wear
such a warm suit!
Hey, you! Get away!
I can't help that you're so fluffy...
Quit making fun of reindeer!
Monster!
Chopper. Don't turn big.
We need your warmth.
Yahoo!
So warm!
Come closer!
See? Warm, isn't it?
Yeah!
It must be a real surprise for you.
I mean Luffy-san.
I was surprised too, at first.
Maybe it's that he isn't captain-like,
or that normal pirate captains are
respected by their crewmates...
But just this afternoon, a simple
drink of water caused that big fight.
But...
But, you know...
The longer I've been with them,
the more I've come to understand.
That's how Luffy does things.
Eh?
He hasn't changed a bit
since he was a kid.
Despite how he seems,
people always gather around him.
Even though he's my little brother,
he has a mysterious charm to him.
Oh. You already knew.
He and I do go way back.
But thanks.
Eh?
You were worried that
I was concerned, right?
Yes. But it looks like I didn't
need to worry after all.
Whoa! I found a shrimp!
So this is a shrimp?! Wow!
--Shrimp don't live in the desert!
--See?!
Oh, you're right!
Is it a "desert shrimp"?
--It looks yummy!
--Hey, now! Are they edible?!
Probably! Crawfish are edible, after all!
I've never seen a real shrimp before!
Stop, Luffy-san! Throw that away!
No! That'd be a waste!
That's a scorpion! It's small
but it's very poisonous!
You'll die if it stings you!
Oh. It's not edible? How boring.
--You can have it.
--Don't give it to me!
Then I'll throw it away.
I'm sorry.
I should've mentioned it earlier.
That's for sure!
What is it, Chopper?
Something's... coming.
Something? What?
Oh? Is the wind picking up?
Everyone!
Hide behind the rocks!
What?
A storm! A sandstorm is coming!
Oh?
Whoa! Cool!
Again?! Deserts are nothing but storms!
I forgot to mention it, but sandstorms
are one of the desert's dangers!
Mention these things sooner!
What the hell was that?!
Can't people get some rest?!
Hey! Sanji! Let's have a lunch!
A Pirate Boxed Lunch!
Not yet. Not until Vivi-chan says so.
Come on, Vivi! Let's eat!
I'm out of strength!
But we're only one-tenth of
the way to Yuba, Luffy-san.
You're so dumb! Haven't
you heard of this proverb?
"If you're hungry, eat!"
You liar! Quit making stuff up!
All right.
Then what do you say we take a
break at the next rocks we find?
Alright! Rocks!
Guys! Let's hurry to the next rocks!
Whoever wins rock-paper-scissors
has to carry everyone's stuff!
Quit deciding things!
Shouldn't the loser carry the stuff?
Alright, here goes!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Hold on, now!
--Hey! You went after!
--Woohoo! I win!
Idiot.
H-Heavy... So heavy... And hot...
I won rock-paper-scissors,
so why me?
It's because you won.
Now shut up and haul.
Don't drop it, now!
Rocks spotted a small ways ahead!
For reals?!
Break time! Food!
Whoa! He's fast!
Shade! Feels so good!
Hey! Say something!
I'll go get you a doctor!
Bad news!
Huh? He's coming back!
There's lots of hurt birds
that can't move! Chopper!
Right!
--Alright! Let's go, Chopper!
--Yeah!
We gotta help the birds!
Birds?!
Wait, Luffy-san! Don't tell
me these birds are--!
Eh?
All our stuff is gone!
We've been had...
It's the truth! There really
were dying birds here!
I'm sorry. I should've
mentioned it earlier.
Warusagi birds are
"desert bandits" that trick travelers
and steal their belongings.
What?!
Birds playing dead?!
That's dishonest!
Yes, that's how they are.
They tricked me?!
Luffy! Is that all you can
say for yourself?!
There were three days
of provisions in there!
And you just had to let some
damn birds steal everyone's stuff
smack in the middle of this desert?!
How're we supposed to cross the
desert without food or water now?!
It's not my fault. They tricked me.
Is your brain less than a bird's?!
Say what?!
Stop it, you two!
There's no use.
At times like this,
it's best to let them have it out.
Yeah, huh?
Let's take a short break.
This heat is what has them fuming.
I'm sure we'll manage food-wise.
It's nothing that'll kill us.
Let's just put it out of our minds.
Yeah. Just thinking makes me thirstier.
Give us our stuff back!
Luffy-san! Don't chase them!
That idiot.
Hey, you! Will you be
able to come back?!
Come back, Luffy!
Stop! You can't get away from me!
Get back here!
What are these?!
What is this thing?
A mystery desert plant?
Neat!
What are you doing?
That's funny!
Huh? You want me to help you?
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Good thing you didn't get eaten!
The birds got away while
I was beating these guys up!
The desert sure is full
of strange creatures!
Hey, camel. What're you doing
out here all by yourself?
What is it?
Did you find something?
What the--?!
What's taking Luffy so long?!
Yeah. Do you think he got lost?
He has a horrible sense of
direction but always has to run off!
And there are so many desert
dangers he doesn't know about...
Y'know, isn't he hungry
from not eating anything?
He's such a lost cause.
You can say that again.
Sorry.
For my little brother's ineptness.
I apologize for the trouble.
Good luck finding him!
Yeah.
What's that?!
What's this rumbling?!
Another sandstorm?!
No, wait! That's--!
Luffy?!
No... it couldn't be!
Why is he on a camel?!
So?! What's that chasing him?!
I can't really see!
But it seems more like
something's in the sand!
It's huge!
What is that?!
A Sandora Dragon!
A what now?!
They're the largest of the
reptiles living in the desert
and they wait under the
sand for their prey!
They have sharp claws and fangs,
but they hardly ever use them!
The reason being that they tend
to swallow their prey whole
because they're so large!
He really does have a gift
for attracting trouble.
Setting aside the camel for the moment...
...what star was he born under to be
able to attract trouble like this?!
Hey! Camel! Stop!
--Luffy! Is it too much for you?!
--We'll lend a hand!
Yeah! I brought some meat!
Here goes, lizard!
Gum-Gum...
--Tatsu...
--êpaule...
...Whip!
--...Maki!
--...Shoot!
Y-You didn't have to go that far...
When they're fighting,
you almost pity the monsters...
There's more?!
I forgot to mention it,
but Sandora Dragons hunt in pairs!
Mention these things!
--Ace!
--Look out!
What a nuisance.
You wanna play?
Oh, okay. If that's what you want.
Check it out! These rocks
are natural frying pans!
So, what's with the camel?
I dunno.
It was getting eaten by a mystery
plant when I was chasing the birds.
It doesn't seem to be a wild camel.
No. It even has a saddle...
I knew it!
Oh! Good for you!
Huh? You know each other?
Yeah! He gave me a ride
when I escaped from Katorea!
That's great! We can ride it?!
That'll make things easier!
Yeah, that'll be a real help!
Looks like it could carry two people!
Camels do go hand-in-hand with deserts!
Then I'll be the first one!
What was that for?!
"I am a freedom-loving,
hard-boiled, compassionate camel!
Thanks for helping me out of that pinch.
I can give you a lift,
but no men allowed!"
This guy's a punk!
Yeah! You let Chopper ride you!
"I'm manly!"
--Quit being stupid!
--Why, you--!
I'm so sorry!
My crewmates are so ill-bred!
You're a good boy!
What should we call you?
--Idiot!
--Moron!
Doofus!
"Lashes" it is, then!
Uhh, that's the weirdest one of all.
Okay! Get on, Vivi!
No, I can still walk!
Just get on.
Pervy camel! Pervy camel!
Now we should make a little better time!
We need to get to Yuba as fast as
we can to talk to the rebel army!
Giddyup, Lashes!
Hold on!
Hurry, guys! If you get separated,
you'll never leave the desert alive!
Quit being stupid!
I like this side of Nami-san, too!
After them! Hurry!
--Get on, Chopper!
--Yeah!
Wait for us!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
--So hot...
--Nami-san! How far did you go?!
We're completely separated now!
Come to think of it,
I don't see Ace, either.
--Do you think he got separated?
--What a troublesome big brother!
--Huh?! What's that?!
--Do you see Nami's group?!
A ship! A pirate ship in the sand!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Enter the Desert Pirates!
The Men Who Live Freely"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!