Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing.
As Luffy and company left
the green city of Erumalu
for the Yuba oasis,
where the rebel army is,
they met sand pirates, and set out
after attaining new friendship.
"False Fortitude!
Camu, Rebel Soldier at Heart!"
Ahead is a village called Ido.
You should be able to get water there.
Huh? You're not coming?
We sand pirates can't
go any further ahead.
This land belongs to the people
who've lived and died here
for generations, you see.
Is that how it is?
Yeah. The desert is the land of the free.
But not everyone can
survive in the harsh desert.
The village ahead is a place
where such people eke out a living.
So, what're you gonna do?
Nothing much!
We've freely lived as we pleased
on this ocean of sand,
and that's what we'll keep on doing!
That's just like us, then!
Yeah? That's great!
--So long!
--Take care!
See ya, old umbrella guy!
--They were great guys!
--Yeah!
By the way, where'd your brother go?
Dunno. But he's Ace.
Nothing to worry about.
He'll suddenly show up
again out of nowhere!
Why do you keep making
such groundless claims?
Anyways, let's hurry to this Udo village!
--You mean Ido.
--Ido?
Yeah.
Th-That's a desert pirate flag!
Crap! I gotta tell Big Bro!
Yes, you utterly are rebel army soldiers!
Ever since you and your
companions arrived, Camu-sama,
attacks on the village
have utterly stopped!
Yup! You'd have to be
pretty crazy to take us on!
Rest easy and leave it to us, Mayor!
Yes! You're utterly correct!
But word is the rebel army and the
royal army will be clashing soon.
Won't staying in a place
like this interfere with that?
No, we can't just leave a
place that lets us eat all we--
Nah, this is this, that is that!
We may be rebels, but we haven't
completely given up on the king!
Yes, we have utter faith
in the king as well,
so we were hoping things
could be handled carefully.
Say no more!
After careful consideration, we've
decided to keep you guys safe, too!
All we ask for in return
is booze and food!
Yes! Of course!
Well, I must be going now...
Big Bro Camu.
Would giving up on the king
make us real rebel soldiers?
C'mon, get real.
We can't leave this village until
we've sucked all of its sweet nectar!
Big Bro! Terrible news, Big Bro!
What do you want?!
Pipe down, I'm trying to eat!
Sand pirates!
Sand pirates are attacking!
For real?! What do we do?!
What do you mean?!
There's nothing we can do against them!
But we can't stick our tails
between our legs and run, either!
Tell us, Big Bro! What should we do?
Alright! Let's stick our tails
between our legs and run!
We're running away?!
But what happens after we run away?
Live on the edge of starvation again?
You moron! Staying alive is all that matters!
There are plenty of other villages like this!
Now let's scram!
That's for sure...
What're you?
You cowards got real guts to
call yourselves rebel soldiers.
If you ask me, it's a pretty despicable
thing for four grown men to do.
Who the hell're you?!
Mind your own business!
When did you get in here, anyway?!
Food thief!
More.
Yes, yes, yes! I'm sorry, sir!
This place has good food.
Yes, thank you!
I'm sorry! I now realize
you're no ordinary person!
As you can see, we stand no
chance at all against sand pirates!
Please lend us your help!
Hmm. I'm not against the idea...
...but on one condition.
Yes! Anything you want!
Hey!
--Hey!
--Ace!
That's where he was?
What is this thing?
Oh! So you're the sand pirates?
Huh? What do you mean?
We just left the sand pirates.
Oh? Really? Well, whatever.
Anyways, great news, Luffy!
I brought plenty of food and water!
Oh! Much appreciated!
This should be more than
enough for a good while!
Ace is incredible...
That's for sure! He's nothing like
a certain little brother we know!
You can say that again.
--I was so thirsty...
--Oh! Drink up, drink up!
Me too!
Umm, Ace-san?
I assume you don't have
the money for that.
Don't tell me you stole
it from that village...
Nothing of the sort!
The rebel army gave it to me!
The rebel army?!
Well, I should say "clearly fake
rebel soldiers" to be more precise.
--Eh?
--Fake? What do you mean?
Basically, they call
themselves rebel soldiers
and were hired to protect the village.
The villagers are so grateful that
they've been completely fooled.
They're really just some hoodlums.
And they're bodyguards?
Wouldn't they get found out right away?
Apparently, the mere
mention of the rebel army
will send most bandits running.
It's real convenient.
Makes money and prestige come
rolling your way on its own.
Rebel soldiers aren't hoodlums,
nor does the title serve as decoration.
Vivi-chan. Should we teach 'em a lesson?
I dunno. Duping the villagers isn't
so different from what bandits do.
At the very least, the villagers
live in peace with them around.
Should we get 'em just the same?
But, big brother. Consider it
from Vivi-chan's perspective.
Surely you'd want to
pulverize people like them.
Yeah, she should do what she wants.
I only gave my own thoughts.
I don't want to hear your excuses!
I waited all alone in the
middle of this vast desert!
There's no reason to
cover for these bastards.
I'm not. I just know you
guys are in a hurry here...
Now that the kingdom can't keep
watch over every little place,
there's nothing wrong with
villages upholding public safety
on their own whenever possible.
Then...
No. I want to test them first.
--Test?
--Yes.
If these impostor rebel soldiers
truly wish to protect the villagers,
I don't think it matters
what they call themselves.
So you want to test what's
in their hearts, huh?
Yes. So, I hate to ask, but there's
something I'd like you all to do.
No sweat, Vivi-chan!
Alright! Things are
getting interesting now!
Eh? It's going to be interesting?!
Hold on, Luffy! This isn't
going to be a game! Understand?!
Yeah, I get it!
We're basically gonna beat these
fake rebel guys up, right?!
He doesn't understand a thing!
Someone do something about him!
He's been gone a long time.
It's been almost an hour since he said,
"Leave it to me!" and left...
You saw his strength!
I bet he's beating the
sand pirates up as we speak!
No, think about who he's fighting!
They might've beaten him
before he even got a chance!
In which case, we're next, huh?
No, I can't do this!
I hate to lose such good room and board...
...but staying alive is all that matters!
That's for sure.
--Good luck!
--We're counting on you!
--You can do it!
--Camu-sama!
Camu-sama! We're relying on you!
I was utterly about
to come calling for you,
but I should've known you already
knew the sea pirates were here!
Eh?! Sea pirates?!
Not sand pirates?!
That's correct. Sea pirates.
They're far more
ferocious than sand pirates.
Plus one is a special-edition pirate
with a 30 million-Berry bounty!
Once we heard you were going to go,
"Hiyaaah!" and get rid of them,
we were so utterly moved and grateful!
We know you can do it!
Good luck, mister!
Don't lose to some stupid sea pirates!
I'm gonna get strong just like you!
Let's go!
H-Hey, Big Bro. Are you serious about this?
Don't be stupid. Of course he isn't serious.
Shut up, you guys!
Once we've left town, we run in
the opposite direction of the pirates!
We run to our last gasp!
What other way is there?!
That's for sure.
Dammit.
They're following us...
What a bunch of jerks...
Alright. We got one shot at this.
Once we're out, immediately figure
out which direction is pirate-free
and then run for your lives! Got it?!
Gotcha, loud and clear!
Here goes! One! Two! Three!
O-Oh, crap...
Get 'em, get 'em, rebel army!
Give that a rest, will ya?!
What's that?! You're a rebel soldier?!
N-No, nothing of the sort!
We're just travelers passing through!
Say your prayers, sea pirates!
These rebel soldiers are gonna
make mincemeat out of you!
Be quiet, you!
Right! How utterly rude of me!
Good luck, Camu-sama!
He seems especially spineless to me.
Doesn't seem reliable at all.
Yes...
Are you sure about this?
It might be best for the village
if we take care of them now.
A little more. Let's watch
things just a little more...
--Get 'em, rebel soldiers!
--You can do it!
Hey!
You really are rebel soldiers after all!
N-No, it isn't, uhh...
Wh-What now, Big Bro?
We lost our chance to escape...
Hey, you guys!
--Ace-sama?
--Please help...
This is your fight.
Try to get through it on your own.
We can't do that! We're fakes!
If you're men, act like it!
How long are you gonna keep
up this petty crap of yours?
What do we do, Big Bro?
Wh-What do you mean, what do we do?
We have no choice now but to lie
our way out of this, impostor-style!
Impostor-style?
Listen, you! Don't be shocked
by what I have to say!
We're not the only rebel soldiers here!
In the village there are...
...100 million more soldiers like us!
Oh, geez. That's worse than a kid's lie.
You're no one to talk.
What?! 100 million?!
Hold on, you!
That's not even believable!
He's obviously bluffing!
What?! It's a lie?!
Obviously!
--Oh, it was a lie?
--Oh, geez!
You! How dare you trick me?!
Damn! They realized I was lying!
Did you really think
that would fool them?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
What was that?!
He has Devil Fruit powers!
One hit knocked him out!
Not even rebel soldiers stand a
chance against something like that!
Luffy, you idiot! It's all
over if you knock him out!
Then what would we do?!
Big Brother Camu!
You can do it!
The sea pirate is coming!
--You can do it!
--Big Brother!
Stand up!
That's right...
When I was a kid, I looked up
to the warriors of Alabasta
and wanted to be as strong
as them someday...
No, even now I do...
Someday, I want to be as strong
as the warriors I saw as a child...
Someday...
How long are you gonna keep up
this petty crap of yours?
Big Bro!
Yes, we're fake rebel soldiers.
Even if all we want is to be as
strong as the heroes we saw as kids,
we're just a bunch of scoundrels now.
But, even if my dream never comes true,
I can't take those kids' dreams away!
Even if I'm no match for you,
I'm going to fight so that someday
those kids can beat you all!
If my only other choice is to remain
a punk in those kids' memories,
then I'd rather die as a hero right here!
Big Bro!
Bastard!
What's your deal?
I'll fight, too!
Your dream is my dream, Big Bro!
We've done all sorts of petty
things since we were kids,
but you were always there
to protect the weak, Big Bro!
Hyaaaa!
I-I'll always be there with you, Big Bro!
I'm gonna be a hero with you!
He's...
That's for sure!
What do we have to lose?!
I can show you my spirit, too!
Yeah! There's no running
away now, anyways!
Guys...
They're looking different now...
Though part of it seems because
their backs are to the wall...
Yes.
But I don't think they
could change like that
unless they're holding
something dear in their hearts.
Then... they're okay?
Yes. Let's go. We'll entrust
this place to them for now.
Hey! Retreat! Retreat!
Sea pirates or not, bring it on!
Over my dead body will I let you
take one step into this village!
Yeah, now that's more like it!
Now I can go beat up
Crocodile without worrying!
Whew! What a relief!
Shut your trap and come on!
Those bastards!
Those are rebel soldiers for ya!
I've never seen such strong people before!
I suck at plays like this!
W-Wait for me!
Wh-What just happened?
Utterly well done, rebel soldiers!
--Hey, Luffy!
--Oh, Ace!
How long are we gonna run?!
The act's over by now, right?!
The way they abandoned
their lives was scary!
I see.
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Bye, Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
Say, Vivi. How are we going
to stop the rebel army?
When we get to Yuba,
I'll meet him-- Koza-- first.
--Koza?
--We just need to beat him up, right?!
--Please stop!
--Pay attention more!
Who is this Koza guy?
Koza is my friend, and the
leader of the rebel army!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Rebel Warrior Koza!
The Dream Vowed to Vivi!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!